<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13838" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>32</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2019-02-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shounen Ashibe: Go! Go! Goma-chan (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Goma-chan Season 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">少年アシベ GO! GO! ゴマちゃん (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shonen Ashibe Go! Go! Goma-chan (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">少年阿贝GO！GO！小芝麻 第3季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14720" type="Sequel">Shounen Ashibe: Go! Go! Goma-chan (2019)</anime>
<anime id="12904" type="Prequel">Shounen Ashibe: Go! Go! Goma-chan (2017)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www6.nhk.or.jp/anime/program/detail.html?i=gomachan</url>
<creators>
<name id="43871" type="Animation Work">Husio Studio</name>
<name id="24618" type="Animation Work">Bridge</name>
<name id="7346" type="Series Composition">Takeuchi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="6397" type="Direction">Kondou Nobuhiro</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13">3.57</permanent>
<temporary count="13">4.17</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221717.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37368</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www6.nhk.or.jp/anime/program/detail.html?i=gomachan</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>少年アシベ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="197493" update="2018-04-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アスニクルにロボガクル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robot Arrives in Asnikul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asnikul ni Robo ga Kuru</title>
<summary>Gomabo has drifted all the way to Asnikul and is found by none other than Sugao! When Sugao sees Gomabo`s resemblance to Goma-chan and hears it speak in Ashibe`s voice, the two quickly become inseparable... but Chit and Yeti become jealous of all the attention Sugao is giving to the newcomer!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767413</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197494" update="2018-04-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマボが来た!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gomabo Is Here!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomabo ga Kita!</title>
<summary>Ashibe`s grandpa brings him a gift, a toy robot called Gomabo that looks like Goma-chan and sounds like Ashibe! Gomabo is super smart, with all kinds of cutting-edge functions and capabilities... but it seems to have a little trouble understanding humans.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767411</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197495" update="2018-04-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オイラたちに明日はない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Have No Tomorrow!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oiratachi ni Ashita wa Nai!</title>
<summary>School is starting tomorrow, so Ashibe-kun calls his friends together to do lots of playing while they still can. He`s even worked out a very detailed play schedule for them all to follow. They work their way through the list, but after a while, they start to grow tired of the whole thing. This isn`t even "playing" anymore!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767409</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197496" update="2018-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパーアザラシ ゴマちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Seal Goma-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Super Azarashi Goma-chan</title>
<summary>Ashibe is making a paper airplane, but Goma-chan smashes it before he`s finished. But somehow, the crushed paper looks even more like a paper airplane now! Later, a bored Goma-chan scribbles at random with a marker, and his family is shocked to see what looks like English letters on the paper! Goma-chan the super seal can truly do anything!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767407</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198121" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チットちゃんの贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chit-chan`s Gift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitto-chan no Okurimono</title>
<summary>Sugao-kun has been living in the Republic of Asnikul, but now he finally gets to move back to Japan! He can finally see Ashibe-kun again! But he must also say goodbye to Chit-chan, Yeti, and his other friends in Asnikul. Chit-chan goes out to find some of the flowers that she wants to give Sugao-kun as a goodbye gift, but she gets lost in the woods. This is terrible! She won`t make it back in time to see off Sugao-kun!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767421</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198122" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アシベのポケット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ashibe`s Pockets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashibe no Pocket</title>
<summary>Eek! Ashibe-kun`s mom runs into a surprise while doing the laundry: she finds a bunch of pillbugs in Ashibe-kun`s pocket! So she tells him not to put pillbugs in his pockets anymore... and next time, she finds pillbugs in his sock! Eek! So Ma decides to turn Goma-chan in to a pillbug and teach Ashibe-kun a lesson!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767419</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198123" update="2018-05-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ! ゴマちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Goma-chan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire! Goma-chan</title>
<summary>Goma-chan is napping in the sun with his frog friend Hirao... when suddenly, he accidentally tips the bowl of water Hirao was lounging in! Worried that Hirao will dry up if he has no water, Goma-chan hurries to get some, but all kinds of obstacles get in his way. Time is ticking by... You have to find a way to save Hirao! Run, Goma-chan! For Hirao`s sake!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767417</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198124" update="2018-05-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマちゃんVS赤ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goma-chan vs Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goma-chan vs Akachan</title>
<summary>A baby has come to visit Ashibe-kun`s house! It`s Yumiko-chan`s baby sister, Ruriko-chan! Ashibe-kun and his Ma and Pa are all so enamored with Ruriko-chan that Goma-chan isn`t getting any attention, making him a bit grumpy. Ruriko-chan appears to like Goma-chan, but Goma-chan is irritate that she treats him like a plaything. And so the battle between Goma-chan and Ruriko-chan begins?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767415</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200086" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜ふかしゴマちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ashibe Stays Up Late</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru Fukashi Goma-chan</title>
<summary>The Japanese soccer team`s world tournament matches are starting late at night on Japanese TV, and Ashibe-kun wants to watch and support the team... but the next thing he knows, it`s morning. It seems he fell asleep without realizing it. So in order to stay awake for the next night`s match, he tries taking a nap during the day and even drinking coffee... but again, the next thing he knows, it`s morning! He`d determined to see the next match and cheer on Japan`s team, but can he stay awake long enough?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767427</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200087" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スガオVSゴマちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sugao vs Goma-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugao vs Goma-chan</title>
<summary>Sugao-kun is visiting Ashibe-kun`s house! The two are thrilled to finally be reunited! Goma-chan tries to include himself in the fun, but Ashibe-kun is so focused on playing with Sugao-kun that Goma-chan ends up left out. When Ashibe-kun won`t give him any attention, Goma-chan starts to worry that Sugao-kun is taking Ashibe-kun away from him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767425</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200088" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかえりスガオくん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Back, Sugao-kun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaeri Sugao-kun!</title>
<summary>Yay! Sugao-kun is returning to Japan! Ashibe-kun and Goma-chan immediately start to prepare a welcome party for him! Yuma-kun and all his other friends, even the owner and staff of Wang Wang Ken, come to the Ashiya house for the party! They`ve rehearsed what to do when Sugao-kun arrives, and everything is all set! But... they keep waiting and waiting, and Sugao still doesn`t show up. Sugao-kun really did come back to Japan, right?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767423</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202148" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋する湘南海岸ミステリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Romantic Shonan Beach Mystery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Shounankaigan Mystery</title>
<summary>Ashibe and his friends are visiting the location where Yuma-kun`s mom is shooting a drama, and Omata Tamao-chan has a role as a lifeguard in a beach scene! But then they find out that Tamao-chan can`t swim. The director is ready to have Yuma-kun appear in her place... but Tamao-chan can`t have that, so she has Goma-chan teach her how to swim!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767431</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202149" update="2018-07-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メ~メ~ゴマちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Baa-Baa Goma-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meemee Goma-chan</title>
<summary>Ashibe-kun and his friends are visiting a ranch! Sugao-kun comes along too, so Ashibe-kun introduces him to everyone and asks them all to be his friends! Since Sugao-kun lived among the wildlife of the Republic of Asnikul for so long, all the animals on the ranch love him. He can even ride a horse! Amazing! But Sakata doesn`t seem too fond of Sugao-kun for some reason. Can the two of them become friends?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767429</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204456" update="2018-10-15">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">つまみぐい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneaking Bites</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumamigui</title>
<summary>Ashibe-kun and Sugao-kun discover a cake in the fridge. They try to put it back without eating any, but Ashibe-kun accidentally gets some cream on his finger! He has no choice but to lick it off, right? So he does... and it`s so delicious, he feels like he`s flying through space! He invites Sugao-kun to have a little taste too, but Sugao-kun adamantly shakes his head...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776901</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204457" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら天堂先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Mr. Tendou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Tendou-sensei</title>
<summary>The normally energetic Mr. Tendou makes a very somber announcement at a school staff meeting: he`s decided that it`s time to say goodbye. Word spreads quickly around the school, quickly reaching Ashibe and his friends. Is Mr. Tendou really going away forever?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776900</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204458" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマちゃんと影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goma-chan and Shadows</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goma-chan to Kage</title>
<summary>One day, Goma-chan happens to discover his own shadow. It moves in the same ways he does, and even when he runs away from it, it follows him! He jumps in a fountain to hide and thinks he`s safe... until he spots the shadow drifting below him in the water. No matter where he runs, it follows him! Will he ever escape this terror?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776899</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206534" update="2019-06-15">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激ウマ! チャーハン選手権</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delicious! The Fried Rice Championships</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekiuma! Chaahan Senshuken</title>
<summary>Wang Wang Ken is in trouble! They`re not getting any customers at all! To escape this crisis, Riko brings a flyer with information on the Fried Rice Championships. Wang-san is determined to win and get his restaurant`s name out there, so he begins rigorous training to perfect the secret recipe that`s been in the Wang family for generations: Golden Para-Para-Para Fried Rice! Ashibe-kun and Goma-chan cheer him on with their own para-para dance!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777378</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206535" update="2019-06-15">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人なアシベ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grown-up Ashibe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otona na Ashibe</title>
<summary>Ma and Pa are going out for the day, which means Ashibe-kun and Goma-chan will be staying home alone! Ashibe-kun confidently tells his parents that he`s a grown-up now and won`t have any problems, so they ask him to help out around the house while they`re away. Ashibe-kun does everything he can to feel like a grown-up while home alone, but can he handle all the tasks his parents have asked him to do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777379</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206536" update="2019-06-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アシベと魔法のランプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ashibe and the Magic Lamp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashibe to Mahou no Lamp</title>
<summary>Ashibe-kun tries to pour hot water into a pot for tea, but then Goma-chan the Genie pops out! It turns out the "teapot" was a magic lamp, and Goma-chan the Genie tells Ashibe-kun he`ll grant him 99 wishes! Ashibe-kun wastes no time making his first wish. He asks for a winning ice pop stick, and Goma-chan gives him one! But then, other people set their sights on the magic lamp...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777380</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206537" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名探偵ゆうま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Great Detective Yuma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meitantei Yuuma</title>
<summary>Ashibe-kun is staring at what appears to be a drawing of Goma-chan`s face. Yuma-kun deduces that the drawing must be a note Ashibe-kun made to remind him where he hid something, but Ashibe-kun can`t even remember why he made it. Can Yuma-kun figure out the truth behind the mysterious note?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777381</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209085" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">商人アシベ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ashibe the Peddler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounin Ashibe</title>
<summary>Step right up! Ashibe-kun is working at a flea market stall with Ma and Goma-chan. They try to sell some toys that he doesn`t play with anymore, but Ashibe-kun says they`re all his treasures and doesn`t want to sell them. As he`s trying his hardest to keep his toys, a little boy comes along and buys Goma-chan for 100 yen! But wait, Goma-chan isn`t for sale!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777382</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209086" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマのフレンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gomano Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goma no Friends</title>
<summary>Ashibe-kun is visiting a safari park built by his grandpa`s company. He`s been told that animals from all around the world are at the park, but all they see as they drive through it is cats. Goma-chan is worried that they`ll try to make him their scratching post, but Ashibe-kun tells him he`ll be fine as long as he doesn`t fall out of the bus... and then, Goma-chan falls out of the bus! He then meets a cat called Photo-chan...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777383</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209087" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">面接官アシベ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ashibe the Job Interviewer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mensetsukan Ashibe</title>
<summary>Uncle Akio decides to interview for a job at Ashibe`s grandpa`s company! It seems his goal is to get closer to Peppeppe-san, the president`s secretary. When he arrives at the company, it turns out his interview is to be conducted by Ashibe-kun and Goma-chan! How will this turn out when Ashibe-kun doesn`t even understand what a job interview really is?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777384</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209983" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アシベのヒミツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ashibe`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashibe no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Ashibe-kun uses Goma-chan as a model to make a craft for his homework. The finished product looks a little odd... but Sugao-kun`s project comes out looking just like Goma-chan! Sugao-kun is a genius! At school the next day, Ashibe-kun unveils his project... but find out that he brought Sugao-kun`s project by mistake! But he can`t bring himself to admit it, and then his craft is chosen for the town art festival... What will he do?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780044</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210318" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユミコのしりとり道場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yumiko`s Shiritori Dojo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumiko no Shiritori Doujou</title>
<summary>At Yumiko-chan`s suggestion, the gang decides to play shiritori. Yumiko-chan wants their group to be the best shiritori players in the world... but when Sakata`s brother has to say a word starting with "go" on his turn, all he can come up with is "Goma-chan"! Everyone knows he loves Goma-chan, but any word ending in the "n" sound means the end of the game! Try harder and become the best in the world at shiritori!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780045</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210319" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2018-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">GO! GO! ゴマチューバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go! Go! GomaTuber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go! Go! Goma Tuber</title>
<summary>A video of Goma-chan was uploaded to the shopping district`s webpage and became a huge hit! So the chairman of the shopping district asks Ashibe-kun for more videos of Goma-chan. As they`re pondering what sort of videos to shoot, Sakata`s brother, the Goma-chan specialist, steps in to help! Sakata`s brother is even more enthusiastic than usual to shoot some adorable Goma-chan videos!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780046</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211415" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2019-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマデレラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gomaderella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomaderella</title>
<summary>Once upon a time, there lived a seal named Gomaderella. Gomaderella had two mean sisters... rather, two very kind brothers, the Sakatas?! When they won`t take him to the ball because it`s too dangerous outside, the wizard Ashibe appears and uses his magic to give Gomaderella a beautiful dress! And then they`re off to the ball in an eggplant carriage!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780792</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211416" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2019-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマちゃんの雪まつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Goma-chan Snow Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goma-chan no Yukimatsuri</title>
<summary>Goma-chan is fascinated by footage of the Snow Festival on TV. He must really want to see snow! But there`s no snow in Tokyo right now... So Sugao-kun brings up the idea of making it snow for Goma-chan! Yuma-kun, Mao-chan, Yumiko-chan, and the Sakata brothers all join in to set up a Snow Festival just for Goma-chan!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780793</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211681" update="2019-02-09">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2019-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チットちゃんにとどけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deliver to Chit-chan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitto-chan ni Todoke!</title>
<summary>Since Sugao-kun returned to Japan, his friend Chit-chan has been eagerly awaiting a visit from him back in the Republic of Asnikul. But she`s a little sad that she hasn`t received any letters from him recently. Meanwhile, back in Japan, Ashibe-kun talks to his grandpa about finding a way to help Sugao-kun talk to Chit-chan. Will Sugao-kun and Chit-chan be able to talk to each other?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780794</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211809" update="2019-02-09">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2019-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴマちゃん卒業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduating from Goma-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goma-chan Sotsugyou</title>
<summary>Sakata`s big brother`s love for Goma-chan can`t be stopped. It`s reached a point where everyone is starting to worry about Goma-chan. So Ashibe-kun and his friends decide to try to help Sakata`s big brother "graduate" from Goma-chan! They attempt several things, like trying to get him interested in other animals and popular idols... but can Sakata`s brother ever outgrow his love for Goma-chan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780795</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211810" update="2019-03-04">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2019-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドットちゃんとゴマちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dot-chan and Goma-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dotto-chan to Goma-chan</title>
<summary>As Goma-chan is swimming in the river, a shark`s silhouette appears behind him?! The shark turns out to be Dot-chan, a young whale shark that escaped from the local aquarium! Goma-chan and Dot-chan quickly become great friends and have fun swimming in Dot-chan`s tank at the aquarium together. But when Ashibe-kun calls out to Goma-chan that it`s time to go home, Goma-chan doesn`t seem to understand him... What`s happened to Goma-chan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780796</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212309" update="2019-03-05">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2019-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなの想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone`s Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna no Omoi</title>
<summary>Since becoming friends with Dot-chan the whale shark, Goma-chan doesn`t seem to understand anything Ashibe-kun says anymore. With Goma-chan staying at the aquarium, Ashibe-kun is alone and sad at home... but then Sugao-kun brings him a stack of books on seal language. Time to try one more time to communicate with Goma-chan using seal language! Will Ashibe-kun`s feelings finally reach him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780797</identifier>
<identifier>shonen-ashibe-go-go-goma-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
