<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13844" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi de tte Itta yo ne!</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Хіба я не просила зробити мої здібності у наступному житті посередніми?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">noukin</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Didn`t I Say to Make My Abilities Average in the Next Life?!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ألم أقل أن تجعل قدراتي معتدلة في الحياة الأخرى؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我，不是说了能力要平均值么！</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14232" approval="16" total="19">Endro~!</anime>
<anime id="149" approval="1" total="5">Dragon Half</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="231802">Didn`t I tell you that this is very much more than average!

Surprisingly good watch. Didn`t expect that it would have such a nice balance of laughs, friendship power, cute-ness, serious times and fun action as well.
Its generally a slice of life group of (girls) friends isekai adventure. Often time its a laid back trashcan full of cuteness powered tropeful jokes, but it does have a serious undertone occasionally.
Jokes as further enhance by the nice chemistry and growth around the nicely composed group as they developed from school into full fledged adventurers.

The prod quality is OK, but I love the water colored art style backdrops of the detailed designed world. It does also come with a catchy OP song.
Aside from its meandering slice-of-life, it does have a bigger back plot and S2 will be very welcomed. 

Hop on this adventure for how easy it is to join along, and you would be sure to get your laughter worth. 
For me definitely very above average at 7/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="73747">The premise of a MC dying and being reincarnated as someone OP in another world has been done before, but what makes this iteration different is it follows a group of girls and the tone is completely carefree, relaxing, fun and an easy watch.  This is for those that aren`t looking for a serious watch but rather a carefree time with girls going on adventures.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://noukin-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="26990" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Susumu</name>
<name id="9769" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kiyomaru Satoru</name>
<name id="35813" type="Animation Work">Project No.9</name>
<name id="26990" type="Character Design">Watanabe Susumu</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="23374" type="Original Work">Akata Itsuki</name>
<name id="7852" type="Direction">Oota Masahiko</name>
<name id="7802" type="Music">Misawa Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="53966" type="Original Work">Funa</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr53966 [Funa] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr23374 [Akata Itsuki].
When she turns ten years old, Adele von Ascham is hit with a horrible headache–and memories of her previous life as an eighteen-year-old Japanese girl named Kurihara Misato. That life changed abruptly, however, when Misato died trying to aid a little girl and met god. During that meeting, she made an odd request and asked for average abilities in her next life. But few things–especially wishes–ever go quite as planned.
Source: seven seas</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="504">5.09</permanent>
<temporary count="507">6.71</temporary>
<review count="1">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>237741.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22283</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37393</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://noukin-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Didn`t_I_Say_to_Make_My_Abilities_Average_in_the_Next_Life%3F!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>私、能力は平均値でって言ったよね!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5417</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22296</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>noukin_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Rpz5HCGAlNA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=P1bIjU4Dru4</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=6ADTgH8qVCM</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=fgb4UqgPLLA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=AFs2dLocMvQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=GdWkzv__Xzg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2769" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>hyperspace mallet</name>
<description>It comes from nowhere, it strikes without mercy, and disappears again. It`s a mallet the size of a circus sledgehammer, and it`s evidence that anime characters watch too many Bugs Bunny cartoons or Three Stooges shorts. An angry character — usually but not restricted to short-tempered schoolgirls — can often whip out a massive hammer with which to slam the target (and cause) of her ire.
In Fan Fic circles, the notional storage place for mallets when not in use is known as hammerspace or malletspace.
A recent variation is to have the character pull out a http://anidb.net/t1662 [harisen], a huge folded fan made out of paper or metal, a.k.a. the Paper Fan of Doom, and smack them with that. This is usually less painful-looking than the mallet, unless she uses it to deliver a Megaton Punch.
Ironically, this is now a Dead Horse Trope in the West, where it originated; modern Western examples are typically from shows invoking anime, which has added its own touches to the mix, or from homages to Warner Brothers cartoons.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>10253.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3379" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-25">
<name>killing criminals</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3508" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-09-26">
<name>school for the rich elite</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4397" parentid="2867" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-13">
<name>court politics</name>
<description>Court politics are the power struggles internal to the retinue of sovereign rulers, nobles, and other persons of similar social stature, generally in monarchical contexts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4517" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>inter-dimensional schoolgirl</name>
<description>One, or more, schoolgirls cross through time, space or some dimension using a space-warp-magic-portal-wormhole-singularity-thing to save one, or more, worlds, or planets.
A major twist could be that the schoolgirl might originate from that very magic-futuristic world, bearing one great secret legendary power to defeat one big bad legendary foe. The return back home is the leitmotiv of the whole series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5420" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-24">
<name>it`s funny because they`re poor</name>
<description>A character`s relative lack of wealth is used as a source of humour.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5543" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-13">
<name>magic school</name>
<description>A school where magic is taught.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7402" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>corrupt nobility</name>
<description>The nobility is characterized by decadence, sadism, and contempt towards the baseborn.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="104783" type="main character in" update="2019-08-29">
<rating votes="9">9.34</rating>
<name>Mile</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42471" picture="242433.jpg">Waki Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104784" type="main character in" update="2019-08-29">
<rating votes="4">7.87</rating>
<name>Reina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104785" type="main character in" update="2019-08-29">
<rating votes="3">4.26</rating>
<name>Mavis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38903" picture="239362.jpg">Uchimura Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104786" type="main character in" update="2019-08-29">
<rating votes="4">6.35</rating>
<name>Pauline</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38504" picture="235939.jpg">Tazawa Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104910" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="2">7.71</rating>
<name>Kurihara Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42471" picture="242433.jpg">Waki Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105002" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-12">
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<name>Lenny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51410" picture="223259.jpg">Kouno Hiyori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105003" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-12">
<name>Nano-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105703" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-30">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Marcela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43438" picture="186227.jpg">Kawase Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105704" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-30">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Monica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105705" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-30">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Oriana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106181" type="appears in" update="2019-10-14">
<name>Maube</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56133" picture="223455.jpg">Zouza Shoumaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106182" type="appears in" update="2019-10-14">
<name>Elbert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106183" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Alady</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="58939" picture="239668.jpg">Kikunaga Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106711" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Reina no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53925" picture="213519.jpg">Tsuyuzaki Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106712" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Morena Oujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47036" picture="211659.jpg">Watabe Sayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106713" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Adele Gibo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57905">Nitta Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106714" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Prishy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57155" picture="228651.jpg">Hirose Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106715" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Brown</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56133" picture="223455.jpg">Zouza Shoumaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106716" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Crimson Lightning</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="106717" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>August</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40893" picture="223270.jpg">Furukawa Yurina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106718" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Gordon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="59245" picture="241058.jpg">Itou Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106719" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Eric</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49793" picture="201315.jpg">Okano Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106720" type="appears in" update="2019-11-05">
<name>Pauline no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47011" picture="223588.jpg">Hasegawa Nodoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106909" type="appears in" update="2019-11-11">
<name>Rou Gyosha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40230" picture="220313.jpg">Maruyama Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106910" type="appears in" update="2019-11-11">
<name>Anne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38294" picture="150942.jpg">Okuno Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107144" type="appears in" update="2019-11-25">
<name>Alan (Pauline no Otouto)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241515.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107145" type="appears in" update="2019-11-25">
<name>Boardman Shishaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107146" type="appears in" update="2019-11-25">
<name>Shoukaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3375" picture="72525.jpg">Bandou Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107147" type="appears in" update="2019-11-25">
<name>Austien Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107288" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<name>Receptionist</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39928" picture="181237.jpg">Yaehata Yukine</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107289" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<name>Booneclift</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107525" type="appears in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Cu Leleia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54287" picture="215346.jpg">Funato Yurie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107526" type="appears in" update="2019-12-16">
<name>Joshu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40893" picture="223270.jpg">Furukawa Yurina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107527" type="appears in" update="2019-12-16">
<name>Koryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107638" type="appears in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Kurihara Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42038" picture="166998.jpg">Nakano Saima</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107639" type="appears in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Kami-sama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29613" picture="78208.jpg">Aoi Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107640" type="appears in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Koryuu (Sherara)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107641" type="appears in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Koryuu (Beldetes)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="219000" update="2019-07-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!」ティザーPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 - Teaser PV (1:30)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi dette Itta yo ne!" Teaser PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219279" update="2019-08-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!」キャラクターPV:マイル (CV:和氣あず未)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 - Character PV: Mile (0:25)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi dette Itta yo ne!" Character PV: Mile (CV: Waki Azumi)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219293" update="2019-08-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!」キャラクターPV:レーナ (CV:徳井青空)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 - Character PV: Reina (0:26)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi dette Itta yo ne!" Character PV: Reina (CV: Tokui Sora)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219352" update="2019-08-15">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!」キャラクターPV:メーヴィス (CV:内村史子)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 04 - Character PV: Mavis (0:25)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi dette Itta yo ne!" Character PV: Mavis (CV: Uchimura Fumiko)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219806" update="2019-08-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!」キャラクターPV:ポーリン (CV:田澤茉純)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 05 - Character PV: Pauline (0:26)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi dette Itta yo ne!" Character PV: Pauline (CV: Tazawa Masumi)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219807" update="2019-08-28">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「私, 能力は平均値でって言ったよね!」メインPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 06 - Main PV (2:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi dette Itta yo ne!" Main PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221573" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新天地でやり直しって言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Said I`d Get a Do-Over in a New World!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit un nouveau départ dans un nouveau monde !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">قلت بأنني سأحظى بفرصة ثانية في عالم جديد!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Tenchi de Yarinaoshitte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Mile is a super normal 12 year old girl! Or so it seems... She`s actually one of those reincarnated-into-another-world people that are all the rage right now, who has all her memories of her past life as a Japanese high school girl named Kurihara Misato! Lots of stuff happened and Mile decided to become a Hunter, so she`s arrived in the Kingdom of Tiers where she learns of a series of child kidnappings in the capitol. Being a good person, Mile looks into the incident, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789445</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221574" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四人でパーティーって言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say the Four of Us Would Be a Party?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit qu’on ferait équipe à quatre !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن نكون نحن الأربعة فريقًا؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yonin de Partytte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>After successfully(?) concluding the incident, Mile enters the Kingdom of Tils` Hunter Prep School where she reunites with the three girls she met while investigating - Reina, Mavis, Pauline - and ends up forming a party with them. The experiences from her previous life make Mile dream of average happiness, but the three girls are very curious about the cheat-level power she just can`t seem to keep hidden. Will Mile`s dream ever come true?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789446</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221575" update="2019-11-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業は地味にって言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say to Make My Graduation Plain and Simple?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit une fin de formation discrète !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن تجعل تخرجي بسيطًا وعاديًا؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou wa Jimi nitte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>It`s been six months since they started at the Hunter Prep School. Drawn along by Mile`s insane abilities, Reina and the others` skills have rapidly improved so that they`ve mega leveled up without noticing. But just before graduation, Mile is pulled into a sordid plot. In order to protect the Hunter Prep School and keep it from getting closed down, Mile and the others must take on the challenge of the "Graduation Certification Mock Battle." It`s a fight they can`t afford to lose!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789447</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221576" update="2019-11-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤き誓いの第一歩って言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say This Was the Crimson Vow`s First Step?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit un premier pas pour le Serment rouge !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن هذه كانت الخطوة الأولى للعهد القرمزي؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akaki Chikai no Daiippotte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Now full-fledged Hunters, Mile, Reina, Mavis and Pauline form the "Crimson Vow." That said, they`re still just novices, so they work some questionable side-jobs while steadily gaining experience through straight-foward quests. One day, while on a quest as guards, they are attacked by bandits. The bandits think they`ll have an easy time of things, but Reina`s acting strangely...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789448</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="223461" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなの昔話って言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say That We`re Doing Everyone`s Backstories?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit le passé de tout le monde !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">قلت أننا سنصنع ماضي الجميع، أليس كذلك؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna no Mukashibanashitte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Reina reveals her past... Memories of a tragedy that torments her still. Then Pauline reveals her past, and Mavis reveals hers too. Then, suddenly, Mile gives confirmation of her past as well. Up until now, she`s managed to gloss things over, but the truth of her reincarnation into another world is here! And, of course, "those girls" will make an appearance too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789449</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="223462" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう森へなんて行かないって言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say I`m Not Going into the Forest Anymore?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit qu’on n’irait pas en forêt !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أنني لن أذهب إلى الغابة بعد الآن؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Mori e Nante Ikanaitte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Now that they each know the burdens of each other`s pasts, the Crimson Vow has only grown closer. Their job guarding has come to a successful close and they have a moment to enjoy a brief rest, but sudden bad news brings the smoldering embers of Reina`s resentment roaring back to life. How will Mile and the others face this first threat to the Crimson Vow? Their friendship is about to be tested...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789450</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="223463" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たまには休暇って言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say We Should Take Breaks Sometimes?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit des vacances de temps en temps !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">!ألم أقل أننا ينبغي أن نأخذ استراحة أحياناً؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama ni wa Kyuukatte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Having worked much too hard, Mile and the others decide the Crimson Vow should cease activities for a little while. In plain terms this means... That`s right, every working person`s inalienable right —— a vacation! While each of the friends enjoys their time off in their own way, Mile, with her sad history as a master of spending time by herself in her previous life, goes off to savor her time off on her own, but...
Also, on an unrelated note, this episode contains swimsuits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789451</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="223464" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポーリンが結婚って言ってないよね?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No One Mentioned That Pauline`s Getting Married, Did They?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On n’avait pas dit que Pauline se mariait !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن باولين ستتزوج؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pauline ga Kekkontte Itte Nai yo ne?!</title>
<summary>After a holiday, cruel reality is the destiny that awaits... Even in another world, that doesn`t change. Mile and the others are worried about Pauline who has suddenly disappeared. Then Mavis receives a letter from home saying that her older brother is getting married, and his bride to be is none other than Pauline!?
In order to settle the debts of Pauline`s past and deal with Mavis` family situation, Mile and the others head to Pauline`s home town!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789452</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224096" update="2019-11-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224097" update="2019-11-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224467" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワイバーン討伐って言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say Wyvern Hunting?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit une chasse à la vouivre !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن نصطاد وايفرن؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wyvern Toubatsutte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>To make it through, you need money! Even in another world, money is valued more than life! Being poor is the problem! To turn the tables on a tightfisted little girl, Mile and the others take on a high-paying quest with a high degree of difficulty -- that fantasy standard, wyvern hunting. For the sake of money, they`ll even make their friends cry! This is the epic struggle of Hunters running low on money! Also, completely unrelated, there will be baths in this episode.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789453</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224468" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サプライズは内緒でって言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say Surprises Should Be Kept Secret?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit de garder secret la surprise !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن المفاجآت ينبغي أن تبقى سرًا؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surprise wa Naisho dette Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Someone once said that to be alone is to be indifferent to one`s surroundings... Preposterous! When you`re alone, because you`re alone, you are more sensitive to your surroundings than anyone else. That is why Mile, with a long history of alone-ness, notices. She has noticed. And she wonders, "could it be that everyone`s avoiding me?!" Mile fears the looming threat of being alone again. What are Reina and the others` true intentions?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789454</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224469" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">慢心は禁物って言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say Arrogance Leads to Trouble?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit pas d’orgueil !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن التكبّر يؤدّي إلى المتاعب؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manshin wa Kinmotsutte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Having made tremendous advances, breaking through everything in their path since their Hunter debut, the Crimson Vow is now being treated as the next generation of ace Hunters by the Guild. They take on a difficult quest that other Hunters shy away from, but, lurking in the shadows of the quest, beastpeople are on the move. And it seems even that is not all there is to this quest... The Crimson Vow faces its most dire threat ever. The greatest of enemies appears before Mile!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789455</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224470" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤き誓いは不滅って言ったよね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Say the Crimson Vow Would Never Be Destroyed?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On avait dit que le Serment rouge était immortel !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألم أقل أن العهد القرمزي لن يدمر أبدًا؟!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akaki Chikai wa Fumetsutte Itta yo ne!</title>
<summary>Mile has been utterly defeated by the strongest creature in the world -- the elder dragon. The average abilities she wished for when she was reborn failed against the elder dragon, crushing her spirit and breaking her heart. Who speaks to Mile in her moment of despair? What will become of Reina and the others who stand in the face of the elder dragon because they believe in Mile? Will Mile ever attain normal happiness? This is the end. Blaze away, Crimson Vow!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789456</identifier>
<identifier>didnt-i-say-to-make-my-abilities-average-in-the-next-life</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225463" update="2019-12-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2019-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スマイルスキル＝スキスキル! Music Clip</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smile Skill = Suki Skill! Music Clip</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Smile Skill = Suki Skill! Music Clip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227291" update="2020-02-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2020-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲンザイ↑バンザイ↑ Music Clip</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Genzai Banzai Music Clip</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genzai Banzai Music Clip</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
