<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1387" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-09-10</startdate>
<enddate>1996-09-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gokinjo Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Neighborhood Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Повесть о соседях</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GokiMono</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ご近所物語</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Curiosando nei cortili del cuore</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3145" type="Same Setting">Paradise Kiss</anime>
<anime id="1790" type="Alternative Setting">Gokinjo Monogatari (1996)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3145" approval="26" total="37">Paradise Kiss</anime>
<anime id="475" approval="8" total="10">Super GALS! Kotobuki Ran</anime>
<anime id="4143" approval="4" total="5">Nana</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="80266">To those who love Yazawa Ai`s work: this is the anime that reveals the basic character design of her later work, such as Paradise Kiss and Nana.  Unfortunately, this anime is far too slow and reused a lot of scenes for my liking.  If it were made today, it`d be done in 2 seasons.  Also, I was disappointed at the special they skipped out from the manga that reveals the childhood story of Miwako and Arashi (later on became characters in Parakiss).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="305957">Easy going love comedy that strikes your heart</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/gokinjyo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1259" type="Original Work">Yazawa Ai</name>
<name id="5277" type="Music">Kawasaki Masahiro</name>
<name id="2208" type="Character Design">Umakoshi Yoshihiko</name>
<name id="1973" type="Direction">Umezawa Atsutoshi</name>
<name id="5374" type="Series Composition">Matsui Aya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shoujo manga by http://anidb.net/cr1259 [Yazawa Ai]-sensei, originally published in http://anidb.net/cr22563 [Ribon] magazine.
The story is about of http://anidb.net/ch25828 [Kouda Mikako], a creative, energetic girl who dreams of becoming a fashion designer, http://anidb.net/ch25829 [Yamaguchi Tsutomu] (the boy next door), and their friends at the Yazawa School of Design.
Source: Sumire-ya Anime and Manga Pages</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="204">6.16</permanent>
<temporary count="208">7.09</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>1193.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1764</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>859</identifier>
<identifier>guyebw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://annex.s-manga.net/gokinjyo/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/gokinjyo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Neighborhood_Story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ご近所物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88996</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>521</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/521</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1995/gokinjyo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="17">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gokinjyo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3263" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>fashion</name>
<description>Fashion is a popular aesthetic expression in a certain time and context, especially in clothing, footwear, lifestyle, accessories, makeup, hairstyle and body proportions.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25828" type="main character in" update="2015-01-23">
<rating votes="27">5.36</rating>
<name>Kouda Mikako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouda Mikako is a student at Yazawa Geijutsu Gakuen, a special high school for the arts in Tokyo.
Driven by her dream of becoming a fashion designer and having all the stores sell her handiwork under the brand name "Happy Berry", Mikako is at her most conspicuous when she is inspired or in a stormy mood for one reason or another. The former earns her the admiration of her classmates while the latter incenses her teacher Hamada-sensei who thinks nothing of keeping her after school to revise her clumsy handiwork. Mikako has a ferocious rivalry with Mariko who she fears will wield Tsutomu to his detriment along with unrealistic expectations of Tsutomu that leads to a very vivacious and adversarial divergent concourse that often inflames matters on many occasions.
Her younger sister is http://anidb.net/ch10014 [Sakurada Miwako], one of the protagonists of http://anidb.net/a3145 [Paradise Kiss].
The picture shows her the way she appears in Paradise Kiss, with pink hair. She is also known to feature brown and blond hair, as well as different lengths.</description>
<picture>167861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25829" type="main character in" update="2015-01-24">
<rating votes="12">2.68</rating>
<name>Yamaguchi Tsutomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A photographer and husband to Happy Berry`s star designer Kouda Mikako.</description>
<picture>61049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26117" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="5">4.07</rating>
<name>Tashiro Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26121" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<name>Nishino Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3704" picture="76764.jpg">Tsukui Kyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26122" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="1">4.11</rating>
<name>Oota Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26123" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="8">7.06</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1448" picture="18913.jpg">Niiyama Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26124" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Nakasu Mariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26127" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="8">4.45</rating>
<name>Oikawa Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26130" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="1">2.71</rating>
<name>Nakasu Shintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17081" picture="46372.jpg">Yonemoto Chizu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26131" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<name>Akindo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>61532.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26137" type="appears in" update="2015-01-27">
<rating votes="4">6.54</rating>
<name>Hamada-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hamada-sensei is, as the name suggests, a teacher at the Fashion school. She is strict when it comes to breaking the school`s rules, which doesn`t make her be less respected by her students at all.
The picture shows her appearance in Paradise Kiss.</description>
<picture>168017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4747" picture="171418.jpg">Hagimori Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26141" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<name>Tokumori Hiroaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26142" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<name>Kuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26143" type="appears in" update="2015-01-27">
<name>Sunami Noriji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The condo manager of the place Hiroyuki and Miwako grew up in.</description>
<picture>61544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26145" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<name>Kouda Ruriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3732" picture="25105.jpg">Kawanami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26148" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<name>Yamaguchi Kimiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61552.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26149" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<name>Yamaguchi Youichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61553.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26150" type="appears in" update="2011-03-23">
<name>Sakurada Hirohiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="14893" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">気になるアイツ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Childhood Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ki ni Naru Aitsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14894" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼なじみってやつ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dealing With a Childhood Friend!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osananajimitte Yatsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14895" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイスなバディ子!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nice Body-ko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nice Body Ko!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14896" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハマった方の負け!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fitting Direction For Defeat!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hamatta Kata no Make!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31255" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えるパツキン女!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flaming Blond Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeru Patsukin Onna!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31256" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サークルしようぜ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">More than just a Circle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Circle Shiyouze!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31257" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツトムかアキンドか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsutomu and Akindo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsutomu ka Akindo ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31258" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリーマーケット!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fleamarket!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flea Market!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31259" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪深きママの恋人!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Serious Crimes of Mom`s Boyfriend!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumibukaki Mama no Koibito!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31260" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のおもわくリレー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love`s Perplexing Relay</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Omowaku Relay</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31261" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Wデートって本気[マジ]?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seriously? A Double Date?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">W Datette Maji?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31262" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラれたツトム!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Swinging Tsutomu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furareta Tsutomu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31263" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイクに関する誤解</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Misunderstanding concerning a Bike</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bike ni Kan Suru Gokai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31264" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピイちゃんパニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">P-chan Panic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P-chan Panic</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51789" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンタへの贈りもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Present to Santa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Santa e no Okurimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51790" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛祈願! 初もうで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love Prayer! Happy New Year</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`ai Kigan! Hatsu Mou de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70021" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バディ子と新太郎!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Body-girl and Shintarou!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Body-ko to Shintarou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70022" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情か? 恋愛か?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What is Friendship? What is Love?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yujou ka? Ren`ai ka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70023" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発覚! リサの彼氏!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revealed! Risa`s Boyfriend!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakkaku! Risa no Kareshi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70024" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリマで恋のお勉強</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lessons in Love at the Flea Market</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">FleaMa de Koi no Obenkyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70025" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">素直になれたら...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If I`m Honest...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunao ni Naretara...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70026" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">及川歩って何者?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s Oikawa Ayumi?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oikawa Ayumutte nani Sha?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70027" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞い降りた天使!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Alighting Angel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maiorita Tenshi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70028" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人になっちゃった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Grown Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otona ni Nacchatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70029" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人に関する妄想</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delusions of the Duo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari ni Kan Suru Mousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70030" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉でメラメラ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fired Up at the Hot Springs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen de Meramera!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70031" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バディ子のイライラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Body-Ko`s Gripe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Body-Ko no Iraira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70032" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フキゲンの理由は?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Why So Sullen?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukigen no Riyuu wa?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70033" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリマ・アゲイン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flea Market Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">FleaMa Again!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70034" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋も夢も一歩ずつ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Step-By-Step With and Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi mo Yume mo Ippo Zutsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70035" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキッ! 師匠再び...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Omigosh! Shishou Again...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doki!! Shishou Futatabi...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70036" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心をつなぐロボット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robots Entwining the Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro o Tsunagu Robot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70037" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">軽い女に惚れたヤツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Guy Who Fell for the Vapid Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karui Onna ni Horeta Yatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70038" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一夜の天使...リサ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night with an Angel... Risa!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichinichi no Tenshi... Risa!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70039" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">せつない想い・歩!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feeling Heartbroken - Ayumi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsunai Omoi Ayumi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70040" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バディ子のゆううつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Body-ko`s Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Body-ko no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70041" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まだ帰りたくない...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Still Don`t Want To Go Back...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mada Kaeritakunai...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70042" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハンパじゃない16才</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making the Most of 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanpa ja Nai 16-sai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70043" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一番ほしいものは...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What I want the Most...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichiban Hoshii Mono wa...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70044" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">写真のないアルバム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Albums with No Pictures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shashin no Nai Album</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70045" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パパへのメッセージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Message for Papa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Papa e no Message</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70046" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パパの青い空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Papa`s Blue Skies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Papa no Aoi Sora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70047" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ママ, どうして...?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mama, Why...?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mama, Doushite...?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70048" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐のまえぶれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Storm Warnings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Maebure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70049" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘をつくのは...ヘタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bad at Lying</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso o Tsuku no wa... Heta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70050" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛してるなんて...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Before I Say I`m In Love With You...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itoshiteru Nante...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70051" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ママ!...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mama!...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mama! ...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70052" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"愛"ってやつ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Love You Have...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Ai"tte Yatsu...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70053" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二度めのプロポーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Proposal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nidome no Propose</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70054" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ありがとう, みんな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thank You, Everyone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arigatou, Minna</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
