<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13891" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2019-01-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Revisions</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">リヴィジョンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">revisions</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Revisions</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="600394">I`d rather a 1 hour movie summary instead of the full 12 episodes. 

Episode 1+2 is all you need to watch to determine whether or not 
the characters are too annoying [i](because they [b]basically[/b] never change)[/i] or 
the story is interesting enough to watch 10 more. 

If you like mecha and can ignore the characters, then I`m sure you could get the enjoyment that I failed to find in this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="729315">Pros: good animation, interesting setting, nice mecha design, overall production quality.
Cons: simplified "shounen`d" plot, featuring unexplained overcomplicated world mechanics, cartoonish villains (like talking teddy bear), unrewarding character archs and some deus ex machinas; general lack of substance.
In short - if you`re a fan of mecha/sci-fi/time travel stuff it`s worth checking out, otherwise there are probably better things to see.
Additional note: some people found CGI used in the series (specifically in character animation) unpleasant, so if it`s a pet peeve, might want to check the trailer first.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="219363">A very generic mecha show involving poorly executed time travel. The protagonist is a clone of Shinji from EVA, but much more childish, annoying and stupid.

The mecha and technobabble parts are very poorly executed or overly simplified(believable by 7 year old kids tops). The ideas behind the time travel and antagonists is pretty damn good, but the execution is extremely bad(a loli, a rabbit girl slut and a squirrel that can`t even get along, really?).

On a side note the last few episodes are very well done, the music is pretty good (especially the op) and if you ignore 5-6 episodes in the middle it can be an enjoyable watch. These episodes are pretty much the main character doing nothing and bitching about how he is (literally) the protagonist, so everyone should just bow before their savior for 15 minutes per episode.

If you are desperate for some mecha, you could enjoy this, but is a 5/10 at best.
If they made this into a 2 hour movie, it would be 7/10.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://revisions.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="22100" type="Animation Work">Shirogumi</name>
<name id="54105" type="Music">Kikuchi Azusa</name>
<name id="34196" type="Series Composition">Fukami Makoto</name>
<name id="23877" type="Series Composition">Hashimoto Taichi</name>
<name id="1" type="Direction">Taniguchi Gorou</name>
</creators>
<description>"This is a prophecy. Someday, the five of you will be put into terrible danger. And when that happens, you`re the only one who can protect everyone."
http://anidb.net/ch96595 [Doujima Daisuke], a 2nd-year student in high school who was kidnapped when he was younger, experiences a strange phenomenon along with his friends http://anidb.net/ch96596 [Gai], http://anidb.net/ch96597 [Lu], http://anidb.net/ch96598 [Marimari], and http://anidb.net/ch96599 [Keisaku]: "Shibuya Adrift". The center of the city of Shibuya is transported more than 300 years in the future. The people sent with it find nothing there but vast wastelands and forests, dotted with ruins... and hostile beings called "Revisions" that control massive mechanical monsters. As the monsters tear through Shibuya, someone appears to save the people: a girl with the same name, "http://anidb.net/ch96594 [Milo]", as the one who helped Daisuke when he was kidnapped, who looks identical to her as well. She gives Daisuke and his friends weapons called "String Puppets" that they can pilot, and tells them to protect Shibuya. Daisuke has spent his whole life believing in the prophecy that Milo gave him when he was kidnapped, and he`s overjoyed that the time has come at last and at the power he`s gained. But the kidnapping incident tore the 5 childhood friends apart.
An isolated city. An unknown enemy. An uncertain past and a prophecy of the future. The children fight the "future" to bring back the "present". No matter what, they`re going home...
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="174">3.29</permanent>
<temporary count="177">5.48</temporary>
<review count="1">5.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>227422.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21122</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://revisions.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Revisions_(TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Revisions_リヴィジョンズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5200</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363618</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21698</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>revisions_PR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7129" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-28">
<name>Plus Ultra</name>
<description>+Ultra is an anime programming block established by http://anidb.net/cr741 [Fuji TV] that began in October 2018.</description>
<picurl>66247.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="96594" type="main character in" update="2019-01-13">
<rating votes="7">5.87</rating>
<name>Milo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A descendant of humanity from the far future, which has been destroyed by a pandemic. One of the few humans who was resistant to the Revisions. She is an agent called a "Balancer" who works for the organization AHRV, which protects the future where humanity still survives. She has strong feelings of hatred towards the Revisions for their massacres of AHRV`s members, and devotes herself to the organization entirely. Emotionally inexpressive, she lives a logical, orderly life.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96595" type="main character in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="5">1.63</rating>
<name>Doujima Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>17 years old, and a second-year student at Seisho Academy. After being kidnapped as a child, he was saved by a mysterious woman named Milo, who told him, "You will be visited by a terrible danger. When that happens, you`ll be the only one who can protect everyone." He blindly believed her words, and has spent the rest of his life preparing for that moment. None of his other friends believe it, though, and he has become a social outcast. But he refuses to change his beliefs, and won`t listen to what anyone else says.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96596" type="main character in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Chang Gai Steiner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>17 years old, and a second-year student at Seisho Academy. Lu`s twin brother. An excellent student, and athletic as well. He dislikes Daisuke for the childish way he`s acting now that his dream of being a hero is coming true. But in fact, just like Daisuke he remembers the prophecy Milo gave him: "Doubt everything." He has the capability to be a cool and collected leader, a talent he puts to good use in the S.D.S. (Shibuya Defense Service).
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96597" type="main character in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<name>Chang Lu Steiner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>17 years old. Gai`s twin sister. Just like her brother, she`s good at sports and gets excellent grades. Strong on the outside, inside she is dependent on her brother, and follows him everywhere. Just like her brother, she`s aggravated by Daisuke`s overprotective nature, and keeps her distance from him. The only member of the team who doesn`t remember Milo`s prophecy.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96598" type="main character in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="3">2.37</rating>
<name>Temari Marin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>17 years old, and a second-year student at Seisho Academy. A classmate of Daisuke`s, who goes by the nickname "Marimari". Easygoing and cheerful, she`s beloved by her classmates, but she is also indecisive and lacking in confidence. Milo`s prophecy to her, "In the end, you`ll need to decide for yourself," weighs on her heavily. When she was young, she was fond of Daisuke, but in the future she has complicated feelings about the way he behaves as a "hero".
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49536" picture="228921.jpg">Iwami Manaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96599" type="main character in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<name>Asano Keisaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>17 years old, and a second-year student at Seisho Academy. Daisuke`s one real friend, and the only person who understands him. He acts as a buffer between the selfish Daisuke and the S.D.S. He`s always chipper and upbeat, but at the same time self-effacingly says that he "has no luck". He clearly remembers Milo`s words to him from the kidnapping incident, "Accept everything", and for this reason a part of him seems like he`s given up.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100255" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="3">4.35</rating>
<name>Chiharu Isurugi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A beautiful Revisions with dog ears and a tail. Always calm and relaxed, she`s very arrogant towards the people of Shibuya. She believes she is fulfilling a great duty for the sake of her fellow Revisions. Mukyu`s younger twin sister.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100256" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Nicholas Satou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Revisions that resembles a stuffed dog. His full name of "Nico of Laos, First Name Sugar", but nobody bothers to remember it. He has a carefree personality and enjoys never taking things too seriously. Chiharu and Mukyu slightly outrank him, and the two look down upon him.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100257" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Mukyu Isurugi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Revisions who wears a gothic lolita maid outfit, and has dog ears and a tail. She has a sadistic personality and shows no mercy to the people of Shibuya. She outranks Nicolas, and thus treats him very harshly, but she`s very kind to her twin sister Chiharu.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100258" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Doujima Mikio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daisuke`s uncle. He allowed Daisuke to move into the house he has in Shibuya, and attend school from there. A doctor who believes in comprehensive medical care, he is knowledgeable, courageous, and trusted by those around him.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100259" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="2">4.85</rating>
<name>Izumi Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female officer working for the Shibuya police. Works with Daisuke`s group as the person on the force responsible for handling the S.D.S. She has a strong sense of right and wrong and takes her work very seriously. Highly trusted, cheerful, and kind.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100260" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<name>Muta Seiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayor of Shibuya. Quick-witted and intelligent, and an excellent example of a typical politician. Also the head of the Disaster Response HQ. He tries to avoid taking responsibility for anything, and it`s very common for him to foist anything he doesn`t want to deal with onto his underlings.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100261" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Yazawa Yumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The school nurse at Daisuke`s school. She tries her hardest to be a good teacher, but because of her young age, all the students call her by her first name, and it bothers her.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100262" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Kuroiwa Ryouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief of the Shibuya Police. As the head of the only public safety organization that was sent to the future, he does his best to keep the peace in a city that`s fallen into chaos. He`s direct and bold, but can also be forceful and overbearing. He`s supposedly famous among other police for his skill with a gun.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>228918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="211443" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渋谷転送</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shibuya Transfer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Shibuya`nın Yolculuğu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shibutani Tensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211444" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者願望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heroic Desire</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kahraman Kompleksi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Ganbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211445" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守護者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Muhafızlar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shugosha-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211446" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第一次帰還計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Return Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İlk Dönüş Planı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiichiji Kikan Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211447" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来の姿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Appearance of the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gelecek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai no Sugata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211448" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だって, 人だから...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because They`re Humans...</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ne de Olsa İnsan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datte, Hito Dakara...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211449" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真夜中の狂詩曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Midnight Rhapsody</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gece Yarısı Rapsodisi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayonaka no Kyoushikyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211450" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オペレーション・ネフィリム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Nephilim</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Nephilim Operasyonu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Operation Nephilim</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211451" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消失の運命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loss of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yok Olmaya Mahkûm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushitsu no Unmei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211452" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなの街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone`s City</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Şehrimiz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna no Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211453" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Son Umut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kibou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211454" update="2018-12-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">revert</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revert</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">eskiye dönüş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Revert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211790" update="2019-01-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211791" update="2019-01-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
