<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13890" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-18</startdate>
<enddate>2018-10-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ingress the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">イングレス</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">INGRESS THE ANIMATION</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="733904">The ending seemed a bit rushed, but a decent watch nonetheless.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="684617">Kizuna AI appears in this anime.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://ingress-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="30484" type="Direction">Sakuragi Yuuhei</name>
<name id="54102" type="Original Work">Niantic</name>
<name id="40267" type="Music">Kawai Hidehiro</name>
<name id="54467" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Maru</name>
<name id="46540" type="Animation Work">Craftar</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an augmented-reality mobile game developed by http://anidb.net/cr54102 [Niantic].
At the CERN facility in Geneva, in the shadow of discovery of the Higgs-Boson, a secret project was taking place: The Niantic Project, where scientists discovered a mysterious substance that can interface directly with the human brain. This substance, called "Exotic Matter (XM)", has existed since ancient times, influencing human minds and the progress of humanity. In the wake of this discovery, a battle of powerful nations and corporate giants has been unleashed. Organizations across the globe have embarked on a secret race to exploit XM. It represents both an opportunity and a threat to humanity.
Two Factions seeks to control the XM, and through it, human destiny. The Enlightened view XM`s power as a gift that enhances human experience and discovery. The Resistance see XM as a hostile takeover of the human mind, choosing technology as humanity`s best path forward.
XM, and the mystery behind it, lie at the center of this battle for the fate of humanity.
2018 -
Now, a new struggle is about to unfold in Tokyo and across the globe. Dangerous and powerful forces seeking to exploit the potential of XM will collide.
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="118">3.36</permanent>
<temporary count="118">5.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224726.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21121</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37438</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ingress-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ingress_(TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>INGRESS_THE_ANIMATION</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5093</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363619</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21527</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>IngressAnime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.netflix.com/title/80992853</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3489" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>car chases</name>
<description>Car chases occur as part of the action setting in this anime.</description>
<picurl>211263.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4691" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-08">
<name>Switzerland</name>
<description>Switzerland, officially the Swiss Confederation is a federal republic in Europe. While still named the "Swiss Confederation" for historical reasons, modern Switzerland is a federal directorial republic consisting of 26 cantons, with Bern as the seat of the federal authorities, called "federal city". The country is situated in Western-Central Europe, and is bordered by Italy to the south, France to the west, Germany to the north, and Austria and Liechtenstein to the east. Switzerland is a landlocked country geographically divided between the Alps, the Swiss Plateau and the Jura, spanning an area of 41,285 km². While the Alps occupy the greater part of the territory, the Swiss population of approximately eight million people is concentrated mostly on the plateau, where the largest cities are to be found: among them are the two global and economic centres Zürich and Geneva.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192470.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7129" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-28">
<name>Plus Ultra</name>
<description>+Ultra is an anime programming block established by http://anidb.net/cr741 [Fuji TV] that began in October 2018.</description>
<picurl>66247.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97681" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="3">7.97</rating>
<name>Sarah Coppola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97682" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Jack Norman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3162" picture="151662.jpg">Kiyama Shigeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97683" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">3.38</rating>
<name>Hank Johnson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5576" picture="224283.jpg">Sasaki Hiroo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97684" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">8.23</rating>
<name>Midorikawa Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33069" picture="225127.jpg">Nakajima Yoshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97685" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<name>Jinkouchinou ADA</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98699" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<name>Christopher Brandt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98700" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">1.03</rating>
<name>Liu Tien Hua</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98701" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="1">3.38</rating>
<name>Kunikida Zion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="208871" update="2020-02-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Begin / Danger / Message</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Begin / Danger / Message</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Başla / Tehlike / Mesaj</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Begin / Danger / Message</title>
<summary>Able to see the memories of anything he touches, Special Agent Makoto Midorikawa is asked to help investigate the scene of a mysterious gas explosion.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208872" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Escape / Past / Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape / Past / Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaçış / Geçmiş / Kader</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Escape / Past / Destiny</title>
<summary>A Sensitive himself, agent of the resistance Jack Norman uses his extrasensory "flash forward" ability to pursue former XM researcher Sarah Coppola.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208873" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Advance / Discover / Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Advance / Discover / Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İlerle / Keşfet / Çatış</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Advance / Discover / Conflict</title>
<summary>Sarah and Makoto head to the secret Hulong lab deep in the woods of Kyoto, but they`re confronted by Liu`s security forces and Jack along the way.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208874" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Separate / Together / Pursue</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Separate / Together / Pursue</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ayrıl / Birleş / Takip Et</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Separate / Together / Pursue</title>
<summary>Overwhelmed by the incoming security force, Sarah gives herself up in order to spare Makoto`s life but is double crossed by Liu soon after.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208914" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Journey / Portal / Potential</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey / Portal / Potential</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yolculuk / Portal / Potansiyel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Journey / Portal / Potential</title>
<summary>After securing fake passports from a professional forger named Zion, Makoto and Jack Norman board a flight to Switzerland to rescue Sarah from Hulong.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208915" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Enlightenment / Resistance / Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enlightenment / Resistance / Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aydınlar / Direnişçiler / Kaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enlightenment / Resistance / Chaos</title>
<summary>While Hulong scientists test the effects of dark XM on Sarah`s body, her heightened ability enables her to speak to Makoto through the portal network.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208916" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Nature / Civilization / Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nature / Civilization / Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Doğa / Uygarlık / Ruh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nature / Civilization / Soul</title>
<summary>Aided by protectors of an ancient holy site, Makoto uses his powers to look for an escape route while hired mercenaries close in on their position.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208917" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Forget / Data / Rebel</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forget / Data / Rebel</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Unutma / Veri / İsyancı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Forget / Data / Rebel</title>
<summary>En route to rescuing Sarah inside CERN, Makoto and Jack are contacted by "ADA," the AI program originally created to analyze complex XM data.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208918" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Live / Die / Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live / Die / Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yaşam / Ölüm / Gerçek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Live / Die / Truth</title>
<summary>When Jack’s body begins to fail him, Liu reveals how far Christopher Brandt went in harnessing the Dark XM’s ungodly powers.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208919" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Destroy / Create / Answer</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destroy / Create / Answer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yok Etme / Yaratma / Yanıt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Destroy / Create / Answer</title>
<summary>With red portals overtaking the entire XM network, those wearing goggles embedded with Dark XM matter begin to collapse in agonizing pain.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208920" update="2020-02-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Us / Them / All</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Us / Them / All</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Biz / Onlar / Herkes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Us / Them / All</title>
<summary>The true mastermind’s diabolical plan moves one step closer to completion. Meanwhile, Makoto faces Liu, who`s hellbent on finishing what he started.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="209347" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209348" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212539" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212540" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212541" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212542" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212543" update="2019-02-12">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
