<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13924" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2019-10-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Black Fox</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ブラックフォックス</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الثعلب الأسود</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">ثعلب أسود</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BLACKFOX</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blackfox</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">بلاك فوكس</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="194065">Ninjas? Ok, it has some science too... Super power? hmmm, well, still good... wait, big robots? what?
...I can`t tell that it is bad, but I was waiting something... with less typical cliches in one anime. Still, I gave 8/10 for everything else.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://project-blackfox.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="58495" type="Music">Hashiguchi Kana</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
<name id="39884" type="Animation Work">Studio 3Hz</name>
<name id="2652" type="Character Design">Saitou Atsushi</name>
<name id="46528" type="Direction">Shinohara Keisuke</name>
<name id="8586" type="Chief Direction">Nomura Kazuya</name>
</creators>
<description>Living in a ninja residence tucked away in a corner of a futuristic city is http://anidb.net/ch99272 [Rikka], the eldest daughter of a Ninja clan, who looks up to her father—a researcher—very much. Carrying on with her life normally, Rikka`s home came suddenly under attack one day. Driven into a corner, what would she do to overcome this crisis?
Rip darkness to pieces and become "BLACK"!
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="356">5.97</permanent>
<temporary count="360">7.23</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231622.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20802</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://project-blackfox.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blackfox_(2019_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5468</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363831</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>blackfox_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>blackfox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7587" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2020-04-09">
<name>fake city</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="99270" type="main character in" update="2019-04-16">
<rating votes="7">7.78</rating>
<name>Mia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A powerful psychic with a sharp mind and is skillful in chess.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>232728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99271" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Melissa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/character/99272 [Rikka]`s roommate. She takes cares of all the chores while Rikka makes a living to support the both of them.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>232729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99272" type="main character in" update="2019-09-28">
<rating votes="8">7.67</rating>
<name>Isurugi Rikka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born into the Isurugi ninja clan. Though she is expected to succeed her http://anidb.net/character/101584 [grandfather] as the head of the clan, she looks up to her http://anidb.net/character/101582 [father] very much and wishes to follow in his footsteps to become a researcher.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>232727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43471" picture="200335.jpg">Nanase Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101577" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Oboro</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A droid resembling a dog.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101578" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Kasumi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A droid resembling a bird.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101579" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Harold</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owner of the detective agency http://anidb.net/character/99272 [Rikka] is working at.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101580" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Brad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>CEO/President of Gradsheim Tech Corp., a major corporation in Brad City.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101581" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Madara</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A droid resembling a flying squirrel.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101582" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Allen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/character/99272 [Rikka]`s father. A researcher who builds animal droids. He is peace-loving, kind and laid-back.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101583" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Lauren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A researcher who once worked for Gradaheim Tech Corp., engrossed in research involving potential abilities.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101584" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-28">
<name>Hyoue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/character/99272 [Rikka]`s grandfather and 17th head of the Isurugi Family. A stern man who values tradition.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>238891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="562" picture="17888.jpg">Tsuda Eizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102255" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-08">
<name>Kitsune Men no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious figure who wears a fox mask. She appears in the streets in the dead of the night dressed in all black and is often the talk of the town.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>232730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43471" picture="200335.jpg">Nanase Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218055" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2019-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789392</identifier>
<identifier>blackfox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221724" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Preview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
