<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13948" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2020-01-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Babylon</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">بابلون</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Вавилон</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バビロン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Babylon</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">BABYLON</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">巴比伦</title>
</titles>
<url>https://babylon-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="50050" type="Animation Work">Revoroot</name>
<name id="21425" type="Character Design">Gotou Keisuke</name>
<name id="23652" type="Direction">Suzuki Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="40358" type="Music">Yamada Yutaka</name>
<name id="46631" type="Original Work">Nozaki Mado</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a suspense novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr46631 [Nozaki Mado].
Shinki is a new "autonomous zone" being established in western Tokyo to accommodate the metropolis` ever-growing population, and the upcoming mayoral elections have dominated discussion in the media for weeks. In the middle of investigating pharmaceutical law violations for the Tokyo Public Prosecutor`s Office, Prosecutor http://anidb.net/ch105939 [Seizaki Zen] and his assistant http://anidb.net/ch105938 [Fumio Atsuhiko] stumble on to evidence linking the bizarre suicide of an anesthesiologist to one of the mayoral candidates, http://anidb.net/ch105941 [Nomaru Ryuuichirou]. Suspecting a scandal that could tear Shinki`s burgeoning political scene into pieces, Zen and Atsuhiko begin pulling at the threads of the case, and with the body count rising, its impossible to say just how deep the corruption in the city could possibly go.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="271">4.24</permanent>
<temporary count="281">5.93</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>237571.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20775</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37525</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://babylon-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Babylon_(novel_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>バビロン_(小説)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5437</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>babylon_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=8hVJv6loLVE</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=kPTgxJMt6I8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=hxOaJ7V0QyY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07YQPR7X3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4244" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>healthcare and medicine</name>
<description>The anime contains themes related to healthcare, medicine, or the human body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4851" parentid="4340" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>group suicide</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="105935" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-27">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Kujiin Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105936" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-27">
<rating votes="2">1.16</rating>
<name>Hanta Ariyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105937" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-27">
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<name>Morinaga Yasutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105938" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Fumio Atsuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105939" type="main character in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="4">8.70</rating>
<name>Seizaki Zen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105940" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-30">
<rating votes="4">6.67</rating>
<name>Sekuro Hiasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68121.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105941" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-18">
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<name>Nomaru Ryuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105942" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-18">
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<name>Itsuki Kaika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106102" type="appears in" update="2020-03-30">
<rating votes="6">9.20</rating>
<name>Magase Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106511" type="appears in" update="2019-10-27">
<name>Mitoni Ben</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106512" type="appears in" update="2019-10-27">
<name>Okuda Ryousei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106513" type="appears in" update="2020-02-18">
<name>Hiramatsu Emiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43275" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108710" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-16">
<name>Alexander W Wood</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245004.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221398" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『バビロン』ティザーPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:25)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Babylon" Teaser PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221399" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ【バビロン】第一弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Babylon" Dai Ichi Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221400" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ「バビロン」第二弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (1:07)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Babylon" Dai Ni Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221585" update="2019-09-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suspicion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suspicion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giwaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221586" update="2019-10-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">標的</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouteki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221587" update="2019-10-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">革命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221588" update="2019-09-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poursuite</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223435" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223436" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Stratégie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223437" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最悪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Most Evil</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le plus grand mal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223438" update="2019-11-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Espoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224455" update="2019-11-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">連鎖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaîne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rensa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224456" update="2019-11-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Décision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224457" update="2019-11-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Curtain Rises</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rideau se lève</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaimaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224458" update="2019-11-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終[おしまい]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshimai</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
