<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13956" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-01</startdate>
<enddate>2018-12-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Akanesasu Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あかねさす少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Girl in Twilight</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">노을빛 소녀</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">茜色少女</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1093" approval="5" total="7">Yami to Boushi to Hon no Tabibito</anime>
<anime id="70" approval="3" total="8">Abenobashi Mahou Shoutengai</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://akanesasushojo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7652" type="Character Design">Harada Hiroki</name>
<name id="12362" type="Direction">Abe Yuuichi</name>
<name id="19696" type="Series Composition">Yasukawa Shougo</name>
<name id="30966" type="Direction">Tamamura Jin</name>
<name id="41683" type="Work">Juumonji</name>
<name id="32298" type="Work">DandeLion Animation Studio, LLC</name>
<name id="21040" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamoto Akitomo</name>
</creators>
<description>Constantly on the lookout for her next big adventure, the cheerful and kind http://anidb.net/ch97204 [Tsuchimiya Asuka] is always ready to try new things with her high school friends from the Crystal Radio Club. One day, the group performs a ritual from an urban myth just for fun. However, several conditions had fallen into place to put the ritual in motion, opening the door to a new world of gold and jet black. In this world, Asuka finds a different version of herself and soon finds out that some doors were never meant to be opened.
Source: sentai filmworks</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="342">4.26</permanent>
<temporary count="342">5.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224633.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20780</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37561</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://akanesasushojo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Akanesasu_Shōjo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あかねさす少女</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5043</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363779</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21504</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>akanesasu_shojo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=KJnar9nfAUM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97202" type="main character in" update="2018-09-10">
<rating votes="5">6.02</rating>
<name>Mia Silverstone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97203" type="main character in" update="2018-09-10">
<rating votes="3">5.73</rating>
<name>Nanase Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97204" type="main character in" update="2018-09-10">
<rating votes="10">9.21</rating>
<name>Tsuchimiya Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97205" type="main character in" update="2018-09-10">
<rating votes="4">5.89</rating>
<name>Morisu Chloe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97206" type="main character in" update="2018-09-10">
<rating votes="4">7.79</rating>
<name>Tounaka Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98272" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Annie Makusuda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98273" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>White Goat</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98274" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Chiba Tomoya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98275" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Tsuchimiya Kyouhei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98276" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Ookubo Daichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="46602" picture="224736.jpg">Kubota Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98277" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Yamanashi Mayuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="51124" picture="205672.jpg">Kusunoki Tomori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98278" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Matsu Akane</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="55692" picture="224737.jpg">Suzushiro Sayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98279" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Ooga Teru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="43438" picture="186227.jpg">Kawase Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98280" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Kitta Kurato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98281" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Hiishi Saro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98282" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Abuta Shioku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98283" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Yaji Yuudai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98284" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-01">
<name>Hakuma Jin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="207923" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4時44分の儀式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ritual at 4:44</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4 Ji 44 Pun no Gishiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207924" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">違う世界[フラグメント]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Fragment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fragment</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207925" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウェディング・ベルが鳴る前に ~The bride can`t help it~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Before the Wedding Bells Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wedding Bell ga Naru Mae ni: The Bride Can`t Help It</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207926" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">荒野の五人, もしくは十一人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magnificent Five, or Eleven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouya no Gonin, Moshikuwa Juuichinin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208851" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209069" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209185" update="2018-10-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒーローの条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero in Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hero no Jouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209186" update="2018-10-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりのアイランド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alone in the Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori no Island</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209187" update="2018-10-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Tu n`es pas seule.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tu N`Es Pas Seule.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tu N`Es Pas Seule.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209188" update="2018-10-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日架とアスカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Asuka and Asuka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asuka to Asuka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210045" update="2018-11-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そこに在る黄昏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing Twilight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soko ni Aru Tasogare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210046" update="2018-11-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うそつきの宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Liars` Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usotsuki no Utage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210047" update="2018-11-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優等生 ~You~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You, the Honor Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuutousei: You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210048" update="2018-11-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつか, 黄昏の降る空の</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Twilight Falls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuka, Tasogare no Furu Sora no</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219186" update="2019-08-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2019-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">3Dバトルシーン (ディレクターズカット版)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3D Battle Scene (Director`s Cut)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">3D 배틀 장면 (Director`s Cut)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3D Battle Scene (Director`s Cut Han)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
