<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13972" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-09-21</startdate>
<enddate>2019-04-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yarichin Bitch-bu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヤリチン☆ビッチ部</title>
</titles>
<url>http://yaribu.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="11871" type="Character Design">Haneda Kouji</name>
<name id="19290" type="Direction">Yoshimura Ai</name>
<name id="33733" type="Music">Katayama Shuji</name>
<name id="54285" type="Original Work">Ogeretsu Tanaka</name>
<name id="54297" type="Animation Work">Grizzly</name>
<name id="11871" type="Chief Animation Direction">Haneda Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: Episode 1 was bundled with the limited edition 3rd volume manga.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="34">4.45</permanent>
<temporary count="35">6.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221140.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21142</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37585</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://yaribu.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヤリチン☆ビッチ部</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363825</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yaribu_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="201362" update="2018-09-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217676" update="2019-05-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2019-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219046" update="2019-07-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
