<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="140" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>1999-10-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou Tsukai Tai! (1999)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magic User`s Club TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magic User`s Club</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Клуб любителей магии [ТВ]</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mahou Tsukai Tai TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">MUC TV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MTT TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法使いTai! (1999)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Magic User`s Club! TV Series</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il club della magia!</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Escuela de Brujas</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">마법을 쓰고 싶어!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="141" type="Prequel">Mahou Tsukai Tai!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/ttl/index.php?ttl_c=229</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="789" type="Animation Work">Triangle Staff</name>
<name id="3611" type="Original Plan">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="3611" type="Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
<name id="3742" type="Series Composition">Konaka Chiaki</name>
<name id="4280" type="Character Design">Itou Ikuko</name>
<name id="4280" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Ikuko</name>
</creators>
<description>One day everything changed, an alien civilization of immense power sent a probe to the Earth. Their forces were so powerful and overwhelming the combined might of the UN forces were destroyed in the blink of an eye. But after the initial battle the aliens settled into a quietly peaceful, even polite observation of the citizens of earth. Life went on as usual except for the odd appearance of a robotic probe. People accepted their new neighbours.
Everyone except a small group of students at a local high school. Drawing upon long since forgotten knowledge, the Magic User`s Club sets their mission as the defeat of the forces of the alien "Bell".</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="519">5.25</permanent>
<temporary count="521">6.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>152797.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>41</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>630</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>259</identifier>
<identifier>qflyyj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/ttl/index.php?ttl_c=229</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magic_User's_Club#TV_series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法使いTai!#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1312</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159334</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19044" type="main character in" update="2010-12-09">
<rating votes="4">6.48</rating>
<name>Nakatomi Nanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 2nd year and a friend of Sae since childhood. She just wants to be a normal high school girl and gets frustrated with Sae`s obsession with the Magic Club, although she is proficient in magic herself. Nanaka has a crush on Aburatsubo but is afraid to admit her feelings because she knows they won`t be returned. She describes her family as "all over the place", and though often embarrassed and aggravated by their antics, she loves them dearly. (wiki)</description>
<picture>60532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2138" picture="21613.jpg">Iizuka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19047" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="6">8.34</rating>
<name>Aikawa Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aikawa Akane is a 1st year and another new member of the Magic Club. Akane is a spoiled rich girl who often misses going to club meetings in order to go on dates with boyfriends. She seems to be a natural at using magic, and it comes very easily to her (such is her inate skill that she is able to make makeshift wands out of rudimentary objects, though they are rather primitive and weak compared to her regular wand), though it can`t be said the same for her flying. Akane often uses magic for selfish reasons against what Takakura has taught, which causes Sae to lecture her in several instances. In a cute touch, anything affected solely by her magic spins before the spell`s true effect come to pass, something which she has no control over.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>60531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19049" type="main character in" update="2010-12-09">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Sawanoguchi Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>2nd year student at Kitanohashi High School and a new member of the Magic Club. Sae is eager to learn magic, but often has setbacks due to her clumsy nature. She looks up to Takakura as a great mentor. Although she actually has feelings for him beyond that, she is too shy to express them. Of the five members, Sae has the greatest amount of power to utilize, but lacks the training and concentration to fully tap into this potential. (wiki)</description>
<picture>60533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4037" picture="174276.jpg">Konishi Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19050" type="main character in" update="2012-06-02">
<rating votes="5">6.44</rating>
<name>Aburatsubo Ayanojou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19051" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-16">
<rating votes="3">4.22</rating>
<name>Miyama Mizuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19053" type="main character in" update="2011-01-16">
<rating votes="5">8.28</rating>
<name>Takakura Takeo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53059" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-21">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Jinno Jurika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2360" picture="228063.jpg">Miyahara Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1095" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪と, 子馬と, ファースト・キッス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow, the Colt, and a First Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki to, Kouma to, First Kiss</title>
<summary>Sae is off to the Hokkaido countryside to visit the family farm! It’s fun to see her parents again, and to take care of the horses that she loves. But suddenly, Jurika appears. How did he get there, and what could he possibly want?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725071</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1096" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">茜ちゃんと, しゃっくりと, アヤシイ関係</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akane, the Hiccups, and a Strange Relationship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akane-chan to, Shakkuri to, Ayashii Kankei</title>
<summary>Something’s wrong with Akane. Her magic is out of control, she’s constantly blushing, and… did she just ask Takeo to go out with her?! Time for the rest of the club (and Mizuha Miyama) to snoop around and get to the bottom of this!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725061</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1097" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沙絵と, 風呂場と, 扉の向こう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sae, the Bathroom, and the Other Side of the Door</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sae to, Furoba to, TObira no Mukou</title>
<summary>Today’s lesson for the Magic User’s Club is a spell that will let them teleport anywhere they want. But it doesn’t really work… or does it? Now, whenever they walk through a door, they have no idea what will be on the other side!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725059</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1098" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">油壷先輩と, 朝顔と, 親子面談</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aburatsubo, Morning Glories, and Parent-Teacher Meetings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aburatsubo-senpai to, Asagao to, Oyako Mendan</title>
<summary>It’s time for Parent-Teacher Meetings, and no one is dreading it more than Aburatsubo. He’s normally cool, calm and composed, but the mere mention of his mother sends him into a panic - and she’ll be arriving any minute now!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725057</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1099" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七香と, ケーキと, 危険な夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanaka, a Cake, and a Dangerous Evening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanaka to, Cake to, Kiken na Yoru</title>
<summary>Nanaka has had enough of her rude, careless family! She’s running away to live with Sae (again). When Akane drops by, the three girls set up a slumber party full of fun, laughter, and out-of-control magic.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725055</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1100" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沙絵と, 魔法クラブと, 桜の木</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sae, the Magic Club, and the Cherry Blossom Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sae to, Mahou Club to, Sakura no Ki</title>
<summary>The Magic User’s Club defeated a giant ship from outer space! But their close encounter left a huge cherry blossom tree in the middle of the city. Takeo calls a club meeting to deal with the tree, but their magic backfires…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725053</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1101" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">振袖と, 短パンと, 華の時代</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long-Sleeved Kimonos, Shorts, and the Age of Joy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furisode to, Tanpan to, Hana no Jidai</title>
<summary>Sae wants to find the mysterious person she keeps seeing – and Akane knows just where to look. She leads Sae and Nanaka to a place where the two are quickly dressed in kimonos, handed scripts, and told to get ready for an audition!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725069</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1102" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沙絵の魔法, 沙絵の気持ち, いつまでもずっと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sae`s Magic, Sae`s Feelings, Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sae no Mahou, Sae no Kimochi, Itsumademo Zutto</title>
<summary>The truth about Jurika has been revealed, and Sae has vowed to never use magic again. But Jurika won’t let her go – he’s locked her away in a place no one can reach. Takeo and the others have to find her, before she’s lost forever!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725077</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1103" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリスと, 踏切と, ソースせんべい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alice, the Railroad Crossing, and Rice Crackers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alice to, Fumikiri to, Sauce Senbei</title>
<summary>Sae’s plans for the Culture Festival are quickly falling apart. Takeo is fighting with Miyama, everyone else is overbooked, and now a strange new person has appeared. Is this mysterious “Alice in Wonderland” a friend or a foe?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725067</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1104" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タコと, 稲妻と, ミッキー先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Octopus, a Flash of Lightning, and Micky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tako to, Inazuma to, Mickey-senpai</title>
<summary>Akane is on a rampage! Or at least, she would be, if it wasn’t for all that ennui. But one way or another, she needs to be stopped before she hurts someone. It’s up to Sae and Nanaka, but they aren’t alone – Micky appears to help!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725075</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1105" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沙絵と, トマトと, 絵筆のダンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sae, a Tomato, and the Dance of the Paintbrush</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sae to, Tomato to, Efude no Dance</title>
<summary>The Culture Festival is coming, and Sae wants to make it something special! But the rest of the club isn’t quite so enthusiastic. What’s more, if they want the space to hold their own event, they’ll have to fight Miyama to get it!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725065</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1106" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">茜ちゃんと, 鏡と, 歳末バーゲン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akane, the Mirror, and the End of the Year Sale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akane-chan to, Kagami to, Saimatsu Bargain</title>
<summary>Jurika has many powers, but the strangest one of all is that he seems to know everyone’s heart. He knows what each member of the club is thinking, and he’s about to bring those thoughts into the open, whether they want him to or not.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725073</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="1107" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高倉先輩と, やっこと, 秘密のデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takakura, Origami, and the Secret Date</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takakura-senpai to, Yakko to, Himitsu no Date</title>
<summary>The club made origami using magic, and Sae did really well! But ever since then, something has been a bit off. Time keeps flashing around Sae, as her dreams and reality start mixing together. There’s only one person who can help…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725063</identifier>
<identifier>magic-users-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="14467" update="2004-01-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OutTakes 01-04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14468" update="2004-01-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OutTakes 05-07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14469" update="2004-01-28">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OutTakes 08-10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14470" update="2004-01-28">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OutTakes 11-13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49197" update="2006-04-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
