<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14000" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-30</startdate>
<enddate>2018-07-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sword Gai: The Animation Part II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソードガイ The Animation PartII</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10858" type="Prequel">Sword Gai The Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://swordgai-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="30252" type="Animation Work">LandQ Studio</name>
<name id="1419" type="Character Design">Nakajima Atsuko</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="3719" type="Original Work">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="52815" type="Original Work">Kine Osamu</name>
<name id="8462" type="Original Work">Amemiya Keita</name>
<name id="17984" type="Direction">Naka Tomohito</name>
<name id="17590" type="Chief Direction">Ikezoe Takahiro</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>While the cursed power of Shiryu grows stronger within http://anidb.net/ch94217 [Gai] each day, both Shoshidai and the mysterious Gabi continue their mission to protect mankind.
Source: netflix</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="99">2.44</permanent>
<temporary count="101">5.23</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221134.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21243</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37655</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://swordgai-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sword_Gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ソードガイ_装刀凱</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3339" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-11">
<name>demon hunt</name>
<description>Demons are tracked down and probably killed in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="95252" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-28">
<name>Himiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of Gabi. She mastered the Hollow Kempo which enables her to hold dozens of weapons inside her body.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>216864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95254" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-28">
<name>Matoba Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student who helps out his father major enterprise Matoba Group`s president`s job. He transfers to the same school as Sayaka.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>216865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="203606" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<summary>With the all-powerful Grimms looking on, Gai and Shin face-off in a ferocious battle, wielding their respective Shiryus against one another.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203607" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<summary>Gai`s awakening unleashes chaos into the world. Busoma Zsoltgewinn in Miura`s human form appears before Amon and Kigetsu.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203608" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<summary>With his resentment towards Gai intensifying, Shin resolves to devote himself to combating the Busoma as a Chrysalis.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203609" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<summary>Shin makes a grim discovery at the hospital where Rie resides. Meanwhile, both Yasuko and Arnys pay a visit to Issei who has left the Shoshidai.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203610" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<summary>The true reason for the Shoshidai-sponsored hospitalization of Rie and the others is revealed. Shin and Ogata ask Kuromaru to take them to meet Gai.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203611" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<summary>Shoshidai sends three Chrysalises to kill Miura`s Zsoltgewinn, but Kyoka begs them to use their prototype vaccine on her father to save him instead.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203612" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<summary>Shin undergoes a risky procedure to rid his body of the core alma. Kuromaru takes a liking to Gai after Gai rescues him from attack.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203613" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<summary>Under the care of the Gabi, Gai dedicates himself to meditation and receives a new prosthetic arm. A bullied kid seeks help from an unlikely source.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203614" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<summary>Himiko, leader of the Gabi, locates the Busoma responsible for her comrade Soin`s death. Kagami is ordered to stand down against Marcus` Azoth.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203615" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<summary>With a Busoma running rampant outside Shoshidai headquarters, Kagami reawakens three Chrysalises from cold sleep to neutralize the hostile threat.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203616" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<summary>Although content with his missions for Shoshidai and relationship with his girlfriend, Marcus senses something is not right after his date with Aya.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203617" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<summary>With the long-fought battle with Miura`s Zsoltgewinn coming to a dramatic end, Gai must now fulfill a promise he made with Ichijo.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
