<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14009" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-27</startdate>
<enddate>2016-07-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Patisserie no Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">パティシエのモンスター</title>
</titles>
<description>Pâtisserie no Monster focuses on the titular monster Powan, the owner of a small pastry shop in France.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13">3.28</permanent>
<temporary count="13">4.34</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>215802.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33122</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2795" parentid="1973" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>baking</name>
<description>The art of making bread, cakes, pastries, pies, tarts, quiches, cookies and similar food in the oven.
Mmmm.... smells nice.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2973" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>cute monster</name>
<description>Cute monster refers to animal soldiers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3206" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-06">
<name>stop motion</name>
<description>Stop motion (also known as stop-action or frame-by-frame) is an animation technique to make a physically manipulated object appear to move on its own. The object is moved in small increments between individually photographed frames, creating the illusion of movement when the series of frames is played as a continuous sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="200610" update="2018-06-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200611" update="2018-06-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200612" update="2018-06-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200613" update="2018-06-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200614" update="2018-06-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
