<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14008" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>2018-10-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Overlord III</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">オーバーロード III</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Overlord 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">OVERLORD III</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">오버로드 3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">OVERLORD III</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12952" type="Prequel">Overlord II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272004">Season three picks up where season one left off in terms of story-telling and episode quality. In this regard, it`s much more enjoyable than season two in my opinion and I recommend you to watch it (you really have to if you`ve watched its predecessors).
If you can, watch all three seasons at once. The show feels much more flshed out that way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="415669">If you liked the first 2 seasons, you`ll like this one too. Nothing much to say except that it continues the story and is still really good to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="274570">The storyline gets better even despite the lack of appearance of the main char. The only thing that will bother you is the CGI if you didn`t watched the first two season watch it first to enjoy this season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://overlord-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="7839" type="Character Design">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="33391" type="Series Composition">Sugawara Yukie</name>
<name id="42661" type="Original Work">Maruyama Kugane</name>
<name id="6476" type="Direction">Itou Naoyuki</name>
<name id="33733" type="Music">Katayama Shuji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel series by the same name written by http://anidb.net/cr42661 [Maruyama Kugane] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr42662 [So-Bin].
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event held at United Cinemas Aqua City Odaiba on 24.06.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1787">6.25</permanent>
<temporary count="1809">7.13</temporary>
<review count="1">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221902.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21105</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37781</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37675</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://overlord-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Overlord_(novel_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オーバーロード_(小説)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4998</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365086</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>363967</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>over_lord_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07GNXYM4Z</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4342" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-06">
<name>large-scale war</name>
<description>When the whole world, or, at least, a big part of it, partakes in the hell that is war.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7141" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-16">
<name>goblin</name>
<description>A goblin is a monstrous creature from European folklore, first attested in stories from the Middle Ages. They are ascribed various and conflicting abilities, temperaments and appearances depending on the story and country of origin. They are almost always small and grotesque, mischievous or outright malicious, and greedy, especially for gold and jewelry. They often have magical abilities similar to a http://anidb.net/t780 [fairy] or http://anidb.net/t2646 [demon].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>220782.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="72777" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-13">
<rating votes="94">3.98</rating>
<name>Aura Bella Fiora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72778" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="344">6.05</rating>
<name>Albedo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albedo is the Overseer of the Floor Guardians of the Great Tomb of Nazarick. She is in charge of the general management and supervises the activities of the seven Floor Guardians, meaning that she ranks above all the other NPCs in Nazarick. She is the sister of Nigredo and Spinel. She was created by Tabula Smaragdina.
She was originally programmed to be a nymphomaniac, but Momonga altered her personality and changed her setting to be in love with him.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>174511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72779" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="57">7.09</rating>
<name>Cocytus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cocytus is the Guardian of the 5th Floor of Nazarick.
Cocytus is the personal creation of Warrior Takemikazuchi, one of the 41 members of Ainz Ooal Gown. Cocytus was created to personify the perfect warrior both in body and spirit. Cocytus is loyal to a fault to the Supreme Beings but he`s not just a dumb muscle and is willing to learn in to better serve his lord. Amongst the denizen of Nazarick, he`s more accepting of outsiders provided they share the same strength, honor, and warrior spirit that he epitomizes.
Cocytus design is based on the Gelugon, a type of ice-devil from D&amp;D. He has the highest offensive capabilities of melee fighters in Nazarick backed up by ice-elemental skills. Cocytus have no need for armor as his exoskeleton serves as a living armor. His creator, Warrior Takemikazuchi, has equipped Cocytus with many of his own personally crafted weapons and has programmed Cocytus with the knowledge of all of the Divine Weapons own by the Supreme Beings.
Cocytus seems to prefer the company of other insectoids like him from Nazarick. He also hold good relations with Demiurge and often asks the demon for advice too difficult for himself to understand.</description>
<picture>174516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72780" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="227">4.40</rating>
<name>Shalltear Bloodfallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shalltear Bloodfallen is the first, second and third floor guardian. She is a true vampire and the Floor Guardian of the first to third floors in the Great Tomb of Nazarick. She was created by Peroroncino.
Shalltear is the strongest of the floor guardians and is completely loyal to Ainz and is also a love rival to Albedo for his affections. She takes great joy in being able to prove her worth and fantasizes about the praise she expects to receive. When a situation doesn`t go in her favor, she panics about the scolding she believes that she will get.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>174512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72781" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="90">7.42</rating>
<name>Sebas Tian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72782" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="144">4.06</rating>
<name>Demiurge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Demiurge is the Guardian of the 7th Floor of the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
Demiurge is the personal creation of Ulbert Alain Odle, one of the 41 members of Ainz Ooal Gown. Ulbert created Demiurge as the personification of evil. As such, Demiurge relish in acts that embodies this twisted morality scripted onto him. He is cruel and uniformly incompassionate to all beings who do not belong to the Tomb of Nazarick and thinks little more of them than tools and toys to amuse himself with. However, to all of his comrades, Demiurge demonstrate true care and loyalty. Demiurge suffers an existential crisis, more than other denizens of Nazarick, due to his fear of losing Ainz Ooal Gown as the last remaining Supreme Being.
Demiurge is amongst the weakest of the Floor Guardian in pure destructive power. However, he has an extremely high intellect and excel at long term strategic planning. Often, he can predict the actions of people with high standing on a national level and equally high hubris down to the exact detail. Though his own personal power is low, Demiurge commands the Demon Lords, a group of high level subordinate whom themselves command legions of inferno demons.
Though he`ll get along with anyone who`s a comrade in Nazarick, Demiurge have an unexplained dislike of Sebas Tian. Unbeknownst to both NPCs, they`ve inherited the conflict from the personal dispute of their own creators.</description>
<picture>174515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72783" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="255">6.35</rating>
<name>Narberal Gamma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narberal Gamma is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades], combat maids under http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas Tian]. She`s a doppelganger and http://anidb.net/ch76797 [Momon]`s companion in their adventurers` guild, Darkness. She was chosen as one due to her most human-looking appearance out of all other maids. As an adventurer, she refers to herself as Nabe.
Like most of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick] residents, she holds great disdain towards humans. This often proves troublesome, as she becomes incredibly violent when human males make advances on her.</description>
<picture>176197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72784" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="69">5.53</rating>
<name>Mare Bello Fiore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72785" type="main character in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="513">5.24</rating>
<name>Ainz Ooal Gown</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momonga is the guildmaster and only remaining active player of the guild Ainz Ooal Gown from the DMMORPG game Yggdrasil, once one of the top guilds in the game. When the guild`s base, the Underground Tomb of Nazarick, was transported to an alternate reality and a new world, Momonga soon assumed for himself the name of Ainz Ooal Gown and began a campaign to make his guild legendary, subsequently turning to world domination.
When he was still human and an Yggdrasil player, Ainz was an adult man already jaded by life, making him prone to analyse things from his perspective as a company worker. In the new world, his game avatar, an undead lich, became his real body, along with all the physical characteristics such a body would have; as a result, he is nigh immune to strong emotions and worldly temptations and desires, because his status as an undead physically shuts them down.
Ainz is calculating, subversive, and cowardly when approaching or in the imminence of a battle, placing his continued survival, as well as that of the guild and its NPCs, who gained life with the transfer, above all else, and planning many moves ahead; once his plans are set in motion, he is ruthlessly efficient in their execution, and will not bat an eyelid at slaying his opponents when pressed. His actions are vicious and ruthless towards any and all that oppose him, and he is motivated by his own gains and survival and the glory of his guild`s name. His greatest weakness is his great fear of not being recognized as a proper leader by the guild`s NPCs, causing him to play along with their plans when he does not understand them simply to not be forced to admit to them that he is not following what they have in mind.</description>
<picture>174510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75833" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="38">7.32</rating>
<name>Enri Emmot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75834" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="58">7.83</rating>
<name>Gazef Stronoff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76484" type="appears in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="8">5.77</rating>
<name>Nemu Emmot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76772" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-12">
<rating votes="26">4.61</rating>
<name>Nfirea Bareare</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nfirea is a famous pharmacist in E-Rantel. He is the grandson of Lizzie and the childhood friend of Enri Emmot whom he holds romantic feelings towards.
He is a young boy with short blonde hair that half-covered of his face like a bowl cut. He is dressed in ragged work clothes from the potion making workshop. Nfirea is described as a nice, calm and timid person. He also works hard at making potions with his grandmother everyday.
Nfirea was originally a girl named Fay in the web novel, but his gender and name changed when the series was published into a light novel.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>176248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76773" type="appears in" update="2018-03-23">
<rating votes="43">5.79</rating>
<name>Hamusuke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hamusuke, also known as the Virtuous King of the Forest, is a monster capable of using magic, possessing incredible power. It lives deep in the forest, so there are few eyewitness reports, but its existence has been known for quite a long while. Some even say it is a several hundred years old, four-legged, silverish white beast with a snake-like tail. It is a giant hamster and http://anidb.net/ch76797 [Momon]`s pet.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>178716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76778" type="appears in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="15">5.58</rating>
<name>Britta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43275" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76780" type="appears in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="6">2.41</rating>
<name>Lizzy Bareare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176202.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76782" type="appears in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="3">4.65</rating>
<name>Uketsukejou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36620" picture="134995.jpg">Ayase Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76788" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="48">6.31</rating>
<name>Yuri Alpha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri Alpha is the vice captain of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a http://anidb.net/t804 [dullahan], and like http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas], she doesn`t like killing humans without reason. The other Pleiades look up to her and her behavior is strict like a teacher.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76791" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Sonchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76792" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="6">4.40</rating>
<name>Fukuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40343" picture="223254.jpg">Kameyama Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76797" type="appears in" update="2018-01-30">
<rating votes="123">6.35</rating>
<name>Momon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momon is http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz Ooal Gown]`s alter ego as an Adamantite-ranked Adventurer.
Ainz created this persona for the purpose of gaining fame in the Kingdom of Re-Estize and intelligence about possible high level adversaries in the area. He stylized himself as the quiet and enigmatic dark warrior. The iconic raven black armor and red cape has earned his adventurer team the unofficial name of Darkness.</description>
<picture>176222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76799" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="109">3.87</rating>
<name>Solution Epsilon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Solution Epsilon is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a slime and one of the most dangerous Pleiades to humans, since she enjoys devouring humans alive. An assassin and poisoner who can decide to protect or dissolve things she absorbs, she can also control the speed of her digestion. Solution gets along with http://anidb.net/ch72780 [Shalltear] because of their similar tastes.</description>
<picture>217386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76801" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-16">
<rating votes="106">3.59</rating>
<name>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades] and an insect-summoner who likes preying on humans.
Her face is actually a bug shell that hides her true face, while she disguises her voice with that of a cute girl by using a leech that can mimic a human`s voice. Her original voice, which she dislikes using is harsh and grating, similar to that of http://anidb.net/ch72779 [Cocytus]. She harbors a big grudge against an adventurer named http://anidb.net/ch93725 [Evileye] who used anti-bug magic to destroy her cute voice in battle.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76802" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="53">6.30</rating>
<name>CZ2128 Delta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>CZ2128 Delta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s an automaton whose weapons look rather futuristic compared to the setting. Her personality is silent and emotionless, but she dislikes cannibalism and likes cute things. Her neutral personality also makes her safer to humans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76803" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="125">5.04</rating>
<name>Lupusregina Beta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lupusregina Beta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a werewolf with a very bright and outgoing personality and a druid capable of using healing magic, and often carries a massive staff to fight. While she appears to be sociable and friendly toward humans, it is only a mask to conceal her brutal and cunning personality.
Lupusregina is later assigned by http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz] to protect the inhabitants of Carne Village after he tames http://anidb.net/ch76773 [Hamsuke] (as her presence was the only thing keeping monsters away from there). However, when she fails to notify him about a threat to the village, believing it to be an unnecessary action, Ainz flies into a rage, terrifying all those around.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77873" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="74">7.88</rating>
<name>Brain Unglaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77877" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="14">6.73</rating>
<name>Pandora`s Actor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pandora`s Actor is the area Guardian in charge of the Treasury and finances of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick], who was created by http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Momonga] himself. He`s a high level Doppelgänger whose face is a simple egghead with three holes dressed in a Neo-Nazi-esque uniform but can transform himself into others, even copying their abilities and powers.
In Momonga`s original design, he`s the combination of everything that he thought was cool, with exaggerated gestures and body language but now that he is actually alive, he embarrasses Momonga. Despite his appearance and personality, he is on the same level as the Floor Guardians and is considered as intelligent as http://anidb.net/ch72778 [Albedo] and http://anidb.net/ch72782 [Demiurge]. He is granted permission to secretly call Ainz his father—secretly he does not want rumors of favoritism to spread.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89828" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="7">8.19</rating>
<name>Pleiades</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Pleiades are a team of special maids led by http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas Tian], who were originally designed to protect and serve in the Throne room of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. Despite each member, with the exception of Sebas, being weak by Nazarick`s standards, their strength is equivalent to a legendary monster in the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>203682.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92890" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="39">6.25</rating>
<name>Climb</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Climb is the personal bodyguard of princess http://anidb.net/ch92895 [Renner]. She saved him when he was just a street urchin about to die from sickness. As such, he views his services to her as a fulfilling of that debt he owes and is even willing to give up his life for her. However, he remains unaware of Renner`s true nature.
He is rather disliked due to him having such a position despite not even being a commoner, but an urchin. Despite this position, he holds no talent in fighting, making up for it with sheer effort. He eventually meets http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas] and, after convincing him to teach him some of his skills, they become friends, though he remains unaware of his loyalty towards http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>222179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92892" type="appears in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="18">6.94</rating>
<name>Zaryusu Shasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zaryusu Shasha is a lizardman of the Green Claw tribe and younger brother of http://anidb.net/ch92893 [Shasuryu Shasha], the Chief of the Green Claw tribe. He is the one, who managed to unify all lizardman tribes to fight against http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz], who declared a slaughter upon them.
Zaryusu is a Traveler, a member of the tribe who leaves the social hierarchy and is untethered from its traditions and obligations. It is an uncoveted position that is both shunned and respected at the same time.
Zaryusu is a renaissance man due to his circumstances. He single handledly bring his tribe`s level of technology from purely hunting/gathering to near sustainable agriculture. He`s a powerful warrior and his fame is widespread for defeating and succeeding the previous owner of Frost Pain (a legendary sword made of pure ice.) He`s a experienced adventurer and knows of many monsters and mystic arts from his time as a traveler. He`s keenly aware of politics, economy, and population geography. As the crisis of war with the Tomb of Nazarick is inevitable, he is the first one to act and come up with a solution for continuing the survival of his race.
Source: Wikipedia, Novel</description>
<picture>211796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92894" type="appears in" update="2018-01-16">
<rating votes="4">6.67</rating>
<name>Zenberu Gugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zenberu Gugu is the Chieftain of the Dragon Tusk tribe.</description>
<picture>212009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92895" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="30">5.57</rating>
<name>Renner Theiere Chardelon Ryle Vaiself</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Renner Theiere Chardelon Ryle Vaiself is the Third Princess of the Kingdom. She is publicly known as the Golden Princess due to her great beauty, benevolence and kindness as well as being a reformer who brought positive changes to the Kingdom. However, in reality she has a psychopathic personality and does not care about the feelings of others. The only exception to this is http://anidb.net/ch92890 [Climb] towards who she harbours a demanded love, viewing him as her "puppy". She merely maintains this facade in order to maintain her good reputation.
Her love towards Climb emerged from that fact that her mental capacities were overdeveloped, causing no one to truly understood her until she saved him and he began to hold onto her every word. Initially, she merely influenced events behind the scenes to increase Climb`s reputation.</description>
<picture>222178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93153" type="appears in" update="2018-07-10">
<rating votes="4">3.71</rating>
<name>Eclair Ecleir Eicler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eclair Ecleir Eicler is the assistant butler.</description>
<picture>217371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93157" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Boullope-kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marquis Boullope was the leader of the Nobility Faction and one of the six leaders of the Six Great Nobles of http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>224511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93158" type="appears in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<name>Ramposa III</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93729" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="55">8.03</rating>
<name>Tuare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tuare is a former sex slave from a brothel in the capital of Re-Estize. In the course of her job, she was thoroughly broken physically and mentally, to the point she was slated for "disposal". At the time she was being disposed of, http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas] chose to rescue her and take her in.</description>
<picture>217367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93892" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="5">3.55</rating>
<name>Elias Brandt Dale Raeven</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elias Brandt Dale Raeven is the leader of the Royalty Faction and the most powerful noble among the Six Great Nobles of the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45579" picture="211758.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93894" type="appears in" update="2018-02-20">
<rating votes="7">4.32</rating>
<name>Zanac Valleon Igana Ryle Vaiself</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17167" picture="170235.jpg">Fujiyoshi Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94887" type="appears in" update="2018-05-10">
<rating votes="4">6.85</rating>
<name>Lockmeier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="92099.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95428" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="4">6.85</rating>
<name>Nazarick Chika Dai Funbo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Great Tomb of Nazarick is the guild headquarters of http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz Ooal Gown], widely renowned for being an unconquerable dungeon throughout DMMO-RPG named Yggdrasil.
Prior to Ainz Ooal Gown conquering this dungeon, the Great Tomb of Nazarick was originally set to have only six floors. After he conquered it, the dungeon was completely reconstructed and was stretched to over ten floors. For travel between floors, there are specific points on each floor, where gates open to allow magical transit. Each floor has its own guardians as well as numerous monsters under their command.
At the start of the series, the Great Tomb of Nazarick was transported to another world along with Ainz and its custom NPCs, who also came to life as a result of this. After finding himself in an unknown world, Ainz began to strengthen the tomb and collect information to protect it from any threats.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>217377.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95431" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="3">5.08</rating>
<name>Re-Estize Oukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Re-Estize Kingdom, commonly referred to as The Kingdom, is a human nation located to the north-west of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. Throughout the nation`s history, it has been plagued by corrupt and inept nobles who view commoners as mere pawns in their power plays. In recent years, they have even started to attempt to usurp the king`s authority and take control of the Kingdom. To make matters worse, the Baharuth Empire annually declares war on the Kingdom and criminal organizations are undermining the nation from within.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</character>
<character id="95432" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="3">2.31</rating>
<name>Baharuth Teikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Baharuth Empire, commonly referred to as The Empire, is a human nation located to the east of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. It was once a feudal state, like the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom], until the current Emperor established an absolute monarchy by purging many of the nobles. Under his rule, the Empire continues to gain more and more prosperity. The Empire also annually wares war with the Re-Estize Kingdom. However, these invasions are merely meant to slowly weaken the Kingdom while the Empire waits for the opportunity to conquer it with minimal losses.
The Empire became the first nation to make official contact with Nazarick. Fearing the power of its inhabitants, the Emperor chose to accept it as an independent nation while attempting to rally other human nations against it. However, this never came to be, as everyone became terrified of Nazarick`s military might. Afterwards, the Emperor submitted to Nazarick, causing the Empire to become its first vassal state.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</character>
<character id="95433" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="12">4.66</rating>
<name>Jircniv Rune Farlord El Nix</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jircniv Rune Farlord El Nix is the current Emperor of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Empire]. He holds the nickname Bloody Emperor, for the numerous nobles he killed after his ascension to the throne. He is a calm and pragmatic person who is willing to purge anyone who gets in his way and replace them with whomever he sees as more fitting, be it a noble or a commoner.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>223200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95434" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="8">5.39</rating>
<name>Fluder Paradyne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fluder Paradyne is the imperial court wizard of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Empire]. He is the strongest magic caster in existence, being able to use up to tier 6 magic, the highest rank attainable by humans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>223201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95437" type="appears in" update="2018-10-07">
<rating votes="4">6.67</rating>
<name>Death Knight</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Death Knight is a skeleton warrior that http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz] summoned when he came to help the http://anidb.net/ch95439 [Carne Village], which was under attack by the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Empire]`s knights led by http://anidb.net/ch76486 [Belius].</description>
<picture>217402.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95439" type="appears in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>Carne-mura</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Carne Village is a small village in the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom]. It is located at the frontier near the border with the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire], making it very close to the Great Forest of Tob where various demi-humans, including http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick], reside.
http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz] saved the village when it was attacked by soldiers of the http://anidb.net/ch95438 [Slane Theocracy] and the inhabitants have remained loyal to him ever since. They are so loyal, in fact, that they sided with Ainz when Nazarick and the Kingdom went to war.
The village later becomes part of the Sorcerer Kingdom after Nazarick was victorious in the war. The village has also started to take in demi-human inhabitants, starting with goblins summoned using an item given to the villagers by Ainz, then ogres from the Great Forest of Tob and most recently dwarfs who formed business relations with the Sorcerer Kingdom.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>220778.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96644" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Eight-Edge Assassin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>220793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43270" picture="173943.jpg">Maki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96645" type="appears in" update="2018-07-13">
<rating votes="5">6.05</rating>
<name>Cixous</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96646" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="2">3.02</rating>
<name>Foire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54819" picture="220172.jpg">Okasaki Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96647" type="appears in" update="2018-07-13">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Pulcinella</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38804" picture="232223.jpg">Nishimura Taisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96648" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="3">4.69</rating>
<name>Lumiere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96800" type="appears in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Agu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54272" picture="223458.jpg">Kowaka Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96801" type="appears in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Unlai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96802" type="appears in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="1">9.22</rating>
<name>Kaijali</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43270" picture="173943.jpg">Maki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96803" type="appears in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Kyumei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96804" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Kuunel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96805" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Cona</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96806" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Gokou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="92099.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96807" type="appears in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Jugem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96808" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Dyno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54272" picture="223458.jpg">Kowaka Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96877" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Shuringan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96878" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Suigyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96879" type="appears in" update="2018-07-25">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Nosuli</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97023" type="appears in" update="2018-07-31">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Gu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>221118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97024" type="appears in" update="2018-07-31">
<name>Ryraryus Spenia Ai Indarun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>221117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11009" picture="39517.jpg">Miyazawa Tadashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97183" type="appears in" update="2018-08-14">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Gurindai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="92099.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97184" type="appears in" update="2018-08-14">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Chousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97421" type="appears in" update="2018-08-15">
<rating votes="31">8.57</rating>
<name>Arche Eeb Rile Furt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arche Eeb Rile Furt was a worker and magic caster of http://anidb.net/ch97463 [Foresight] who volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb]. She was a former noble and student of the Imperial Magic Academy.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97422" type="appears in" update="2018-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Barbro Andrean Ield Ryle Vaiself</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97423" type="appears in" update="2018-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Arche Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30755" picture="189414.jpg">Seki Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97424" type="appears in" update="2018-08-15">
<rating votes="4">5.70</rating>
<name>Imina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Imina is a half-elf worker and member of http://anidb.net/ch97463 [Foresight]. She and her companions volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97425" type="appears in" update="2018-08-15">
<rating votes="3">6.80</rating>
<name>Hekkeran Termite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hekkeran Termite is the leader of http://anidb.net/ch97463 [Foresight] and also a worker. He and his worker group volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97426" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="2">7.69</rating>
<name>Roberdyck Goltron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roberdyck Goltron is a worker and the priest of http://anidb.net/ch97463 [Foresight]. He and his companions volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97427" type="appears in" update="2018-08-14">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Ureirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51392" picture="206521.jpg">Amano Kokoa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97428" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Erya Uzruth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Erya Uzruth was a worker and the leader of http://anidb.net/ch97860 [Tenmu]. He and his slaves volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97429" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Gringham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97430" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Parpatra Ogrion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97431" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Nimble Arc Dale Anoch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nimble Arc Dale Anoch is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch97462 [Four Imperial Knights] of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire].
The second son of a Baron, with an elder brother, an elder sister, and a younger sister. While he is able to get along well with his family members, Nimble caught http://anidb.net/ch95433 [Jircniv]`s attention at a young age and his older brother worked to get him into Jircniv`s service. Currently, Nimble has earned the title of Count through his personal achievements. He worries about whether or not to marry off his little sister. Both his older and younger sisters are worried about him being single.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38674" picture="215795.jpg">Kasama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97432" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Baziwood Peshmel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baziwood Peshmel is the acting leader of the http://anidb.net/ch97462 [Four Imperial Knights] of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5887" picture="203017.jpg">Nagano Yoshikazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97433" type="appears in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="2">3.02</rating>
<name>Leinas Rockbruise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leinas Rockbruise is the only female member of the http://anidb.net/ch97462 [Four Imperial Knights] of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire].
Leinas prioritizes her own life above all else, it is said that she is the least loyal among the Four Imperial Knights. She works for http://anidb.net/ch95433 [Jircniv] only because it is most profitable for her to do so, and will immediately abandon her position if someone else can provide her with what she wants.
Due to her disfigured face, she is shown to be envious of other beautiful women. This was shown when she clicked her tongue whenever the men gave a compliment for the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades] beauty which was enticing them.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97434" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Loune Vermillion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Loune Vermillion is a scribe and the secretary of Emperor http://anidb.net/ch95433 [Jircniv Rune Farlord El Nix].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97435" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Nazami Enec</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nazami Enec was a member of the http://anidb.net/ch97462 [Four Imperial Knights] of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire]. Like the other Four Imperial Knights he was selected by http://anidb.net/ch95433 [Jircniv] to be a member due to his skills rather than his background.
When http://anidb.net/ch72784 [Mare] and http://anidb.net/ch72777 [Aura] visited the Imperial Palace to warn Jircniv, Nazami came out to confront the trespassers. Jircniv ordered http://anidb.net/ch95434 [Fluder] to tell Nazami to withdraw but Mare cracked the earth before he can be told to do so. Nazami was swallowed by the resulting earthquake along with several Royal Guards and subsequently killed by Mare`s spell.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222339.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="97462" type="appears in" update="2018-08-15">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Teikoku Yonkishi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Four Imperial Knights are the strongest elite military unit of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire]. They serve as the personal guard of the Emperor, http://anidb.net/ch95433 [Jircniv Rune Farlord El Nix].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
</character>
<character id="97463" type="appears in" update="2018-08-15">
<rating votes="2">1.23</rating>
<name>Foresight</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Foresight was one of the four groups of workers who volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb].
Foresight had existed for at least two years, when http://anidb.net/ch97421 [Arche] ask to join them. The team had the fame of being an abnormality among the worker teams of Arwintar, with any team member being obsessed with money or battle lust. That being the reason of why Arche wanted became part of the team.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>222397.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="97614" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Neuronist Painkill</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97615" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="3">1.41</rating>
<name>Kyoufukou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97616" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Heavy Masher Magic Caster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97617" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Heavy Masher Senshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97618" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Heavy Masher Touzoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="92099.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97619" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Heavy Masher Shinkan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97673" type="appears in" update="2018-08-28">
<rating votes="2">6.57</rating>
<name>Kuuderika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42138" picture="184598.jpg">Kino Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97860" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Tenmu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Tenmu was one of the four worker groups, led by http://anidb.net/ch97428 [Erya Uzruth], who volunteered to explore and investigate the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [mysterious tomb]. It consisted of four members, though it is better to think of it as Erya`s one man team as the other three were elven slaves from http://anidb.net/ch95438 [Slane Theocracy].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
</character>
<character id="97861" type="appears in" update="2018-09-05">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Demiurge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97941" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Urovana-henkyouwaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Margrave Urovana is one of the six leaders of the Six Great Nobles of the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33065" picture="90146.jpg">Kikuchi Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97942" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Cheneko-danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baron Cheneko is a baron from an unknown domain in the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2135" picture="66343.jpg">Nakakuni Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97943" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Natel Inyem Dale Carvain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natel Inyem Dale Carvain is the General of the Second Legion of the Imperial Army.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47441" picture="223819.jpg">Tajima Akihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97944" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Blumrush-kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marquis Blumrush is one of the six leaders of the Six Great Nobles of http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom]. However, he is secretly betraying the Kingdom by leaking information to the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Baharuth Empire] for monetary gain.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32890" picture="89265.jpg">Nogawa Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97945" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Pespea-kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marquis Pespea is one of the six leaders of the Six Great Nobles of the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom] and he is the son-in-law of http://anidb.net/ch93158 [King Ramposa III].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97946" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Lytton-haku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Count Lytton is one of the six leaders of the Six Great Nobles of http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97947" type="appears in" update="2018-09-11">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Lee-tan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34976" picture="188448.jpg">Fujita Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97948" type="appears in" update="2018-09-11">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43468" picture="186260.jpg">Fujita Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98045" type="appears in" update="2018-09-18">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Goblin Gunshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98046" type="appears in" update="2018-09-18">
<rating votes="2">4.71</rating>
<name>Goblin Konoe Tai Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44361" picture="226057.jpg">Kiuchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98047" type="appears in" update="2018-09-18">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Goblin Sei Kishi Tai Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98048" type="appears in" update="2018-09-18">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Goblin Kijuu Heidan Danchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98049" type="appears in" update="2018-09-18">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Goblin Ansatsu Tai Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98171" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Boris Axelson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98172" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Goran Dixgard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98173" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Lundqvist</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98174" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Hishokan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34376" picture="151699.jpg">Egoshi Akinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98352" type="appears in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36620" picture="134995.jpg">Ayase Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="202086" update="2018-08-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東の巨人, 西の魔蛇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Giant of the East, Demon Snake of the West</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le géant de l`est, le serpent de l`ouest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higashi no Kyojin, Nishi no Ma Ja</title>
<summary>Ains decides to go and see the Giant of the East and Demon Snake of the West himself. If they are similar to Hamusuke, they may have some worth as experimental subjects. They may also be useful in testing Lupisregina`s capabilities with the village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775055</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202087" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンリの激動かつ慌ただしい日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enri`s Upheaval and Hectic Days</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vie trépidante d`Enri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enri no Gekidou Katsu Awatadashii Hibi</title>
<summary>Enri meets Agu, who tells everyone that the Giant of the East and Demon Snake of the West are gathering forces to fight the master of the Monument of Ruin. Enri and the others take action, but little does she know how crazy the day will become...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775054</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202088" update="2018-07-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カルネ村再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Carne Village Once More</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour au village de Carné</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Carne Mura Futatabi</title>
<summary>As Nazarick decides on their next steps, the village of Carne focuses on rebuilding their homes. Enri and her goblin troop are busy protecting the villagers, training the vigilante troop, and manning the fields. All the while, unrest builds in the forest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775053</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202089" update="2018-07-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">支配者の憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Ruler`s Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mélancolie du souverain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shihaisha no Yuuutsu</title>
<summary>With the events of Re-Estize Kingdom and the Lizard Men behind them, the loyal servants of Nazarick return to their daily routines. Ains, however, is worried about the work/life balance of his NPCs. They work day in and day out without rest...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775052</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202679" update="2018-08-07">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の4「守護者筆頭, 略して○」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 4 "The Guardian Overseer, in Short"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 4 "Shugosha Hittou, Ryakushite *"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202680" update="2018-07-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の3「遠離で微妙かつ悩ましい状況」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 3 "His Distant and Worrying Delicate Status"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 3 "Enri de Bimyou Katsu Nayamashii Joukyou"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202681" update="2018-07-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の2「シャルティア再び」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 2 "Shalltear Once More"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 2 "Shalltear Futatabi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202682" update="2018-07-11">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の1「支配者の新たな憂鬱」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 1 "A Ruler`s New Melancholy"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 1 "Shihaisha no Arata na Yuuutsu"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202683" update="2018-07-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202684" update="2018-07-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203320" update="2018-08-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="24">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一握りの希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Handful of Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un fragile espoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitonigiri no Kibou</title>
<summary>The worker group Foresight is teleported to the fighting arena in the sixth floor to challenge the great Ains Ooal Gown. Ains tries to restrain his smoldering fury as he disposes the last of the filthy thieves that dare trample into his treasured Nazarick.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775059</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203321" update="2018-08-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蜘蛛に絡められる蝶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Butterfly Entangled in a Spider`s Web</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les papillons pris dans la toile de l`araignée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumo ni Karamerareru Chou</title>
<summary>The foolish workers that have entered the Tomb of Nazarick greatly anger Ains Ooal Gown. Albedo and the others have already finished preparations for their welcome and Lord Ains watches on, determined that not a single one leaves his tomb alive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775058</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203322" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死出への誘い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation to Death</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Invitation à la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shide e no Izanai</title>
<summary>The Tomb of Nazarick continues their plan for world domination and Ains visits the Baharuth Empire as Momon of Darkness. Meanwhile, Count Femel hires a large number of Workers to explore a certain tomb recently discovered in Re-Estize Kingdom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775057</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203323" update="2018-08-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の指導者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Leaders</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux Leaders</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Shidousha</title>
<summary>The "Giant of the East" has come to attack Carne Village, but the villagers are willing to put their lives on the line to protect their home and families. While the goblin troop defends the front gates, Enri and Nphirea defends the village from behind.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775056</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203812" update="2018-08-07">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の5「二人の先駆者のひとり」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 5 "One of the Two Pioneers"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 5 "Futari no Senkusha no Hitori"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204285" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の6「解放への誘い」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 6 "Invitation to Release"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 6 "Kaihou e no Sasoi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204434" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="29">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PVP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Player vs Player</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">PvP</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PVP</title>
<summary>Gazef challenges Ains to a duel that is impossible to win and Ains decides to accept. The battle will soon come to an end and the fate of E-Rantel will be decided. Even amongst the bloodshed, Gazef and Ains both hold the other in deep respect.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775064</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204435" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="19">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大虐殺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Massacre</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand massacre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daigyakusatsu</title>
<summary>The war is finally starting. The Empire plans to use this chance to see the depths of the Sorcerer King`s strength and the Kingdom is confident that their have fully prepared themselves for this war. Gazef stands ready. Now, let the despair begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775063</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204436" update="2018-09-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一つの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`autre bataille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouhitotsu no Tatakai</title>
<summary>Carne Village is in a pinch once again. An army led by the first prince of Re-Estize has appeared, demanding to be let in so the villagers can be questioned about Ains Ooal Gown. Enri must make a decision for the village and its people.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775062</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204437" update="2018-09-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦争準備</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preparation for War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Préparatifs de guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensou Junbi</title>
<summary>After receiving a formal declaration of the Alliance between the Empire and Nazarick`s newly-founded Sorcerer Kingdom, along with demands to formally cede the territory surrounding E-Rantel to Sorcerer King Ainz Ooal Gown, the Re-Estize Kingdom begins preparations for war. Having witnessed Gown`s strength first-hand and seeing no chance for victory, Gazef Stronoff pleads with the court to accede to his demands, but is powerless to stop the events set in motion.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775061</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204438" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舌戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">War of Words</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Joutes verbales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zessen</title>
<summary>Ains sends Aura and Mare to the Empire with a message. Come and apologize or watch as your country burn to the ground. With no other option, Emperor Jircniv heads toward Nazarick with the head of a noble in tow. Though, things are not as they seem.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775060</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204455" update="2018-08-21">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の7「流行に絡まっている男の娘」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 7 "Otokonoko Entangled in a Fad"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 7 "Ryoukou ni Karamatte Iru Otokonoko"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204656" update="2018-08-28">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の8「一握りの萌え要素」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 8 "A Handful of Moe Elements"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 8 "Hitonigiri no Moe Youso"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206046" update="2018-09-04">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の9「絶世」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 9 "Matchless"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 9 "Zessei"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206526" update="2018-09-22">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の10「解決準備」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 10 "Preparation for Settlement"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 10 "Kaiketsu Junbi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208194" update="2018-09-22">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の11「もう一つの真実」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 11 "Another Battle"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 11 "Mouhitotsu no Shinjitsu"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208572" update="2018-10-04">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の12「大混乱」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 12 "Mass Chaos"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 12 "Daikonran"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208849" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです3】ぷれ3の13「MVP」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 Ch 13 "MVP"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 3: Ple 3 no 13 "MVP"</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
