<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14025" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-11</startdate>
<enddate>2018-12-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Beelzebub-jou no Oki ni Mesu Mama.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">beelmama</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ベルゼブブ嬢のお気に召すまま.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">As Miss Beelzebub Likes.</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">벨제붑 아가씨의 뜻대로</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">只要贝尔哲布布大小姐喜欢就好。</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="614578">A simple love story with a lot of interesting characters. But they tried to make it sooo cute that it became uncute.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://beelmama.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="35233" type="Animation Work">Liden Films</name>
<name id="13386" type="Character Design">Sumimoto Etsuko</name>
<name id="29506" type="Series Composition">Tomita Yoriko</name>
<name id="54531" type="Original Work">Matoba</name>
<name id="47475" type="Direction">Kazuto Minato</name>
<name id="22500" type="Music">Chiba Naoki</name>
<name id="6585" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoda Masahiko</name>
<name id="13386" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sumimoto Etsuko</name>
<name id="13982" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Daisuke</name>
<name id="12572" type="Music">Wakeshima Kanon</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr54531 [Matoba]`s fantasy romantic comedy manga.
http://anidb.net/ch96080 [Myurin]`s lands his dream job with the http://anidb.net/ch96079 [demon king] he`s always held in awe, but when his tenure begins, it turns out the demon king isn`t quite what he expected...
Source: Yen Press</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="318">4.85</permanent>
<temporary count="320">6.37</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>222034.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20847</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37716</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://beelmama.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>As_Miss_Beelzebub_Likes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ベルゼブブ嬢のお気に召すまま。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5064</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364051</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>beelmama_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="96079" type="main character in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="9">8.42</rating>
<name>Beelzebub</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96080" type="main character in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="2">4.87</rating>
<name>Myurin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54151" picture="225419.jpg">Yasuda Rikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97674" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="2">1.62</rating>
<name>Azazel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97675" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="1">1.08</rating>
<name>Astaroth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97676" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<name>Sargatanas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97677" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="5">4.32</rating>
<name>Belphegor</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97839" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="3">1.72</rating>
<name>Eurynome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97840" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Dantalion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97841" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-21">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Molech</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99762" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Astaroth (Shounen)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99763" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Jiijou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46282" picture="188355.jpg">Makino Amane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99764" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Nisroch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99765" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Camio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99766" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Adramelech</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99767" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Gusion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56858" picture="227735.jpg">Yanagi Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99768" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Otis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44871" picture="182505.jpg">Inoue Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99786" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<name>Buer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99787" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Morrigan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99788" type="appears in" update="2018-12-13">
<name>Myurin no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54091" picture="225341.jpg">Sugiyama Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="207975" update="2018-10-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーイ・ミーツ・モフみガール. / 近侍の心, 閣下知らず.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boy Meets Fluffy Girl. / Her Highness Knows Not Her Assistant`s Heart.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Boy Meets Softness Girl / Son Excellence ne connaît pas le cœur de son assistant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boy Meets Mofumi Girl. / Kinji no Kokoro, Kakka Shirazu.</title>
<summary>The world of hell, Pandemonum, is made up of fallen angels. Mullin is excited to work under Beelzebub, a demon which he has always looked up to… But things don’t exactly go as planned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777958</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207976" update="2018-10-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄貴はメルヘンなお味. / 登場, バイブレーションガール.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother Tastes Like a Fairy Tale. / She`s Here, Vibration Girl.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon modèle a un goût de conte de fées / Vibration girl entre en scène</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aniki wa Marchen na Oaji. / Toujou, Vibration Girl.</title>
<summary>Mullin falls from the stairs and a gallant male demon comes to his rescue. His name is Azazel. Mullin wants to imitate this male demon, but Azazel turns out different than he expected...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777959</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207977" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翼をつけた元天使[エンジェル]. / その近侍, ドSにつき.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Former Angel with Wings. / The Assistant, a Complete Sadist.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’ex-ange qui mettait des ailes / L’assistante, cette sadique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa o Tsuketa Moto Angel. / Sono Kinji, Do S ni Tsuki.</title>
<summary>Beelzebub and Mullin run across someone Beelzebub seems to know. His name is Astaroth, and he`s surrounded by adoring girls. He calls himself Beelzebub`s older brother, and starts going off on how much he loves Beelzebub. However, Astaroth starts to wonder about Mullin, and goes to visit the two while they were working, leaving behind is own work. But then Astaroth`s assistant, Sargatanas, comes to get him, and he seems pretty afraid of her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777960</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207978" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羽ばたけ! 想像の翼. / 閣下, はじめてのお見舞い.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly! Imaginary Wings. / Her Highness Checking in on Someone Sick for the First Time.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Volez, ailes imaginaires ! / Son Excellence se rend au chevet d’un malade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Habatake! Souzou no Tsubasa. / Kakka, Hajimete no Omimai.</title>
<summary>Mullin meets a new girl, Eurynome, in a meeting, but every time their eyes meet, she gives him a look of complete disgust. Mullin’s worried that Eurynome hates him for some reason, but he finds out the real reason. Later, Mullin wins some movie tickets, and ends up promising to go with Beelzebub, but things don’t quite go as planned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777961</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209127" update="2018-10-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209128" update="2018-10-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209464" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょっぴりビター, ビブリオマニア. / 進め, ブラウニーとともに.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bit Bitter, Bibliomania. / Go Forth, with Brownies.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une bibliomanie un peu amère / Faites le premier pas avec des brownies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choppiri Bitter, Bibliomania. / Susume, Brownie to Tomo ni.</title>
<summary>Mullin visits the Pandemonium Library along with Azazel and runs into the sleepy bookworm, Dantalion, as well as the ancient demon, Moloch, who always tends to talk in a loud voice. Later, Belphegor wants to come up with an excuse to talk to Azazel, so she starts making brownies with Beelzebub.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777962</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209465" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">9センチ分の. / 閣下の秘密.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">9 Centimeters. / Her Highness`s Secret.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’équivalent de 9 centimètres / Le secret de Son Excellence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">9 Centi Bun no. / Kakka no Himitsu.</title>
<summary>Beelzebub breaks her heels on her way to the office. Adramelech, Pandemonium’s advisor of all things fashion, vows to fix the heels, and we learn just why Beelzebub insists on wearing high heels in the first place. Later, Beelzebub does an interview with a Pandemonium magazine, and we learn a bit more about her likes and dislikes...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777963</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209466" update="2018-12-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンデモ湯よいとこ一度はおいで. / "もっと知りたい"のに....</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pandemonium Baths Are Great. You Should Visit. / I Want to Learn More...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les bains du Pandémonium / Je veux mieux te connaître</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pandemo Yu Yoi Toko Ichido wa Oide. / "Motto Shiritai" no ni....</title>
<summary>The members of Pandemonium are not getting enough exercise, so they decide to build a gym, but when it comes time for the opening ceremony, Beelzebub and the others find themselves staring at a Japanese-style bath instead. Since the facility already exists, they might as well get in… Later on, Beelzebub learns more about Mullin and the pet he keeps at home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777964</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209467" update="2018-12-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわいいって言いたい. / 海に行こう.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Say "Cute." / Let`s Go to the Beach.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je veux dire que c’est mignon / Allons à la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaiitte Iitai. / Umi ni Ikou.</title>
<summary>Sargatanas loves the characters from Fluffy Whiskers &amp; Friends. The show and a cafe are doing a joint colaboration together, and Sargatanas would love to go. The only problem is that it’s too cute, and she doesn’t think she’d fit in. Later on, Beelzebub and Belphegor make plans to go to the beach, and ask Adrammelech to help them pick out swimsuits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777965</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210255" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたり, ときどきすれ違い. / 夢を見たから.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">They Pass Each Other by Sometimes. / I Had a Dream.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ils se croisent parfois / Parce que j’en ai rêvé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari, Tokidoki Surechigai. / Yume o Mita kara.</title>
<summary>Mullin jokes that he might put in a transfer request and Beelzebub takes it pretty hard. Mullin gets worried that he might have upset her, so he goes to Astaroth for advice. Meanwhile, Belphegor can`t help but run away when she sees Azazel. Belphegor wishes she could tell Azazel how she feels, but just can`t work up the courage, and that`s when she runs into him in the library...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777966</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210256" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">缶コーヒー1本分の距離. / 寒い日, あなたの香り.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Separated by One Can of Coffee. / Your Scent on a Cold Day.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une canette de café de distance / Ton odeur, les jours froids</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kan Coffee Ippon Bun no Kyori. / Samui Hi, Anata no Kaori.</title>
<summary>Astaroth`s always slacking off, not doing his work, and messing around with girls. As always, Sargatanas heads off to find him. After wrangling him in, they stop by a park, and Sargatanas suddenly finds herself having to face her feelings towards Astaroth. Later, a cold front descends upon Pandemonium, but Beelzebub can`t handle the cold very well. Mullin and Beelzebub try various things to keep her warm, but Mullin comes up with one last idea...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777967</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210257" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごっちん・IN・メリーランド.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gocchin in Merryland.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gocchin in Merryland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gocchin in Merryland.</title>
<summary>One day at a tea party, Belphegor accidentally drinks alcohol and falls asleep. Azazel finds her, panics, and goes to look for help. But then a sleepy Belphegor pulls him back...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777968</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210258" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">閣下の心, 近侍知らず. / その気持ちの名前は.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Assistant Knows Not Her Highness`s Heart. / The Name of That Feeling Is...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`assistant ne comprend pas Son Excellence / Ce sentiment s`appelle...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakka no Kokoro, Kinji Shirazu. / Sono Kimochi no Namae wa.</title>
<summary>Part A
The sweater that Beelzebub had gotten from Mullin that she liked so much starts to come undone. Beelzebub is in so much shock that she keeps sighing and trying to avoid eye contact with Mullin. Mullin misunderstands and feels like he made her upset again somehow...
Part B
Beelzebub have a flower viewing party now that spring is here. Beelzebub says that she’s never being to a flower viewing party, so the others go all out for her. Since the day is so chill, Mullin happens to remember when he first became Beelzebub’s attendant...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777969</identifier>
<identifier>as-miss-beelzebub-likes-it</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
