<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14038" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Isekai Cheat Magician</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">異世界チート魔術師[マジシャン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Isekai Cheat Magician</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">异世界超能魔术师</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12603" approval="9" total="13">Death March kara Hajimaru Isekai Kyousoukyoku</anime>
<anime id="13004" approval="9" total="10">Isekai wa Smartphone to Tomo ni.</anime>
<anime id="13624" approval="8" total="16">Arifureta Shokugyou de Sekai Saikyou</anime>
<anime id="13757" approval="7" total="11">Isekai Maou to Shoukan Shoujo no Dorei Majutsu</anime>
<anime id="9332" approval="6" total="12">Mondaiji-tachi ga Isekai kara Kurusou Desu yo?</anime>
<anime id="13896" approval="6" total="7">Hyakuren no Haou to Seiyaku no Valkyria</anime>
<anime id="13477" approval="5" total="7">Kenja no Mago</anime>
<anime id="11261" approval="3" total="11">Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku o!</anime>
<anime id="13439" approval="3" total="7">Shichisei no Subaru</anime>
<anime id="9855" approval="2" total="8">Outbreak Company</anime>
<anime id="14068" approval="2" total="6">Conception</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="618720">This show does attempt to cultivate a proper dynamic for an epic fantasy, but the writing quality overall is simply too juvenile. It relies too heavily on common template elements, and the script is painfully cliche. Though the artwork is typically passable, the script, acting, plot, and direction are all uninspired, making this show just another "average" B-tier isekai. The childhood friend being isekai`d alongside the MC (and actually being independently powerful herself) was a hook that I appreciated, but they didn`t do enough with it. I suppose there`s enough here to be entertaining for fans of the genre who aren`t particularly critical about "quality", but there`s little here for anyone else.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="55065">A grand mixing-pot of cliche elements surrounding an "isekai" main plot, that failed to turn them into charm points.

While the character design/anime production is mostly ok (except for posing and scene composition), characters are shallow, and plot and lines are so unnaturally incoherent. Most of the time is spent on uninspired scenes/lines mechanically building up towards some totally predictable supposed climax scene which disappoints, unless you are looking to be amused by the awkwardness.

I would **recommend** for anybody who has free-time (nothing else to watch) to give the first couple of episodes a try. If you repeatedly face-palm, yet cannot suppress the urge to peep through your finger gaps just to see how the next totally predictable scene unfolds in the most unnatural manner to deliver another jab to your brain, you may actually find it interesting enough to manage finish watching the series, like I did.

P.S. I am not M. Seriously.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://isekai-cheat-magician.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="54624" type="Original Work">Uchida Takeru</name>
<name id="19117" type="Animation Work">Encourage Films</name>
<name id="14960" type="Character Design">Maruyama Shuuji</name>
<name id="27350" type="Series Composition">Ikami Takayo</name>
<name id="11638" type="Direction">Chikushi Daisuke</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr54624 [Uchida Takeru] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr54625 [Nardack].
http://anidb.net/ch101272 [Nishimura Taichi] is a typical, average high schooler, and http://anidb.net/ch101271 [Azuma Rin] is a beautiful woman with the build of a model and excellent reflexes. The two live a normal high school life until one day they`re suddenly enveloped in a mysterious magic circle and transported to an unknown land. That world is full of terrifying monsters, beastmen, dwarves, elves, and many other races right out of fantasy. In order to survive in this new world Taichi and Rin decide to become adventurers, but when they take the aptitude test they discover they both possess cheat level magic...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="608">1.99</permanent>
<temporary count="624">4.87</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>234217.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21891</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37744</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://isekai-cheat-magician.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Isekai_Cheat_Magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>異世界チート魔術師</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5351</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364085</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isekai_cheat_tv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3166" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-18">
<name>political unrest</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3374" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>civil war</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6068" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-20">
<name>human sacrifice</name>
<description>Human sacrifice is the act of killing one or more human beings as part of a ritual. Throughout the majority of human history, primitive societies have engaged in human sacrifice, generally as a religious act, such as an offering to please or appease deities, spirits, or the deceased. Other uses that have been seen include magic rituals, usually related to black magic or the summoning of demons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101271" type="main character in" update="2019-08-28">
<rating votes="17">8.52</rating>
<name>Azuma Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azuma Rin, is capable of manipulating the four great magical elements of fire, wind, earth and water making her an extremely rare Quad Magician. She excels in utilizing the knowledge learned in school to enhance her magic as well as casting mixed spells using multiple elements. She teams up with http://anidb.net/ch101272 [Taichi] and becomes an adventurer, though she is often embarrassed by his speech and conduct.</description>
<picture>234243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101272" type="main character in" update="2019-08-28">
<rating votes="7">1.84</rating>
<name>Nishimura Taichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishimura Taichi is a unique magician with no aptitude for any of the magical elements. However, his magical strength and capacity is off the scale, which he utilizes to enhance his physical abilities in battle. He happens to be unperceptive toward the affections of others, as well as believing that http://anidb.net/ch101271 [Rin], who came with him, only views him as a friend.</description>
<picture>234242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40642" picture="62085.png">Amasaki Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103194" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-28">
<rating votes="4">4.23</rating>
<name>Aerial</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aerial, a wind spirit, and an existence of higher standing than both human and dragon. Her existence is shrouded in mystery, however, no ordinary human could possibly hope to hear her voice, let alone see her. Usually she appears in the shape of a small spirit.</description>
<picture>234241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103195" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="6">8.31</rating>
<name>Muller</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Muller, in spite of being an excellent magician capable of manipulating both fire and earth magical element, she is also very proficient with the sword. These abilities allows her to solo A-rank adventurer quests. She is an elf with blond hair and an attractive face and figure, an appearance which caused the other adventurers to give her the nickname of "Golden Fencer".</description>
<picture>234244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38297" picture="150939.jpg">Tanaka Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103196" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="9">8.41</rating>
<name>Lemia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Remia, nicknamed the "Mage of Falling Leaves", is an elite magician with such magical prowess that her name has echoed across the world. It is not an overstatement to consider her to be one of the best magicians in the entire world. At the present she makes her base in the woods, on the outskirts of the frontier town Azpire, where she can conduct her hobby of researching magic and the culinary arts while also instructing Muller.</description>
<picture>234240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104315" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-28">
<rating votes="1">1.03</rating>
<name>Kasim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A farmer running a plantation on the outskirts of Azpire. In order to repel bandits who are causing damage to his plantation, he puts up a work request at the Adventurers Guild, however...</description>
<picture>236121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104316" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-28">
<rating votes="3">1.31</rating>
<name>Grami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grami, an elusive magician. She possesses an abnormal love for battle, and prefers a life and death battle with her opponent over assassination.</description>
<picture>236120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104337" type="appears in" update="2019-07-10">
<name>Gerard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22" picture="231891.jpg">Uoken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104338" type="appears in" update="2019-07-10">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Raquelta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24946" picture="200733.jpg">Tamaru Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104339" type="appears in" update="2019-07-10">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Mejilla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43471" picture="200335.jpg">Nanase Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104340" type="appears in" update="2019-07-10">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Barada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="58264" picture="236247.jpg">Kino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104341" type="appears in" update="2019-07-24">
<name>Marie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47240" picture="223452.jpg">Kamakura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104620" type="appears in" update="2019-07-24">
<name>Almeda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50497" picture="223462.jpg">Sugimura Chikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104621" type="appears in" update="2019-07-24">
<name>McGill</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236612.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104622" type="appears in" update="2019-07-24">
<name>Leithe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236613.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104623" type="appears in" update="2019-08-07">
<name>Assassin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46938" picture="223461.jpg">Mano Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104940" type="appears in" update="2019-08-22">
<rating votes="7">5.55</rating>
<name>Anastasia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46938" picture="223461.jpg">Mano Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105058" type="appears in" update="2019-08-22">
<rating votes="1">1.26</rating>
<name>Shiroi Fuku no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105059" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<name>Milu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42138" picture="184598.jpg">Kino Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105060" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<name>Melo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42138" picture="184598.jpg">Kino Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105157" type="appears in" update="2019-08-22">
<name>Twin Head Dragon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105159" type="appears in" update="2019-08-22">
<name>Celt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="59146" picture="240761.jpg">Iwata Kyouyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105160" type="appears in" update="2019-08-22">
<name>Adelina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="59147" picture="240762.jpg">Makita Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105213" type="appears in" update="2019-09-09">
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Princess Charlotte Elistain, [spoiler="a magician capable of manipulating time and space."]the person responsible for summoning Nishimura Taichi and Azuma Rin into this world.[/spoiler]</description>
<picture>238141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38248" picture="140190.jpg">Suegara Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105214" type="appears in" update="2019-09-09">
<name>Gilmar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105215" type="appears in" update="2019-09-09">
<rating votes="1">2.09</rating>
<name>Alsena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105216" type="appears in" update="2019-09-05">
<name>Bella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bella Lafuma, Head Royal Magician.</description>
<picture>238023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54919" picture="223457.jpg">Aizawa Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105217" type="appears in" update="2019-09-09">
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<name>Sumella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>General Sumella, supreme commander of the Royal Army.</description>
<picture>238144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105218" type="appears in" update="2019-09-09">
<name>Dorteisheim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105219" type="appears in" update="2019-08-28">
<name>Inimeeks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105274" type="appears in" update="2019-09-05">
<name>Nilgan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43270" picture="173943.jpg">Maki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105275" type="appears in" update="2019-09-05">
<name>Marchese</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38328" picture="140889.jpg">Watanabe Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105328" type="appears in" update="2019-09-11">
<rating votes="1">1.26</rating>
<name>Kage no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105474" type="appears in" update="2019-09-18">
<name>Mistfolos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105475" type="appears in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="1">2.09</rating>
<name>Susora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45121" picture="225365.jpg">Fujiwara Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218033" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界からの「迷い人」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost Ones from Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Égarés d`un autre monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai kara no "Mayoi Hito"</title>
<summary>Nishimura Taichi and Azuma Rin were normal high school students before the light of a magic circle enveloped them after they dodged a speeding bicycle on the way to school. When the two next awake they find an unfamiliar land with forests and open fields of grass. While they`re both confused by the sudden turn of events, things take another turn for the worse as a huge horse with a sharp horn on its head attacks them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787185</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218034" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔術修行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic Training</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entraînement magique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majutsu Shugyou</title>
<summary>The Golden Swordsman Myura leads Taichi and Rin to the mage, Lemiya. After a reevaluation they discover that both of them possess astounding magic power, and so they begin to train under Lemiya`s tutelage. During their training Rin begins to get a feel for how to cast magic. On the other hand, Taichi faces difficulty using his magic power, but just as he`s about to give up on mastering his task in one day he hears a mysterious voice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787186</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218035" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">駆け出し冒険者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginner Adventurers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les débuts des aventuriers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakedashi Boukensha</title>
<summary>After safely qualifying to become adventurers Taichi and Rin begin working out of the inn, Mithril, completing the easiest E-Rank quests. Then one day the guild makes its decision to directly entrust them with a difficult quest, holding high hopes for their abilities. The quest is one that D-Rank adventurers have already failed twice - the investigation of a smuggling operation in the slums.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787187</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218036" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真紅の契約</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crimson Pact</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pacte écarlate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkou no Keiyaku</title>
<summary>Lately there has been a string of thefts targeting Azpire`s local specialty - melila fruit. As a result, prices within the city are steadily skyrocketing. Taichi and the others accept a quest to guard the melila orchards, but when the monsters attacking the fields prove to be monsters that don`t live in that region, they begin to suspect that someone else is responsible for setting up the attacks. Shortly thereafter a new threat begins closing in on Rin and Taichi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787188</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218628" update="2019-09-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218629" update="2019-09-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218990" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">策動の匂い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hint of Schemes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`odeur de la machination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakudou no Nioi</title>
<summary>Taichi manages to defeat the Red Element with the power of the wind spirit, Aerial. So when he speaks to Lemia about hearing the spirit`s voice and using her power, she pronounces him a Summoner. While he feels like that power is just another cheat, he heads into the city to find Rin and Muller. Along the way he rescues a woman being harrassed by some men, but that woman seems familiar somehow...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787189</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218991" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アズパイア防衛戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense of Azpire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ligne de défense d’Azpire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Azpire Boueisen</title>
<summary>After defeating the golem beneath Azpire Taichi and Anastasia encounter the young magicians Milo and Melo, who command a large horde of Red Goblins. Meanwhile Rin and Muller alert the guild to an impending attack from an army of several thousand monsters. A dour mood hangs over everyone there, but Rin and Muller resolve to defend the city. Luckily that`s when Lemia arrives, having sensed something wrong within the city...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787190</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218992" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">召喚術師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summoner</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Invocateur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoukan Jutsushi</title>
<summary>After wiping out the Red Goblins beneath the city, Taichi races to the battlefield and gallantly appears in time to rescue Rin. With his aid the adventurers of Azpire continue past their exhaustion to defeat the monsters one after another. While Taichi faces down the Red Ogres with his physical enhancement, Milo and Melo join them in the counterattack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787191</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218993" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王都ウェネーフィクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Royal Capital Wennifix</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Venefix, la capitale royale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Outo Venefix</title>
<summary>After overcoming the monster assault Taichi and the others are visited by a messenger from the Royal Family. Alsena, the emissary acting on behalf of Gilmar, King of Elistain Magic Kingdom, asks for their help. The Royal Capital, Wennifix, is currently divided between those supporting the King who`s put great effort into diplomacy and those supporting his younger brother who opposes him. With tensions so high, a civil war is imminent.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787192</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219589" update="2019-09-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦のはじまり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Commencement of Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le commencement de la guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikusa no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Word reaches the Royal Capital that the King`s younger brother has finally reading his troops for an attack. As the battle draws closer minute by minute, Taichi tries to convince Rin to stay away from the battlefield, yet she displays her strong resolution to fight alongside him. After learning of Rin`s resolve he vows to himself that he will protect her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787193</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219590" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとつの決着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turning Point</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une conciliation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitotsu no Kecchaku</title>
<summary>After driving off the army of the King`s younger brother, King Gilmar rewards Taichi and the others are with weapons from the royal treasury. Taichi, Rin, and Muller head down to the training grounds to test out their new weapons. However, Taichi grows ill along the way and goes downton by himself to buy some medicine. There he encounters Cassim, set on revenge, who forces him to accept a duel...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787194</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219591" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーウォルトの会戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Marwalt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille de Marwalt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marwalt no Kaisen</title>
<summary>The King`s brother, Dortesheim has declared war on Elistain Magic Kingdom, and finally waged a formal battle on the plains of Marwalt. The Kingdom has dispatched its soldiers against them, accompanied by Taichi and the others. Rin, Muller, and Lemia all face their own battles against strong opponents, while Taichi storms the enemy`s main camp and takes action to end the war. Yet during the intense battle, the Kingdom`s Cardinal, Lodra, is meeting with a mysterious person in the cathedral...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787195</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219592" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界チート魔術師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Isekai Cheat Magician</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Isekai Cheat Magician</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai Cheat Majutsushi</title>
<summary>The tragedy of the "Bloody Rhapsody" - the worst battle in the history of the world - is about to befall the world once more. With dark magic turning the soldiers into berserkers who can`t distinguish friend from foe, both armies begin advancing on the royal capital to slaughter it and everything that lies beyond. Faced with countless berserkers, Taichi is forced to make a decision. He finally resolves to use his power that`s too great for one man in order to protect those precious to him, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787196</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-cheat-magician</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221668" update="2019-09-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221669" update="2019-09-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
