<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14098" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>2018-12-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ani ni Tsukeru Kusuri wa Nai! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Please Take My Brother Away S2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Please Take Away My Brother 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">没有给我哥吃的药2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="synonym">Kuai Ba Wo Ge Dai Zou 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">兄に付ける薬はない! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">오빠를 치료할 약은 없다</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">快把我哥带走2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14956" type="Sequel">Ani ni Tsukeru Kusuri wa Nai! 3</anime>
<anime id="12921" type="Prequel">Ani ni Tsukeru Kusuri wa Nai!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://anitsuke.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="35949" type="Animation Work">Imagineer</name>
<name id="23366" type="Animation Work">Fanworks</name>
<name id="31380" type="Direction">Rareko</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="145">6.58</permanent>
<temporary count="146">6.88</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221512.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anitsuke.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ani_ni_Tsukeru_Kusuri_wa_Nai!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>兄に付ける薬はない!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364717</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21306</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>快把我哥帶走</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anitsuke_info</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6493" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manhua</name>
<description>The Chinese equivalent of the Japanese manga, produced in Mainland China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan.
See also http://anidb.net/t2798 [manga] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89123" type="main character in" update="2019-04-14">
<rating votes="8">6.96</rating>
<name>Shi Miao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89124" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="4">5.57</rating>
<name>Shi Fen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="202640" update="2018-07-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪童的挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akudouteki Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202641" update="2018-07-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寄生的兄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseiteki Ani</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202642" update="2018-07-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄的算段</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki Sandan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202643" update="2018-07-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軍事的訓練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gunjiteki Kunren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203288" update="2018-07-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪異的転校生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiiteki Tenkousei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203289" update="2018-07-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃的報復</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougekiteki Houfuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203290" update="2018-07-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼熱的放課後</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakunetsuteki Houkago</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203291" update="2018-07-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">平民的生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heiminteki Seikatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203816" update="2018-08-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204461" update="2018-08-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴族的内偵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizokuteki Naitei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204462" update="2018-08-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴族的休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizokuteki Kyuujitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204463" update="2018-08-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人気者的苦悩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ninkimonoteki Kunou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204464" update="2018-08-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸福的食堂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koufukuteki Shokudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208601" update="2018-09-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃避的睡眠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhiteki Suimin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208602" update="2018-09-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">承認的願望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouninteki Ganbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208603" update="2018-09-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛的予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`aiteki Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208604" update="2018-09-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密的告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsuteki Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209070" update="2018-10-08">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">精神的外傷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishinteki Gaishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209071" update="2018-10-08">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望的馬鹿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubouteki Baka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209205" update="2018-10-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脆弱的友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zeijakuteki Yuujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209206" update="2018-10-15">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甘美的関係</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanbiteki Kankei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210092" update="2018-11-14">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独的家路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodokuteki Ieji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210093" update="2018-11-14">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">打破的行動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dahateki Koudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210094" update="2018-11-14">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時秒的誕生日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiimyoteki Tanjoubi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210095" update="2018-11-14">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">充実的一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juujitsuteki Ichinichi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
