<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14109" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>23</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2019-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaze ga Tsuyoku Fuite Iru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kaze ga Tsuyoku Fuiteiru</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">風が強く吹いている</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Run with the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">바람이 강하게 불고 있다</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">强风吹拂</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8870" approval="1" total="7">Sakamichi no Apollon: Kids on the Slope</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="209879">The writing here is excellent. The series is just great in portraying its well-built characters, in telling its story and making you care for its development - even as there is no character to identify with or to clearly like as in other anime, I became invested in the story and fate of the cast as a whole. Be it as a story on sport, on friendship or on personal development, the series was able to connect these different elements superbly and poignant. While not as flashy or dramatic as other recent shows, for me its definitely a series to keep.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kazetsuyo-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="332" type="Series Composition">Kiyasu Kouhei</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="6186" type="Character Design">Chiba Takahiro</name>
<name id="45253" type="Original Work">Miura Shion</name>
<name id="8586" type="Direction">Nomura Kazuya</name>
<name id="9577" type="Chief Animation Direction">Mukouda Takashi</name>
<name id="5366" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takahashi Hideki</name>
<name id="27786" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuki</name>
<name id="6186" type="Chief Animation Direction">Chiba Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a novel by http://anidb.net/cr45253 [Miura Shion].
The Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race or "Hakone Ekiden," one of the biggest university marathon relay races in Japan. The race is held every year on January 2-3 and goes between Tokyo and Hakone and back, for a total run of of nearly 217.9 km
A friendship between two sidelined athletes helps them return to their beloved sport and build a team for a competitive long-distance relay race.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="445">7.98</permanent>
<temporary count="448">7.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>223142.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21078</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37965</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kazetsuyo-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Run_with_the_Wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>風が強く吹いている</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364464</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21467</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kazetsuyo_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2753" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>track and field</name>
<description>A collection of sports events that involve running, throwing, and jumping.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2827" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>sudden naked guy appearance</name>
<description>A male specimen previously unknown to the viewer and not dressed in any clothes suddenly appears out of nowhere.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3671" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>footage reuse</name>
<description>Footage reuse is the employment of a sequence of frames many times, generally as a side effect of a constrained anime production budget. This can happen by using the same footage once at a time, but many times over the course of the show, or by directly looping it. Types of scenes that tend to get reused include: transformations, such as those typical of superheroes or magical girls, characters that change into powered-up versions of themselves, or robots changing shape; attacks, especially when involving a series of steps that must be followed before the attack can be launched; and any kind of action that involves repeating the same movement.
This tag does not apply if the footage changes significantly between iterations. An example of that is the infamous Endless Eight arc of http://anidb.net/a6367 [the 2009 iteration of Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu]; even as the plot repeated itself, each episode of the arc showed it in different ways.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3734" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-14">
<name>school rivalry</name>
<description>Simple description for a "School vs School in all-out physical-combat" series.
No matter how geographically close or far apart the schools are, students from different schools are enemies by default and are likely to engage in physical fights on sight (except on the occasion that certain schools form pacts of alliance or peace).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="72202" type="appears in" update="2014-12-24">
<rating votes="16">9.74</rating>
<name>Rikiishi Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166412.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95844" type="main character in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="6">6.36</rating>
<name>Kiyose Haiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95845" type="main character in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="4">2.63</rating>
<name>Kurahara Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51377" picture="216960.jpg">Ootsuka Takeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97693" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<name>Musa Kamala</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46757" picture="224841.jpg">Kabumoto Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97694" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<name>Sakaguchi Youhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3696" picture="224842.jpg">Kitazawa Riki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97695" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<name>Jou Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33512" picture="225800.jpg">Enoki Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97696" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<name>Jou Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37466" picture="225911.jpg">Uemura Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97697" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="2">7.11</rating>
<name>Iwakura Yukihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97698" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="1">6.43</rating>
<name>Hirata Akihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224838.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97699" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Sugiyama Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97700" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-02">
<rating votes="3">8.19</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Akane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100998" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-22">
<name>Katsuta Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38677" picture="145133.jpg">Kimura Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100999" type="appears in" update="2019-02-22">
<name>Sakaki Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101000" type="appears in" update="2019-02-22">
<name>Fujioka Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101001" type="appears in" update="2019-02-22">
<name>Tazaki Genichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10832" picture="233750.jpg">Nakamura Koutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101002" type="appears in" update="2019-02-22">
<name>Nira</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230493.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="208215" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">10人目の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 10th Man</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dixième homme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">10 Ninme no Otoko</title>
<summary>Kurahara Kakeru runs through the city streets at night. A single man chases after him on a bicycle. That man`s name is Kiyose Haiji.
When Haiji catches up to Kakeru, he asks him a question: "Hey, do you like running?"
Led by Haiji, Kakeru arrives at the Chikusei-so student dorm. He meets the strange residents living there.
Haiji behaves in a peremptory manner. Kakeru is bewildered by the sudden development.
No one at the dorm is aware of Haiji`s ulterior motive.
That night, the residents hold a welcoming party for Kakeru.
At the party, from Haiji`s mouth comes a grand and reckless plan.
How will Kakeru respond...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777545</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208559" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼が来りて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ogre`s Arrival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La venue du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni ga Kitarite</title>
<summary>"The residents of the Chikusei-so will run in the Hakone Ekiden together." Kakeru responds strongly to Haiji`s rash suggestion.
All the residents are amateurs when it comes to long distance running. Nobody takes Haiji`s words seriously.
The residents attempt to carry on with their college lives, but Haiji`s shadow approaches.
Threatened by Haiji`s mysterious pressure, several tragically fall to Haiji`s hand.
Kakeru tries to leave the Chikusei-so, but he runs into Nico-chan in the city.
Meanwhile, the Chikusei-so`s bath breaks for unknown reasons, and they decide to go to the "hellish" public bath instead...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777546</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208560" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花, 一輪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Single Flower</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une seule fleur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana, Ichirin</title>
<summary>When their hot water contest ends in a tie, Kakeru participates in the dorm`s morning jogs while continuing to rebel against Haiji.
His plan is to make the other residents give up.
The next morning, several of the residents decide to boycott the jogging.
A young girl wearing a school uniform runs up to Kakeru and his cool attitude.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777547</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208561" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えない影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadows That Don`t Fade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ombre persistante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kienai Kage</title>
<summary>"It`s been a while..." Sakaki smirks fearlessly. He and Kakeru are old acquaintances.
Kakeru is unable to hide how shaken he is by their unexpected reunion.
Swirling inside Kakeru was the loneliness he experienced as a high school student due to his talents.
Kakeru runs as though fleeing from shadows, when before him appears "the other Kakeru."
It is the desperate man he used to be before he met Haiji. Kakeru glares resentfully at his past.
Just as he`s about to lose hope in himself, someone with a kind voice reaches out to him.
It`s Prince and his friends...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777548</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208861" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208862" update="2019-01-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209304" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選ばれざる者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ones Not Chosen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les élus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erabarezaru Mono-tachi</title>
<summary>After being challenged by Tokyo Sport University`s Sakaki, Kakeru and the other residents of Chikusei-so have grown closer.
As they celebrate the renewal of their resolve, King comes home wearing a suit for a change.
Meanwhile, Kakeru voices his objections to participating in a track meet so soon.
What point is there in forcing the amateurish residents to face reality?
In response to Kakeru, Haiji asks his own question.
Kakeru`s doubts remain unresolved as Haiji begins holding proper practices.
However, King refuses to participate because he`s busy looking for a job...
Under a cloud of anxiety, their proper training begins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777549</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209305" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裸の王様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Emperor`s New Clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le roi dénudé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hadaka no Ousama</title>
<summary>King rebels against Haiji`s escalating demands.
His job search continues to go poorly, causing him to close himself off to even Shindo, who is concerned for him.
Eventually King begins acting independently. The other residents are also unable to hide their befuddlement at being told they can`t work.
Meanwhile, Kakeru goes to Nico-chan in order to dispel his doubts about Haiji, but he`s unable to find a definitive answer.
While this is happening, Shindo has an idea and suggests it to the other residents, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777550</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209306" update="2018-11-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">頂きに牙を剥け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bear Your Fangs at the Summit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Montre les crocs au sommet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itadaki ni Kiba o Muke</title>
<summary>The residents of the Chikusei-so go to Tokyo Sport University in order to attend their first track meet. While there, Kakeru is reunited with his old teammate Sakaki Kosuke. Sakaki persistently attempts to provoke Kakeru. When Haiji tries to stop them, a man calls out to him. That man is the champion of Hakone and Rikudo University`s ace, Fujioka Kazuma.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777551</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209307" update="2018-11-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険人物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Character</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dangereux personnage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken Jinbutsu</title>
<summary>The residents of the Chikusei-so experience a crushing defeat at the track meet.
When Kakeru sees his teammates complain and praise one another for their powerlessness, he explodes. While trying to calm down Kakeru, Nico-chan reveals his feelings towards running that he`s been hiding. Kakeru advises him to try as hard as possible. The next morning, Kakeru and Nico-chan abandon Haiji`s coaching and begin training alone. Meanwhile, in order to regain the comic reading time that was taken from him by practice, Prince plans to have a certain item delivered to the apartment...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777552</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210119" update="2018-11-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぞろいの選手たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mismatched Runners</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des athlètes inégaux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuzoroi no Senshu-tachi</title>
<summary>Kakeru asks Prince to quit the team depending on his performance at the next track meet.
Though Haiji says Kakeru`s words are ineffective, Prince asks if he`ll be able to achieve an official record. But there`s something else bothering Haiji: there`s one leftover portion of food.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777553</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210120" update="2018-12-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちの速度</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Speed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Notre rythme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi no Sokudo</title>
<summary>Haiji suddenly faints.
The residents realize how Haiji has been supporting them, and Nico-chan encourages Kakeru and Prince to reconcile.
However, the stubborn boys refuse to bridge the gap.
The next day, Shindo suggests that the team pick a temporary captain.
When all the older members refuse, Kakeru agrees to do the job.
Desperate to do something about Prince, Kakeru follows him around while nagging him. Prince`s opposition increases in response.
As the residents are unable to even feed themselves, someone comes to extend a helping hand...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777554</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210121" update="2018-12-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こぼれる雫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overflowing Drops</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des gouttes qui se répandent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koboreru Shizuku</title>
<summary>The twins and Musa achieve official records, and the residents of the Chikusei-so feel there`s hope for them. However, Shindo and Yuki begin to panic as they fail to beat their personal records for close to a month. Haiji tries to reason with them, but words alone aren`t enough to save them. Meanwhile, the heavy rains continue, impeding the progress of the residents.
The other residents grow concerned as Shindo continues to work hard at practice and his studies. Meanwhile, Kakeru and Haiji spot champion Fujioka Kazuma in a track and field magazine...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777555</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210122" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏のいたずら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Prank</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Farce d’été</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Itazura</title>
<summary>Kansei University`s battle to achieve official records formally begins.
Having already achieved their official records, Musa, Jota, and Joji watch the race with Hanako.
Kakeru joins the lead pack and competes with exchange students from strong schools.
Meanwhile, the stagnating Shindo and Yuki utilize their strengths to make a strong effort towards achieving an official time.
During the final lap, Haiji`s words cut through Kakeru`s mind. "Do you like running?"
In that moment, something inside him opens, and Kakeru bangs out an astonishing time.
After the race, a lone reporter approaches Kakeru, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777556</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210929" update="2019-01-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして走り出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Then Start Running</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et je commence à courir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Hashiridasu</title>
<summary>The Kansei University track team runs into Tokyo Sport University at Lake Shirakaba, where they`re holding their training camp.
Sakaki insistently provokes Kakeru over his past actions.
Pushes to his limit, Kakeru grabs ahold of him, but his friends come between them before anything can happen.
Later they begin their grueling practice, but Kakeru can`t stop recalling heavy memories from his high school days: 
a cruel past that pushed a group of elite runners to their breaking point.
Recalling how he chose his own destruction, Kakeru agonizes over his past.
That night, the sky is full of stars. Haiji appears next to Kakeru as he`s hanging around by himself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777557</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211780" update="2019-01-08">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211781" update="2019-01-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211811" update="2019-01-29">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人じゃない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re Not Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tu n’es pas seul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori ja Nai</title>
<summary>The Kansei University track team accepts Kakeru`s past and begins running once again.
Their hellish training camp continues, and once they return to the city, they busily engage in recruiting for the fan club, fundraising, and job hunting. The last traces of their amateurism fade as every one of them swells with the strength of a true athlete.
The ten of them sprint through a single fleeting summer.
As Hanako watches over their brilliant progress, they begin to see a certain path leading towards their future.
A single man`s dream passes from one man to another.
Nico-chan and King draw ever closer to achieving official records. Only one man remains...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781793</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211812" update="2019-02-09">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Place of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un endroit destiné</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Basho</title>
<summary>The entire team achieves offical records.
Having earned the right to compete in the qualifier, Haiji reports their progress to Coach Tazaki.
Though they still have many challenges to face before they make it through the qualifier, the expections of everyone around them continue to rise.
They even receive an interview request from a TV station. While the others are excited, Yuki alone seems unhappy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781794</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211813" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢と現[うつつ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams and Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rêve et réalité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume to Utsutsu</title>
<summary>A runner from another school trips and falls right in front of Haiji.
Fortunately, he`s able to avoid crashing into him, but he puts all his weight on his right leg.
The fall causes a commotion at the water station. The cold rain mercilessly pounds down on the runners and the fans watching over them.
Eventually the races moves into the city streets, and the runners` race for survival accelerates.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781795</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212318" update="2019-03-04">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">答え探して</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Searching for the Answer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la recherche de réponses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotae Sagashite</title>
<summary>The Kansei University track team miraculously makes it through the qualifier.
The team is inundated by club applicants and interview requests.
Despite them, Haiji calmly focuses on preparing for the race.
However, Jota and Joji suddenly begin to oppose him.
"Haiji`s fooling us, isn`t he?"
What misgivings weigh heavily on their minds?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781796</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212319" update="2019-03-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして朝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Then, Morning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et puis, le matin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Asa</title>
<summary>While walking home with Musa, Kakeru runs into reigning champion Rikudo`s Fujioka Kazuma.
When Kakeru can`t let go of the inconsiderate remarks made by some passers-by, Fujioka methodically and without faltering shows him the answer.
Then Fujioka tells them about his shared history with Haiji.
The burden Haiji has borne alone. The response he gave to Fujioka.
In Fujioka`s words, Kakeru begins to sense the meaning of the "strength" Haiji once described to him.
Meanwhile, Haiji is at a consultation with his doctor.
His eyes are glued to the harsh reality they see...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781797</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212320" update="2019-03-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">解き放つ時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moment of Release</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au moment de laisser partir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokihanatsu Toki</title>
<summary>The Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race finally begins.
Haiji was right, and Section 1 moves at a slow pace while the teams try to feel each other out.
Prince, who bears the heavy responsibility of starting the race, takes up his position behind the other runners and conserves his strength.
It`s all part of Haiji`s plan to take the top.
Haiji also sends a message to Prince through Tazaki in the coach`s vehicle and heads to the Tsurumi Relay Station where Musa waits.
The group raises its pace. Prince desperately hangs on.
And in the back of his mind, he recalls a conversation he once had with Haiji...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781798</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212321" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壊れても</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even If I Break</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Même brisé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowarete mo</title>
<summary>Hanako cheers for him on the sidelines. Pieces of memories run through his head.
Finally realizing his romantic feelings, Jota accelerates and climbs in the standings.
As the older twin passes the sash to his younger brother,
Joji is informed about Hanako`s feelings and becomes distracted.
The sudden Hanako panic leaves the other members of the team disconcerted as well.
In order to get the race back on track, Kakeru asks Tazaki to deliver a message.
Meanwhile, Haiji calls Shindo, who has arrived at the relay station.
Their time feels simultaneously too long and too short. A tragic resolve spreads through Shindo`s burning, feverish body...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781799</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212825" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら, 美しきこの世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Beautiful World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, monde magnifique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara, Utsukushiki Kono Sekai</title>
<summary>Run with the Wind Episode 21 “Goodbye, Beautiful World”
His teammates faced death to pass the sash along.
Bearing that weight in his mind, Yuki prepares for the race.
Shindo approaches him. Turning his overflowing anxiety and regrets into strength, Yuki waits for the race to start.
Meanwhile, in Yokohama, Kakeru and Haiji wait for Sections 9 and 10 to start.
However, when Haiji is nowhere to be found, Kakeru grows uneasy.
As though confirming his concerns, a sports doctor exits Haiji`s room.
Kakeru interrogates Haiji, but Haiji remains the same calm Haiji he`s always been.
It`s 8AM. The second half begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781800</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212826" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">寂しさを抱きしめろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Embrace Your Loneliness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Étreins ta solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabishisa o Dakishimero</title>
<summary>Sakaki`s fighting spirit verges on tragic.
As though dragged along by it, King loses his pace.
He thinks back on a conversation he had once with Haiji.
The words he can`t say, the reality he can`t escape.
Will Haiji`s words free him from the doubts that cling to him?
King`s thoughts eventually arrive at the day he arrived at the Chikusei-so.
It was the beginning of a lonely but also dream-like time.
That small disappointment, that small pride. Carry all of it with you as you run.
The men continue to fight to find themselves...!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781801</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212827" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは風の中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au cœur du vent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Kaze no Naka ni</title>
<summary>Kakeru is bewildered by this new experience. His speed overwhelms the other competitors.
Meanwhile, reigning champion Rikudo`s ace Fujioka breaks the section record as promised and pushes his team into first place.
Fujioka finds Haiji. What answers wait for them at the ends of their roads?
They reassure one another as they exchange words. Prince`s smile pushes Haiji`s quiet resolve forward.
Kakeru eventually appears at the relay station, running at shocking speeds.
Their dream lies before them. Kakeru passes to Haiji. Their sash unites them and their entire team.
At what peak will the Kansei University track and field team arrive?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781802</identifier>
<identifier>run-with-the-wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
