<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1414" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1985-08-10</startdate>
<enddate>1985-08-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Odin: Koushi Hansen Starlight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Odin - Koshi Hansen Starlight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Odin</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">オーディーン・光子帆船スターライト</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Odin: Photon Space Sailer Starlight</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Один: Космический корабль "Звёздный свет"</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Odin</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">فرسان الفضاء</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Odin</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8787" approval="4" total="4">Uchuu Senkan Yamato 2199</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Work">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="5221" type="Original Plan">Nishizaki Yoshinobu</name>
<name id="3327" type="Direction">Yamamoto Eiichi</name>
<name id="5236" type="Chief Animation Direction">Udagawa Kazuhiko</name>
<name id="3469" type="Music">Haneda Kentarou</name>
<name id="4483" type="Music">Amano Masamichi</name>
<name id="5269" type="Direction">Shirato Takeshi</name>
<name id="5288" type="Chief Direction">Masuda Toshio</name>
<name id="5423" type="Music">Miyagawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="6622" type="Music">Anzai Fumitaka</name>
<name id="8442" type="Music">Takasaki Akira</name>
</creators>
<description>In the year 2099, mankind has colonized parts of the Solar System thanks to the evolution of space travel. To venture further beyond what man has accomplished, the space vessel Starlight is launched. After rescuing a mysterious girl from a wreckage near the asteroid fields, the crew of the Starlight plot a perilous journey towards the Canopus system in search of the planet known only as "Odin" - the possible key to all forms of life.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="185">3.11</permanent>
<temporary count="189">5.39</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>48212.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>704</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1287</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>292</identifier>
<identifier>tgqwqv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Odin:_Photon_Sailer_Starlight</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オーディーン_光子帆船スターライト</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>149520</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="15145" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>140</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24432" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24433" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24775" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24776" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24778" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 4 of 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
