<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1424" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-07-26</startdate>
<enddate>1997-07-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Siu Sin</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">A Chinese Ghost Story: The Tsui Hark Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">قصة أشباح صينية</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">Xiao Qian</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">cgs</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">チャイニーズ・ゴースト・ストーリー スーシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">A Chinese Ghost Story</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Histoire de fantômes chinois</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">천녀유혼</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">A Lenda de Ning</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Ένα Φάντασμα στην Κίνα</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">小倩</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="112" approval="2" total="4">Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="217707">This anime was released in 1997. I only watched it recently, in 2014. The writers and producers must be senior in age now. I thought it is very similar to Spirited Away, because it has other-worldly dimensions.

It actually portrays subtle scenes of the other dimensions, the dream-like contents are put up very, very well.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="789" type="Animation Work">Triangle Staff</name>
<name id="3184" type="Character Design">Komatsubara Kazuo</name>
</creators>
<description>A Chinese Ghost Story is a movie that follows a young man named Ning. After the loss of his girlfriend he works as a debt collector to forget his troubles only to encounter more than he had imagined. Accompanied by his constant companion Solid Gold, Ning ends up in a ghost town and from there the adventure ensues. This movie explores some of China`s myths and fantasies as the viewer is taken through a world of drama, romance, and battles between good and evil.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="256">4.12</permanent>
<temporary count="258">6.25</temporary>
<review count="1">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>51587.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>128</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>315</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>A_Chinese_Ghost_Story:_The_Tsui_Hark_Animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>チャイニーズ・ゴースト・ストーリー_スーシン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>小倩</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="15267" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>1997-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19502" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1997-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19503" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1997-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219356" update="2019-08-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
