<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1425" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>1998-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam: Dai 08 MS Shoutai - Miller`s Report</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam: The 08th MS Team, Miller`s Report</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam: L`ottavo plotone - Il Rapporto Miller</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダム 第08MS小隊 ミラーズ・リポート</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam: The 08th MS Team - Miller`s Report</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="217" type="Full Story">Kidou Senshi Gundam: Dai 08 MS Shoutai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gundam.channel.or.jp/program/_08m_ova.shtml</url>
<creators>
<name id="4236" type="Original Series Composition">Okeya Akira</name>
<name id="1542" type="Direction">Kase Mitsuko</name>
<name id="662" type="Character Design">Kawamoto Toshihiro</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
</creators>
<description>Universal Century 0079 - Federation Intelligence Officer Alice Miller has been assigned to investigate http://anidb.net/ch2424 [Shiro Amada], Commander of the http://anidb.net/ch2466 [08th MS Team]. Her mission: to uncover details of his mysterious prolonged absence after the last battle and to determine whether or not he is a spy for the Zeon forces.
Facing the potential end of his military career, Shiro must finally choose between military duty and his relationship with Aina as the 08th MS Team strives once more to prove itself in battle.
Miller`s Report is a compilation of episodes 1-8 of the Mobile Suit Gundam: The 08th MS Team OAV series, only with additional footage featuring a new character in the form of Alice Miller, a Federation intelligence officer investigating Ens. Shiro Amada`s alleged ties with the Principality of Zeon. This movie was played in Japanese theatres along with http://anidb.net/a496 [Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz Special Edition].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="530">4.73</permanent>
<temporary count="536">6.49</temporary>
<review count="1">4.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148973.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1002</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>83</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2453</identifier>
<identifier>vmgkys</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam.channel.or.jp/program/_08m_ova.shtml</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>846</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>153649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4849" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Zaku</name>
<description>A mobile suit type from the Gundam series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2422" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="85">8.42</rating>
<name>Principality of Zeon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Republic of Zeon was initially founded by Zeon Zum Deikun, who declared the colony located at the second Earth-Luna Lagrangian Point, named Side 3, independent from the Earth Federation in U.C.0058. For the next several years, Zeon Zum Deikun and his followers dealt with diplomatic issues surrounding their independence, chiefly the economic pressure applied to Side 3 by the Earth Federation, in their efforts to force Side 3 back into the Federation. During this time, Side 3 formed its first national guard unit. Unfortunately, for the Republic of Zeon, Zeon Zum Deikun unexpectedly died (almost certainly assassinated by the Zabis) in UC 0068, leaving Side 3 without a leader. After the end of the One Year War, the Republic was re-established with a pro-Earth Federation puppet government.</description>
<picture>17677.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2423" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="22">8.20</rating>
<name>Aina Saharin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The devoted sister of mad scientist Ginias Saharin, Aina serves in a semi-official capacity as a Zeon test pilot. Shortly after she encounters Shiro Amada during a test flight in Earth orbit, Aina travels to Earth to help her brother with his newest project. Little does Aina suspect that she`ll encounter Shiro again, or that her loyalty to her brother and his cause is about to be tested for the first time...</description>
<picture>17679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2424" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="12">7.68</rating>
<name>Shirou Amada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A native of the Side 2 space colonies, Shiro personally witnessed the carnage of the war`s first weeks, an experience which filled him with hatred for the Zeons. Now, freshly graduated from officer school, he`s been transferred to Earth to take command of the Kojima Battalion`s 08th MS Team. While Shiro is a talented pilot with a knack for creative tactics, his inexperience as an officer and fondness for fuzzy inspirational speeches at first earn the scorn of the 08th MS Team`s veteran members. Meanwhile, his chance encounter with an enemy pilot leads Shiro to question his own determination to wage war.</description>
<picture>17721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2425" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="15">6.66</rating>
<name>Karen Joshua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karen, as one of the two longest-serving members of the 08th MS Team, has little patience for the team`s bumbling newcomers. Cynical and hot-tempered, she`s rumoured to have been the primary cause of her last commander`s nervous breakdown. Still, Karen`s three months of ground-combat experience make her an invaluable asset to the 08th MS Team. And, as a former medical student - and the widow of a military surgeon - Karen can also serve as a field medic in emergencies.</description>
<picture>17681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2426" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="6">6.32</rating>
<name>Terry Sanders, Jr.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In his previous assignment as a test pilot, Sanders has already become one of the Federation`s first mobile suit aces. However, his skill as a pilot is accompanied by a grim jinx; each time Sanders joins a new team, his comrades are wiped out on their third mission together. When Shiro saves him en route to Earth, Sanders tags along and becomes a member of the 08th MS Team, hoping that his optimistic new friend can help him break his "Team Killer" curse. Loyal and serious, Sanders usually plays a support role in combat, carrying ammunition and spare weapons in his Gundam`s cargo container.</description>
<picture>17683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2427" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="7">5.33</rating>
<name>Eledore Massis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At first glance, Eledore seems a poor choice for a soldier. Whether planning for his musical career, putting the moves on his teammate Karen, or just spacing out and listening to his Walkman, the 08th MS Team`s hovertruck operator never seems to have his mind on his work. But Eledore is all business whenever the team enters combat, and his keen musician`s ears give him an uncanny ability to pinpoint enemy forces with the hovertruck`s sonar sensors.</description>
<picture>17686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2428" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="7">4.78</rating>
<name>Jidan Nickard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wily chief of the Kojima Battalion`s supply company. Despite his age, not to mention his fondness for gambling and booze, Nickard is a capable supply chief who can use his wits and connections to obtain everything from ammunition to forged mission orders.</description>
<picture>17684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2429" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="13">6.28</rating>
<name>Kiki Rosita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During his first mission as leader of the 08th MS Team, Shiro manages to become lost in the jungles of Southeast Asia. As he wanders aimlessly, Shiro comes across a young woman named Kiki, who turns out to be the daughter of a local guerilla leader. Though Shiro and Kiki`s initial encounter goes badly, she and her comrades eventually grow to trust the young Federation officer, and become valuable allies of the 08th MS Team.</description>
<picture>17685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2430" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="6">2.06</rating>
<name>Michel Ninorich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Michel, a young recruit transferred to Earth along with Shiro, also ends up assigned to the 08th MS Team. Here, he`s relegated to the unglamorous role of Eledore`s assistant, helping operate the team`s hovertruck and serving as its navigator and machine-gunner. In his spare time, Michel pens long letters to his friend B.B... or is she just a friend?</description>
<picture>17687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2431" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="7">6.02</rating>
<name>Kojima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2433" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="3">4.56</rating>
<name>Sally</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2436" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="8">5.23</rating>
<name>Ginias Saharin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginias is a brilliant scientist, charged by Sovereign Degwin Zabi himself with a top-secret weapons development project. At a hidden base on the Tibetan plateau, Ginias works frantically on the Apsalus, a powerful new mobile armor which may yet tilt the balance of the war in Zeon`s favor. As his dedication turns into obsession, Ginias comes to see everything else - his allies, his underlings, even the love of his own sister - as expendable in his desperate effort to complete his masterpiece.</description>
<picture>17694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2441" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Earth Federation</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The unified world government that launched the space settlement program and now rules over both Earth and the space colonies. Its main decision-making body is the Earth Federation Assembly, which meets occasionally to pass new legislation.
Though not as cruel and aggressive as the Principality of Zeon`s leaders, the bureaucrats who rule over the Earth Federation are corrupt, weak-willed, and insensitive to the space colonists` desire for independence. After the One Year War, the Federation decides to concentrate its energies on reconstructing Earth instead of the space colonies, further increasing political tensions.</description>
<picture>17701.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2445" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Lunen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17705.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2447" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="4">2.84</rating>
<name>Arth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2448" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="3">3.64</rating>
<name>Dell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2449" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<name>Topp</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2452" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<name>Earth Federation Forces</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The military arm of the Earth Federation. The Federation Forces are divided into several branches, including land, sea, air, and space forces. Until mass production of the RGM-79 GM begins in the final weeks of the One Year War, the Federation Forces are forced to battle the Principality of Zeon`s mobile suits using conventional tanks, planes, and space fighters. Even in the postwar years, the Federation Forces are usually inferior to their opponents in terms of skill, morale, and equipment.</description>
<picture>1824.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="2454" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="5">1.27</rating>
<name>Hige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>17716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2457" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Apsaras I</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>As the war approaches its fiery conclusion, Zeon`s scientists and engineers have begun working on a new generation of weapons to surpass the mobile suit - huge, non-humanoid fighting machines known as "mobile armors." One such weapon is under development at Ginias Saharin`s secret base on the Tibetan plateau. The bulky body of the mobile armor Apsalus houses a huge mega particle cannon. and a "Minovsky craft" system, which pushes against the Earth`s surface and enables the Apsalus to soar through the atmosphere at high speeds. Hoping that this ingenious new weapon will change the course of the war, Ginias entrusts it to his sister Aina for flight testing.</description>
<picture>1825.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="2465" type="appears in" update="2009-01-16">
<name>Kojima Daitai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A mechanized battalion supervised by Lieutenant Colonel Kojima, which fights as part of the Federation`s Southeast Asia forces during the latter half of the One Year War. The Kojima Battalion is organized into two mobile suit companies, each subdivided into four teams of three mobile suits apiece, as well as an anti-mobile suit infantry company. 2nd Lieutenant Shiro Amada commands the Kojima Battalion`s 08th MS Team.</description>
</character>
<character id="2466" type="appears in" update="2009-01-18">
<name>Dai 08MS Shoutai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Part of a mobile suit company in Kojima Battalion, consists of 3 mobile suits, lead by 2nd Lieutenant Shiro Amada.</description>
<picture>17849.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="15777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1998-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133988" update="2011-10-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
