<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14332" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-11-08</startdate>
<enddate>2008-11-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Chou Tanpen Precure All Stars Go Go Dream Live!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ちょ~短編 プリキュアオールスターズ GoGoドリームライブ!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6453" type="Same Setting">Eiga Yes! Precure 5 Go Go! Okashi no Kuni no Happy Birthday</anime>
<anime id="2765" type="Other">Futari wa Precure Max Heart</anime>
<anime id="4117" type="Other">Futari wa Precure: Splash Star</anime>
<anime id="5593" type="Other">Yes! Precure 5 Go Go!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
<name id="23742" type="Direction">Ootsuka Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>The Precures from http://anidb.net/a2765 [Futari wa Precure Max Heart], http://anidb.net/a4117 [Futari wa Precure: Splash Star] and http://anidb.net/a5593 [Yes! Precure 5 Go Go!] go to a concert, but the venue is mysteriously empty. They`re suddenly attacked by a huge monster.
Note: A short screened alongside the film http://anidb.net/a6453 [Eiga Yes! Precure 5 Go Go! Okashi no Kuni no Happy Birthday]. Created to celebrate the 5th anniversary of the Precure franchise and also acts as a prototype for http://anidb.net/a6433 [Precure All Stars DX].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="29">5.37</permanent>
<temporary count="29">6.10</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>222941.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17027</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>映画_Yes!プリキュア5GoGo!_お菓子の国のハッピーバースディ♪#同時上映</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6157" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="46">7.21</rating>
<name>Misumi Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misumi Nagisa is the ace of her school`s lacrosse team. Her alter ego Cure Black is the strong fighter of the Pretty Cure duo. She is quite girly, image conscious, and has a large collection of stuffed animals. Nagisa is weak in academics but makes up for it with pure spirit and energy. She also has a large appetite and loves to eat chocolate and, according to Honoka, foods with the word "yaki" in the name. She likes shopping but tends to squander her money and ends up having none when she needs it most. Nagisa has a crush on Honoka`s friend, Fujimura-senpai, also known as Fuji-pi, gets flustered whenever he is around. To her dismay, Nagisa is more popular with the girls than the boys. She has a younger brother, Ryouta, who seems to be very fond of Honoka. Aside from Honoka, Nagisa`s best friends are Shiho and Rina.</description>
<picture>23357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6158" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="47">7.63</rating>
<name>Yukishiro Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukishiro Honoka is the quiet and reserved one, but that does not keep her from having her own friends and following. She can be quite strict and domineering when the situation calls for it. Her alter ego is Cure White. Honoka is very poised and intelligent and enjoys reading. Her specialty is the science club, where she is looked up to by the others. Honoka hasn`t had many friends, but the few she has seem to be really close to her. It has also been noted that she`s relatively popular with the boys, though she seems to have little interest in them.</description>
<picture>23358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6161" type="main character in" update="2010-02-01">
<rating votes="57">7.23</rating>
<name>Cure Black</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2143.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6162" type="main character in" update="2010-02-01">
<rating votes="65">6.10</rating>
<name>Cure White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2144.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7621" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="29">5.59</rating>
<name>Kujou Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujou Hikari has no fighting strength, but she can enhance the power of Cure Black and Cure White when she transforms into Shiny Luminous. She is the "Life of the Queen", having lost all of her abilities and memories from being Queen and is living as a passive human girl. She makes friends with Nagisa and Honoka.</description>
<picture>3012.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9361" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="29">6.31</rating>
<name>Yumehara Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second-year student at L`École des Cinq Lumières Middle School, Nozomi appears to be a typical shoujo heroine, and does not know what to do with her life. Her father works as an author of children`s stories and her mother runs a beauty shop. She has a habit of saying "It`s decided!" when she decides on something not exactly with everyone`s permission. Formed a crush on Coco (in his human form) at first sight, and her feelings grow as the series progresses. This also has started a love triangle between her and Milk for Coco, because both have feelings for him. Though her teammates are vastly different from her, Nozomi learns how to become their friend, and their leader. Cure Dream wears pink, and her costume has a design resembling that of Cure Rouge. Her given name is pronounced, though not written, the same way as the Japanese word for hope, nozomi, and part of her surname (yume) means "dream" in Japanese. According to the release date of the movie Yes Precure 5 Gogo Happy Birthday in the Land of Sweets, Nozomi`s birthday is 8th November.
She introduces herself as "Great Power of Hope, Cure Dream!"
In the first movie, her counterpart is Dark Dream, who is voiced by Nishimura Chinami. In the second movie, she gets a power-up: Shining Dream.</description>
<picture>81332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9362" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="58">7.87</rating>
<name>Cure Dream</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9363" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="25">8.56</rating>
<name>Natsuki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This second-year student appears as a tomboy and plays enough sports to have every team clamouring for her to join them, but indulges in a few feminine pursuits, such as a love of boys. She has a very straightforward and down-to-earth personality that sharply contrasts with the cheery and optimistic Nozomi. Her parents run a flower shop. Rin wears red-orange, and she transforms into Cure Rouge; her counterpart is her best friend, Cure Dream. She introduces herself as "Red Flame of Passionate, Cure Rouge!"</description>
<picture>81324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9364" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="10">2.14</rating>
<name>Cure Rouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9365" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="34">5.68</rating>
<name>Kasugano Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urara is the youngest member of the Pretty Cure. She is a sweet blonde first-year and a transfer student. She puts on a smiling face to all, but can only be herself around Nozomi and her friends. Because she is always busy and is now acting in a TV drama, she has no friends outside of the Cures. Before she joined the team, she learned of Nozomi`s and Rin`s identities, and was not nearly as shocked as the others, likely because the drama that she had been cast in appears to be based on the Splash Star series. Her mom died when she was young. She is half Japanese (from her mom) and half French (from her dad). Cure Lemonade wears yellow and has no counterpart. She introduces herself as "Effervescent Scent of Lemon, Cure Lemonade!"</description>
<picture>81320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9366" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="15">8.36</rating>
<name>Cure Lemonade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9367" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="27">5.72</rating>
<name>Akimoto Komachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another third-year, Komachi is kind and shy, and likes to read books and write. However, once she is angered enough, she will snap and release her temper. Along with her best friend Karen, Komachi is also a popular senior at her school. She is a volunteer at the school library, along with Karen/Cure Aqua, and often spends her time there writing stories. Her dream is to become a writer, and she exhibits particular talent in this: Nuts praised her first completed story (upon the 7th revision), and he does not give praise lightly. She has romantic feelings for Nuts, which she expresses in the form of her second novel. Her parents own a traditional Japanese sweetshop.
The green-clad Cure Mint is the counterpart of Cure Aqua. Fans noted that her appearance is similar to Lettuce Midorikawa of Tokyo Mew Mew. She introduces herself as "Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!"</description>
<picture>81329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9368" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="17">7.03</rating>
<name>Cure Mint</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another third-year, Komachi is kind and shy, and likes to read books and write. However, once she is angered enough, she will snap and release her temper. Along with her best friend Karen, Komachi is also a popular senior at her school. She is a volunteer at the school library, along with Karen/Cure Aqua, and often spends her time there writing stories. Her dream is to become a writer, and she exhibits particular talent in this: Nuts praised her first completed story (upon the 7th revision), and he does not give praise lightly. She has romantic feelings for Nuts, which she expresses in the form of her second novel. Her parents own a traditional Japanese sweetshop.
The green-clad Cure Mint is the counterpart of Cure Aqua. Fans noted that her appearance is similar to Lettuce Midorikawa of Tokyo Mew Mew. She introduces herself as "Tranquility of the Green Earth, Cure Mint!"</description>
<picture>81328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9380" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="16">7.43</rating>
<name>Minazuki Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karen is the oldest member of the team. This third-year student comes from an affluent family and is a member of the student council. Her parents are musicians and often go on tour. She misses them, but will not ask for them to come home for fear of disturbing their work, so despite wealth and popularity, she is often lonely. Komachi is her best friend and a fellow student council member.
Seen around school as cool and inspiring, most of the students look up to her. She, as Nozomi learns, is the most trustworthy Cure. In the beginning, she is reluctant to join the Cure team. In episode 6, as the girls are being manhandled, Karen stands up to her friends, vowing to protect them regardless of transformation. The butterfly that eluded her previously reappears and successfully lands on her wrist, enabling her to transform to Cure Aqua. As Cure Aqua; counterpart of Cure Mint, she wears deep blue in her outfit, resembling Cure Mint`s outfit. She introduces herself as "Blue Spring of Intelligence, Cure Aqua!" Like Nozomi and Komachi with Coco and Nuts respectively, she has a special bond with Milk.</description>
<picture>81330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9381" type="main character in" update="2012-02-10">
<rating votes="14">7.23</rating>
<name>Cure Aqua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14669" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="12">7.31</rating>
<name>Cure Bloom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Like Nagisa, Saki is a cheerful athletic girl. She is a member of Yuunagi Middle School`s girls` softball team, and a very good player and like Nagisa she enjoys sweets a lot. Her family runs a bakery. She also has a sister named Minori, who she shares a room with. Saki`s whole name can translate into "A flower that blooms toward the sun" or a sunflower, and a sunflower is also Cure Bloom`s symbol.
As Cure Bloom, Saki introduces herself as, "The Shining Gold Flower, Cure Bloom!"</description>
<picture>2979.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="595" picture="17993.jpg">Kimoto Orie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14670" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="11">7.42</rating>
<name>Cure Egret</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mai is a reserved academic girl however, unlike Honoka, she seems to prefer arts to sciences. Her father is an astronomer, her mother is an archeologist and her brother, Kazuya, wishes to follow in his footsteps. She and her family live in an observatory. Her whole name can translate into "The beautiful flying dance".
As Cure Egret, Mai introduces herself as "The Radiant Silver Wing, Cure Egret!"</description>
<picture>2980.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14706" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="36">5.47</rating>
<name>Shiny Luminous</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujou Hikari has no fighting strength, but she can enhance the power of Cure Black and Cure White when she transforms into Shiny Luminous. She is the "Life of the Queen", having lost all of her abilities and memories from being Queen and is living as a passive human girl. She makes friends with Nagisa and Honoka.</description>
<picture>2142.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14732" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="16">6.04</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Like Nagisa, Saki is a cheerful athletic girl. She is a member of Yuunagi Middle School`s girls` softball team, and a very good player and like Nagisa she enjoys sweets a lot. Her family runs a bakery. She also has a sister named Minori, who she shares a room with. Saki`s whole name can translate into "A flower that blooms toward the sun" or a sunflower, and a sunflower is also Cure Bloom`s symbol.
As Cure Bloom, Saki introduces herself as, "The Shining Gold Flower, Cure Bloom!"</description>
<picture>42437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="595" picture="17993.jpg">Kimoto Orie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14733" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="13">8.65</rating>
<name>Mishou Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mai is a reserved academic girl however, unlike Honoka, she seems to prefer arts to sciences. Her father is an astronomer, her mother is an archeologist and her brother, Kazuya, wishes to follow in his footsteps. She and her family live in an observatory. Her whole name can translate into "The beautiful flying dance".
As Cure Egret, Mai introduces herself as "The Radiant Silver Wing, Cure Egret!"</description>
<picture>42438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14741" type="main character in" update="2010-02-04">
<rating votes="8">6.24</rating>
<name>Mimino Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a cooperator of Pretty Cure that appears in Yes! PreCure 5! GoGo! Her civilian name backwards has the same pronunciation with Miruku no Mimi meaning "Milk`s ears." She has long, violet, curly hair and fuchsia eyes. When transformed, she wears violet with blue flower decorations. A calm, smart character, her cool persona acts as a mask to her bizarre personality.
She introduces herself as "The Blue Rose is The Secret Mark, Milky Rose!" (Aoi Bara ha Himitsu no Shirushi, Milky Rose!)
She is actually Milk in human form, who got her powers from a blue colored seed left behind after the events of episode 7. Milk/Kurumi can`t stay in this form for too long, as it drains her energy and reverts her back to mascot form.</description>
<picture>42453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14742" type="main character in" update="2010-02-04">
<rating votes="13">9.01</rating>
<name>Milky Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a cooperator of Pretty Cure that appears in Yes! PreCure 5! GoGo! Her civilian name backwards has the same pronunciation with Miruku no Mimi meaning "Milk`s ears." She has long, violet, curly hair and fuchsia eyes. When transformed, she wears violet with blue flower decorations. A calm, smart character, her cool persona acts as a mask to her bizarre personality.
She introduces herself as "The Blue Rose is The Secret Mark, Milky Rose!" (Aoi Bara ha Himitsu no Shirushi, Milky Rose!)
She is actually Milk in human form, who got her powers from a blue colored seed left behind after the events of episode 7. Milk/Kurumi can`t stay in this form for too long, as it drains her energy and reverts her back to mascot form.</description>
<picture>42452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39717" type="main character in" update="2012-10-30">
<rating votes="4">4.77</rating>
<name>Cure Bright</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="595" picture="17993.jpg">Kimoto Orie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39719" type="main character in" update="2012-10-30">
<rating votes="3">4.35</rating>
<name>Cure Windy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97771" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-29">
<name>Kage no Kyojin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="97479" update="2018-08-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
