<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14360" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Magia Record: Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica Gaiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">magireco</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マギアレコード 魔法少女まどか☆マギカ外伝</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Magia Record: Puella Magi Madoka Magica Side Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">سجلات ماجيا: قصة جانبية للفتاة السحرية مادوكا</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">魔法紀錄 魔法少女小圓外傳</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15472" type="Sequel">Magia Record: Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica Gaiden 2nd Season</anime>
<anime id="8069" type="Other">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://anime.magireco.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7866" type="Character Design">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="10196" type="Series Composition">Gekidan Inu Curry</name>
<name id="3528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamura Hiroki</name>
<name id="7770" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugiyama Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="10196" type="Chief Direction">Gekidan Inu Curry</name>
<name id="12305" type="Music">Ozawa Takumi</name>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="39802" type="Original Work">Magica Quartet</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a smartphone role-playing game.
In exchange for the fulfillment of a wish, Magical Girls keep fighting, unbeknownst to the rest of the world. But http://anidb.net/ch101568 [Tamaki Iroha] can`t seem to remember her wish.
"When I became a Magical Girl, what did I wish for again?"
There is a gaping hole in her life. Something important has been lost. But she continues to fight every day, without even knowing why... Then, a rumor begins to spread among Magical Girls.
"Magical Girls can be saved if they go to Kamihama."
Kamihama City, the city where Magical Girls and Uwasa are gathering. The story of Tamaki Iroha, in search of her lost wish, begins...
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="210">4.36</permanent>
<temporary count="210">6.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238105.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://anime.magireco.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://magiarecord-animeusa.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magia_Record</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マギアレコード_魔法少女まどか☆マギカ外伝</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5516</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>magireco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.funimation.com/shows/magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25163" type="appears in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="101">5.59</rating>
<name>Tomoe Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoe Mami is a Puella Magi contracted to http://anidb.net/ch25645 [Kyuubee] and a third year student at Madoka`s school, living alone in a penthouse after her parents`s deaths. She has the ability to produce a near-infinite amount of flintlock rifles, can use ribbons to suspend her enemies, and is also able to perform healing magic. Due to being involved and seriously injured in a car accident (which also claimed the lives of her parents) at the time Kyuubey approached her, she was forced to use her wish to save herself. Unlike other Puella Magi, who mostly focus on obtaining valuable Grief Seeds, Mami is particularly focused on saving those around her. Though she often has a cheery disposition, she is also often lonely and scared due to the nature of her work and is pleased when Madoka offers to become her partner.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>60589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25642" type="appears in" update="2010-12-10">
<rating votes="122">6.87</rating>
<name>Tomoe Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25643" type="appears in" update="2012-04-01">
<rating votes="104">5.11</rating>
<name>Miki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Magical Girl form of Miki Sayaka.</description>
<picture>60592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25645" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="170">6.37</rating>
<name>Kyuubee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuubee is a familiar who can grant any wish to a certain girl, on the condition that she become a Puella Magi and fight against witches.
When someone makes a contract with him, he extracts their soul and places it inside a Soul Gem, replacing their body with a shell that`s more resilient to fighting witches. He has so far made contracts with Mami, Kyouko and Sayaka, and shows particular interest in making Madoka a magical girl. It is yet to be revealed if there are other familiars besides him. As a magical creature, he can only be seen or heard by Puella Magis and those with magical potential. He is shown to consume used Grief Seeds, though for what reason is unknown. His true motives are unknown, and he constantly tries to find chances to persuade girls with magical potential to form a contract with him despite knowing the dangers that a Puella Magi faces. He tends to have little understanding of human values and doesn`t believe what he`s doing is cruel. If he is killed, another Kyuubee takes his place and consumes the previous one. Homura recognizes his true identity as Incubator.</description>
<picture>60594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27945" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<rating votes="133">7.40</rating>
<name>Sakura Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28165" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="114">7.54</rating>
<name>Sakura Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura Kyouko is a rival Puella Magi who comes to the city after Mami is killed by a witch. A girl with red-colored long hair and an equally fiery personality to match. Amusingly, she is always seen eating something, even while she is battling Sayaka. When Kyouko learns Sayaka had become a Puella Magi just before she arrived, she becomes Sayaka`s enemy for allegedly stealing her territory, although she later tries to help her after learning the truth about Soul Gems. She comes from a poor church family and used her wish so that people would listen to her father`s preachings. However, when her father learned of this, he went mad and killed his entire family. As such, Kyouko decided only to use her magic for herself, since using it for others will only cause despair. Having grown up in a poor family, she often has to steal food and hates wasting it, a logic she also applies to Grief Seeds, as she only goes after fully grown witches. Kyouko wields a spear which can extend itself, split into multiple sections, and produce a ball at the end of the chain, which can constrict and hit others at the same time.</description>
<picture>64987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101563" type="main character in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Nanami Yachiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanami Yachiyo is a veteran Magical Girl in Kamihama City. She is a college student who`s not affiliated with a team, preferring to instead work alone. She is very territorial and is strict toward Magical Girls from other areas, especially when their skills don’t measure up. Yachiyo has been documenting all of Kamihama City’s "rumors."
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>240496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101564" type="main character in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Futaba Sana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101565" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Togame Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Togame Momoko is a benevolent Magical Girl who saves inexperienced Magical Girls when they’re in a pinch.
As the middle child with two brothers, she grew up very assertive and outspoken, almost boyish. Despite that, she likes stuffed animals and other cute things. As a direct result of those preferences, she is also a fan of female idols.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>243994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101566" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Minami Rena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minami Rena is a socially awkward Magical Girl who’s bad at expressing herself. She hides her lack of confidence by putting up a determined front, which makes it easy for her to be misunderstood by people she doesn’t know well yet. Contrary to her unsociable attitude, she likes sweets and has a childish taste when it comes to food. She is a female idol groupie.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>243996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101567" type="main character in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="2">5.42</rating>
<name>Mitsuki Felicia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mitsuki Felicia is a Magical Girl who makes a living as a mercenary. She is a skilled fighter, but loses her cool when battling Witches, and is known as a troublemaker. She often acts like a spoiled child that is lazy and self-centered.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>244421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101568" type="main character in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<name>Tamaki Iroha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki Iroha is a Magical Girl who lives in Takarazaki City. She is very responsible, but being overly considerate toward everyone around her, she does not fit in at school. Iroha cannot remember the wish she made when she became a Magical Girl, so she decides to go to Kamihama City to investigate a certain rumor that could provide her with answers.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>240495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37985" picture="175206.jpg">Asakura Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101569" type="main character in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="3">7.81</rating>
<name>Yui Tsuruno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34603" picture="175431.jpg">Natsukawa Shiina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101570" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Akino Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akino Kaede is a cowardly Magical Girl who’s prone to worrying. Still, she’s kind, cares about her friends, and will face any dilemma for the sake of her team. She loves plants, animals, insects, and nature, and works hard on her vegetable garden at home. One of her favorite hobbies is playing UFO catcher games, even though she’s not good at them.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>243995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106543" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<name>Kuroe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroe is a Magical Girl who lives in Takarazaki City. She fights alongside Iroha from time to time, but mostly they’re acquaintances who get together on a regular basis to exchange information. Kuroe is afraid of fighting in life or death battles and wishes she could be saved from being a Magical Girl. She begins to become obsessed with Kamihama City after hearing a certain rumor.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>240497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106544" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<name>Chiisai Kyuubee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smaller than Kyubey, this mysterious Kyubey only exists in Kamihama City.
Unlike Kyubey, it cannot speak.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>240498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108907" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Yakumo Mitama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108908" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Kozue Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38613" picture="200781.jpg">Aisaka Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108909" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Satomi Touka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108910" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Tamaki Ui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49536" picture="228921.jpg">Iwami Manaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108912" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Azusa Mifuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108913" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Natsume Kako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108914" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Shinobu Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32035" picture="151695.jpg">Muranaka Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108915" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Tokiwa Nanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108916" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Chun Meiyui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108918" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Amane Tsukuyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108920" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Amane Tsukasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108921" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Hiiragi Nemu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108922" type="appears in" update="2020-03-28">
<name>Alina Gray</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108926" type="appears in" update="2020-03-29">
<name>Yukino Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38753" picture="145652.jpg">Mori Nanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108927" type="appears in" update="2020-03-29">
<name>Anna Mel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43732" picture="177230.jpg">Takao Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108929" type="appears in" update="2020-03-29">
<name>Isuzu Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44218" picture="223383.jpg">Ozaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225453" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やぁやぁ, 知ってる? 魔法少女のその噂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Heard? That Rumor About the Magical Girls.</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أسمعت إشاعة الفتيات الساحرات؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ya Ya, Shitteru? Mahou Shoujo no Sono Uwasa</title>
<summary>Iroha Tamaki, a Student in Takarazaki City, has been battling Witches as a Magical Girl. However, Iroha can`t seem to remember the wish she made when she became a Magical Girl. One day, she hears a rumor from another Magical Girl, Kuroe, that Magical Girls can be saved if they go to Kamihama City. During a battle with a Witch, Iroha unexpectedly finds herself in Kamihama but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792696</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225454" update="2020-01-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それが絶交証明書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Proof of the End of a Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">هذا سينهي صداقتكما حتمًا</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore ga Zekkou Shoumeisho</title>
<summary>Iroha remembers that her wish was to cure her younger sister, Ui’s, illness; however, there is no sign of Ui’s existence in her life. She goes to Kamihama City to find clues about her, but is attacked by a Witch and subsequently saved by a trio of Magical Girls, Momoko, Rena, and Kaede. There is a rumor going around about the Friendship Ending Staircase at Rena and Kaede’s school. Momoko and the others believe that a Witch is involved in the rumor, so they’ve been investigating it, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792697</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225455" update="2020-01-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達にしてごめんね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorry for Making You My Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أعتذر عن جعلك صديقتي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi ni Shite Gomenne</title>
<summary>Rena wrote Kaede`s name on the Friendship Ending Staircase. Kaede apologizes to Rena, but she is kidnapped by the Chain Monsters, confirming that the rumor about the staircase was true. In order to find Kaede and bring her back, Momoko and her companions come up with a strategy to lure out the Chain Monsters.
Yachiyo has joined the group after being asked by Momoko to help them. Yachiyo claims that Iroha will hinder the operation and refuses to let her participate in the battle with the Chain Monsters.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792698</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225456" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去じゃないです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Isn`t the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">هذا ليس ماضي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako ja Nai Desu</title>
<summary>Iroha decides to investigate Kamiahama City’s rumors in order to find clues about her missing sister, Ui. Mitama introduces Iroha to Tsuruno, the daughter of the owner of a Chinese restaurant called Banbanzai. Tsuruno asks someone who is familiar with the rumors to help investigate, but Yachiyo is the one who shows up at the meeting spot. Tsuruno says Yachiyo is knowledgeable about the rumors of Kamihama City. The three suspect that the Séance Shrine may have something to do with Ui’s disappearance…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792699</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225659" update="2019-12-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2019-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">年末特別番組「アニメ放送直前SP~マギレコ夜噺~」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nenmatsu Tokubetsu Bangumi "Anime Housou Chokuzen SP: Magi Reco Yoru Hanashi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226193" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたが割って入る隙間なんてないんですよ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s No Place for You Here</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أنت غير مرحب بك هنا</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata ga Wattehairu Sukima Nante Naindesu yo?</title>
<summary>At the Séance Shrine, Iroha wrote her sister`s name, Ui, and Yachiyo wrote the name of her former best friend, Mifuyu, on votive plaques. As if to confirm the truth of the rumor, Ui and Mifuyu appear, but they are twisted imposters of their loved ones. Iroha and Yachiyo are attacked by the fake Mifuyu and the master of the Séance Shrine, a Horse Monster, and find themselves in a bind that threatens to end their lives. Iroha`s Soul Gem gets cloudy, making her slowly lose consciousness. What sort of transformation will she undergo?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792700</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226194" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんだってしてやるよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Do Anything</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">سأفعل أي شيء</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nandatte Shite Yaru yo</title>
<summary>Iroha wanders into Kosho Ward in Kamihama City. On the street, she is offered some Lucky Owl Water, which is said to bring good fortune, and without much thought, takes a sip. Another Magical Girl named Felicia also happens to drink the Lucky Owl Water. Wherever they go together they have extremely good luck. They have such good luck, in fact, that Iroha finds it a little strange. Felicia makes a living as a mercenary, and offers her services to Iroha to help find Ui, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792701</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226195" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一緒に帰りたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Go Home with You</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أريد العودة للبيت معك</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issho ni Kaeritai</title>
<summary>Felicia was asked to join the Wings of the Magius, an organization that works within the shadow of rumors. She betrays Iroha and her friends and joins them. Kyoko is also invited by the Wings of the Magius and decides to join the organization. Iroha and company track Felicia down to an underground waterway, where the Wings of the Magius lurk. When the good luck count from the Lucky Owl Water reaches zero, it is said that unimaginably bad luck will befall whoever drank it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792702</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226196" update="2020-02-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対に返信しちゃだめよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Definitely Shouldn`t Respond</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يجب ألا تردي على الرسائل المزعجة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai ni Henshin Shicha Dame yo</title>
<summary>Iroha moves into Mikazuki Villa and transfers to Kamihama City University Affiliated School. She discovers that even though Kaede goes to the same school, she is unable to contact her. Iroha has a hard time getting used to her new surroundings, so when she sees that Rena doesn`t have many friends in class, they decide to eat lunch together on the rooftop. Iroha is still gathering information about various rumors, and Rena tells her about the rumor of the Invisible Girl and Endless Solitude. Tsuruno hears about the rumor of the Radio Wave Girl from a regular at Banbanzai and tells Iroha about it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792703</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226933" update="2020-03-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私しかいない世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World with Just Me</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">عالم فيه أنا فقط</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Shika Inai Sekai</title>
<summary>Iroha responds to an unknown sender who`s been messaging her and asking her if she is a Magical Girl. Once the message is sent, Iroha immediately gets a reply back pleading to Iroha to come to Endless Solitude to save the girl who is being held captive there. When Iroha asks how she could get there, things suddenly take a dangerous turn...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792704</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226934" update="2020-03-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私の名前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Name</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">اسمي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Namae</title>
<summary>Iroha and the girl who was being held captive inside the Uwasa of Endless Solitude succesfully break out of it. Alina Gray is not happy about this and attempts to collect the payment she is owed. However, an unlikely Magical Girl comes to their rescue. Now with their fourth Uwasa destroyed, how will the Wings of the Magius proceed?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794320</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226935" update="2020-03-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束は午後三時, 記憶ミュージアムにて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory Museum at 3:00 PM</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">في متحف الذاكرة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku wa Gogo Sanji, Kioku Museum nite</title>
<summary>As Mikazuki Villa becomes more lively, Yachiyo is reminded by Mifuyu about the dangers of making new friends because of what happened to them in the past. Yachiyo becomes distant from the rest of the tenants while the others set off to visit the Uwasa of the Memory Museum.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794321</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226936" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どうしてこんなにみじめなんですか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Why Is This So Unbearable?</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">كلما زاد عدم تحملي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doushite Konna ni Mijime Nan Desuka</title>
<summary>Iroha and the other Magical girls finally meet one of the Wings of the Magius, and Iroha asks her many questions. Mifuyu reminds the girls that they are here for a lecture that will reveal the intentions of the Magius.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794322</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226937" update="2020-04-05">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たったひとつの道しるべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Faint Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الأمل الخافت</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatta Hitotsu no Michishirube</title>
<summary>Iroha refuses to join the Magius. When she and Yachiyo meet up, she is eager to go search for Tsuruno and the other girls. However, Yachiyo believes that her wish brings tragedy to those around her and tells Iroha that she is disbanding the team. The Memory Museum begins to collapse. Iroha and Yachiyo try to escape, but Mami, who has become an entirely different person, attacks them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794323</identifier>
<identifier>magia-record-puella-magi-madoka-magica-side-story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227380" update="2020-03-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227381" update="2020-03-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
