<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1440" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>193</episodecount>
<startdate>1963-01-01</startdate>
<enddate>1966-12-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tetsuwan Atom</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mighty Atom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tetsuwan Atomu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">鉄腕アトム</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Astro Boy</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12148" type="Prequel">Atom: The Beginning</anime>
<anime id="7341" type="Same Setting">Akuma Tou no Prince: Mitsume ga Tooru</anime>
<anime id="1916" type="Same Setting">Jetter Mars</anime>
<anime id="2991" type="Alternative Setting">Hyakumannen Chikyuu no Tabi Bander Book</anime>
<anime id="13225" type="Alternative Setting">Pluto</anime>
<anime id="807" type="Alternative Setting">Tetsuwan Atom (2003)</anime>
<anime id="1446" type="Alternative Setting">Tetsuwan Atom (1980)</anime>
<anime id="4456" type="Character">Fumoon</anime>
<anime id="1496" type="Character">Jungle Taitei</anime>
<anime id="7876" type="Character">Ravex in Tezuka World</anime>
<anime id="8488" type="Other">Tezuka Osamu ga Kieta?! 20 Seiki Saigo no Kaijiken</anime>
<anime id="1514" type="Other">Tetsuwan Atom: Uchuu no Yuusha</anime>
<anime id="1513" type="Other">Tetsuwan Atom: Shinsengumi</anime>
<anime id="13476" type="Other">Tetsuwan Atom (Shinsaku)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5673" approval="4" total="8">Kaiba</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/30.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="833" type="Work">Mushi Production</name>
<name id="1195" type="Chief Direction">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="13993" type="Music">Takai Tatsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch34134 [Atom] is created by http://anidb.net/ch34144 [Dr. Tenma] as a replacement for his human son Tobio following the boy`s death in a car accident. Despite his best of intentions, Tenma soon becomes frustrated that Atom never grows any taller and continues to make mistakes as he learns to harness his robot powers. In a moment of mental weakness, Tenma sells Atom to the owner of the Robot Circus, but is soon rescued by the newly appointed head of the Ministry of Science, the kindly http://anidb.net/ch34143 [Dr. Ochanomizu].
In the adventures to come, Atom proves himself time and again, helping with rogue robots, desperate criminals, missions to other planets and even finding time to attend school.
Along the way he is helped by his teacher, http://anidb.net/ch35816 [Shunsaku "Higeoyaji" Ban], his friends, his sister http://anidb.net/ch16593 [Uran] and the rest of his robot family.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="143">5.24</permanent>
<temporary count="144">6.24</temporary>
<review count="1">5.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>33758.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2747</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>558</identifier>
<identifier>awhwmq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/30.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/en/anime/51.html#prev</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rightstuf.com/rssite/nozomiEntertainment/seriesSites/astroboy/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Astro_Boy_(1963_TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>鉄腕アトム_(アニメ第1作)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89672</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6010" parentid="1278" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-12-29">
<name>human-replacement robots</name>
<description>In an usually sci-fi setting robots, or quite probably actually androids, take the place of humans.
Examples: Humans have become infertile and androids now take the place of children. Or it may be a more sinister undermining of human society by artificial intelligence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6017" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>perpetual ongoing</name>
<description>No end in sight!
No matter what the genre may be or what the storyline consists of, this series just keeps on going... and on... and on.
The obvious downside to this is the lack of story-related focus, usually some vague goal is simply never reached. This lack of conclusion can tend to annoy, making the whole series pretty much pointless.
Examples: One Piece, Naruto, Bleach, Detective Conan, Dragon Ball (Z), or Pocket Monsters (Pokemon).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16593" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="4">2.14</rating>
<name>Uran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uranium is Astro Boy`s sister constructed by Dr. Ochanomizu as a gift for his birthday. Has 100,000 horsepower strengh.</description>
<picture>4348.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="21669" picture="229311.jpg">Mizugaki Youko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="15692" picture="228933.jpg">Mutou Reiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="30749">Yoshikawa Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34134" type="main character in" update="2011-07-02">
<rating votes="8">2.14</rating>
<name>Atom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25083" picture="70125.jpg">Shimizu Mari</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="23398">Tagami Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34143" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-03">
<rating votes="6">1.63</rating>
<name>Ochanomizu Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4346.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3238" picture="186228.jpg">Katsuta Hisashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34144" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-03">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Tenma Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4347.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="30029" picture="79286.jpg">Yokomori Hisashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34145" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-03">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Tawashi-keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4349.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="27963" picture="26672.jpg">Chiba Kouichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3643" picture="24947.jpg">Kanemoto Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34148" type="appears in" update="2011-07-03">
<name>Nakamura-keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33711" picture="92485.jpg">Sakamoto Shinpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35815" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Cobalt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25044">Komiyama Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35816" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="5">1.63</rating>
<name>Hige Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1264.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3388" picture="24415.jpg">Yajima Masaaki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="32742" picture="233949.jpg">Wada Ayao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79431" type="appears in" update="2016-09-10">
<name>Rock Holmes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the world of show business, it is common knowledge that actors who start out playing the role of children rarely make it to the top of their profession. This is because child stars, who are loved in the role of cute children, even if they grow, are burdened with the fate of having to continue showing the same image to audiences. In the same way, in the Manga of Tezuka Osamu, loveable, law-abiding characters like Kenichi and Atom were restricted to continuously playing the same role. But Rock is different. He was not simply a virtuous character. From the time he started performing in child roles, he never believed in the image that "a bright future will be born if only justice triumphs". "The world is full of inconsistencies. The world will not weep even if the fight for justice is lost and evil triumphs. Come spring the flowers will still bloom, the sunshine will still pour down in the summer." Rock was a boy who stared these realities in the face. As might be expected from a character that got his name from Sherlock Holmes, Rock is a highly intelligent young boy. That`s why he never had to trade on his charms even as he grew up. He concealed the malicious face of the devil under his handsome visage. He built up his character as the portrait of a villain. Part of the appeal of Tezuka Osamu`s Manga lies in the fact that such warped boy stars are incorporated into the stories, and in the inclusion of elements of profundity and philosophy.</description>
<picture>191106.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="15380" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="2">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム誕生の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of Astro Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom Tanjou no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Tenma, Director General of the Science Ministry, loses his dearest son Tobio in an accident, so he decides to create the robot Astro Boy, who looks like Tobio, using the best of the Science Ministry`s technology.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15381" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="2">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フランケンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Colosso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Franken no Maki</title>
<summary>Franken, who has been classified as an inferior product at the robot factory, harbors a violent hatred for humans. As a result, humans begin to say, "We cannot trust robots," and even start to persecute the good robots.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15382" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火星探検の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Expedition to Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasei Tanken no Maki</title>
<summary>Astro Boy is appointed leader of an exploration to Mars. Lieutenant Cap, who has to work for Astro Boy, however, rises in revolt against Astro Boy because he does not like the idea of robots ordering humans around.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15385" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">1.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲルニカの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Million Mammoth Snails</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guernica no Maki</title>
<summary>Many cities fall one after another due to a huge group of monsters called "Guernica." Astro Boy fights against Guernica to save the people.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15386" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スフィンクスの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sphinx</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sphinx no Maki</title>
<summary>Astro Boy is captured by a gang of thieves looking for treasures hidden in a Pyramid, and he tries to destroy the beast of the god Sphinx, which has a lion`s body and the face of a beauty.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15387" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">1.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電光人間の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zero, the Invisible Robot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denkou Ningen no Maki</title>
<summary>Skunk steals the invisible robot Denko that was made of paper glass, and releases prisoners from jail. He wants to use Denko in order to build an empire of gangs...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15388" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム大使の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captain Atom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom-taishi no Maki</title>
<summary>A swarm of aliens who look exactly like specific earthlings such as Dr. Ochanomizu and Higeoyaji immigrate to the Earth from a planet very similar to ours. However, a food shortage occurs, and humans begin to attack the aliens with cell-reducing fluid.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15389" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊製造機の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spirit Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuurei Seizouki no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Ochanomizu is taken away to the country Gorgonia, where he finds the Dictator Hillar`s plot to conquer the world with a cloning machine, which is also a ghost-manufacturing machine that can make endless copies of any objects.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15390" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラックルックスの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Deep Freeze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Black Looks no Maki</title>
<summary>A group called Black Looks sets out to exterminate robots, and they attack in succession. Astro Boy begins to fight against them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15391" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イワンの馬鹿の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strange Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ivan no Baka no Maki</title>
<summary>Astro Boy lands on an unknown planet, where he finds the tomb of a female leader of an expedition and a stupid but faithful robot Ivan that guards the tomb.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15392" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイムマシンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Machine no Maki</title>
<summary>A boy who comes from the future is looking for his father, who has gone to capture ancient creatures and has never come back. So Astro Boy and the boy depart for the ancient world in search of the boy`s father.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15393" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十字架島の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juujika-tou no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Serizawa is an escaped convict trying to steal the underground resources of Cross Island by using the robot Puke that can transform itself into anything. He is planning to run away on a rocket. Astro Boy follows the man to Cross Island.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15394" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">キリストの眼の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eyes of Christ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christ no Me no Maki</title>
<summary>A priest has marked one of the eyes of Jesus in the church before he dies. This seems to be a clue to the identity of a gang that had broken into the church. Now the same gang starts to go after Higeoyaji, who has discovered the gang`s secret.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15395" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">人工太陽の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Artificial Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinkou Taiyou no Maki</title>
<summary>Suddenly an artificial sun appears. It is a threat to the world from the gang Kaito Kinsankaku. Astro Boy sets out to destroy the gang, together with detective Sherlock Homespan.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15396" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">植物人間の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grass Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokubutsu Ningen no Maki</title>
<summary>A flying disk from Planet Alfee is busily collecting water from the Earth. Astro Boy learns that they are collecting water for their hometown because it suffers a water shortage. Planet Alfee, however, had already been ruined...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15397" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い惑星号の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silver Comet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Wakusei Gou no Maki</title>
<summary>The vehicle "White Planet" participates in the Round-the-world Grand Prix, but a gang breaks it to prevent it from winning. So Dr. Ochanomizu offers to load White Planet with Astro Boy`s artificial intelligence.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15398" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットランドの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hullabaloo Land</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Land no Maki</title>
<summary>"Robot Land" is a theme park where robots dressed as the main characters of children`s books entertain children. In its underground factory, however, slave robots are forced to make weapons.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15399" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガデムの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gangor, the Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gadem no Maki</title>
<summary>A gang tries to smuggle the robot Gadem, which begins to act violently in a passenger boat. Then Astro Boy, who happens to be on the boat, tries to stop them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15400" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム対魔神の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cosmic Giant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom tai Majin no Maki</title>
<summary>The robot Garon, who re-models planets, is transported to Earth by mistake, and humans consider attacking it with nuclear weapons. Astro Boy, however, takes to other means to face Garon.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15401" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">気体人間の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toxor, the Mist Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitai Ningen no Maki</title>
<summary>A "gas man" enters into Dr. Ishizu`s body in space, and comes back to the Earth. Then a number of gasmen enter into human bodies, and begin to act violently. Astro Boy challenges these invisible cosmic creatures to a fight.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15402" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">人工衛星R-45の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Satellite R-45</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinkoueisei R-45 no Maki</title>
<summary>A member of the cosmic patrol is struggling against gangs. When Astro Boy comes to help him, however, he says that he does not need any help from a robot. He does not know that he is also a robot.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15403" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海蛇島の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sea Serpent Isle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umihebi-tou no Maki</title>
<summary>Astro Boy heads for Sea Serpent Island to rescue the girl Anna, who has been captured, but he is also caught. Moreover, Astro Boy`s body begins to rust because the island is rich in salt...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15404" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミュータントの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Deadly Flies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mutant no Maki</title>
<summary>A mysterious murder case occurs. Astro Boy happens to be on the scene and is arrested as a suspect. The real culprit, however, is a mutant created by X party, which plans to conquer the world.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15405" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底王国の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kingdom of the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei Oukoku no Maki</title>
<summary>Why don`t we destroy humans and build a kingdom only of robots? Disposable bomb robots for a submarine kingdom make this suggestion to Astro Boy.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15406" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底戦車の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Deep-underground Tank</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitei Sensha no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Jordan runs away from a president who plans to conquer the world. Astro Boy gets on a deep-underground tank with him to fight against the president. But they lose control of the tank and it begins to head toward a volcano.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15407" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトラスの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don Tay`s Infernal Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atlas no Maki</title>
<summary>Atlas has the same kind of power as Astro Boy, but he has an evil heart. For Astro Boy, the fight with Atlas means fighting with his own dark side.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15408" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パール星の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pearl People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pearl-sei no Maki</title>
<summary>To build a submarine dam, bombs for construction work are set up in a place where inhabitants of Planet Pearl have been living secretly. When Astro Boy finds that out, he plays a major part in rescuing their community under the sea.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15409" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">マッドマシンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wacky Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mad Machine no Maki</title>
<summary>Mad Machine causes all machines to go wrong and malfunction. The machine goes out of control, and the city is thrown into chaos. Because Astro Boy is also a machine, he begins to malfunction...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15410" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">想い出の日の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide no Hi no Maki</title>
<summary>When Astro Boy gets inside the unfinished time machine in Jiro`s room, he hears the voice of Jiro, who is supposed to be dead. Jiro might have traveled to another time and perhaps is having trouble coming back.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15411" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ZZZ総統の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Agent 3-Z</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ZZZ Soutou no Maki</title>
<summary>The President of ZZZ Gang is so eager to conquer the world that he even kills his twin brother. So Astro Boy stands up to destroy his ambition.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15412" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い宇宙線の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Cosmic Rays</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Uchuusen no Maki</title>
<summary>A monster appears in the city, and it turns out to be Dr. Dorian, who has been exiled to Mars. He turns into a monster because he cannot get cosmic X rays on the Earth.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15413" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホットドッグ兵団の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Dog Corps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hot Dog Heidan no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Ponkotsu implants dogs with robot brains. Then the dogs form the "Hot Dog Army" to take on the humans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15414" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の魔術師の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Magicians</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Majutsushi no Maki</title>
<summary>A man takes on the police with a robot thief. Then a gifted magician is suspected of theft, so he and Astro Boy go against the robot thief together.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15415" update="2006-07-27">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミドロが沼の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beast from 20,000 Fathoms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midoro ga Numa no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15416" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間牧場の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen Bokujou no Maki</title>
<summary>Astro Boy sets out on a rocket to rescue people who have been kidnapped for use as livestock on a planet that looks like the Earth.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15417" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">プイプイ教の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Elixir of Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pui Pui Kyou no Maki</title>
<summary>The religious group "Pui Pui" is looking for a wonder drug that will give them immortality. Then Dr. Tatsuji, who has succeeded in developing such a drug, is taken away by the religious group. So Astro Boy fights them to ensure the peaceful use of the drug.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15418" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウランちゃんの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strange Birthday Present</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uran-chan no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Ochanomizu gives Astro Boy a younger sister as a birthday present. This younger sister Uran is a very cute girl, but she is such a tomboy that Astro Boy is kept terribly busy settling the confusion she causes.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15419" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂った小惑星の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Asteroid Menace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurutta Shouwakusei no Maki</title>
<summary>The small planet Mezusa goes out of its orbit and heads straight to the Earth. To save the Earth from a collision with the planet, Astro Boy heads for the planet with a convict who is a bomb professional.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15420" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い猫の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Neko no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Shisoku despairs of human beings that continue the ongoing destruction of nature, and makes animals attack cities in his machine that hypnotizes with ultra short waves.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15421" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネオ・シーザーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Abominable Snowman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neo Caesar no Maki</title>
<summary>A man named Caesar dreams of rebuilding the Roman Empire with robots under his control. However, he is destined to follow the same path that as that of Julius Caesar.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15422" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">X爆弾の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deadline to Danger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">X Bakudan no Maki</title>
<summary>X Bomb, which is capable of turning any substance to water, drops into the Pacific Ocean. There are fifty hours left till the explosion. Astro Boy goes to recollect it, but learns that Uran, who has followed him, has been swallowed along with the bomb by a whale.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15423" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄色い馬の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Yellow Horse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiiroi Uma no Maki</title>
<summary>Astro Boy gets into a satellite owned by the drug smuggling organization "Yellow Horse." There, the members of the organization are secretly creating missiles for use in war.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15424" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">デッドクロス殿下の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ditto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Cross Denka no Maki</title>
<summary>The robot president Rag is the target of an assassin. Then Astro Boy finds out that the culprit is Dead Cross, Rag`s creator. He had created Rag to run in the presidential election, but when Rag gets elected, he begins to hold a grudge against Rag.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15425" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エジプト陰謀団の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleopatra`s Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Egypt Inboudan no Maki</title>
<summary>Uran is kidnapped. She is made a hostage in an operation to steal Cleopatra`s necklace from Astro Boy. The gang of conspirators believes that whoever possesses the necklace can build the greatest empire in the world.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15426" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレオパトラの首飾りの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return of Cleopatra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cleopatra no Kubikazari no Maki</title>
<summary>The gang of conspirators obtains the coveted necklace, and at last sets about conquering the world. However, Astro Boy stands in the way of their boss, Cleopatra.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15427" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット宇宙艇の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Phantom Space Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Uchuutei no Maki</title>
<summary>The robot spaceship "Lever Robot" is stolen. Astro Boy is sent to retrieve it, but in the process has his energy stolen.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15428" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙ガニの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gigantic Space Crab</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuugani no Maki</title>
<summary>Ham egg exchanges a pig from the Earth for the huge crab that the alien Pork has. He is trying to make a lot of money by making a show of the creature in a circus...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15429" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">天馬族の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Space Horse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenmazoku no Maki</title>
<summary>Nuu, member of the Tenma Tribe, a rarely seen race of people, comes from the depths of the mountains of Mongolia. People rush to the city just to try and see Nuu, throwing the city into a big chaos. Moreover, a gang plots behind the scenes to capture Nuu.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15430" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">透明巨人の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3D Tee Vee</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toumei Kyojin no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Hanabusa develops an electrical transmitter for substances. No sooner does he get into the machine for testing than his rival scientist breaks the machine, which makes Dr. Hanabusa an invisible man. Astro Boy tries to save the doctor.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15431" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム西部へ行くの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Westward, Ha!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom Seibu e Iku no Maki</title>
<summary>To find Hekku, who had departed to the west in the past but has not returned yet, Astro Boy and Higeoyaji also travel back in time.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15432" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">子象プーラの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jimbo the Great</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kozou Pura no Maki</title>
<summary>The robot elephant Zora malfunctions and runs away into the jungle. There, Astro Boy is taking care of a little elephant Pura that has gotten separated from its fellows.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15433" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">1.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪ライオンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Snow Lion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki Lion no Maki</title>
<summary>An old man who comes from Planet Regel to the Earth brings a snow lion with him. Then, aliens from Planet Regel start to spray cosmic snow that sucks up all energy... Astro Boy takes off for space to save the Earth, where cities have stopped functioning.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15434" recap="true" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さようなら1963年の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye 1963</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayounara 1963-nen no Maki</title>
<summary>It is New Year`s Eve, 1963. Uran finds a picture while cleaning the house. With the picture as a clue, Astro Boy and Dr. Ochanomizu begin to piece together the past. This episode is a special edition that includes an introduction of "The making of the film of Astro Boy."
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15435" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルプスの決闘の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel on the Alps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alps no Kettou no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Tenma, who once dumped his "child" Astro Boy, wants him back and asks the gang Skunk for help. Skunk`s group, the "Illusionary Club," succeeds in abducting Astro Boy and his family...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15436" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">若返りガスの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rejuvenating Gas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakagaeri Gas no Maki</title>
<summary>The royal family of the palace satellite Yoranna gets what they are told is “rejuvenating gas" from earthlings. When it turns out to be just teargas, however, they launch an H-bomb missile toward the Earth in retaliation.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15437" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球防衛隊の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moon Monsters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Bouei-tai no Maki</title>
<summary>Aliens planning to collect information about the Earth abduct Dr. Ochanomizu. Atom, on a mission to rescue the doctor, visits Earth Defense Base on the moon, but the aliens destroy the base.
(In color)
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15438" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット学校の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Astro Boy Goes to School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Gakkou no Maki</title>
<summary>Humans can see the beauty of things and be impressed by them. In order to learn these feelings, called “heart," Atom, Uran and Lara start attending a robot school.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15439" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">13の怪神像の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Island of Mystery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">13 no Kai Shinzou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and Dr. Ochanomizu decipher ancient code of 200,000 years ago. Discovering that hidden hints in the thirteen statues of god in Western Island might lead them to the secrets of outer space, they head for the island.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15440" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白熱人間の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Super Duper Robot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakunetsu Ningen no Maki</title>
<summary>Gaston, who has stolen a blueprint of a robot from a UFO requests the Science Ministry to build the robot exactly as shown on the blueprint, without indicating its source. The completed robot Buron turns out to be a destructive weapon, and starts to destroy everything.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15441" update="2006-07-27">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダーマの宮殿の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dogma Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Darma no Kyuuden no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15442" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の寄生虫の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Parasites</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Kiseichuu no Maki</title>
<summary>The last of the Nazis demand the government of the Earth to turn over the planet, threatening to shower it with space parasites. When the government refuses to surrender, a group of UFOs containing space parasites come swarming toward the Earth.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15443" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊船の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Haunted Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuureisen no Maki</title>
<summary>Wishing to have a “heart" like a human, Atom has his body equipped with a heart that can feel fear. Soon after, a phantom ship appears over the Indian Ocean. Atom is sent to investigate it, but he is scared out of his wits.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15444" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">人工氷山の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man-Made Iceberg</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinkou Hyouzan no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Zulu places a bomb in an artificial iceberg and tries to trigger a flood. Discovering the plot, Atom sets out to prevent the explosion, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15445" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">こうもり伯爵の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vampire Vale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koumori Hakushaku no Maki</title>
<summary>Tick and Tack get lost in the depths of the Unzen Mountain, and decide to stay for a night in a deserted house inhabited by a vampire. The vampire (Dr. Pedan) tries to turn Tick into a vampire, but Atom comes to rescue them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15446" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇敢な脱走者の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Terrible Tidal Wave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuukan na Dassousha no Maki</title>
<summary>A massive tidal wave breaks. Atom flies up to stop the wave, but crashes into the sea. Then an escapee robot Boggy saves the unconscious Atom.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15447" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペースバイキングの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vikings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Space Viking no Maki</title>
<summary>In order to rid the earth of space pirates, Atom destroys their mother ship. The pirates, however, are holding some hostages and demand that Atom withdraw. Atom is helpless.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15448" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜の勇士達の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru no Yuushi-tachi no Maki</title>
<summary>While playing in the toy section, Uran imbues some of the toys with artificial intelligence. Among these are some with evil hearts. Atom asks the good toys to help him stop the bad dolls from doing misdeeds.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15449" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐龍人の反乱の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dinosaur Dilemma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouryuujin no Hanran no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom is babysitting in an ancient amusement park when a dragon flies off with a small child in front of his. Then the dinosaurs demand food for ransom. So Atom...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15450" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">時計塔の秘密の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Clock Tower Mystery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokeitou no Himitsu no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Temp, who has completed his killing-beam machine, is planning to ruin the “Conference of Scientists." Discovering the plot, Atom takes on the doctor.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15451" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラフレシアの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flower Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rafflesia no Maki</title>
<summary>Rafflesia, the largest flower on earth, is found to be in fact a plant man from outer space. This flower, which needs radioactivity to survive, is stronger than it looks, and even Atom is no match for it.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15452" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球最後の日の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack from Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Saigo no Hi no Maki</title>
<summary>“Red Star" is heading toward the Earth. Watching Atom struggle to save the Earth from a collision, Bem, a high-powered bomb robot, decides that the only way to save the Earth and Atom is to blow himself up.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15453" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の漂流7日間の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shipwreck in Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Hyouryuu Nanokakan no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom is chasing gangs who have run away by rocket. Then he finds them in a shelter station being attacked by aliens. He helps the gangs, but finds himself drifting in space with them after the station is destroyed.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15454" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグタイタンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Titan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big Titan no Maki</title>
<summary>The daughter of Dr. Putt, a descendant of the Mohican tribe, is kidnapped. When he sees Uran, who is a look-alike of his daughter, he takes Atom and his fellows for the kidnappers.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15455" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球探検の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission to the Middle of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Tanken no Maki</title>
<summary>It is thought that a highly advanced civilization might exist underground. To test this hypothesis, Atom and Uran set out on an underground expedition. There they get attacked by underground men.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15456" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">空とぶ町の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inca Gold Fever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soratobu Machi no Maki</title>
<summary>In order to collect the hidden treasures of the Inca that are scattered around the world, the old man Kapack, who has the power to move things with his mind, asks Tondale for help. Tondale, however, plans to get all the gold to himself, and starts an attack on the world with a special machine that enhances mind power.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15457" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンスターマシーンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monster Machine no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Morse succeeds in corresponding with Planet Paranoia, which is more civilized than the Earth. With the help of Atom, the doctor assembles a mysterious box following the instructions on a blueprint sent from the planet, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15458" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケープタウンの子守歌の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hooligan Whodunit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cape Town no Komoriuta no Maki</title>
<summary>A boy named “Looks" is deeply attached to the robot that has brought him up. He loves the robot as if it were his mother. From the day the robot is destroyed by another robot, he begins to hate all robots. Then he forms an exclusive organization called “Black Looks," and starts to oppress robots...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15459" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">50万年後の世界の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funnel to the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">50-mannengo no Sekai no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and his friends jump into the far future world by accident. There, they see the cruel Pepper tribe treating their enemy tribes as slaves.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15460" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドクター脳の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Brain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doctor Nou no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Kanekura kills world famous brain surgeon Dr. Ibal, making it look like an accident. Since the incident, a strange robot named Friday follows him around. In truth, Dr. Ibal`s brain waves are controlling the robot.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15461" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒューマノイドピルの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mighty Minute</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Humanoid Pill no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom meets a strange creature in the wooded outskirts of Tokyo. It is a humanoid, a product of science. The humanoid named Bill does not know whether he is a creature or a machine.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15462" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢みる機械の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dream Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumemiru Kikai no Maki</title>
<summary>What kind of dreams do robots have? Atom participates in an experiment of a dream machine created by Dr. Poron, and becomes the first robot that dreams. In his dream, he turns into a human.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15463" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット競技大会の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robot Olympics</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Kyougi Taikai no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom participates in the Olympic games for robots, where he finds a group of robots destroying other participants in a vicious act of sabotage designed to ensure that they win the games.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15464" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪鳥ガルダの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dunder, Bird of Doom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaichou Garuda no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Raja, who believes in the Indian god of destruction Carley, creates a robot bird. Then it comes flying over Japan. The bird Garuda demands Atom as a sacrifice to Carley...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15465" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">イルカ文明の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dolphins in Distress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iruka Bunmei no Maki</title>
<summary>Claiming to possess every inch of the ocean floor, Hall tries to build an autocratic submarine civilization. He starts to persecute the aboriginal Dolphin tribe. Atom stands up to preserve the peace on the ocean floor.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15466" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂ったベルトウェイの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mad Beltway</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurutta Beltway no Maki</title>
<summary>One of the latest means of traffic the new city boasts, the Beltway, is almost complete. However, someone tries to obstruct its construction, setting the site aflame. Atom sets off to protect the Beltway.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15467" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">時間銃の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Terrible Time Gun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikan Juu no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Tempo is waiting for a chance to become the next director of the Science Ministry. With his time gun that can send its targets to the past, he sends the bothersome Atom and Dr. Ochanomizu to the middle Ages.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15468" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">新かぐや姫の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Kaguya-hime no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom exchanges messages with a star nymph, and sets out on an expedition to find the pure water the nymph needs. The star nymph is, in fact, a princess of the Planet Keios. She is trying to turn into a cocoon with pure water on a full-moon night in preparation for emergence.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15469" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">細菌部隊の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mighty Microbe Army</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin Butai no Maki</title>
<summary>The pilot of a rocket that has made an emergency landing is suffering from a strange disease. After they hear a voice from within the pilot`s body, Atom and Higeoyaji are reduced to tiny figures, and get into the body. Inside, they see bacteria-sized aliens.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15470" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴメスの亡霊の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horrible King Horrid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomes no Bourei no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Ochanomizu accepts a request to repair robots in the Scambo Empire. The robot he repairs, however, turns out to be the president of the Empire. The doctor`s life is in danger, as he now knows the secret.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15471" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット砦の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery of Amless Dam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Toride no Maki</title>
<summary>A robot child has a fight with a human child, making the child cry. The humans become angry when they hear this, and a war breaks out between humans and robots.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15472" update="2017-03-16">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガロン逆襲の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Galeom from Galaxy G</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garon Gyakushuu no Maki</title>
<summary>Garon, a robot Atom has sent back to space, comes back. Seeing Atom struggle hard to fend off Garon, the Earth Robot Army stand together to attack Garon.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15473" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット三銃士の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Robotiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Sanjuushi no Maki</title>
<summary>In order to save patients suffering from space disease on Mars, a serum is sent to Mars from the Earth. All the transport ships carrying the serum, however, get destroyed on their way. Atom, together with the three robot knights, goes into space to protect the last of the serum.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15474" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コバルトの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother Jetto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cobalt no Maki</title>
<summary>There is a robot that has been dumped along with other junk during the cleaning of the warehouse in the Science Ministry. It is a prototype of Atom, made by Dr. Tenma, named Cobalt. When Cobalt wakes from sleep, he tries to go back to the Science Ministry, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15475" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルプスの天使の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel of the Alps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alps no Tenshi no Maki</title>
<summary>The construction of a dam near the Bering Strait is hampered by difficulties. Dr. Zeman`s research is required to solve the problem. Atom goes to ask for help from the doctor who lives a secluded life in the depth of the Alps because of his hatred for civilization. Atom, however, finds the doctor being attacked by another robot that is after the research material.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15476" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔のパンチカードの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic Punch Card</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ma no Punch Card no Maki</title>
<summary>A missile base is completely controlled by computer. Now, the computer is out of control, setting the stage for nuclear attack. In fact, this is a means of personal revenge by Dr. Yakoref, who has lost the competition for the design of the base. Atom starts to disassemble the computer, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15477" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">1.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットヒューチャーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Rocket Robbery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Future no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Akuta, who is after the gold ingot on Mars, controls a robot called “Future." The robot, however, becomes humble after hearing out Atom. Then Atom and Future pursue the doctor, who has run away with the gold ingot.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15478" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の対決の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Contest in Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Taiketsu no Maki</title>
<summary>Planet Hyper is the most civilized planet in the galactic system. Now it chooses a pair of a human and a robot each from both the Earth and Planet War to have them fight against each other, and decides to destroy the loser`s planet. Atom and Ponkotsu Tetsu, the safebreaker, are chosen to represent the Earth.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15479" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼオの遺産の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gift of Zeo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zeo no Isan no Maki</title>
<summary>A big robot is excavated from the construction site of a tunnel. It turns out to be a time capsule that was created to pass down information on a super ancient civilization of a million years ago to posterity.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15480" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さなコロンブスの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Deep, Deep Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Columbus no Maki</title>
<summary>Colon-bu-bu, the explorer of the underground state of Chombo, heads for the ground hoping to see a new world. Then he meets Cobalt, and takes him underground as prisoner.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15481" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットハウスの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wonderful Christmas Present</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot House no Maki</title>
<summary>On Christmas night, Dr. Ochanomizu opens the will of his scientist friend who died 10 years before. It says that he has left an invention in Bururu Mountain. Atom and his friends happen to be on the mountain, and encounter a boy called Akio who lives alone there. They become friends, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15482" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">1.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地図にない世界の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uncharted World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chizu ni Nai Sekai no Maki</title>
<summary>The visiting Prince Dorian of the Camellia Kingdom disappears. Atom goes searching for him using the latest four-dimensional detection device, and finds the prince wandering in another world. That world is inhabited by people who have been spirited away from various time periods.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15483" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔境の女王の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jungle Mystery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyou no Joou no Maki</title>
<summary>Uran is going to be in a movie. Her role is Tarzan. When she goes on location to the jungle, however, a mysterious woman takes her away. The woman is planning to make Uran, who is dressed as a boy, a prince of the demon`s place-a place where nobody grows old.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15484" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙への階段の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Terrible Spaceman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu e no Kaidan no Maki</title>
<summary>Humans are drawn toward a flight of stairs that suddenly appear one day, and they start to walk toward a spaceship hidden among the clouds. When there are no humans left on earth, the robots start to talk about taking over the planet.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15485" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の風船の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil`s Balloon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Fusen no Maki</title>
<summary>A balloon in the shape of Atom appears over the city. Children love Atom so much that they begin to run after the balloon and disappear. Because such incidents frequently occur, Atom comes to be regarded as a fearful enemy of children.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="17851" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Official Preview Clips</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23101" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">193</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球最大の冒険の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest Adventure on Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Saidai no Bouken no Maki no Maki</title>
<summary>As the temperature of the Earth rises due to the influence of a sunspot, all humans evacuate the Earth and head for space. Only robots are supposed to remain on the Earth, but there is one villain left, and he is trying to seize this chance to conquer the planet.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44288" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">131</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムーンチャンピオンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moon Champion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moon Champion no Maki</title>
<summary>Shooting, fencing, an obstacle race, and wrestling: Atom wins easily in these four games, advancing to the final league of the Moon Champion. However, war robot Goram, controlled by Ham Egg, starts to get in Atom`s way.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44289" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">サターンマンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Human Beings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saturn Man no Maki</title>
<summary>hree scientists gain supernatural power on the surface of the moon. Then Dr. Arden- who has a grudge against Dr. Ochanomizu-stages an attack against him. In order to protect Dr. Ochanomizu, Atom fights fiercely against the scientists who have supernatural power.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44290" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">127</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">実験ロボットの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Experimental Robot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikken Robot no Maki</title>
<summary>“Please help me," a robot pleads as runs into the house of Dr. Ochanomizu. He tells the doctor that in a country called Yumani, the science minister Mooshy is demolishing robots in an experiment. So Dr. Ochanomizu and Atom travel to the country, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44291" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">172</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘラルド兄弟の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Herald Brothers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Herald Kyoudai no Maki</title>
<summary>The Herald brothers are trying to defeat every robot in the world. Dr. Herald, disguised as a robot, is controlling them. Then he even captures Atom.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44292" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">164</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙ぐもの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Space Spider</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuugumo no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and Dr. Ochanomizu investigate a UFO. Judging the empty disk dangerous, they stage an attack on it with a missile. Then a huge spider appears from the same type of disk that has landed on earth, and starts attacking humans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44293" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">114</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">メトロモンスターの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Metro Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Metro Monster no Maki</title>
<summary>A huge slug appears in a subway station yard, and begins to eat trains. Atom sets out to destroy it, but the slug proves to be a much tougher enemy as it appears in unexpected places.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44294" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">147</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">空中スクリーンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mid-Air Screen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuchuu Screen no Maki</title>
<summary>A machine for projecting pictures in the air has recently been invented. Then the owner of a theater steals it, and starts to take away energy from machines and robots in order to get enough energy for screening.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44295" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">174</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底大運河の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Submarine Canal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei Daiunga no Maki</title>
<summary>Strange incidents start occurring, such as an event where a vessel that had disappeared in the Japan Sea turns up in the Pacific Ocean. Dr. Ochanomizu thinks that there could be a submarine canal right beneath Japan. So Atom goes in search of the canal, and encounters subterranean people on the ocean floor.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44296" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">171</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠のクッチャーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kutcher Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Kutcher no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Kutcher, inventor of artificial intelligence, is dead. People become crazy trying to uncover his immense legacy. In the middle of this, Atom receives a message from the doctor who is supposed to be dead.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44297" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">184</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイム戦争の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Sensou no Maki</title>
<summary>People who have white blood come from the future with Robot Jijiru following them. Blood transfusion are needed to save them. When Atom and Dr. Ochanomizu fly to the future, they discover a post- nuclear war-world. Man has become extinct, and there is a continuous war between artificial men and robots.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44298" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">117</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">史上最大のロボットの巻 (後篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Biggest Robot on Earth (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijou Saidai no Robot no Maki (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>The strongest of all robots, Pluto, has electromagnetic horns that can destroy anything. Pluto destroys the world`s most powerful robots one by one. Depicted here is Atom`s hard struggle to challenge this mighty enemy.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44299" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">153</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い木馬の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Merry-Go-Round</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Mokuba no Maki</title>
<summary>Uran is on a merry-go-round in an amusement park when she disappears. The merry-go-round turns out to be an electrical transmitter for sending certain substances that was made by Dr. Umazuki, who lost his daughter and horse ten years before.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44300" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">128</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">インカ帝国の宝の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasures of the Inca Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inca Teikoku no Takara no Maki</title>
<summary>A passenger plane flying over the Amazon crashes. Atom, who is on board, saves a girl called Milly who has a map showing the places where treasures of the Inca Empire are hidden. But a group of men looking for the treasures are after her.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44301" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">118</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットグラビーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robot Grabby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Grabby no Maki</title>
<summary>A robot named Grabby is a 1/2 G fighter robot that has run away from a country called Nickrasia. Atom tries to help Grabby, who is too gentle to live as a weapon.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44302" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球解放の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery of the Metal Men</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Kaihou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom is involved in an explosion during the construction of a dam. The impact sends him into a parallel world where Tobio, the son of Dr. Tenma, never died in an accident that killed him in our world. In other words, it is a world where Atom has not been born.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44303" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">126</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボイドの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roboids</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roboid no Maki</title>
<summary>An army of Roboids that look like robots but are extremely close to creatures come to the Earth from the outer space. Dr. Ochanomizu sends all the robots on earth to fight off the Roboid Army, but the robots are destroyed one after another by the mighty foes.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44304" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">146</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来からの報告の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Report from the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai kara no Houkoku no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Muder reports, “Tomorrow, robots will start a rebellion" when he comes back from a time machine trip to the next day. Hearing this, humans start a riot, shouting that the robots should be destroyed now. The scared robots run into a fortress.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44305" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死鳥の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phoenix Bird</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushichou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom finds a big egg in a cave on a little island where he is playing with Uran. He asks Dr. Ochanomizu to identify the egg, but they are unsuccessful. So Atom goes back to the island, where he encounters a strange bird that lives there.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44306" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">笑わぬバック国の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Mission</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warawanu Back-koku no Maki</title>
<summary>A country called “Back" suddenly withdraws from the World Peace Union, and announces to its people a ban on invention and laughter. Atom and Dr. Ochanomizu visit the country to find out what is behind this closed-door dictatorial policy.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44307" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">160</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄金のフルートの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Flute</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougon no Flute no Maki</title>
<summary>The flute expresses the player`s feelings through its tunes. Ryuryu, who possesses the flute, comes to Japan in search of her beloved grandfather, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44308" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">163</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">別世界への道の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Road to Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bessekai e no Michi no Maki</title>
<summary>A flaming car disappears as if being swallowed up in another dimension, leaving behind a silver coin that was used in the ancient civilization of the Mu continent. Atom tries to solve the mystery of Mu.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44309" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">180</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">青騎士 (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blue Knight (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao Kishi (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Count Burg hates serial killer robot Blue Knight so much that he even destroys innocent robots. Atom is caught in the middle of the hatred between robots and humans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44310" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">135</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット犬バッキーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robot-Dog Backy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Inu Backy no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom goes to see a robot-dog contest with Dr. Ochanomizu. There, Atom becomes aware of poor stray robot-dogs left behind in the shadow of more beautiful, more accomplished robot-dogs. He feels sorry for the forgotten dogs.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44311" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">137</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さいクーリーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Cooley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisai Cooley no Maki</title>
<summary>A sister-robot and her younger brother-robot run away from a space station and head for the Earth. The two robots are equipped with heat resistant devices that enable them to work near the sun. When their bodies touch each other, the surrounding temperature rapidly drops. If they come to the Earth, everything will freeze...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44312" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">177</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ばかでかいロボットの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gigantic Robot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakadekai Robot no Maki</title>
<summary>In a country called Herenia, the national budget is all used to make the world`s largest robot Gorem. The robot, however, turns violent because its artificial intelligence is imperfect.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44313" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">133</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">10年目の復讐の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge After Ten Years</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">10-nenme no Fukushuu no Maki</title>
<summary>The ordinary robot Riboryu suddenly turns violent and lets Dr. Marus and his accomplices escape from jail. Riboryu has been preprogrammed to save Dr. Marus after ten years.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44314" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">156</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット市長の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robot Mayor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Shichou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and his friends visit a city governed by a robot mayor. The artificial intelligence of the popular mayor, however, turns out to be malfunctioning. When Atom realizes this, he thinks the mayor should not continue his work any more, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44315" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">166</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジュエルの魔像の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Jewel-Eating Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jewel no Mazou no Maki</title>
<summary>Since the science ministries of the world refuse to stop producing war weapons, Dr. Jugemu starts to destroy the ministries with a monster figure that produces tremendous power when it consumes jewels.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44316" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">175</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット大戦争の巻 (前篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robot Wars (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Daisensou no Maki (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Super artificial intelligence robot Logos threatens to melt the ice on the South Pole and to sink the world into the ocean unless the world surrenders. In response to this threat, Atom and his friends go off to destroy Logos.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44317" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">149</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">カンヅメ狂騒曲の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Can Capriccio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanzume Kyousoukyoku no Maki</title>
<summary>A can with a parachute falls from the sky on Atom`s house on New Year`s Day. He tries hard to open it without success. Meanwhile, a can opener falls from the sky in a different place...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44318" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">189</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">撮影所騒動の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confusion at the Shooting Studio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsueijo Soudou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and Uran go to see the shooting of a film. There, they see robots that look exactly like themselves, and take part in the filming after secretly changing places. In the shooting studio, however, stunt robots are treated as harshly as if they were objects.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44319" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">145</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム深海を行くの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Atom in the Deep Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom Shinkai o Iku no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Ochanomizu assigns Atom a new mission that requires him to find an H-bomb plane from the deep waters and to defuse it. Then Atom`s mother becomes angry because he is always summoned for dangerous missions.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44320" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">122</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪獣マントラーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Mantler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaijuu Mantler no Maki</title>
<summary>A big earthquake wipes out the city. Atom is buried under a collapsed building, but still manages to fight a huge monster that has appeared in the city. Unfortunately Atom has lost his seven powers during the earthquake.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44321" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">144</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">失われた友情の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ushinawareta Yuujou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom saves Robot Muller from villains, and a friendship develops between them. Muller plays happily with Atom and Uran, but in fact he is a robot for terrorist use, made to destroy a nuclear power plant.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44322" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">138</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">長い1日の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Long Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagai Ichinichi no Maki</title>
<summary>Abnormal weather suddenly hits the Earth. After an investigation, it becomes clear that the problem has been caused by Earth`s orbit having gone astray. Then Atom realizes that behind this are evil aliens trying to destroy the Earth.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44323" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">132</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルイ王子の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prince Louis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Louis-ouji no Maki</title>
<summary>The mother of Prince Louis steals Shadow II, a new-style robot designed for spying. She is planning to replace her son`s body with the latest robot. She does not know that ShadowIIis loaded with a time bomb...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44324" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">159</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔と天使の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Devil and Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma to Tenshi no Maki</title>
<summary>Gifted botanist Leaf has created the plant people Freru and Zaboa. Freru is fair like an angel, while Zaboa is an evil monster. When Zaboa becomes violent in the city, Atom and Freru set out to stop Zaboa.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44325" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">186</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おばけは夜来るの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monsters Come Out at Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obake wa Yoru Kuru no Maki</title>
<summary>Due to trouble with their rocket, Atom and other passengers are forced to land on an unknown small planet. On the planet lives a huge monster that eats plants that grow during the night.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44326" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">182</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂ったコバルトの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demented Cobalt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurutta Cobalt no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom is asked to cooperate in defeating the dictator of Planet Batra, and he heads for the planet. The dictator Gammer, however, lures Cobalt out and turns him to a robot that will never disobey him. Now Atom has to fight against his own brother.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44327" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">116</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">史上最大のロボットの巻 (前篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Biggest Robot on Earth (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijou Saidai no Robot no Maki (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>The strongest of all robots, Pluto, has electromagnetic horns that can destroy anything. Pluto destroys the world`s most powerful robots one by one. Depicted here is Atom`s hard struggle to challenge this mighty enemy.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44328" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">125</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">細菌をさがせの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find the Bacteria</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin o Sagase no Maki</title>
<summary>A petri dish containing the bacteria of a dreadful infectious disease is lost by a simple mistake. In order to protect humans from the danger of biohazard, Atom flies off to the depths of the Himalayas following the trail of the bacteria.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44329" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">142</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミーニャの星の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Minya`s Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minya no Hoshi no Maki</title>
<summary>There is a diary of a female soldier who never had the chance to return to Earth after her emergency landing on an ice planet. Now Atom, who is riding on a sightseeing rocket, is forced to land on the same planet, and finds the diary. Then humans begin to quarrel shamefully over the two diamonds mentioned in the diary.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44330" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">141</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">機関車行進曲の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Locomotive March</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikansha Koushinkyoku no Maki</title>
<summary>Children love March, an atomic-powered locomotive. Getting jealous of its popularity, Gold challenges March with another locomotive called “Horsepower." The match starts based on a rule that the loser has to be disassembled. Gold obstructs March by various means.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44331" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">124</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おきみやげの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Trouble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okimiyage no Maki</title>
<summary>An alien who comes to the Earth as an ambassador of friendship leaves a present for Dr. Ochanomizu. It is a blueprint of a highly efficient robot. When he assembles it, it turns out to be a robot that can offer the best of services to humans. Dr. Ochanomizu is pleased, envisioning a more comfortable life for humans, however...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44332" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">192</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">メドッサの館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Medussa`s Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Medossa no Yakata</title>
<summary>A doctor studying the mysteries of eternal youth has built Medussa`s mansion. Atom and his friends visit the mansion and find Medussa`s box, which contains the secret of eternal youth. When they open it, they find a young man named Siegfried lying inside.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44333" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">130</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">火星の嵐の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Storm on Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasei no Arashi no Maki</title>
<summary>Strange incidents occur frequently at the construction site of a base on Mars. Robots are also being demolished one after another. When Atom and his friends travel there to investigate, a gigantic army of ants attacks them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44334" update="2015-04-13">
<epno type="1">120</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイムハンターの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Hunter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Hunter no Maki</title>
<summary>Remake of episode #11. Story ideas and footage combined from episodes #11 and 68. This is not a recap episode and mixes the recycled footage with new material.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44335" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">190</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">メソタミアの奇蹟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miracle of Mesotamia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mesotamia no Kiseki</title>
<summary>Atom and his friends set out on an adventure to look for the mystery capital Mesotamia. When they are hit by a sandstorm, they find a hole up in the sky that they think could lead them to the capital. It seems likely that Mesotamia is a civilization created by aliens who came to the earth 2000 years ago.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44336" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">136</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャガー警部の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inspector Jaguar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaguar-keibu no Maki</title>
<summary>Police inspector Jaguar is the only robot that is allowed to arrest humans. A group of people, however, takes this as an insult and set a trap for the inspector.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44337" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">178</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">チータン夜の冒険の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chi-tan`s Nighttime Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chii-tan Yoru no Bouken no Maki</title>
<summary>Uran secretly takes the baby robot Chi-tan to a robot hospital to make it speak. A robot machine, however, remodels Chi-tan at its discretion. Chi-tan becomes huge, and turns violent in the city.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44338" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">162</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャンデー作戦の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Candy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Candy Sakusen no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom`s friend Carl immigrates to Brazil, where he gets eaten by a dreadful monster. Carl`s father sends Atom some articles left by his son, but the monster`s egg is mixed among those articles.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44339" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">179</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">青騎士 (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blue Knight (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao Kishi (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Count Burg hates serial killer robot Blue Knight so much that he even destroys innocent robots. Atom is caught in the middle of the hatred between robots and humans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44340" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムソンの髪の毛の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samson`s Hair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samson no Kami no Ke no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Ochanomizu succeeds in developing the robot Samson, who is activated by solar power. Samson, however, malfunctions and becomes violent when exposed to moonlight.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44341" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム将軍の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">General Astro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom-shougun no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom is shot by a maser gun that ruins artificial intelligence. He loses all his memory, and is shot away into space.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44342" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">173</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボッティの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robotty</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robotty no Maki</title>
<summary>Robotty is a robot of a size smaller than a tiny bean. He asks Dr. Ochanomizu to make a robot-friend for him because he feels lonely all by himself. So Dr. Ochanomizu makes a robot of the same size for him.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44343" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙から来た少年の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mighty Mite from Ursa Minor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu kara Kita Shounen no Maki</title>
<summary>Ham Egg sees a UFO in the woods that seems to have made an emergency landing, and finds an alien child. He notices the child`s super strength, and plans to win the child fame as a wrestler.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44344" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">140</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">王様とアトムの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King and Atom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ou-sama to Atom no Maki</title>
<summary>Puka-Puka Island is a southern island. In its animal kingdom, however, is a white bear that cannot exist on a southern island. Atom and his friends head for Puka-Puka Island to find out why the bear is there, but an unseen enemy obstructs their way and makes it impossible for them to approach the island.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44345" recap="true" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">129</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム対アトムの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Atom vs. Atom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom Tai Atom no Maki</title>
<summary>A fake Atom, equipped with 200,000 horsepower, appears. This robot has been created to beat Atom by gangs around the world who have always been beaten by him.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44346" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">176</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット大戦争の巻 (後篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robot Wars (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Daisensou no Maki (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Super artificial intelligence robot Logos threatens to melt the ice on the South Pole and to sink the world into the ocean unless the world surrenders. In response to this threat, Atom and his friends go off to destroy Logos.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44347" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">165</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤ん坊騒動の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Great Fuss Over Babies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akanbou Soudou no Maki</title>
<summary>The king and queen of Family Kingdom are distressed at not being able to have a baby. So they decide to adopt a baby robot that wins a contest. Dr. Ochanomizu also participates in the contest with his robot, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44348" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">水星探検の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Menace from Mercury</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suisei Tanken no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom is investigating a super thermal bomb that has fallen on earth. Then he heads for Mercury to find its launching site. On his way, however, Atom loses his sight in an accident, and gets involved in a power struggle with aliens on Mercury.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44349" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">168</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おどりあがった島の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Island That Jumped Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odori Agatta Shima no Maki</title>
<summary>Newsta Island, which had suddenly appeared, is now attracting a good number of tourists as a resort. When Atom and his friends visit the island, a big earthquake occurs. Then Atom realizes that the island, in fact, is a UFO.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44350" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">167</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">風船がいっぱいの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plenty of Balloons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuusen ga Ippai no Maki</title>
<summary>Uncle Poi, who works in a toy factory, is making balloons with hydrogen gas for children. When the machine goes out of order, numerous balloons fly up in the sky. If they are left alone, the balloons may explode violently.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44351" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">134</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">脱出作戦の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dasshutsu Sakusen no Maki</title>
<summary>Dr. Elite, who has succeeded in developing a high-speed rocket engine, is taken away with his daughter to a country called Dark. When Atom receives an SOS message through a carrier pigeon, he sets out to bring them back from Dark. However, the doctor is scared of flying, so they have to escape by other means.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44352" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">170</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の王女の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Princesses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Oujo no Maki</title>
<summary>Two princesses are fighting over sovereignty in a certain country. The princess of the northern castle asks Atom for his cooperation, thus involving him in their dispute.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44353" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">157</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジプシーの星の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gypsy`s Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gypsy no Hoshi no Maki</title>
<summary>A robot planet Kipia has drifted into space, and now it is approaching the Earth. When Atom sets out to investigate the planet, he finds that the Kipia people want to make friends with earthlings. Then, in pursuit of Kipia appears the robot planet Garoa, the destroyer of civilization.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44354" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">185</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの星の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Star of Africa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Hoshi no Maki</title>
<summary>Due to trouble with their plane, Atom and Uran find themselves wandering in Africa. Then they find a cross that emits a mysterious voice. The cross has the power to become the god of robots when fitted with artificial intelligence.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44355" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">187</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベーリーの冒険の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Baily`s Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baily no Bouken no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and Uran visit the Robot Museum. There, Atom finds an empty showcase labeled “Baily." As the name sounds familiar to Atom, he sets out to investigate it and finds that Baily is an important benefactor to him.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44356" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">143</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">バードストリート物語の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bird Street Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bird Street Monogatari no Maki</title>
<summary>Bird Street, is a preserved 20th century-street where robot boys and human boys confront each other in endless petty quarrels. A robot boys ask Atom to join them, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44357" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">115</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃げだした大金庫の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Runaway Safe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigedashita Daikinko no Maki</title>
<summary>The machines in the Mint Bureau experience accumulated stress due to overwork. So they are given hands and legs so that they can rest for a day. Once the machines have known the freedom and joy of moving around, they begin to run away from work.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44358" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">152</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット爆弾の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robot Bombs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Bakudan no Maki</title>
<summary>Robot Bomb Wide wants to be useful to humans. So takes to attacking Atom, mistaking him for a bad robot.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44359" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">119</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">空とぶレンズの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soratobu Lens no Maki</title>
<summary>Planet M, shaped like a convex lens, is approaching the Earth. It reflects solar light toward the Earth, turning its surface into an incandescent hell. Humans, however, cannot cooperate in tackling this global issue because they all motivated by their own greed.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44360" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">183</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙から来たニッポン人の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Japanese People from Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu kara Kita Nipponjin no Maki</title>
<summary>58 million aliens that look exactly like Japanese people immigrate to Japan, causing a serious food shortage. An alien scientist Dohyar plans to take over Japan by making Japanese people small with cell-reducing fluid. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44361" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">169</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来人の贈り物の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gift from the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miraijin no Okurimono no Maki</title>
<summary>People on a time machine from the future leave something behind on earth. It turns out to be a dinosaur that existed in ancient times on Earth. Atom and Uran love the dinosaur and keep it as a pet, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44362" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">148</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロビオとロビエットの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robio and Robiet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robio to Robiet no Maki</title>
<summary>The Ijio family and the Yani family have been on bad terms for generations. The robots made by the doctors in each family also hate each other. Between these enemy families, however, a fragile love begins to grow, and...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44363" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">150</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">マグネットちゃんの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miss Magnet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magnet-chan no Maki</title>
<summary>Miss Magnet produces strong magnetic force when she laughs. One day a group of gangs abduct Dr. Tera, the one who created her. They are planning to rob a bank using Miss Magnet`s power.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44364" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">151</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">1人ぼっちのアトム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lonely Atom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no Atom</title>
<summary>Robot Pulse hypnotizes Dr. Ochanomizu to develop Lucky Machine, a machine that controls the human brain. Then people manipulated by its hypnotizing radio wave start to ignore Atom, leaving him all alone.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44365" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットポリマーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robot Polymer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Polymer no Maki</title>
<summary>Claiming to be the strongest robot in the world, the huge conceited robot Polymer makes a raid on Atom`s house. He tries to show that he is the strongest of all by defeating Atom, but...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44366" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">158</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかしな道づれの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funny Companion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashina Michizure no Maki</title>
<summary>There is a pair of handcuffs that are impossible to take off from a villain`s wrists unless he mends his ways. Atom gets handcuffed with a thief by accident, and has to go to jail with him because he cannot mend his ways.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44367" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">139</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">盗まれたアトムの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Astro Boy Stolen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nusumareta Atom no Maki</title>
<summary>It is an injustice that robots should never grow up, thinks a new scientist who has been appointed to the Science Ministry. He puts Atom`s artificial intelligence into the body of an adult robot. Meanwhile someone steals Atom`s body.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44368" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">191</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">さすらいのロッピの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wandering Roppi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasurai no Roppi no Maki</title>
<summary>Aliens attack a boy and an old man in the deep woods. After Atom saves them, he learns that the boy Roppi and the old man are also aliens. Roppi tells Atom that he is a prince and that he has run away from his planet.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44369" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">181</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊製造機の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Manufacturing Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuurei Seizouki no Maki</title>
<summary>Dictator Hiller takes Dr. Ochanomizu away, and tries to coerce the doctor into making Hiler clones on a massive scale in order to conquer the world. Atom heads to a country called Boruboa to rescue the doctor.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44370" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">188</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">鞍馬の天狗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tengu of Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurama no Tengu</title>
<summary>Robot Tomson, who has the ability to see through objects, sees that most statues of Buddha in Kyoto are fake. Then Atom and his fellows go searching for the real statues, and get surrounded by a group of long-nosed goblins.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44371" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">161</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢を売る宇宙人の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dream Selling Aliens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume o Uru Uchuujin no Maki</title>
<summary>The artificial intelligence of all robots goes awry because of some strange radio waves from space. Dr. Ochanomizu, at a loss as to what to do, has to make the difficult decision of cutting the energy supply of all robots...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44372" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">155</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂った国境線の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crazed Boundary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurutta Kokkyousen no Maki</title>
<summary>In a terrifying country called Libea, robots are under constant surveillance and are sent to an asylum if they disobey orders. Atom sneaks into the asylum to rescue the oppressed robots.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44373" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">121</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガニメート号の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prisoners in Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganimate Gou no Maki</title>
<summary>Atom and Dr. Ochanomizu wander into a space graveyard that lies outside every sphere of gravitation, drifting in space forever. Then an earthling named Bemski, who hates the Earth, rescues them, and...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44374" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">154</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い鳥物語の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Bird Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Tori Monogatari no Maki</title>
<summary>Whenever it hears small birds crying out for help, a robot named Blue Bird rescues them, sometimes even wrecking a building if necessary. Now Blue Bird is trying to rescue a small bird that has wandered into a nuclear power plant...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44375" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">123</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドッグ隊長の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captain Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dog Taichou no Maki</title>
<summary>Higeoyaji`s pet dog Pero has a diamond that it takes back from space. Then Dr. Fooler puts Pero`s memory into the computer of Captain Dog, the robot dog, to make it find diamonds. Atom follows the robot-dog, which is heading for Mars.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="88559" update="2008-03-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168979" update="2015-09-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">"Making Of" Documentary</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
