<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14410" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Chuubyou Gekihatsu Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">厨病激発ボーイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Outburst Dreamer Boys</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ثورة الفتيان الحالمين</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">厨病激发BOY</title>
</titles>
<url>http://chubyou.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="49099" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsuura Arisa</name>
<name id="58035" type="Music">Team Whim</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="49099" type="Character Design">Matsuura Arisa</name>
<name id="19087" type="Series Composition">Gotou Midori</name>
<name id="40326" type="Original Plan">Rerulili</name>
<name id="8886" type="Direction">Ichikawa Kazuya</name>
<name id="9098" type="Music">Technoboys Pulcraft Green-Fund</name>
<name id="57655" type="Original Work">Tonami Minato</name>
</creators>
<description>* An anime adaptation of a light novel by http://anidb.net/cr57655 [Tonami Minato] which is based on the song of the same name by Vocaloid producer http://anidb.net/cr40326 [Rerulili].
http://anidb.net/ch105497 [Hijiri Mizuki] just transferred schools, but her chances of having a quiet high school life shatter when she meets the eccentric members of the Hero Club! These "chunibyo" dudes and their youthful delusions of grandeur quickly sweep Mizuki into a world of outrageous hijinks and nonstop fantasy. http://anidb.net/ch105498 [Noda] dreams of becoming a hero. http://anidb.net/ch105499 [Takashima], resident otaku, longs to date only 2D girls. http://anidb.net/ch105495 [Tsukumo] fancies himself the school`s master manipulator. And then there`s http://anidb.net/ch105494 [Nakamura], a reincarnation of an angel... or a devil, depending on the day. Mizuki has her work cut out for her in the Hero Club, because while their delusions might be the stuff of fantasy, the trouble they cause is as real as it gets!
Source: Sentai Filmworks</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="126">3.35</permanent>
<temporary count="127">5.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236564.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21982</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://chubyou.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>厨病激発ボーイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5441</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367602</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22222</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>chubyou_p</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="105494" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="1">9.65</rating>
<name>Nakamura Kazuhiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46757" picture="224841.jpg">Kabumoto Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105495" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<name>Tsukumo Rei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238537.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33512" picture="225800.jpg">Enoki Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105496" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<name>Mikuriya Futaba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54151" picture="225419.jpg">Yasuda Rikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105497" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="2">5.97</rating>
<name>Hijiri Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105498" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Noda Yamato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105499" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<name>Takashima Tomoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47919" picture="207907.jpg">Nakamura Shuugo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106115" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-12">
<name>Ossan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106116" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-13">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Faust</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106117" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-13">
<rating votes="2">5.97</rating>
<name>Watase Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106118" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-18">
<name>Sora-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51369" picture="206416.jpg">Katahira Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106119" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-13">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Sekiya Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106255" type="appears in" update="2019-10-18">
<name>Yone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18222" picture="81718.jpg">Nagahama Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106256" type="appears in" update="2019-10-18">
<name>Kannushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108330" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Tsukumo Kaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108331" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Tsukumo Kanata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108332" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Tsukumo Tsukiho</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42258" picture="176599.jpg">Sakura Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108333" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Tsukumo Mikoto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34427" picture="128155.jpg">Aoki Ruriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108334" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Tsukumo Haruka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42258" picture="176599.jpg">Sakura Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108335" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Tsukumo Yukina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34427" picture="128155.jpg">Aoki Ruriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108336" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Benjamin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108337" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Shikai no Onee-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108338" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Kaijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4912" picture="172065.jpg">Mine Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108339" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Sora-chan Oshi no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244401.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108340" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Shoujo no Okaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34427" picture="128155.jpg">Aoki Ruriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108342" type="appears in" update="2020-02-11">
<name>Taiiku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244405.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108343" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Fukukaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40342" picture="192446.jpg">Toki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108344" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Shoki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34427" picture="128155.jpg">Aoki Ruriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108345" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Seito Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108357" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Yoshizumi Iinchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57159" picture="228654.jpg">Ono Masamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108358" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Izumi Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108359" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Okabe Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43500" picture="235807.jpg">Hirose Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108360" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Shimokawa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244435.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108361" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Suisougakubu Buchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32215" picture="223325.jpg">Sasamoto Natsue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108362" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Kateikabu Buchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42286" picture="167754.jpg">Tachibana Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108363" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Mankenbu Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221474" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そうさ 俺は目覚めてしまった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Right, I Have Awakened</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">هذا صحيح، لقد استيقظت</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sou sa Ore wa Mezameteshimatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221475" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使か悪魔の生まれ変わりか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reincarnation of an Angel or a Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">التجسيد الجديد لملاك أو شيطان</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi ka Akuma no Umarekawari ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221476" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">子供じゃないし大人でもない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neither a Kid nor an Adult</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليس طفلًا ولابالغ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodomo ja Nai shi Otona demo Nai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221477" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こじらせちゃってパンパカパッパッパーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Got a Complication, There`s a Fanfare in My Head</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kojirasechatte Panpakapappappaan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222670" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強大なチカラ 持ってしまった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Burdened with Great Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai na Chikara: Motteshimatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222671" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チラチラ視線感じてる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Sense Someone Glancing This Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chirachira Shisen Kanjiteru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222672" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンじゃないしone night love</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m No Pretty Boy and It`s a One Night Stand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen ja Nai shi: One Night Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222673" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">理想と現実の狭間で揺れてる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Swaying in the Gap Between Ideals and Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Risou to Genjitsu no Hazama de Yureteru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224337" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかけになった電話は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Number You`re Trying to Reach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okake ni Natta Denwa wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224338" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独と屁理屈の闇に紛れて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mingled in the Darkness of Solitude and Twisted Logic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku to Herikutsu no Yami ni Magirete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224339" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">放て俺のサーチライト!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Forth and Illuminate, Searchlight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanate Ore no Searchlight!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227893" update="2020-04-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">男に生まれた宿命だから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is the Destiny of Those Born as Men</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko ni Umareta Shukumei Dakara</title>
<summary>Hero Club gets a request from the Student Council to help out the lodging house caretaker. Upon arrival, they are met by an unexpected character.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
