<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14442" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ore o Suki na no wa Omae dake ka yo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Are You Really the Only One Who Likes Me</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">ORESUKI</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">俺を好きなのはお前だけかよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Oresuki: Are You the Only One Who Loves Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Єдина, хто кохає великого мене – це ти?!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">喜欢本大爷的竟然就你一个？</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15329" type="Sequel">Ore o Suki na no wa Omae dake ka yo: Oretachi no Game Set</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="813396">If you sympathize with the "Literally me" stereotype character, I guess you can possibly enjoy this? It`s paced weirdly but there`s good fan service if you`re into that.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://oresuki-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="56394" type="Series Composition">Rakuda</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="37485" type="Animation Work">Connect</name>
<name id="11391" type="Character Design">Takimoto Shouko</name>
<name id="11137" type="Direction">Akitaya Noriaki</name>
<name id="56394" type="Original Work">Rakuda</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr56394 [Rakuda] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr24691 [Buriki].
http://anidb.net/ch98513 [Kisaragi Amatsuyu] is invited out alone by the cool beauty upperclassman http://anidb.net/ch98512 [Cosmos] and his childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch98511 [Himawari]. Expecting to hear their confessions, he triumphantly goes to meet each of them in turn. But Cosmos and Himawari both instead confess to Amatsuyu that they like his friend. Amatsuyu fights this lonely battle, but there is another http://anidb.net/ch98514 [girl] who is looking at him. She is a gloomy girl with glasses and braids. Amatsuyu finds that he hates her, because she`s always turning her sharp tongue only on him and finding enjoyment in his troubles. But it turns out that she`s the only one who actually does like him.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="461">3.87</permanent>
<temporary count="467">5.88</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>237687.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21483</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40807</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>38483</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ore.ski/tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://oresukianime-usa.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Oresuki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>俺を好きなのはお前だけかよ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5415</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365770</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22244</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oresuki_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5679" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>machiavellian intrigues</name>
<description>Named after Niccolò di Bernardo dei Machiavelli (3 May 1469 - 21 June 1527). Machiavelli is considered one of the founders of modern political science, and was a philosopher and diplomat.
He is famous for his political treatise `The Prince`, which is essentially a manual about the acquisition and maintenance of power, including the need for deceit and the application of armed force.
It is the use of deceit from which the term `Machievellian` derives. This term generally applies to a person who uses deceit to manipulate others for their own amoral (and usually power hungry) ends.
This anime contains at least one character whose intrigues drive the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5944" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-28">
<name>i got a crush on you</name>
<description>It happens when a person develops an interest in someone that seems mysterious, smart, sexy, cute, fun, etc. Basically just someone you would like to spend more time with. Crushes are usually one sided and they happen more frequently among middle and high school students.
A person with a crush usually has a hard time expressing or conveying his/her feelings to that other person. That other person is usually clueless of the situation. Sometimes that person knows about the crush, but feels annoyed or embarrassed by it for some reason.
Having a crush on someone does not mean you are in love with that person, at least not yet. Depending on the situation crushes could develop differently (for better or worse):
1) Larger scale interactions (love).
2) Dating relationships.
3) Scary obsession or stalker type situations.
4) Disappear over time or distance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5956" parentid="2862" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>broken friendship</name>
<description>For a broken friendship a group of three friends is a must, the break up can be caused by betrayal or death, a love triangle is also possible. The ghost of the old friendship will be the cause of many flashbacks and reminiscences. A dreaded face to face could be a major event or just used as plot device.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="98511" type="main character in" update="2019-10-02">
<rating votes="7">3.84</rating>
<name>Hinata Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33578" picture="225440.jpg">Shiraishi Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98512" type="main character in" update="2019-10-02">
<rating votes="11">5.95</rating>
<name>Akino Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2903" picture="23287.jpg">Misawa Sachika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98513" type="main character in" update="2019-10-02">
<rating votes="4">1.67</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Amatsuyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98514" type="main character in" update="2019-10-02">
<rating votes="18">5.45</rating>
<name>Sanshokuin Sumireko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105490" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-27">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Charisma-gun A-ko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44275" picture="228532.jpg">Saitou Shuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105491" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-02">
<rating votes="3">2.44</rating>
<name>Ooga Taiyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38579" picture="225249.jpg">Uchida Yuuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105492" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-27">
<rating votes="7">4.93</rating>
<name>Youki Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105493" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-23">
<rating votes="7">5.23</rating>
<name>Hanetachi Hina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106395" type="main character in" update="2019-10-23">
<rating votes="13">5.60</rating>
<name>Sanshokuin Sumireko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106908" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="4">6.28</rating>
<name>Kamata Kimie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55415" picture="232227.jpg">Saeki Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107164" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-27">
<rating votes="6">7.80</rating>
<name>Mayama Asaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44275" picture="228532.jpg">Saitou Shuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107165" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-03">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Sakurahara Momo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107166" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-03">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Kusami Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48852" picture="225071.jpg">Kohara Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107167" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-03">
<rating votes="1">4.49</rating>
<name>Hazuki Yasuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108356" type="appears in" update="2020-02-13">
<name>Kisaragi Keiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221405" update="2019-10-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕ってほんと, どこにでもいる平凡な高校生なんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Really Just an Ordinary High School Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutte Honto, Doko ni demo Iru Heibon na Koukousei Nan Da</title>
<summary>My super-energetic childhood friend, Himawari, and the beautiful, mature student council president, Cosmos, have asked me out on a date? Wait, why am I giving them romantic advise? What about my beautiful harem love comedy? Well, it`s time to witness the end of the peaceful rom-com story.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789385</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221406" update="2019-10-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺に襲い掛かる負のスパイラル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Attacked by an Impossible Spiral</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ni Osoikakaru Fu no Spiral</title>
<summary>Who would`ve thought my dream of a high school life would run off the rails and go down a thorny path so quickly, all because of an improbable "double confession of love"? Oh, hello. I`m Joro. Don`t worry! I haven`t given up on the idea of a "harem high school life" just yet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789386</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221407" update="2019-10-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺はお前と会っていた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Was Meeting You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Omae to Atte Ita</title>
<summary>It`s over. It`s all over. One misunderstanding led to the next and now both Himawari and Cosmos are disgusted with me.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789387</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221408" update="2019-10-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺がガンバった結果</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Results of My Hard Work</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حصيلة جهدي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Ganbatta Kekka</title>
<summary>With the "mastermind" exposed and the misunderstandings about my "evil deeds" cleared up to the student body`s satisfaction, my peaceful everyday life resumes. But there`s still something I haven`t gotten back!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789388</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222507" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺にしては, うまくいきすぎてると思ったんだよ......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Thought It Was Working Out Too Well for Me</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ظننت أن الأمور تسير على ما يرام في نظري......</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ni Shite wa, Umaku Ikisugiteru to Omottanda yo......</title>
<summary>The exciting springtime of my life! I`m surrounded by beautiful giggling, jiggling girls! Wait, what the hell is this? Hey, Asunaro, you`re with the newspaper club! What`s this about me being the "enemy of all women" and going out with Himawari, Cosmos, and Pansy at the same time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789389</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222508" update="2019-11-07">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺は, 言う時は言う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When I Need to Say Something, I`ll Say It</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حينما أريد أن أقول شيئًا ما، فسوف أقوله</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore wa, Iu Toki wa Iu</title>
<summary>If there is a "god of inconvenience," he must love me! One minor slip-up and the "Three-timing Joro" article was circulated all over the school! I was back in the pit of despair when who should yank me out but the author of the article herself, Asunaro of the newspaper club.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790233</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222509" update="2019-11-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺は意外な一面を知る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Discover an Unexpected Side</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">اكتشفت جانبًا لم يكن في الحسبان</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore wa Igai na Ichimen o Shiru</title>
<summary>At last, the time has come! With the Flower Dance accomplished, we get a deserving day off. And there`s only one place to go! That`s right, a pool!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790234</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222510" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の悲劇は気づくと始まってる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Before I Knew It, My Tragedy Had Already Begun</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مأساتي قد بدأت، قبل أن أدرك ذلك حتى</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore non Higeki wa Kizuku to Hajimatteru</title>
<summary>"From now on I`ll do everything I can for you with all my heart." That`s what the new girl at school said to me! Finally a kind girl appears before me… Yeah, right!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790235</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224317" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺なりに考えた結果</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Conclusion After Much Consideration</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">استنتاجي بعد تفكير عميق</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore Nari ni Kangaeta Kekka</title>
<summary>I start working at Tsubaki`s shop so I can afford to buy Pansy another copy of her book! It`s rough since I`m not used to the job, but at this rate, I should be able to manage… Ahhh! I messed up big time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790236</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224318" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺だってたまには活躍する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even I`m Useful Once in a While</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore Datte Tama ni wa Katsuyaku Suru</title>
<summary>Now what does this dummy want? Baseball team manager Kimie Kamata (nickname: Tampopo) suddenly drags me into the science lab. You probably think she`s a cute girl since she`s got a flower nickname, right? Well, that’s true. Tampopo is cute… but… but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790238</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224319" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺はいらないかもしれない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I May Not Be Needed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore wa Iranai kamo Shirenai</title>
<summary>It`s been decided that the school library will close for lack of people who use it! Cosmos did her best to stop it, but it wasn`t enough. But apparently, if the library gets more traffic from students, it`ll be saved!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790239</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224320" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が好きなのは......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One I Love Is...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Suki na no wa......</title>
<summary>Huh? What are you talking about, Pansy? You already have someone who`s promised to be your boyfriend? And it`s…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790240</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224780" recap="true" update="2020-01-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別編 ~俺は丁寧に進める~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Episode: I Politely Move Things Forward</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Hen: Ore wa Teinei ni Susumeru</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790237</identifier>
<identifier>oresuki-are-you-the-only-one-who-loves-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
