<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1444" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>38</episodecount>
<startdate>1985-06-07</startdate>
<enddate>1986-02-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou no Star Magical Emi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">魔法のスターマジカルエミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magic Star Magical Emi</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Звездата на магията Меджикъл Еми</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Pierrot Mahou Shoujo Series 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法のスター マジカルエミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Star Magician Magical Emi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Émi Magique</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Magica Magica Emi</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">La magia de Emi</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3633" type="Side Story">Adesugata Mahou no Sannin Musume</anime>
<anime id="7430" type="Side Story">Mahou no Star Magical Emi: Kumo Hikaru</anime>
<anime id="7072" type="Summary">Mahou no Star Magical Emi Finale! Finale! Soushuuhen</anime>
<anime id="5376" type="Other">Mahou no Star Magical Emi Semishigure</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2729" approval="3" total="5">Tokimeki Tonight</anime>
<anime id="246" approval="3" total="3">Mahou no Stage Fancy Lala</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/title/emi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1668" type="Chief Direction">Kobayashi Osamu</name>
<name id="5136" type="Character Design">Kishi Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="5654" type="Music">Oku Keiichi</name>
<name id="4252" type="Direction">Annou Takashi</name>
<name id="8481" type="Character Design">Motoyama Kouji</name>
<name id="5416" type="Direction">Kogawa Yoriyasu</name>
<name id="4149" type="Series Composition">Watanabe Mami</name>
<name id="8604" type="Series Composition">Konishikawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="4127" type="Work">Nunokawa Yuuji</name>
</creators>
<description>Katsuki Mai is the young daughter of a couple who run a small snack shop, while her grandparents lead a troupe of stage magicians called the "Magicalettes". She idolizes a legendary stage magician named Emily Howell and, when her grandparents move in just down the street, she seizes the opportunity to follow in her idol`s footsteps. Unfortunately, since she`s young and inexperienced (and clumsy, to boot), she`s not very good at magic tricks, although the troupe is happy to let her help out, and even allow her to appear on stage as an assistant for their act.
While helping her grandparents move in, she notices a strange, floating light (a Will `O Wisp) and follows it upstairs. There, she sees many lights appear INSIDE a mirror, along with many reflections of herself. Suddenly, a bracelet appears on her wrist, and a stuffed flying squirrel named Topo comes to life and explains to her that the bracelet is a gift which will allow her to transform &amp; do REAL magic.
One day during a performance, Topo causes a disaster, and Mai has no choice but to transform into Magical Emi (a name she chooses in honor of her idol) a young woman with short green hair who amazes the crowd with feats of magic, and saves the show. Magical Emi is also seen by a TV producer named Kogane-san, who happened to be in the audience. He runs JTV, and soon contracts the troupe (including Magical Emi) to appear on his TV station. Mai strives to achieve her dream of becoming a REAL stage magician, without the "cheat" of using real magic to perform her tricks.
This was the third of the four famous 1980s magical girl series created by Studio Pierrot, those being Creamy Mami, Pelsia, Magical Emi, and Pastel Yumi.
Edited from http://shoujo.tripod.com/emikasha.html</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="84">4.32</permanent>
<temporary count="85">6.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>225883.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2038</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1457</identifier>
<identifier>wjujve</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/title/emi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magical_Emi,_the_Magic_Star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法のスターマジカルエミ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89271</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1281</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/595</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1985/magical_emi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="183" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-25">
<name>boxing</name>
<description>Boxing is a combat sport in which two people, usually wearing protective gloves, throw punches at each other for a predetermined set of time in a boxing ring.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29018" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Kazuki Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24139">Aoki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29426" type="main character in" update="2011-03-02">
<rating votes="10">5.54</rating>
<name>Kazuki Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18718" picture="49351.jpg">Obata Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29427" type="main character in" update="2011-11-21">
<rating votes="20">6.29</rating>
<name>Magical Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18718" picture="49351.jpg">Obata Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29428" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Yuuki Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3272" picture="172136.jpg">Mizushima Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29430" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Topo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29431" type="appears in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Nakamori Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29432" type="appears in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Nakamori Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3713" picture="25079.jpg">Mine Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29433" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Kazuki Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="599" picture="226547.jpg">Naya Rokurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29434" type="appears in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Kazuki Misaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3936" picture="245652.jpg">Mita Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29435" type="appears in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Koganei Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8" picture="171393.jpg">Ikura Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29436" type="appears in" update="2011-03-02">
<name>Koganei Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9679" picture="203641.jpg">Komiya Kazue</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="15524" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふしぎ誕生魔法のスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Birth of a Magical Star</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une merveille est née - L`Étoile magique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi Tanjou Mahou no Star</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15525" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あいつの好きなボクシング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Beloved Boxing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune homme qui aimait la boxe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aitsu no Suki na Boxing</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15526" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法でデビュー! 生放送!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Magical Debut... Live on TV!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les débuts d`une magicienne !! L`émission en direct !!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou de Debut! Namahousou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15527" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議色ハピネス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Color of Wonder, Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fushigi-iro Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi-iro Happiness</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21754" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨のたなばたファンタジー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Star Festival Fantasy in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pluvieux festival de Tanabata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame no Tanabata Fantasy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22707" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スターの輝きを秘めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holding Shinings of a Star in Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cachant le scintillement de l`Étoile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Star no Kagayaki o Himete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22846" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏休み家庭科入門</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Home Ec. Primer During Summer Break</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Initiation aux travaux ménagers pendant les vacances d`été</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24330" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボクシングなんて大嫌い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hate Boxing!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je déteste la boxe !</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24331" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海辺のベストキッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Best Kid on the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le meilleur garçon du bord de mer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27604" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高原列車UFOはどこ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Highland Train: Where Is the UFO?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le train de la montagne - Où est l`O.V.N.I. !?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33710" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密のスターライフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Life of a Star</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vie secrète d`une star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu no Star Life</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50922" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら夢色マジシャン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au revoir, magicienne des rêves colorés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Yume-iro Magician</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51882" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お風呂場でドッキリ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choc de la salle de bain !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ofuroba de Dokkiri!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52231" recap="true" update="2009-10-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわいい訪問者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un charmant visiteur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaii Houmonsha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53494" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏は光色のメモリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Is Glowing-colored Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`été est la mémoire des étincelles colorées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu wa Hikari-iro no Memory</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53495" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">家庭教師は16才</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tutor Is 16 Years Old</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le précepteur âgé de 16 ans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kateikyoushi wa 16-sai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53496" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">こてまり台花のステージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kotemaridai`s Flowery Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le théâtre des fleurs de Kotemaridaï</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotemaridai Hana no Stage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53497" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風が残したかざぐるま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pinwheel the Wind Left Behind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fée Éole</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53498" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきパワフルドライバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wonderful Powerful Driver</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un magnifique et puissant chauffeur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki Powerful Driver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53499" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">気分はゆれて学園祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wavering Feelings, the School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon sentiment d`anxiété à la fête de l`école</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53500" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法の光に夢を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magic Light of Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">... Un rêve vers la lumière magique</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53501" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガラス越しのロマンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romance Through the Glass</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Romance à travers la vitrine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53502" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険なシャッターチャンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Shutter Chance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dangereux objectif</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53503" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれ! ドキドキゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go for it! Thrilling Game!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bonne chance ! Le jeu de la course du cœur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53504" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">からっと秋風心もよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon esprit est tel une douce brise d`automne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53505" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごめんねミーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je suis désolé, grande sœur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53506" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鈴の音よもう一度</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La clochette tinte une fois encore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53507" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">枯葉のシャワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pluie de feuilles mortes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53508" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">国分寺さん殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`affaire criminelle de monsieur Chronométré</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53509" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツキが落ちれば陽が昇る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coucher de Lune, lever de Soleil</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53510" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪景色・夢の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Scène de la neige : le pays des rêves</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53511" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワイン色のパーティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête du vin coloré</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53512" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲よし夫婦のギザギザ模様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La dispute d`un couple d`amoureux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53513" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べ! スノードラゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vole ! Snow Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobe! Snow Dragon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53514" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と哀しみのカリントウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Karinto de l`amour et du chagrin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Kanashimi no Karintou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53515" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精の森へようこそ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue dans la forêt de diamants</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei no Mori e Youkoso!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53516" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">北風にひとりぼっち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vent du nord de la solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitakaze ni Hitoribocchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53517" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ためらいの季節</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La saison de l`hésitation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamerai no Kisetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150846" update="2013-05-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>1992-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミュージック・クリップ 「風のinvitation」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Clip - Invitation of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Music Clip "Kaze no Invitation"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150847" update="2013-05-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法少女フェスティバル用 「ごめんなさいフィルム」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic for girls Festival "sorry film"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Shoujo Festival-you "Gomennasai Film"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167436" update="2015-04-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1985-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167453" update="2015-04-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1985-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
