<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14454" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-13</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tsuujou Kougeki ga Zentai Kougeki de Nikai Kougeki no Okaasan wa Suki Desuka?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">momsekai</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Мамка-попаданка</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">twohitmom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">okasuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">okaa-san online</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">通常攻撃が全体攻撃で二回攻撃のお母さんは好きですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Do You Love Your Mom and Her Two-Hit Multi-Target Attacks?</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">普通攻击是全体二连击，这样的妈妈你喜欢吗？</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="39" approval="3" total="10">Slayers</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="813396">It`s an Isekai, it`s nothing great, nothing terrible, but highly contrived. Decent fan service; I`d wait for the Blu-Rays though for uncensored versions.

Pochi`s Art does make this more tolerable to watch and the Studio did a good job of adapting her work.

Now all we have to do is wait for "Ane Naru Mono".</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="14899">Aside from other recommendations, the premise was something new and very interesting. After completing the series, I had wished the son had a bigger role with powers and strength than to always be carried by the mother. Overall its funny, entertaining, and really don`t worry about the mother incest warning, son only fell on a naked mom once by accident ;)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://okaasan-online.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="22244" type="Character Design">Yaegashi Youhei</name>
<name id="4556" type="Series Composition">Akao Deko</name>
<name id="56530" type="Original Work">Inaka Dachima</name>
<name id="1797" type="Direction">Iwasaki Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="27275" type="Music">Inai Keiji</name>
<name id="4511" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="22244" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yaegashi Youhei</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr56530 [Inaka Dachima] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr56531 [Iida Pochi.].
What would you do if you got transported into a video game...with your mom?? That`s the dilemma facing high schooler http://anidb.net/ch98793 [Oosuki Masato], who has been unwittingly thrown into an RPG world with his doting http://anidb.net/ch98792 [mother] close behind as part of a secret government scheme. As an avid gamer, Masato is eager to show off his skills...but that`s hard to do when your mom is an insanely overpowered, dual-wielding, multi-target specialist!
Source: Yen Press</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="483">2.24</permanent>
<temporary count="492">5.03</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233510.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21508</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38573</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://okaasan-online.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://twohitmom-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Do_You_Love_Your_Mom_and_Her_Two-Hit_Multi-Target_Attacks%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>通常攻撃が全体攻撃で二回攻撃のお母さんは好きですか%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5346</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365845</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22117</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>okaasan_online</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2740" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>mother-son incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between a mother and her son.</description>
<picurl>210876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1000" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-09-22">
<rating votes="1994">9.10</rating>
<name>Lina Inverse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lina Inverse is the primary protagonist and the only character appearing in the whole Slayers-franchise. She is an adolescent but very powerful sorceress, with a great love for money, treasure and food. In the anime and manga (but not in the light novel) Lina uses overly destructive magic recklessly, often with little provocation. She is reputed to be an evil, powerful, destructive, diminutive sorceress (the evil part is arguably not true, though one may consider her greed and general lack of concern for others unless they are in danger of being killed can be considered "evil").
Lina has gained many different nicknames, including "Bandit Killer" and "Dragon Spooker", neither of which she`s very fond of, though to her, her most embarrassing nickname is "Lina the Pink" which is her official title amongst the sorcerer`s guild.</description>
<picture>161200.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98792" type="main character in" update="2019-03-23">
<rating votes="15">7.41</rating>
<name>Oosuki Mamako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98793" type="main character in" update="2019-03-23">
<rating votes="3">1.64</rating>
<name>Oosuki Masato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101573" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-15">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Porta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47245" picture="224994.jpg">Harada Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101574" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-23">
<rating votes="8">7.08</rating>
<name>Medhi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101575" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-29">
<rating votes="8">7.34</rating>
<name>Wise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55692" picture="224737.jpg">Suzushiro Sayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101576" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-23">
<rating votes="6">7.38</rating>
<name>Shirase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="217963" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年の壮大なる冒険が始まると思ってたら... え, どういうことだよこれ....</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy Thought He Was Embarking on a Great Adventure... but, Uh, What`s Going on Here?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen no Soudai naru Bouken ga Hajimaru to Omottetara... E, Dou Iu Koto Da yo Kore....</title>
<summary>Teenage boy Masato Oosuki was chosen to beta test a new MMORPG, where you’re actually teleported inside the world of the game. After Masumi Shirase comes to give him a brief explanation, he’s off to start a new life inside a video game! But once he gets there, he finds his mother, Mamako, has followed him.  He’s bewildered, but Mamako is overjoyed at the idea of going on an adventure with her son. And her regular attack skill is incredibly strong, too. Masato’s attack skill only has regular power, and as a normal rebellious teenager, he’s more than a little upset to find his grand fantasy adventure ruined. And thus begins a new RPG journey, with mom in tow!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787258</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217964" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女子ばっかなのは偶然だ. 誤解するな. 笑顔でこっちを見るな.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Just a Coincidence They`re All Girls. Got That? Wipe That Smirk Off Your Face.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joshi Bakka na no wa Guuzen Da. Goukai Suruna. Egao de Kocchi o Miruna.</title>
<summary>Mamako and Masato are now registered as hero and mommy, and they decide to have an interview to decide who’ll join their party. Porter, a tiny merchant girl who comes to the interview, is a nice, kind-looking girl, so she’s allowed to join. The next girl on the list is the sage, Wise. Masato gets a bad feeling from her photograph and tries to get rid of it, but the photograph was actually Wise, herself, who had transformed into a sheet of paper. She gets mad at how she was treated and teleports Masato outside the city. When the two of them are alone, she tells him that the goal of this RPG is for mother and child to become closer. That’s why Mamako is so strong, and why she was brought to this world with him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787259</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217965" update="2019-07-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">下着は防具. 守備面積は大きめに. さもなくば息子が死ぬぞ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underwear Is Armor. Make Sure It`s High in Defense. Otherwise, My Son Might Die!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitagi wa Bougu. Shubi Menseki wa Ookime ni. Samonakuba Musuko ga Shinuzo!</title>
<summary>Wise joins the party, which gets ready to head off to the village of Maman on a special quest that Shirase gave them. But first, they have to buy equipment. Mamako is overjoyed at the idea of going shopping with her son. At the armor shop, she tries on a variety of scanty outfits for Masato, which is something that he does not enjoy. He lectures her that she’s getting too excited, and makes everything awkward. But Mamako manages to make up with her son by cleaning out his ears. The party makes it to the village, where they learn that a demon called “The Empress of Night” is demanding the village’s hottest guys as a sacrifice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787260</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217966" update="2019-08-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">子供は子供で, 親も親で人間で, 色々あるけど何とかするのが親子だろ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kids Are Kids and Parents Are Parents but Also Human Beings, and It Takes All Kinds, but They Get Through It Together, Right?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodomo wa Kodomo de, Oya mo Oya de Ningen de, Iroiro Aru kedo Nantoka Suru no ga Oyako Daro.</title>
<summary>The “Empress of Night” turns out to be none other than Wise’s mother, who she split up with after a fight. When the two of them went their separate ways, the Empress decided to stop playing the game and instead go chasing after attractive men. And since she was using a powerful cheating tool that could change how the system worked, even Shirase and the GM’s couldn’t stop her. Normally, she’d face a huge fine for breaking the license agreement, but if Wise can make up with her, Shirase is willing to let it slide. When she sees her mom flying around on a throne made of shirtless men, Wise is incredibly embarrassed. She agrees to Shirase’s plan, and the rest of the party agrees to help, too.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787261</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218664" update="2019-07-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218665" update="2020-03-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219017" update="2019-08-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そこは夢と希望に満ちた, 子供達の領域. 子供達の, だ. ここ大事!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is a Territory for Children, Filled with Hopes and Dreams. For Children. That`s the Important Part!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soko wa Yume to Kibou ni MIchita, Kodomo-tachi no Ryouiki. Kodomo-tachi no, Da. Koko Daiji!</title>
<summary>Masato, Wise, and Porta become students at Lover’s Lane Academia. Studying here will give them lots of SP and tons of special items. At school they meet a sweet and shy healer named Medhi, and Masato is convinced he’s found the true heroine. But her mother, Medhimama, who treats them all like dirt. And what’s worse, she goes to class and uses her magic to stop anyone else from answering questions, so that Medhi gets all the SP. Wise and Porta both suggest to Masato that the way to beat one mom is to use another, and want to bring in Mamako to help, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787262</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219018" update="2019-08-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんという美少女... いや母さんじゃなくて. その格好で近寄るなやめろ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What a Beautiful Girl... Wait, Not You, Mom. Don`t Get Near Me in That Outfit, Stop!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nan to Iu Bishoujo... Iya Kaasan ja Nakute. Sono Kakkou de Chikayoru na Yamero.</title>
<summary>With Shirase’s help, Mamako is allowed to attend the school as well. Just like Medhimama, she becomes an observer in Masato’s class. When Medhimama finds out that her magic doesn’t work on Mamako, she decides that Mamako is her new rival. And to make things worse, Mamako joins in the school’s cooking class, and wears an old-style school swimsuit to the swimming class, unknowing stealing the spotlight from Medhi and her mom. Medhimama confidently shows off her sexy swimsuit, but gets even madder where Mamako steals the spotlight again. Masato hears someone angrily whispering insults as they watch Medhimama...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787263</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219019" update="2019-08-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学祭の主役は学生だ. それはただ制服を着ている人も含まれてしまうのだがな....</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Students Are the Protagonists of a School Festival. But People Wearing School Uniforms Are Included, Too.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakusai no Shuyaku wa Gakusei Da. Sore wa Tada Seifuku o Kite Iru Hito mo Fukumarete Shimau no Da ga na....</title>
<summary>The person who’d been whispering her hate about Medhimama was actually Medhi herself. Medhi was loyally doing what her mother told her to, but was secretly feeling extremely stressed and angry. When Masato and his mom find out about this, they decide they want to help her. Meanwhile, the school holds a festival, and parents are allowed to participate. The group decides to open a small café where Mamako will cook. Medhimama opens a café of her own, and insists on competing with Mamako to see who can sell more. Mamako reluctantly agrees, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787264</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219020" update="2019-08-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">言わなきゃ伝わらないが, 言ったらかなりの確率でぶつかる. 厄介だよ, 親子.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If I Say Nothing, It Won`t Be Heard, but If I Say Something, It`ll Be a Critical Hit. It Sucks Being a Family.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iwanakya Tsutawaranai ga, Ittara Kanari no Kakuritsu de Butsukaru. Yakkai Da yo, Oyako.</title>
<summary>Medhi was able to say what she felt about her mom when Masato was around, but in front of her mother, she always forced herself to act obedient. Wise and Porta both try to cheer her up and be her friend, but Medhimama, who wants a good daughter so that she can become “the number one mom”, refuses to let her have any friends. When Medhi realizes that her mother’s fanatacism was just for the sake of her own ego, she breaks down, lets her feelings loose, and becomes a powerful dragon. The party tries to stop her, but even in the middle of the fight, Medhimama is so obsessed with being number one that she challanges Mamako to a duel!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787265</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219717" update="2019-09-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おっと, こんなところにスイッチ床があるぞ. まあ踏まないけど. いや踏まないから.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whoa, There`s a Pressure Plate in a Place Like This. Well, I`m Not Stepping on It. No, I`m Saying I Won`t!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otto, Konna Tokoro ni Switch Toko ga Aruzo. Maa Fumanai kedo. Iya Fumanai kara.</title>
<summary>Medhi decides to come along with Masato and the party. They all get a notice about a new “tower dungeon”, which will grant any wish to those who can get to the top. The party heads to the town of Ommym, where the dungeon awaits. As soon as they arrive, a group of mothers begs them to look for their children. Shirase says that this isn’t part of any event, however. They decide to investigate the dungeon  with her. As they get past the traps and the monsters, they’re met by a woman dressed like a gladiator.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787266</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219718" update="2019-09-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お母さんと一緒ギルドは千客万来! ......って, 招かれざる客ばっかかよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The With Mommy Guild Welcomes All! ...Wait, It`s a Bunch of Uninvited Guests!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaasan to Issho Guild wa Senkakubanrai! ......tte, Manekarezaru Kyaku Bakka ka yo!</title>
<summary>The girl who stood in the party’s way announced herself as “Amante, Betrayer of Mothers”, and told them that she belonged to the rebel group "Ribele". She also told them that she’d gotten the adventurers in town to join her party and help her clear the dungeon. She told them all this despite the fact that they hadn’t asked her any of it. The party decided that it needed lots of help to free the adventurers from Amante, and retreated. They opened the “With Mommy” guild, and began to recruit. But Amante’s helper, Pocchi, came to stop them. He and his buddies made a certain demand of Mamako, and told her that if she didn’t do what they wanted,  they’d use bombs to blow up the city!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787267</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219719" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">受け止める勇気. 慈しむ心. あと全身鎧. それが母親に必須の......ん? 鎧?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Courage to Accept Things. A Loving Heart. Also, Full-Body Armor. That`s What a Mother Needs... Wait, Armor?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uketomeru Yuuki. Itsukushimu Kokoro. Ato Zenshin Yoroi. Sore ga Hahaoya ni Hissu no......n? Yoroi?</title>
<summary>After being touched by Mamako’s motherly kindness, Pocchi and his friends changed their ways and went home to their mothers. As a way of saying thank you, the mothers agree to join the With Mommy guild, and help the party clear the tower. There are still a lot of children who are working for Amante. And so the party, now filled with mothers, heads off to the tower, gossiping and chatting all the way. When this not-very-adventurous party makes it inside the dungeon, they’re met by Amante,  who’s gotten sick of waiting for them. She challenges Mamako to… a washing and cleaning contest?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787268</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219720" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その願いは叶えないでくれ, と強く願った. だが願いは叶えられた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hoped Against Hope the Wish Would Not Be Granted. But It Totally Was.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Negai wa Kanaenaide Kure, to Tsuyoku Negatta. Daga Negai wa Kanaerareta.</title>
<summary>Masato’s party makes their way up the tower. They meet Pocchi on the way up, who tells them that Amante’s plan is to clear the dungeon and wish for all mothers to disappear. They have to stop her! Meanwhile, Amante has made it to the top of the 100 floor tower, and defeated the last boss, but she can’t get into the wish-granting room. Masato’s party arrives and challenges her to a duel. During the middle of the battle, Amante tells Mamako that her presence here is stealing away her son’s future! Mamako is caught off guard. But instead, Masato…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787269</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227613" update="2020-03-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波打ち際のお母さんは好きですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="zh">在海岸邊的媽媽 你喜歡嗎？</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Love Your Mom on the Shore?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namiuchigiwa no Okaasan wa Suki Desuka?</title>
<summary>To thank the group for all their hard work in the past, Shirase invites the party to enjoy the sunny beach. While enjoying the wonderful weather and pristine waters, and accident causes Masato to lose all his memories, including those of Mamako!
Source: FUNimation</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787270</identifier>
<identifier>do-you-love-your-mom-and-her-two-hit-multi-target-attacks</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
