<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14476" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Darwin`s Game</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ダーウィンズゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Darwin`s Game</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Игра Дарвина</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">لعبة داروين</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">達爾文遊戲</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">达尔文游戏</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9249" approval="14" total="18">Btooom!</anime>
<anime id="8395" approval="12" total="15">Mirai Nikki (2011)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="498162">The story is fun to watch, but it fails to deliver and ends almost right where the main story line starts.  I would recommend that if you kind of like the story and want to find out what happens, read the manga.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://darwins-game.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59440" type="Series Composition">Miyama Hide</name>
<name id="2435" type="Music">Suehiro Ken`ichirou</name>
<name id="16170" type="Direction">Tokumoto Yoshinobu</name>
<name id="27754" type="Original Work">Flipflops</name>
<name id="8677" type="Character Design">Nakanishi Kazuya</name>
<name id="41906" type="Animation Work">Nexus</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a survival shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr27754 [Flipflops].
An unpredictable battle of superpowers.
http://anidb.net/ch106564 [Sudou Kaname], an ordinary high school student, receives an invitation email to try a mysterious app called "Darwin`s Game." Kaname, upon launching the app, is drawn into a game where players fight one another using superpowers called Sigils. Without knowing the reason for all this, can Kaname survive furious battles against the powerful players who attack him?
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="339">4.79</permanent>
<temporary count="344">6.37</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>241574.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22301</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38656</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://darwinsgame-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://darwins-game.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Darwin's_Game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ダーウィンズゲーム</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5515</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366082</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22443</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>d_game_official</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2620" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-21">
<name>battle royale</name>
<description>Many characters are removed from their normal lives or lifestyles and thrown into a game where they are forced to battle each other until one survivor remains. Much like the famous film `Battle Royale`.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3833" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>there can be only one</name>
<description>The long-term plot of the program revolves around a group of characters whose numbers are being slowly whittled away by one means or another, usually by killing each other. In the case of some reality shows, this is a process of elimination intended to result in a single winner. In other shows, this is a dramatic device, designed to generate tension and conflict with which to drive the overall plot of an episode or Story Arc (if any); in these cases it is sometimes combined with Anyone Can Die to especially heighten the resulting excitement, even when the apparent main character may be protected by Contractual Immortality. Compare Gotta Kill Them All.
Named for one of the catchphrases that came out of the Highlander franchise.
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="106564" type="main character in" update="2019-12-09">
<rating votes="3">6.45</rating>
<name>Sudou Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106565" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-14">
<rating votes="15">3.44</rating>
<name>Karino Shuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106566" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-09">
<rating votes="4">6.32</rating>
<name>Sui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106567" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-09">
<name>Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106568" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-09">
<rating votes="2">3.64</rating>
<name>Maesaka Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106569" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-09">
<rating votes="9">8.13</rating>
<name>Kashiwagi Rein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39890" picture="161176.jpg">Oomori Nichika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107812" type="appears in" update="2020-01-03">
<name>Kyouda Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="54588" picture="228753.jpg">Kobayashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107813" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-03">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Katsura Keiichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="20273" picture="175422.jpg">Kijima Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107814" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-03">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Shinozuka Youta</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="44099" picture="225101.jpg">Ochiai Fukushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107815" type="appears in" update="2020-01-03">
<name>Hamada</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="43500" picture="235807.jpg">Hirose Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107816" type="appears in" update="2020-01-03">
<name>Banda-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107817" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-03">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>One</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225445" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初陣[ファーストゲーム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Game</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">اللعبة الأولى</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Game</title>
<summary>One day, high school student Kaname Sudo’s average life is interrupted by the arrival of an emailed invitation to join “Darwin’s Game.” Without even thinking, he opens the app, thereby becoming a player in the game. Just as Kaname begins to suspect there’s more to the shady app than meets the eye, his first battle suddenly begins, with a mysterious man in a panda suit lunging at him with a butcher knife. 
Will Kaname survive his first, desperate battle against a bloodthirsty killer?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793308</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225446" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渋谷[ジェムストーンマイン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gemstone Mine</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">منجم الأحجار الكريمة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gemstone Mine</title>
<summary>Kaname defeats Banda the rookie hunter and even claims a victory over Shuka “The Undefeated Queen.” After Shuka explains the rules of the game to him, they agree to join forces in their future battles. Together, they explore Shibuya and scope out the battlegrounds to prepare for the upcoming in-game event.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793309</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225447" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">引き金[イグニッション]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ignition</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">اشتعال</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ignition</title>
<summary>The Treasure Hunt Game begins. The rules of the game are simple: find the rings hidden around the city of Shibuya. Kaname is teleported to a hotel and tries to escape its grounds to search for Shuka, but he is pursued by a battle hungry player and finds himself trapped inside. With the building sealed off, he meets a young girl who calls herself Rein.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793310</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225448" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火花[ファイアーワークス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ألعاب نارية</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fireworks</title>
<summary>Kaname and Rein discover that the Florist is watching their every move with the building’s surveillance cameras. They join forces to undermine his plans by destroying the cameras while evading his henchmen. Unable to escape the henchmen, they decide on a desperate strategy that leaves them with only a twenty percent chance of survival!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793311</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226197" recap="true" update="2020-02-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶[ログライン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Log Line</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Log Line</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226198" update="2020-03-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">金剛[ハードネス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hardness</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">صلابة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hardness</title>
<summary>Kaname and Ryuji arrive at the origin point of Shuka’s message. Not hesitating for an instant, Kaname dives in to save Shuka, who he finds unconscious. As Kaname tries to figure out how this happened, Ryuji encounters a young girl named Sui at the entrance to the underpass. When he gives chase, Sui retaliates with her sigil.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793313</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226199" update="2020-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">圧砕[エイス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eighth</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">عشيرة آيس</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eighth</title>
<summary>As the Treasure Hunt Game enters its final stage, the Eighth Clan advances toward Shibuya Central Tower. Realizing that the key to victory is at Shibuya Station, Rein heads there immediately, managing to arrive ahead of the others. However, she finds someone unexpected waiting for her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793314</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226200" update="2020-03-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">平穏[フラジャイル]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fragile</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">هش</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fragile</title>
<summary>Kaname and company engage in a battle with Wang, the leader of the Eighth Clan. Ryuji is prepared to die, but Kaname arrives just in the nick of time to save him. He uses a bluff in an attempt to defeat Wang. Who will be the winner of the Treasure Hunt Game?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793315</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226597" update="2020-03-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水葬[アクアリウム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aquarium</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حوض مائي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aquarium</title>
<summary>It becomes clear to Kaname that in order to win the Treasure Hunt Game, he must defeat the vicious Eighth Clan. To do this, he forms a temporary clan with Rein, Ryuji, and Hiiragi. While they develop a strategy to beat the Eighth Clan, Kaname receives a plea for help from Shuka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793312</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227058" update="2020-04-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘[ヘッズアップ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heads Up</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">احترس</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heads Up</title>
<summary>One month has passed since the conclusion of the Treasure Hunt Game. Kaname has formed his own clan and is undergoing training at Danjo Boxing Club. Danjo, who is the leader of the boxing club, challenges Kaname to a no-holds-barred Vale Tudo style match to gauge Kaname’s training progress and to decide if he is a worthy partner to form an alliance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793316</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227059" update="2020-04-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旧王[オールドワン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Old Wang</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">القديم</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Old One</title>
<summary>After being beaten by Kaname in the Treasure Hunt Game, Wang tries to get revenge by kidnapping Shinozuka, Kaname’s friend, and cutting off his fingers. While Kaname is consumed by guilt for dragging his friend into the D-Game, Rein returns with details on Wang’s hideout and the Eighth Clan’s combat skills.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793317</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227060" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">血盟[サンセットレーベンズ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset Ravens</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">غربان الغروب</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunset Ravens</title>
<summary>Kaname challenges Wang to a clan battle to settle things once and for all. What is the fate of the battle between Kaname and Wang, as well as the Sunset Ravens and the Eighth Clan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793318</identifier>
<identifier>darwins-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
