<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14494" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-11-23</startdate>
<enddate>2018-11-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ple Ple Pleiades: Clementine Toubou Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ple Ple Pleiades: Clementine the Fugitive</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぷれぷれぷれあです ~クレマンティーヌ逃亡編~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10816" type="Parent Story">Overlord</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://www.hikaritv.net/sp/overload/</url>
<creators>
<name id="42661" type="Original Work">Maruyama Kugane</name>
<name id="21007" type="Series Composition">Ashina Minoru</name>
<name id="21054" type="Character Design">Takehara Minoru</name>
<name id="21054" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takehara Minoru</name>
<name id="21007" type="Direction">Ashina Minoru</name>
<name id="23382" type="Animation Work">Studio Pu Yukai</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch76774 [Clementine] is coming back! One of the original Zurrernorn 12 disciples, and the original 9th Seat of the Black Scripture Clementine.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="80">4.10</permanent>
<temporary count="81">6.06</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>228235.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38693</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.hikaritv.net/sp/overload/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オーバーロード_(小説)#ちびキャラアニメ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Rd18GBY3-fs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=_MNBvOuSsdQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6850" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-13">
<name>STAFF MISSING</name>
<description>This anime is missing staff credits. If you can, please assign staff credits to the anime accordingly and then remove the tag.
If the tag is set on an anime level, please assign preferably all credits and then remove it from the anime. If that is not feasible, please assign, at a minimum, credits for all the major/key staff and then transfer it to all relevant episodes (broadly speaking, regular episodes and S-type episodes containing animation). If the tag is already set on an episode level, please assign all credits, including minor staff, to the episode and then remove the tag from it.
Likewise, this tag should either be applied on an anime level, when it is missing key staff (in full or in part), or to all relevant episodes, when key staff is present but at least some episodes don`t have full staff.
For further information on assigning staff credits, please see http://wiki.anidb.net/Content:Staff_Credits [the AniDB Wiki article on them].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7090" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-04-06">
<name>DESCRIPTION NEEDS IMPROVEMENT</name>
<description>This entry has a poor description and needs to have it either edited for improvements or replaced by a higher-quality alternative. If you can, please swap a good enough description in or improve the current one and remove this tag. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="72778" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="345">6.05</rating>
<name>Albedo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albedo is the Overseer of the Floor Guardians of the Great Tomb of Nazarick. She is in charge of the general management and supervises the activities of the seven Floor Guardians, meaning that she ranks above all the other NPCs in Nazarick. She is the sister of Nigredo and Spinel. She was created by Tabula Smaragdina.
She was originally programmed to be a nymphomaniac, but Momonga altered her personality and changed her setting to be in love with him.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>174511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72783" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="255">6.33</rating>
<name>Narberal Gamma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narberal Gamma is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades], combat maids under http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas Tian]. She`s a doppelganger and http://anidb.net/ch76797 [Momon]`s companion in their adventurers` guild, Darkness. She was chosen as one due to her most human-looking appearance out of all other maids. As an adventurer, she refers to herself as Nabe.
Like most of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick] residents, she holds great disdain towards humans. This often proves troublesome, as she becomes incredibly violent when human males make advances on her.</description>
<picture>176197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72785" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="513">5.23</rating>
<name>Ainz Ooal Gown</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momonga is the guildmaster and only remaining active player of the guild Ainz Ooal Gown from the DMMORPG game Yggdrasil, once one of the top guilds in the game. When the guild`s base, the Underground Tomb of Nazarick, was transported to an alternate reality and a new world, Momonga soon assumed for himself the name of Ainz Ooal Gown and began a campaign to make his guild legendary, subsequently turning to world domination.
When he was still human and an Yggdrasil player, Ainz was an adult man already jaded by life, making him prone to analyse things from his perspective as a company worker. In the new world, his game avatar, an undead lich, became his real body, along with all the physical characteristics such a body would have; as a result, he is nigh immune to strong emotions and worldly temptations and desires, because his status as an undead physically shuts them down.
Ainz is calculating, subversive, and cowardly when approaching or in the imminence of a battle, placing his continued survival, as well as that of the guild and its NPCs, who gained life with the transfer, above all else, and planning many moves ahead; once his plans are set in motion, he is ruthlessly efficient in their execution, and will not bat an eyelid at slaying his opponents when pressed. His actions are vicious and ruthless towards any and all that oppose him, and he is motivated by his own gains and survival and the glory of his guild`s name. His greatest weakness is his great fear of not being recognized as a proper leader by the guild`s NPCs, causing him to play along with their plans when he does not understand them simply to not be forced to admit to them that he is not following what they have in mind.</description>
<picture>174510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76774" type="main character in" update="2015-10-21">
<rating votes="57">5.29</rating>
<name>Clementine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clementine is a rogue warrior from Zuranon and a former member of the Black Scripture, the strongest scripture in the Slane Theocracy.
Before she went rogue, Clementine held the 7th seat in the Black Scripture. Betraying the Scripture, she stole the magical Crown of Wisdom from one of the six Shaman-Princesses of the Theocracy, forcing her to flee and join Zuranon.
She is thought to be one of the strongest in the Slane Theocracy since she was a member of the Black Scripture, which is the strongest Scripture in the Slane Theocracy. She is stronger than Hamsuke, Gazef, and Brain, although Gazef can overwhelm her if he were to use use all of his magic items. However, if she were to get the equipment she had when she was in the Black Scripture, even Gazef with full gear could not defeat her.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>178717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76788" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="48">6.31</rating>
<name>Yuri Alpha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri Alpha is the vice captain of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a http://anidb.net/t804 [dullahan], and like http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas], she doesn`t like killing humans without reason. The other Pleiades look up to her and her behavior is strict like a teacher.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76797" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-30">
<rating votes="123">6.31</rating>
<name>Momon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momon is http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz Ooal Gown]`s alter ego as an Adamantite-ranked Adventurer.
Ainz created this persona for the purpose of gaining fame in the Kingdom of Re-Estize and intelligence about possible high level adversaries in the area. He stylized himself as the quiet and enigmatic dark warrior. The iconic raven black armor and red cape has earned his adventurer team the unofficial name of Darkness.</description>
<picture>176222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76799" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="109">3.87</rating>
<name>Solution Epsilon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Solution Epsilon is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a slime and one of the most dangerous Pleiades to humans, since she enjoys devouring humans alive. An assassin and poisoner who can decide to protect or dissolve things she absorbs, she can also control the speed of her digestion. Solution gets along with http://anidb.net/ch72780 [Shalltear] because of their similar tastes.</description>
<picture>217386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76801" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-16">
<rating votes="106">3.60</rating>
<name>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades] and an insect-summoner who likes preying on humans.
Her face is actually a bug shell that hides her true face, while she disguises her voice with that of a cute girl by using a leech that can mimic a human`s voice. Her original voice, which she dislikes using is harsh and grating, similar to that of http://anidb.net/ch72779 [Cocytus]. She harbors a big grudge against an adventurer named http://anidb.net/ch93725 [Evileye] who used anti-bug magic to destroy her cute voice in battle.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76802" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="53">6.31</rating>
<name>CZ2128 Delta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>CZ2128 Delta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s an automaton whose weapons look rather futuristic compared to the setting. Her personality is silent and emotionless, but she dislikes cannibalism and likes cute things. Her neutral personality also makes her safer to humans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76803" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="125">5.05</rating>
<name>Lupusregina Beta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lupusregina Beta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a werewolf with a very bright and outgoing personality and a druid capable of using healing magic, and often carries a massive staff to fight. While she appears to be sociable and friendly toward humans, it is only a mask to conceal her brutal and cunning personality.
Lupusregina is later assigned by http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz] to protect the inhabitants of Carne Village after he tames http://anidb.net/ch76773 [Hamsuke] (as her presence was the only thing keeping monsters away from there). However, when she fails to notify him about a threat to the village, believing it to be an unnecessary action, Ainz flies into a rage, terrifying all those around.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="211505" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2018-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211506" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2018-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211507" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2018-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211508" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211509" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211516" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最新作『 ぷれぷれぷれあです ~クレマンティーヌ逃亡篇~』TVCM公開中! 11/23 (金) 配信開始!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishinsaku "Ple Ple Pleiades: Clementine Toubou Hen" TV CM Koukaichuu! 11/23 (Kin) Haishin Kaishi!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211517" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2018-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ぷれぷれぷれあです ~クレマンティーヌ逃亡篇~』一部映像を公開!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview (3:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Ple Ple Pleiades: Clementine Toubou Hen" Ichibu Eizou o Koukai!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
