<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14493" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2019-06-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">RobiHachi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ロビハチ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">RobiHachi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">RobiHachi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">RobiHachi</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10027" approval="5" total="7">Space Dandy</anime>
<anime id="8101" approval="3" total="6">Tiger &amp; Bunny</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="794914">It`s exactly what it promotes itself as, nothing more, nothing less. A light-hearted simple story with some wacky alien shenanigans, the right amount of fun and sweetness, and some Shinji Takamatsu`s fanservice thrown into the mix (because of course, it`s Shinji Takamatsu, what did you expect?  :D) It aims to be a nice and easy way to pass your time, and that`s what it succeeds at being. It`s just like cotton wool - you won`t be eating this to sate your hunger, but when you`re just up for something light and sweet, it`s the way to go.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://robihachi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="839" type="Animation Work">Studio Comet</name>
<name id="13979" type="Character Design">Yahiro Yuuko</name>
<name id="37903" type="Series Composition">Kanasugi Hiroko</name>
<name id="113" type="Direction">Takamatsu Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>Down-on-his-luck http://anidb.net/ch99335 [Robby Yarge] is about to go from deep trouble to deep space! After a second encounter with http://anidb.net/ch99333 [Hacchi Kita] ends with him on the run, Robby decides to make for Isekandar, a planet that promises happiness. But when he finds Hacchi stowed away on his ship, the two will make the journey across the stars together! Can these total opposites survive a trek through space?
Source: funimation</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="172">3.60</permanent>
<temporary count="172">5.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>230161.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21590</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38707</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://robihachi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>RobiHachi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>RobiHachi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5261</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366220</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21879</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>RobiHachi_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=fpO5bgWjpWY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07R8X57CH</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.funimation.com/shows/robihachi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4488" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-02">
<name>terraforming</name>
<description>Terraforming (literally, "Earth-shaping") of a planet, moon, or other body is the hypothetical process of deliberately modifying its atmosphere, temperature, surface topography or ecology to be similar to the biosphere of Earth, in order to make it habitable by humans.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="70429" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="2">7.15</rating>
<name>Wombat</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162180.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99330" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-05">
<name>JPS-19</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99331" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-05">
<name>Allo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99332" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-05">
<name>Gras</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56831" picture="227634.jpg">Tokudome Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99333" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Hacchi Kita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23393" picture="158026.jpg">Koumoto Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99334" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-05">
<name>Yang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99335" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Robby Yarge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="213612" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅は道連れ Journey to the Star</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Traveling Companions: Journey to the Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi wa Michizure: Journey to the Star</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213613" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タコから出た真実[まこと]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Truth Found from an Octopus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tako kara Deta Makoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213614" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冥王星の惑星[ほし]恨み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pique on Planet Pluto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiousei no Hoshi Urami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213615" update="2019-03-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竿の先に半魚人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Merfolk on the End of the Pole</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sao no Saki ni Hangyojin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214253" update="2019-03-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215962" update="2019-04-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の沙汰もドン次第</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Don Opens All Doors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku no Sata mo Don Shidai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215963" update="2019-04-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寝耳にウナギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Qu-eel-le Surprise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemimi ni Unagi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215964" update="2019-04-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一寸先は夢の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Dreams Just Ahead</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issunsaki wa Yume no Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215965" update="2019-04-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メカるが勝ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heads I`m Tin, Tails You Lose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mekaru ga Kachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217260" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">亭主の好きなヒザクリガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Family That Stays Together, Hizakuriger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teishu no Suki na Hizakuriger</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217261" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">相棒[バディ]喧嘩は犬も喰わない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never Get Involved in a Buddies` Quarrel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buddy Kenka wa Inu mo Kuwanai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217262" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聞いて極楽, イセカンダル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Common Fame Is a Common Isekandar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiite Gokuraku, Isekandar</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217263" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月の夢, 地球の夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream of the Moon, Dream of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki no Yume, Chikyu no Yume</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
