<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14523" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu.</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">防振り</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bofuri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Boufuri</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bofuri: I Don`t Want to Get Hurt, So I`ll Max Out My Defense.</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Не люблю боль, поэтому собираюсь вложить всё в защиту</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">아픈 건 싫으니까 방어력에 올인하려고 합니다.</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">لا أريد أن أتأذى، لذلك سأصقل دفاعي</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">因为太怕痛就全点防御力了</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15464" type="Sequel">Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu. II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13844" approval="5" total="7">Watashi, Nouryoku wa Heikinchi de tte Itta yo ne!</anime>
<anime id="11123" approval="1" total="7">One Punch Man</anime>
<anime id="8692" approval="1" total="4">Sword Art Online</anime>
<anime id="8606" approval="1" total="2">.hack//Sekai no Mukou ni</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="173070">If you`re a fan of "main character overpowered" series, you`ll get that in spades here. There`s really nothing bad to say about the series, it starts hilarious, continues hilarious, and gets absurd.

At no point does that get old. This has just the right amount of content and speed without anything feeling drawn out. It doesn`t feel like a gimmick is frequently used nor is it over done.

Worth every moment, hopefully season 2 is just as fun.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="567315">What an absolutely delightful anime! This show is a great deconstruction of the slew of isekai anime we have seen in the mainstream lately, taking the familiar concept of being inside a video game world, but giving it a tongue-in-cheek sideways analysis.
Where this show stands out is how [i]different[/i] it is from other shows in the genre. Unlike many anime in the genre, nobody is trapped here, there is no life-or-death threat, and there is a positive wholesome undercurrent that not be understated, even in competitive arcs.
The show gives power after power to our lead, each parodying some other genre of anime, in a loving hat-tip to the old annoying Isekai cliche. But the viewer is in on the joke here, and so instead of annoying, it is an absolute treat to see where the heck Maple will end up next!
If you are a fan of deconstruction, and need a wholesome break from some of the more tired cliches of late, check out one of the most enjoyable entries of this last season!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="543137">one of light good time spend anime ou can  lough and get good action  and well designed characters</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194184">This has been one of the few shows I enjoyed instantly and anticipated the most this season.

In my opinion it started rather unpredictable. But I`m not a gamer so I can`t really tell much about game mechanisms. 

I like the main char. Her decisions aren`t the norm since she`s not a typical gamer, an airhead and just there for the fun and not really goal-oriented.

The design all over is in the range of beautiful to cute. The characters are all really likeable. There is not one character who`s unlikeable or annoying. That`s kinda a novum for me. The action scenes are exciting and the questing and farming scenes are relaxing. The background music is quite nice to listen to as well. The world offers a mix of mostly fantasy and a bit of sci-fi.

All in all I really enjoyed this series and can`t await the next season!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="423685">It`s a fun little show about a dumb-broken protagonist who happens to be a cute girl. And it all happens in a VMMORPG world so any shenanigans and carnage that ensue can be fun and relaxing as well.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://bofuri.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59573" type="Music">Masuda Tarou</name>
<name id="11748" type="Character Design">Hirata Kazuya</name>
<name id="11748" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirata Kazuya</name>
<name id="38385" type="Direction">Minato Mirai</name>
<name id="1564" type="Direction">Oonuma Shin</name>
<name id="56790" type="Original Work">Yuumikan</name>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr56790 [Yuumikan] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr9144 [Koin].
Honjou Kaede is invited by her friend Shiramine Risa to play a virtual reality MMO game with her. While Kaede doesn`t dislike games, what she really, truly dislikes is being in pain. She creates a character named Maple, and decides to put all her points in VIT to minimize pain. As a result, she moves slowly, can`t use magic, and even a rabbit can get the best of her. But as it turns out, she acquires a skill known as "Absolute Defense" as a result of her pumping points into VIT, as well as a "Counter Skill" that works against special moves. Now, with her ability to nullify all damage, she goes on adventures.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="641">6.37</permanent>
<temporary count="648">7.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>242404.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22565</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38790</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://bofuri.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BOFURI:_I_Don't_Want_to_Get_Hurt,_so_I'll_Max_Out_My_Defense.</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5521</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22449</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bofuri_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ZeLz3WZHOYs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=rHtjR9b3eoU</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=7NRUGne6Zjk</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=2ji-cLcT-UI</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=eC1VI-C9D1E</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=usSCwmM2k0c</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=6-6rIN8Xe28</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=2cnFSxfkLjM</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=THxPbzgNXBo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=NFUtXTOmUfY</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=AODnWIirajU</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=3TnO5uXV9LY</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=t-Ck0nI8Vts</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=hONMTxGNuEg</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=3urU9IFhAIs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=D66ZPVpA9cw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=gDM9RTPdKU4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0845P8BRT</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2769" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>hyperspace mallet</name>
<description>It comes from nowhere, it strikes without mercy, and disappears again. It`s a mallet the size of a circus sledgehammer, and it`s evidence that anime characters watch too many Bugs Bunny cartoons or Three Stooges shorts. An angry character — usually but not restricted to short-tempered schoolgirls — can often whip out a massive hammer with which to slam the target (and cause) of her ire.
In Fan Fic circles, the notional storage place for mallets when not in use is known as hammerspace or malletspace.
A recent variation is to have the character pull out a http://anidb.net/t1662 [harisen], a huge folded fan made out of paper or metal, a.k.a. the Paper Fan of Doom, and smack them with that. This is usually less painful-looking than the mallet, unless she uses it to deliver a Megaton Punch.
Ironically, this is now a Dead Horse Trope in the West, where it originated; modern Western examples are typically from shows invoking anime, which has added its own touches to the mix, or from homages to Warner Brothers cartoons.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>10253.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="106085" type="main character in" update="2020-02-08">
<rating votes="6">6.37</rating>
<name>Sally</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43444" picture="186203.jpg">Noguchi Ruriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106086" type="main character in" update="2020-02-08">
<rating votes="18">8.13</rating>
<name>Maple</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107148" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-08">
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<name>Kanade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107517" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="3">6.91</rating>
<name>Iz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107518" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="5">7.12</rating>
<name>Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107519" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<name>Kuromu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107520" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="3">3.53</rating>
<name>May</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107521" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="4">4.94</rating>
<name>Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44178" picture="188637.jpg">Suwa Nanaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107626" type="appears in" update="2020-03-12">
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107627" type="appears in" update="2020-01-15">
<name>Dorazou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107628" type="appears in" update="2020-03-05">
<name>Drag</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107629" type="appears in" update="2020-03-05">
<name>Dread</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107630" type="appears in" update="2020-03-05">
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<name>Frederica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107631" type="appears in" update="2020-03-12">
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<name>Pein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107632" type="appears in" update="2020-02-27">
<name>Marx</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107633" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-23">
<rating votes="4">7.77</rating>
<name>Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107634" type="appears in" update="2020-02-27">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Misery</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108010" type="appears in" update="2020-01-15">
<name>Christmas Rose</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39784" picture="153564.jpg">Inoue Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108217" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-01">
<name>Oboro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56180" picture="223769.jpg">Matsui Akiha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108218" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-01">
<name>Syrup</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53024" picture="232385.jpg">Shimabukuro Miyuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108497" type="appears in" update="2020-02-27">
<name>First Generation Machine God</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39784" picture="153564.jpg">Inoue Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108498" type="appears in" update="2020-02-27">
<name>Second Generation Machine God</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="59116" picture="240734.jpg">Nakamura Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="219199" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います.』ティザーPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:54)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu." Teaser PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225532" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います.」アニメ化企画進行中PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:18)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu." Anime-ka Kikaku Shinkou Chuu PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225533" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います.」アニメ化企画進行中TVCM15秒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01 (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu." Anime-ka Kikaku Shinkou Chuu TV CM 15 Byou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225534" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ化決定!「痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います。」TVCM 02</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 02 (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime-ka Kettei! "Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu." TV CM 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225535" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います.』第2弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (2:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu." Dai 2 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225552" update="2019-12-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と初戦闘.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and First Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والمعركة الأولى</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Shosentou.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225553" update="2019-12-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化とお友達.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والأصدقاء</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Otomodachi.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225554" update="2019-12-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と二層攻略.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Reaching Second Level</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والذهاب إلى الطابق الثاني</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Nisou Kouryaku.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225555" update="2019-12-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と第二回イベント.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Second Event</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والحدث الثاني</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Dainikai Event.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225823" update="2020-01-02">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2020-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『痛いのは嫌なので防御力に極振りしたいと思います.』第3弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 04 (2:07)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu." Dai 3 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226260" update="2020-01-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と戦利品.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Spoils of War</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع وغنائم الحرب</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Senrihin.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226261" update="2020-01-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と新戦力.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Reinforcements</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع وقوة الحرب الجديدة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Shin Senryoku.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226262" update="2020-01-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と強化.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Upgrades</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والتعزيز</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Kyouka.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226263" update="2020-01-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と第三回イベント.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Third Event</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والحدث الثالث</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Daisankai Event.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226682" update="2020-02-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第1話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 1.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="226683" update="2020-02-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 2.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="226684" update="2020-02-06">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第3話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 3.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="226685" update="2020-02-06">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第4話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 4.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="226778" update="2020-02-08">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第5話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 5.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="226909" update="2020-02-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2020-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第6話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 6.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227031" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と第四回イベント.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Fourth Event</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والحدث الرابع</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Daiyonkai Event.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227032" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と出撃.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والهجوم</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Shutsugeki.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227033" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化と強敵.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Mighty Foe</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والخصوم الأقوياء</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Kyouteki.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227034" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">防御特化とつながり.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defense and Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الدفاع والعلاقات</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bougyo Tokka to Tsunagari.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227085" update="2020-02-22">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第7話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 7.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227175" update="2020-02-29">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第8話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 8.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227337" update="2020-03-07">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2020-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第9話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 9.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227403" update="2020-03-14">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第10話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 10.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227677" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227678" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227698" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第11話ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 Playback</title>
<summary>NWO developers react to Episode 11.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
