<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14535" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-03-31</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hachi-nantte, Sore wa Nai Deshou!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Eighth Son? That Can’t Be Right!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">八男って, それはないでしょう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The 8th Son? Are You Kidding Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Восьмой сын? Вы шутите?</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">팔남이라니, 그건 아니지!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">الابن الثامن؟ هل تمزح؟</title>
</titles>
<url>http://hachinan-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="60225" type="Music">Catherina Kogaku Gassoudan</name>
<name id="32762" type="Music">Seki Minako</name>
<name id="60224" type="Series Composition">Miyamoto Takeshi</name>
<name id="1284" type="Work">Shin-Ei Animation</name>
<name id="19259" type="Character Design">Tanabe Kenji</name>
<name id="16324" type="Direction">Miura Tatsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>Ichinomiya Shingo, an everyday twenty-five-year-old office worker, wakes up as Wendelin, the 8th son of an impoverished noble family out in the sticks. He soon despairs at his lack of succession rights and knowledge to navigate the political world, but finds hope in his aptitude for magic. 
 
This is the story of that young man earning his keep and his freedom through magic, with no world saving involved, and spending quite a while escaping his solitude. Ultimately, it is also the story of him being unable to escape the shackles of society.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="51">4.17</permanent>
<temporary count="53">6.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>244858.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22285</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38830</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hachinan-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_8th_Son%3F_Are_You_Kidding_Me%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>八男って、それはないでしょう!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5593</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367444</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hachinan_PR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=U376UHBiE6Y</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=6ORAkd4tVpY</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=EkkHgXq2Rig</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-8th-son-are-you-kidding-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="109353" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Amalie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109354" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Alfred Rainford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109355" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Klimt Kristoff von Armstrong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55776" picture="220705.jpg">Yamane Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109356" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Iina Suzane Hirenbrant</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109357" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Elize Katharina von Hohenheim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109358" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Erwin von Alnim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109359" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Kurt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109360" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Brantack Lyngstad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109361" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Louise Yorande Aorelia Oufelbeik</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36224" picture="228578.jpg">Mimura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109362" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Roderich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46709" picture="208260.jpg">Takatsuka Tomohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109363" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Vilma Etol von Asgahan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109364" type="main character in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Wendelin von Benno Baumeister</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33512" picture="225800.jpg">Enoki Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109365" type="main character in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Wendelin von Benno Baumeister (Younen)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218570" update="2019-07-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「八男って, それはないでしょう!」ティザーPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1: Anime `The 8th son? Are you kidding me?` PV (2:01)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Hachi-nan tte, Sore wa Nai deshou!" Teaser PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226112" update="2020-01-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">【2020年4月放送開始】TVアニメ「八男って, それはないでしょう!」PV第1弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:34)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"2020-nen 4-gatsu Housou Kaishi" TV Anime "Hachi-nan tte, Sore wa Nai deshou!" PV Dai 1 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227438" update="2020-04-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八男って, それはないでしょう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 8th Son? Are You Kidding Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le huitième fils ? Dites-moi que je rêve !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الابن الثامن؟ هل تمزح؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hachi-nantte, Sore wa Nai Deshou!</title>
<summary>When the trading company office worker Ichimiya Shingo wakes up from his nap he finds himself in an unfamiliar world in the body of a five-year-old boy, Wendelin (Well), from the noble Baumeister family. Though he`s confused at his new surroundings, he`s reassured to learn that he won`t have to worry about food as a noble`s son, but then he learns that he`s actually the eighth son of a poor noble family in remote lands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794534</identifier>
<identifier>the-8th-son-are-you-kidding-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227476" update="2020-04-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お家騒動って, それはないでしょう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Succession Dispute? Are You Kidding Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une lutte fratricide ? Dites-moi que je rêve !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">نزاع خلافة؟ هل تمزح؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oiesoudoutte, Sore wa Nai Deshou!</title>
<summary>Well becomes the disciple of Alfred the magician, steadily learning magic under his training. Meanwhile, Alfred warns him to keep his ability to use a magic a secret in order to avoid a succession dispute, but Well`s eldest brother Kurt begins to notice his talent for magic...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794535</identifier>
<identifier>the-8th-son-are-you-kidding-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227477" update="2020-04-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボッチって, それはないでしょう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Loner? Are You Kidding Me?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Encore tout seul ? Dites-moi que je rêve !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">وحيد؟ هل تمزح؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bocchitte, Sore wa Nai Deshou!</title>
<summary>Now 12, Well joins the Adventurers` Academy, but as the only scholarship student for magic he finds himself alone and set apart from the rest. Meanwhile, Erwin, Iina, and Louise all join forces to try and get Well to join their party. Hoping to earn Well`s approval, they sneak into the hunting grounds where big game resides, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794536</identifier>
<identifier>the-8th-son-are-you-kidding-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227478" update="2020-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しがらみって, それはないでしょう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Obligations? Are You Kidding Me?!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">التزامات؟ هل تمزح؟</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigarumitte, Sore wa Nai Deshou!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794537</identifier>
<identifier>the-8th-son-are-you-kidding-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="228317" update="2020-04-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228318" update="2020-04-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228319" update="2020-04-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228320" update="2020-04-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
