<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14534" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-19</startdate>
<enddate>2019-07-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tenki no Ko</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">ابنة الجو</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">天気の子</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Weathering with You</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Дитя погоды</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Weathering with You</title>
</titles>
<url>https://www.tenkinoko.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="12506" type="Character Design">Tamura Atsushi</name>
<name id="59025" type="Work">Story</name>
<name id="2210" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="10345" type="Work">CoMix Wave Films</name>
<name id="445" type="Original Work">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="445" type="Direction">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="47019" type="Music">Radwimps</name>
</creators>
<description>High school student http://anidb.net/ch99791 [Hodaka] leaves his home on an isolated island and moves to Tokyo, but he immediately becomes broke. He lives his days in isolation, but finally finds a job as a writer for a shady occult magazine. After he starts his job, the weather has been rainy day after day. In a corner of the crowded and busy city, Hodaka meets a young woman named http://anidb.net/ch99790 [Hina]. Due to certain circumstances, Hina and her younger brother live together, but have a cheerful and sturdy life. Hina also has a certain power: the power to stop the rain and clear the sky.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="183">7.86</permanent>
<temporary count="184">7.88</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238108.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22137</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.tenkinoko.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.cwfilms.jp/en/products/article/tenkinoko.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://gkids.com/films/weathering-with-you/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Weathering_with_You</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天気の子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366483</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22156</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tenkinoko_movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=rzKcrJ77wBY</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=VGksHFs04Rc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="33">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天气之子/23203347</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="38">
<externalentity>
<identifier>269235</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="39">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30402296</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="972" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-18">
<name>part-time worker</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="78861" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-02-14">
<rating votes="50">7.99</rating>
<name>Miyamizu Mitsuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42899" picture="172022.jpg">Kamishiraishi Mone</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78862" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-02-14">
<rating votes="34">7.45</rating>
<name>Tachibana Taki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3785" picture="71854.jpg">Kamiki Ryuunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82380" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="8">7.64</rating>
<name>Teshigawara Katsuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65257.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="46339" picture="188649.jpg">Narita Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82381" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="8">6.65</rating>
<name>Natori Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65254.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82384" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="12">5.90</rating>
<name>Miyamizu Yotsuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65253.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="46341" picture="188650.jpg">Tani Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99790" type="main character in" update="2020-02-07">
<rating votes="4">8.91</rating>
<name>Amano Hina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56841" picture="227651.jpg">Mori Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99791" type="main character in" update="2020-02-07">
<rating votes="1">1.33</rating>
<name>Morishima Hodaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56842" picture="227652.jpg">Daigo Kotarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102969" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Fumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5801" picture="30256.jpg">Baishou Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102970" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Natsumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="58007" picture="234482.jpg">Honda Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102971" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Amano Nagi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="58008" picture="234483.jpg">Kiryuu Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102972" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Yasui</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="41626" picture="165827.jpg">Hiraizumi Sei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102973" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Suga Keisuke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1984" picture="21284.jpg">Oguri Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102974" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-28">
<name>Takai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="210943" update="2019-07-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2019-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214943" update="2019-04-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画『天気の子』予報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (1:00): "Weathering with You" Movie Forecast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiga "Tenki no Ko" Yohou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219045" update="2019-07-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画『天気の子』予報②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (2:00)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
