<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14549" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-03-29</startdate>
<enddate>2019-07-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikatsu Shuukan The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">성활주간</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">性活週間 THE ANIMATION</title>
</titles>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1994</url>
<creators>
<name id="27343" type="Animation Work">Seven</name>
<name id="15385" type="Character Design">Ohara Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="15385" type="Direction">Ohara Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="56905" type="Original Work">Michiking</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch102843 [Shuntarou]`s younger sisters - http://anidb.net/ch102845 [Ayaka], http://anidb.net/ch102846 [Chiaki] and http://anidb.net/ch102847 [Fuyuno] - are very mean to him, so he wishes he had a gentle older sister. Then some mysterious game seems to make him http://anidb.net/ch102844 [younger].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="79">5.41</permanent>
<temporary count="84">6.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>227872.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1994</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=2015</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2693" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>handjob</name>
<description>A handjob is the manual stimulation of the penis by another person`s hand. The female equivalent is http://anidb.net/t7229 [fingering].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2696" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>threesome</name>
<description>Tag for any scene where sexual acts take place with three people of any gender. Should not be used if more than three.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2699" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>sixty-nine</name>
<description>At least one sex position from a group generically called sixty-nine or 69 is featured, characterised by a mutually inverted alignment of two people of any sex in which both perform oral sex simultaneously. Putting it another way, the top of the head of one person points more or less towards the feet of the other, and the head of each is at the height of the other`s genitals, and both perform cunnilingus or fellatio, whichever is appropriate in each case. The name stems from this mutual inversion, which resembles the numbers 6 and 9.</description>
<picurl>162104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2912" parentid="2696" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>threesome with sisters</name>
<description>A sexual act involving three people, in which two or all are female siblings. The third person, if not a third sister, can be of either gender, and may be another family member as well, such as their brother, father or even mother. The sisters do not necessarily have to be blood-related (e.g. stepsisters).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4046" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>foursome</name>
<description>When four people have sex with each other at the same time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6572" parentid="2696" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>FFM threesome</name>
<description>A threesome with two female and one male partner.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="102843" type="main character in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<name>Shuntarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233684.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102844" type="main character in" update="2019-09-16">
<name>Koharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuntarou as his younger sisters see him when hypnotized.</description>
<picture>233685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32318" picture="158557.jpg">Kusano Karen</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102845" type="main character in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="4">5.77</rating>
<name>Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50408" picture="59506.jpg">Momoyama Ion</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102846" type="main character in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="2">9.17</rating>
<name>Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28385" picture="41280.jpg">Shirayuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102847" type="main character in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<name>Fuyuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20574" picture="231415.jpg">Mitaka Rin</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="211240" update="2018-12-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2019-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216104" update="2019-04-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2019-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
