<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14548" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2019-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bakumatsu: Ren`ai Bakumatsu Kareshi Gaiden - Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BAKUMATSU ~恋愛幕末カレシ 外伝~ クライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bakumatsu Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">恋爱幕末男友</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13971" type="Prequel">Bakumatsu: Ren`ai Bakumatsu Kareshi Gaiden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/BAKUMATSU/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2187" type="Animation Character Design">Shimamura Hidekazu</name>
<name id="54286" type="Original Animation Character Design">Natsuo</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="3527" type="Series Composition">Yokotani Masahiro</name>
<name id="45666" type="Original Plan">Furyuu</name>
<name id="28035" type="Direction">Satou Mitsutoshi</name>
<name id="23325" type="Music">Sakabe Gou</name>
<name id="44574" type="Music">Kawasaki Ryou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a smartphone game published by http://anidb.net/cr45666 [FuRyu].
The chronometer is a legendary treasure that has the power to manipulate time.
The Susanoo Incident unfolded in the capital of Kyoto and ended with the death of the masked shogun, http://anidb.net/ch98467 [Mugensai]. Having finished visiting the grave of his former master, http://anidb.net/ch98466 [Yoshida Shouin], http://anidb.net/ch97306 [Takasugi Shinsaku] and his partner, http://anidb.net/ch97303 [Katsura Kogorou], return to Kyoto once again.
Suddenly, the earth trembles and the sky splits open, and the chronometer, which was supposed to have been destroyed, appears from a rift in space-time. Now with a will of its own, the chronometer starts going on an uncontrollable rampage!!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="36">2.01</permanent>
<temporary count="36">3.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>230325.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38860</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/BAKUMATSU/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Renai_Bakumatsu_Kareshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>恋愛幕末カレシ〜時の彼方で花咲く恋〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5297</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366620</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21842</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BAKUMATSU_info</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5818" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-01-21">
<name>out-of-place artefact</name>
<description>Out-of-place artefact (OOPArt) is a term coined by American naturalist and crypto-zoologist Ivan T. Sanderson for an object of historical, archaeological, or palaeontological interest found in a very unusual or seemingly impossible context that could challenge conventional historical chronology.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97295" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Hijikata Toshizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47241" picture="225126.jpg">Someya Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97296" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Sakamoto Ryouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97297" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Yamazaki Susumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97298" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Okada Izou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97299" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Mikado</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42164" picture="176249.jpg">Takeuchi Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97300" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Tokugawa Yoshinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97301" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Saitou Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51378" picture="225125.jpg">Tada Keita</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97302" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Seimei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33069" picture="225127.jpg">Nakajima Yoshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97303" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Katsura Kogorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97304" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Okita Souji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97305" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Kondou Isami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97306" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<name>Takasugi Shinsaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98466" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Yoshida Shouin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98467" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Mugensai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4687" picture="27301.jpg">Kinoshita Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98468" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Takasu Hisako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47785" picture="225124.jpg">Ono Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98469" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Hyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38295" picture="222841.jpg">Yamashita Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98470" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101106" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Nidaime Mugensai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230652.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="214376" update="2019-05-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クロフネ襲来 無限斎の帰還!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Ship Invasion and Mugensai`s Return!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro Fune Shuurai: Mugensai no Kikan!</title>
<summary>"We still have things we need to do." Takasugi Shinsaku and Katsura Kogoro have finished tending to Yoshida Shoin`s grave in Hagi. They return to Kyoto in order to correct the flow of time thrown off balance by the legendary treasure, the chronometer. Suddenly, the earth trembles and the sky splits open, and the chronometer, which was supposed to have been destroyed, appears from a rift in space-time. Now with a will of its own, the chronometer starts going on an uncontrollable rampage! Standing in their way is Takasugi`s fated rival, vice commander of the Shinsengumi, Hijikata Toshizo, who was lost in the previous battle!! Commander of the Shinsengumi, Kondo Isami, refers to the shocking existence of a new Mugensai.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782848</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="214377" update="2019-05-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">京都炎上! 鬼火のナゾ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyoto on Fire! The Mysterious Ghost Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoto Enjou! Onibi no Nazo</title>
<summary>"Several sightings of ghost lights have been reported around Kyoto." While Shinsaku and Katsura are searching for the vanished chronometer they get asked by Tokugawa Yoshinobu to look into rumors of a strange phenomenon. At the same time, having recently assumed control over the giant castle Susanoo, the new Mugensai, with a mysterious boy named Mori Ranmaru serving as his aide, orders the Shinsengumi to look into any connection between the chronometer and the ghost lights. Why have the Shinsengumi once again changed masters to the new Mugensai? In the midst of the constant chaos, the space-time rifts start appearing again! What is the truth behind these peculiar burning red lights?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782849</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="214378" update="2019-05-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幕末怪異譚 トラを見た!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bakumatsu Supernatural Tales: Tiger Sighting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakumatsu Kaiidan: Tora o Mita!</title>
<summary>"In a village outside Kyoto, villagers are being attacked and killed in succession by an unknown creature." Sakamoto Ryoma tells Shinsaku and Katsura. Katsura, who has been collecting information on mysterious incidents and paranormal phenomena that are being reported around Kyoto in his quest for the chronometer, tries to head out to the village to verify the rumors, but Takasugi suddenly seems reluctant to go. On Ryoma`s suggestion, Katsura takes Izo along with him to the village. The unusual pairing wind up dragged into puzzling incident and they find themselves facing one of the twelve commanders of Susanoo!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782850</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="214379" update="2019-05-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会の土方 イケダヤ事変!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion with Hijikata: Ikedaya Incident!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai no Dokata: Ikedaya Jihen!</title>
<summary>"I`ll just have to punch the crap out of Hijikata-san when he does show up." Captain of the 1st division of the Shinsengumi, Okita Soji, keeps mentally going over what happened during the Susanoo Incident when Hijikata went missing. While looking for the chronometer, Soji and the Shinsengumi once again encounter Takasugi and the others. A space-time rift opens up during this encounter and Soji is sucked into it. When Okita awakens, he finds himself in a Kyoto without the giant castle of Susanoo in the distance. He is standing before another Ikedaya when he hears a very familiar voice call out, "We`re here on official business!"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782851</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215617" update="2019-05-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">来たのは誰だ? 夜空のコンペイトウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Goes There? Night Sky Konpeito</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kita no wa Dare Da? Yozora no Konpeitou</title>
<summary>"We have returned from scouting." Tokugawa special agents Hyo and Kasumi make it back to Yoshinobu and the others full of energy after having finished their reconnaissance mission of the giant castle Susanoo. These two young girls work hard to complete their missions despite their youth. Mikado observes the girls one day and notices their interest in konpeito candy after they have an encounter with some local children. Mikado then decides to set off on his own to get some. Worried for Mikado`s wellbeing, Yamazaki sends Hyo and Kasumi to keep an eye on him. Meanwhile, a new commander of Susanoo follows Mikado like a sinister shadow.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782852</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215618" update="2019-05-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時辰儀暴走! 京都のセイシする日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chronometer Out of Control! Kyoto`s Motionless Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jishingi Bousou! Kyoto no Seishi Suru Hi</title>
<summary>"Katsura has been acting weird lately." Katsura has begun to investigate the whereabouts of the chronometer on his own since its presence hasn`t been felt for quite some time. Realizing something is going on with Katsura, Takasugi consults with Ryoma about the situation. Takasugi stubbornly insists that he will get the chronometer back from Katsura and carry out Master Shoin`s dying wish to return time back to normal. But Ryoma questions if that timeline truly is the "right" one and in the midst of their argument a strange phenomenon occurs and they rush outside. Once outside the duo notices that everyone and everything seems frozen in place!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782853</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215619" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時辰儀誕生! 運命のキョウダイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth of the Chronometer! Destined Siblings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jishingi Tanjou! Unmei no Kyoudai</title>
<summary>"If the chronometer is used to return time to its original course..." Suspicious that Ryoma may already have gotten ahold of the chronometer, Katsura confronts him and reveals the reason he is trying so hard to get the chronometer before Takasugi does. Despite knowing Katsura`s motives, Ryoma gives him the slip, and with the chronometer indeed in his possession. Meanwhile, Takasugi learns from Seimei that he is the one who created the chronometer. In order to find out how the chronometer was created, Takasugi travels back to the past with Seimei`s unusual powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782854</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215620" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">慶喜のオモイ 近藤のオモイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshinobu`s Thoughts and Kondo`s Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoshinobu no Omoi Kondou no Omoi</title>
<summary>"What is he going to do with the chronometer?!" Katsura discovers that Ryoma indeed has the chronometer. In a clash with Izo, Katsura demands to know what Ryoma plans to do with the device, but in an instant, Ryoma uses the chronometer to turn back time. Izo calls into question Ryoma`s careless use of the chronometer and in the midst of their skirmish they are startled by a bright flash of light. The chronometer shows the duo a future that hasn`t happened yet. Takasugi, having sensed the chronometer, hounds Katsura with more questions about his suspect behavior, while Yoshinobu arranges a secret meeting with Kondo through Yamazaki. During the meeting, Yoshinobu reveals his secret plans for the future of Japan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782855</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217123" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘めたる想い! 仮面のコクハク!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hidden Feelings! A Masked Confession!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himetaru Omoi! Kamen no Kokuhaku!</title>
<summary>"They are both opponents I`m closely linked to, after all." Okita and the Shinsengumi discover Ryoma and Izo`s hiding place, and Mugensai joins them as they pursue the pair. Ryoma and Izo hatch a plan to trick Mugensai with a fake chronometer and split up, but before they can carry out that plan, they are found by Mugensai and the Shinsengumi. Meanwhile, Yoshinobu turns to a still bickering Takasugi and Katsura for help in rescuing the captured emperor. Suspecting that he knows the true identity of his master, Kondo speaks with Mugensai.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782856</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217124" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消滅! 巨城スサノオ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vanished! Giant Castle Susanoo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoumetsu! Kyojou Susanoo!</title>
<summary>"Toshi...!" Kondo and Okita try to help free their beloved friend from the evil spell of the chronometer. However, Mori Ranmaru appears and arrests both Kondo and Okita, throwing them in a cell for treason. At the same time, Takasugi and the others sneak into the giant castle Susanoo in order to free the emperor, but come across a hidden surprise. Ryoma has also come to the castle seeking revenge for his fallen friend, Izo and to retrieve the chronometer. As things come to a head, Katsura finally admits to Takasugi the reason he has been secretly looking for the chronometer alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782857</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217125" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生! 巨神スサノオ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth! The Great God Susanoo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanjou! Kyojin Susanoo!</title>
<summary>"Kyoto has vanished?" Right after finally getting rid of the twelve commanders of Susanoo, Takasugi and the others find themselves surrounded by a vast plain. Seimei explains the shocking truth that Susanoo Castle has traveled back to the distant past, and taken them with it! They`re not alone though, Mugensai has also been pulled back in time with the castle. Takasugi squares off against his masked foe, but a lucky blow reveals a familiar face hidden underneath. Meanwhile, back in the other time period, Sakamoto stares at the remains of the castle and clutches the chronometer as he contemplates what to do to bring back his friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782858</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217126" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しきBAKUMATSUへ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To a New Bakumatsu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashiki Bakumatsu e!</title>
<summary>"You`re not going anywhere!!" Having become one with the giant castle Susanoo, the hulking figure of the castle and Mugensai stalks towards Lake Ogura to make his plan to plunge Japan into a world of unending war a reality. However, Takasugi, Katsura, Yoshinobu, and the Shinsengumi stand in his way and put their lives on the line to prevent his plan from taking fruit. The longstanding conflict that Takasugi and his companions have been struggling to deal with finally seems to be near its end! How will their feelings surrounding the chronometer be resolved? And what new age will be awaiting them when this is all finished?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782859</identifier>
<identifier>bakumatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221833" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221834" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221835" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221836" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-05-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221837" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221838" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221839" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
