<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14570" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nekopara (2020)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">네코파라</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ネコぱら (2020)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nekopara</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">貓娘樂園</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">猫娘乐园</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12622" type="Prequel">Nekopara</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14514" approval="1" total="9">Sewayaki Kitsune no Senko-san</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="748358">It features a roster of cute catgirls doing, well, cute catgirl stuff. There is no much of a plot and every episode features its own story, but it is peaceful, heartwarming and overall nice action. Fanservice is relatively balanced, and because of its source material, I had hoped it would be a little wilder. Still, not much of an issue. For me, said issue comes with the male protagonist and Cacao, the little aqua-colored catgirl. The first one, which supposedly is the harem lead, barely appears. Like, almost never. His sister, Shigure, is way more featured than him. As for Cacao, her appearance and background made me believe at the beginning that the story was going to revolve around her finding out about her origins, however, she quickly becomes a sideshow. That triggered me somewhat, because it could have been a good plot device.

Other than that, this was a good, somewhat underrated, niche experience. Recommended for nekomusume fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="231802">Just nicely moist, not too wet not too dry. mou uruocchau

This is your sweet indulgence in a neko paradise. Lay back, enjoy the daily antics of a group of catgirls, each cutely delicately designed, with unique likeable and yet funny personalities. 
You will have all sizes as well on the fan service department. Though you should not be worry that its too racy, it`s the family friendly version (unlike the wellknown VN). Its main attraction is actually being cute anyways

Plot wise rather simple &amp; straightforward episodic with sprinkles of comedy and cuteness but though for new comers it lacks proper intro to the girls. Art wise pretty good; in that it has that cute snuggy feel in warm soothing palettes along with nicely drarn catgirls

Join in if u`re fan of catgirls (which of course tags with fans of fan services) that wants a lounging relaxing watch for the extra sweetness &amp; cuteness in your evenings. Well balanced in that aspect. 7/10 for me, thanks for the pleasant experience</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://nekopara-anime.com/ja/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17983" type="Chief Animation Direction">Mishima Chie</name>
<name id="17928" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirano Yuuichi</name>
<name id="59694" type="Original Work">Neko Works</name>
<name id="41009" type="Animation Work">Felix Film</name>
<name id="17928" type="Character Design">Hirano Yuuichi</name>
<name id="8020" type="Series Composition">Zappa Gou</name>
<name id="2172" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yasutaka</name>
<name id="38165" type="Music">Tateyama Akiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a series of adult visual novels developed by http://anidb.net/cr59694 [Neko Works].
http://anidb.net/ch92921 [Minazuki Kashou], a son of a long line of Japanese confection makers, moved out to open his own patisserie "La Soleil". When unpacking his stuff, Kashou found two of the catgirls ("neko") that his family had been raising hiding in the boxes: http://anidb.net/ch92919 [Chocola] and http://anidb.net/ch92920 [Vanilla]. He tried to send them back initially, but they begged and pleaded until he gave in. Now they run La Soleil together. They spent some great time with the help of http://anidb.net/ch92922 [Shigure], sister of Kashou, and other catgirls in their family: http://anidb.net/ch92923 [Azuki], http://anidb.net/ch92924 [Maple], http://anidb.net/ch92925 [Cinnamon] and http://anidb.net/ch92926 [Coconut].
One day, when Chocola goes out to run some errands, she meets a http://anidb.net/ch107901 [kitten]. The story starts with their encounter...
Source: Official website
Note: The first episode received a special screening at Anime Expo 2019 on 06.07.2019.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="182">3.84</permanent>
<temporary count="183">5.89</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>242917.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nekopara-anime.com/ja/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nekopara-anime.com/en/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nekopara#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ネコぱら</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5522</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369011</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22460</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nekopara_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=wSDfoGrDNjk</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=pKnjDJmJ910</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0845PD7DS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6023" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-01">
<name>cosplay restaurant</name>
<description>Cosplay restaurants are theme restaurants and pubs that originated in Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan around the year 1999. They include maid cafés and butler cafés, where the service staff dress as elegant maids, or as butlers. Such restaurants and cafés have quickly become a staple of Japanese otaku culture. Compared with service at normal cafés, the service at cosplay cafés involves the creation of a rather different atmosphere. The staff treat the customers as masters and mistresses in a private home rather than merely as café customers.
The popularity of the cosplay restaurants and maid cafés has spread to other regions in Japan, such as Osaka`s Den Den Town as well as other countries, such as Hong Kong, Taiwan, Singapore, Mexico, and Canada.
Often such cafés or a more simple kissaten, small Japanese-style coffee shops, are part of school festivals where the protagonists` class runs one.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7496" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-01">
<name>preaired episodes</name>
<description>An anime has preaired episodes when one or more episodes, generally the first ones, were aired ahead of the usual schedule.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="92919" type="main character in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="12">8.27</rating>
<name>Chocola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bright, straightforward catgirl with an almost dog-like love for her master.
Alongside her twin, Vanilla they both share the title of youngest among the Minaduki catgirls. She isn`t well-suited to thinking about complicated things, but makes up for it with pure unbridled friendliness. With energy to spare at all times, she tends to leap into action before fully thinking things through. Despite her clumsy moments, her go-getter attitude earns plenty of love anyway.
Chocola and Vanilla were found as strays on the side of the road by the Minadukis. A few days after being adopted, they became ill due to refusing to eat, but recovered after being taken to a clinic. Chocola fell in love with Kashou at this point as he stayed and comforted them when they were sick.</description>
<picture>210987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43394" picture="220599.jpg">Yagi Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92920" type="main character in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="12">9.06</rating>
<name>Vanilla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A reserved-yet-clever catgirl of few words who absolutely loves Chocola.
Alongside her twin, Chocola, they both share the title of youngest among the Minaduki catgirls. Vanilla is prone to being misunderstood when she says too little, but she has remarkable insight and is quite sharp. Her sharp wit and I`ll-do-things-my-way attitude make her Chocola`s complete opposite. However, she remains at once both kind-hearted and, well, catlike.
She loves Chocola both as a sister and in a romantic manner, and sees Kashou as a love rival.
Chocola and Vanilla were found as strays on the side of the road by the Minadukis. A few days after being adopted, they became ill due to refusing to eat, but recovered after being taken to a clinic.</description>
<picture>210989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55415" picture="232227.jpg">Saeki Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92921" type="main character in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="13">5.64</rating>
<name>Minazuki Kashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minazuki Kashou is the protagonist of the Nekopara series and older brother of Shigure.
A patissier at Patisserie Soleil who left his home where his parents ran a Japanese confectionery to pursue his own dream. Applies himself so earnestly and thoroughly that his job and hobbies might as well be one and the same. Yet appealing to his humanity is all too easy, and he can`t help pampering the catgirls.</description>
<picture>210991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92922" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="12">7.19</rating>
<name>Minazuki Shigure</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kashou`s younger sister, and the catgirls` actual owner. Considerably younger than Kashou, she is still in that active and boisterous phase despite her attachment to him. She has quite the talent for economics and in fact secretly runs her own business. She can`t leave the nest yet, though, so she elects to help Kashou from the shadows, a hidden pillar of support. Not that she doesn`t run wild on occasion, of course.</description>
<picture>210992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92923" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="12">8.10</rating>
<name>Azuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A free spirit who doesn`t know fear, Azuki is the eldest of the Minaduki catgirls. Azuki never hides her true nature. She isn`t afraid to speak her mind, often with a few uncouth words. Most tasks are a nuisance to her at best, leaving her with little motivation to do them. She is actually quite capable, though, and can do almost anything if put to work (aside from physical labor, anyway). She has a complex about her body type, however—never, ever mention short legs around her.</description>
<picture>210993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92924" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-19">
<rating votes="15">7.72</rating>
<name>Maple</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A prideful, quick-thinking, and often domineering catgirl. She loves having the latest brand-name products, and never purrs for anyone except when she wants something from Shigure. She typically speaks frankly, but remains attentive to the attitudes of those around her. She is, as the saying goes, a scaredy-cat, always turning on every light on the way to the bathroom at night. Out of all of the catgirls, her tongue is the most sensitive to hot things.</description>
<picture>210994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37283" picture="238137.jpg">Itou Miku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92925" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="19">7.97</rating>
<name>Cinnamon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A relaxed, constantly-grinning lap catgirl. She is in fact a considerate and astute catgirl, often taking a motherly position among the others. She`s sensitive to erotic suggestion, and it doesn`t take much to put her panting in arousal. Her company demands others` patience in the face of her occasional masochistic fantasies. She`s also by far the most confident in her bust size among the catgirls.</description>
<picture>210995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41845" picture="242915.jpg">Noguchi Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92926" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="12">9.14</rating>
<name>Coconut</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall, cool-and-collected, glamorous catgirl. But despite her stature, she`s actually the third youngest after the twins. She has a mild complex about having a not-quite-feminine appearance, but her loyalty to her master (Shigure) is worlds beyond any dog`s and her Maine Coon strength is extraordinary. She loves helping people when she can, though this rarely ends well thanks to her poor coordination.</description>
<picture>210996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44831" picture="182444.jpg">Mizutani Marin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107901" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-15">
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<name>Cacao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52107" picture="228904.jpg">Morishima Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108297" type="appears in" update="2020-02-06">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218368" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「ネコぱら」TVアニメ化決定! 特報映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:09)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Nekopara" TV Anime-ka Kettei! Tokuhou Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224810" update="2019-11-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネコぱら PV "アニメまもにゃくスタート篇"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (2:07)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nekopara PV "Anime Mamonyaku Start Hen"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225607" update="2020-01-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ, ラ・ソレイユヘ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to La Soleil!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso, La Soleil e!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225608" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷子の仔ネコちゃん?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Lost Kitten?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maigo no Koneko-chan?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225609" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">気になるあの子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One on My Mind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ki ni Naru Ano Ko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225610" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Time...!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no...!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226265" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226266" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226293" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カカオの冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cacao`s Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cacao no Bouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226294" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義ニャき戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battles Without Honor and Cat-Humanity!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jingi Nyaki Ikusa!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226295" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネコたちのお留守番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">House-Sitting Cats</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neko-tachi no Orusuban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226296" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時雨の憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Shigure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigure no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227027" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホントノココロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honto no Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227028" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニャがーん! 鈴の更新試験</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh No! Bell Renewal Exams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nya Gaan! Suzu no Koushin Shiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227029" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カカオの恩返し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cacao Repays Her Debts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cacao no Ongaeshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227030" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏だ! 海だ! ネコぱらだいす!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Beach Cat Paradise!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Da! Umi Da! Neko Paradise!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
