<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14580" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lord El-Melloi II-sei no Jikenbo: Rail Zeppelin Grace Note</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Lord El-Melloi II Sei no Jikenbo: Rail Zeppelin Grace Note</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ロード・エルメロイⅡ世の事件簿 -魔眼蒐集列車 Grace note-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lord El-Melloi II`s Case Files: Rail Zeppelin Grace Note</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">君主·埃尔梅罗二世事件簿 -魔眼收集列车 Grace note-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14573" type="Prequel">Lord El-Melloi II-sei no Jikenbo: Rail Zeppelin Grace Note - Hakamori to Neko to Majutsushi</anime>
<anime id="3348" type="Same Setting">Fate/Stay Night</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="541081">this is not an action anime its a mystery anime where the main character solves different mystery  and at the same time  teaches magic in the clock tower 

in this you learn more about waver and  more about how the magic world works 

it has some  fights but the fight are not on the same level as  fate stay night  fate zero and fate unlimited blade works   so if you watch the fate series for the fights and action this one is not for you</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://anime.elmelloi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="12852" type="Chief Animation Direction">Satou Michio</name>
<name id="12790" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsumoto Masako</name>
<name id="6797" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakai Jun</name>
<name id="9841" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kusakabe Chizuko</name>
<name id="3652" type="Chief Animation Direction">Gouda Hiroaki</name>
<name id="6797" type="Character Design">Nakai Jun</name>
<name id="39148" type="Series Composition">Kodachi Ukyou</name>
<name id="38780" type="Work">Troyca</name>
<name id="927" type="Original Work">Type-Moon</name>
<name id="7180" type="Original Work">Sanda Makoto</name>
<name id="38556" type="Direction">Katou Makoto</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Waver Velvet – The boy who fought side by side with the King of Conquerors - Iskandar - during the Fourth Holy Grail War in Fate/Zero.
Time has passed, and the mature Waver has now adopted the name of Lord El-Melloi.
As Lord El-Melloi II, he challenges numerous magical and mystical cases in the Clock Tower, the mecca of all mages-----
Source: crunchyroll
Note: Episode 0 aired during "Fate Project New Year`s Eve TV Special 2018".</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="457">6.45</permanent>
<temporary count="461">7.16</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233639.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21727</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38959</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://anime.elmelloi.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://elmelloi-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Case_Files_of_Lord_El-Melloi_II</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ロード・エルメロイII世の事件簿</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5342</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366712</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>elmelloi_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5543" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-13">
<name>magic school</name>
<description>A school where magic is taught.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="38" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2581">8.43</rating>
<name>Saber</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saber, an agile and powerful warrior. Known as the King of Knights, she maintains a high code of honour. Saber is loyal, independent, and reserved; she appears cold, but is actually suppressing her emotions to focus on her goals. Her class is considered the "Most Outstanding", with excellent ratings in all categories.
In Fate/Zero, though she and Emiya Kiritsugu are Servant and Master seeking the same ultimate goal of peace, their differing ideological perspectives result in a strained relationship where Kiritsugu does not directly acknowledge Saber. After Kiritsugu summoned Saber, he made Irisviel hide Avalon - which had served as a catalyst to the summoning - inside her body so to serve as insurance while she performed her act of fake Master. Irisviel`s and Saber`s role at the time was to openly take action and serve as a decoy in order to lure out enemies, while Kiritsugu worked in the shadows with his assistant, Hisau Maiya. Because Saber could not dematerialise her spiritual body, she disguised herself as a man while staying at Irisviel`s side.
In the Fate route, because her master Emiya Shirou cannot effectively provide her with Mana, she minimises her activity to preserve what she has. Saber is bewildered by Shirou`s "protective" tendencies, and believes his erratic and reckless behaviour jeopardise her chances of winning the Holy Grail War.</description>
<picture>209482.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1951" type="appears in" update="2014-02-11">
<rating votes="7">4.69</rating>
<name>Majutsu Kyoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A trans-national, self-preservative organisation created by western magi for the purpose of controlling, concealing and developing Magecraft. Founded around the Middle Ages by those who foresaw the decline of Magecraft, they decided that in order to preserve their power Thaumaturgy should drift apart from society and become a secret known only by a necessary minimum number of people.
It has many laboratories and research bodies that seek to advance the progress of Thaumaturgy, as well as institutions that transmit their secrets to the next generation. Although the emphasis lies on the pursuit of knowledge, the Association also seeks to increase its own military strength so it can defend itself against those that might threaten it, such as the Holy Church, other mystic organizations and supernatural forces seeking punish mankind for meddling with areas that should not be touched.
The Mage`s Association is currently headquartered at the Clock Tower in London.</description>
<picture>150073.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25941" type="appears in" update="2013-07-21">
<rating votes="68">2.55</rating>
<name>Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Master of Lancer, Kayneth is a nobleman from the Magus Association, Lord of the house of El-Melloi and a prodigy at magecraft. His artifact is stolen by his pupil, Waver Velvet, but he manages to obtain another artifact and summon Lancer instead. While he holds the command spells for Lancer, the energy to materialize the Servant is maintained by Sola-Ui. He is confident in his abilities and takes pride in his heritage, but finds the extent of Kiritsugu`s untraditional and underhanded tactics both offensive and unexpectedly challenging to overcome.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>61345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25952" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="479">8.95</rating>
<name>Rider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rider`s identity is Iskander, the King of Conquerors, famous in history as Alexander the Great, who desires to defeat Saber in particular because he believes her ideals regarding kingship are delusional and that she would thrive as one of his followers. He derives his status as Rider from a set of divine bulls and chariot purportedly a gift from Zeus, known as Gordius Wheel: Wheel of Heaven`s Author, summoned when Iskander slices the air with his Sword of the Kupriotes. His eccentric and overbearing personality along with his incredible abilities creates difficulties for his Master and their opponents. He is notably the only Servant that Gilgamesh truly respects as an equal, the latter inviting him to challenge him in combat as many times as he wished. His first Noble Phantasm is Via Expugnatio: Distant Trampling Domination, the trampling attack used by the Gordius Wheel, which causes lightning strikes upon movement, inflicting massive damage to whatever is in its path. His second and most powerful Noble Phantasm is Ionioi Hetairoi: Army of the King, which is a Reality Marble, a self-contained miniature world that contains thousands of the most trusted of his soldiers who fought alongside him in life resurrected as temporary Servants, marching upon an endless plain of sand.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>61348.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25960" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="227">6.99</rating>
<name>Archer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Archer, the King of Heroes, Gilgamesh, is summoned to the 4th Holy Grail War was the Servant of http://anidb.net/ch25942 [Toosaka Tokiomi], but eventually joins forces with http://anidb.net/ch1916 [Kotomine Kirei]. He survives the 4th Holy Grail War and stays as pretty much of a rogue Servant throughout the 10 years between the 4th and 5th Holy Grail Wars, and takes part in the latter as an 8th, irregular Servant. He dislikes the presence of http://anidb.net/ch38 [Saber] and http://anidb.net/ch25952 [Rider] in particular, since both were kings like he was, but he lusts towards Saber and spares no effort to add her to his endless list of belongings. Much to Tokiomi`s displeasure, Archer has difficulty acting covertly, since he has a strong tendency to show off, and he has trouble regaining his temper when his enormous pride is wounded.</description>
<picture>44105.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35475" type="appears in" update="2011-08-15">
<rating votes="47">3.17</rating>
<name>Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri is the daughter of the head of the spiritual evocation division. She is engaged to Kayneth as a result of a strategic marriage arrangement and the decision of her family to entrust their crest to her brother instead. However, she is coldhearted and does not reciprocate Kayneth`s love for her; instead, she becomes infatuated with Lancer, who in turn does not reciprocate her feelings and regards her only as his Master`s wife.</description>
<picture>44096.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57870" type="main character in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="39">7.45</rating>
<name>Lord El-Melloi II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85946" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-15">
<rating votes="36">4.29</rating>
<name>Olgamally Animusphere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89992" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="14">6.33</rating>
<name>Shishigou Kairi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shishigou Kairi is a freelance necromancer. He summoned http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Saber of Red] with a splinter of the Round Table.
Kairi is the seventh generation head of the Shishigou family, surprising for a family whose origins lie in the Far East where magecraft had a lesser standing. It was thought that he would follow in the footsteps of his father, Touki Shishigou, whose treatise had been highly praised at the Clock Tower of the Mage`s Association. The curse of the previous Shishigou generation has activated on Kairi, resulting him unable to produce children. His parents decided that Kairi should adopt a distant relative as his daughter, who they hoped will receive his Magic Crest. Unfortunately, she died as they tried transferring Kairi`s Crest onto her. He was devastated when she died and accepted that the Shishigou would end with his generation. Rather than following the similar path of a researcher, he left his family and education behind him before the end of his third year there, taking on the path of a bounty hunter and freelancer. He didn`t cut all ties with the Association and latest job he took was from http://anidb.net/ch91565 [Rocco Belfeban].
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89994" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="11">4.56</rating>
<name>Fiore Forvedge Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fiore Forvedge Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88736 [Archer of Black]`s Master and a magus with great talent who is well versed in spiritual evocation and human engineering. She has been confined to a wheelchair since birth and wishes to have the Grail to heal her legs while keeping her magus abilities (something that would not be possible otherwise).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209558.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89995" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="7">3.48</rating>
<name>Caules Forvedge Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caules Forvedge Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88740 [Berserker of Black]`s Master and an magus who can summon low-class spirits, insects and animals.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91565" type="appears in" update="2017-09-26">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Rocco Belfeban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91566" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="8">4.79</rating>
<name>Flat Escardos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93235" type="main character in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="40">7.52</rating>
<name>Reines El-Melloi Archisorte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100127" type="main character in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="61">8.38</rating>
<name>Gray</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100128" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="4">6.63</rating>
<name>Add</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100130" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="4">5.02</rating>
<name>Svin Glascheit</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102568" type="appears in" update="2019-09-16">
<name>Inorai Valueleta Atroholm</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102569" type="appears in" update="2019-09-16">
<name>Bram Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104564" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="7">5.79</rating>
<name>Yvette L. Lehrman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54819" picture="245730.jpg">Okasaki Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104565" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="7">6.57</rating>
<name>Luviagelita Edelfelt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104566" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Melvin Weins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Mage affiliated with the Creation department at the Clock Tower. Born with a feeble body, he often coughs up blood. He is a long-standing acquaintance of Lord El-Melloi II, and is the only one that still calls him "Waver Velvet".
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>236518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105750" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-30">
<rating votes="4">7.05</rating>
<name>Adashino Hishiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105751" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hephaestion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108151" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<name>Doctor Heartless</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="217915" update="2019-07-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バビロンと刑死者と王の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Babylon, the Condemned, and the Memories of the King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Babylon to Keishisha to Ou no Kioku</title>
<summary>Waver Velvet, who fought side by side with Iskandar during the Fourth Holy Grail War, receives a visit from Reines El-Melloi Archisorte and Melvin Weins. Reines asks Waver to help her with something as payment for the debt.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787064</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217916" update="2019-07-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七つの星と永遠の檻[はこ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seven Stars and the Eternal Cage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanatsu no Hoshi to Eien no Hako</title>
<summary>The difficult issue Reines and Melvin brought up with Lord El-Melloi II was a case involving a former student of his, Mary Lil Fargo.  Mary is the only daughter of the Fargo family, a branch of the Animusphere family that rules over the Astromancy division. Responding to Mary who felt she needed her former mentor`s assistance, Lord El-Melloi II and Gray visit the Fargo estate to witness the dismantled corpse of Mary`s father, Ernest Fargo. Disjoined from traditions of Astromancy, the crime scene is representative of Modern Magecraft. Lord El-Melloi II dives in to elucidate the matter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787065</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217917" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷鳴と地下迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunder and the Underground Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raimei to Chika Meikyuu</title>
<summary>The rowdiness of the classroom seems like how it usually is in Modern Magecraft Theories, but there is something wrong with Lord El-Melloi II`s behavior. Luvia, who had come to visit and attend one of his lectures, asks Gray the reason why, and it turns out it`s because his favorite tearoom has basically closed shop. Lord El-Melloi II heads to the tearoom to inquire on their circumstances as he realizes work just can`t progress at this rate, but when he goes down into the sewer system to investigate, an ominous shadow attacks him. Gray, worried that he hasn`t shown any signs of returning from the investigation, seeks help from Flat and Svin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787066</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217918" update="2019-07-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">工房と塚と死霊魔術師[ネクロマンサー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Workshop, a Grave, and a Necromancer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koubou to Tsuka to Necromancer</title>
<summary>Primary Lecturer Wills is an authority in the Spiritual Evocation division. His father, Sir Trevor, owned the Marburry Workshop that utilizes an entire wasteland to operate as a Magical Workshop. However, the Workshop went out of control, causing many casualties including that of Sir Trevor himself. Lord El-Melloi II, seeking assistance from Spiritual Evocation in order to participate in the Holy Grail War, begrudgingly accepts the request to solve this case. However, what awaited the entourage who arrived at the mansion was Hishiri Adashino, a member of the Policies Department that investigates and enforces rules within the Clock Tower.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787067</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218676" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218677" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218820" update="2019-08-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最果ての槍と妖精眼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lance That Shines to the End of the World and the Fairy Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saihate no Yari to Yousei Me</title>
<summary>As the investigation in Marburry Workshop continues, lightning strikes yet again to create a new victim. Lord El-Melloi II and Hishiri Adashino once again are on opposing grounds concerning the perpetrator of this case. Lord El-Melloi II seeks the help of the Necromancer Kairi Shishigou to reinvestigate. Gray and Shishigou are assaulted by a fierce beast, the Black Dog, that suddenly appeared before them. Based on the fact that the Black Dog reacted to Gray`s Mystic Code, Lord El-Melloi II elicits a certain conclusion. He then starts preparing for a ritual with the assistance of all Mages who were gathered at Marburry Workshop.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787068</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218821" update="2019-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女とデパートとプレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Girl, a Department Store, and a Gift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo to Depaato to Present</title>
<summary>One peaceful day, Gray heads by herself to see Reines. With an unexpected turn of events, the two head out to Carnac, an established department store, to go shopping. Not accustomed to shopping in a department store, Gray continually is at Reines` mercy. Furthermore, Luvia coincidentally joins the two midway, causing the three girls to start a tea party.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787069</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218822" update="2019-08-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔眼蒐集列車1/6 汽笛と第一の殺人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rail Zeppelin 1/6: A Train Whistle of Departure and the First Murder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magan Shuushuu Ressha 1/6: Kiteki to Daiichi no Satsujin</title>
<summary>King of Conquerors Iskandar`s Relic was stolen from Lord El-Melloi II`s possession. An invitation from Rail Zeppelin, the train said to have dealings of Mystic Eyes, was left in its place. Lord El-Melloi II, with Gray and Caules in tow, head towards Rail Zeppelin. Various faces have gathered at the train, such as Hishiri Adashino from Policies, Yvette from the El-Melloi Class, Olga-Marie Arsimilat Animusphere who is the daughter of the Lord of Astromancy, and even Karabo Frampton from the Holy Church. The train departs, together with the various agendas of the passengers...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787070</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218823" update="2019-08-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔眼蒐集列車2/6 神威の車輪[ゴルディアス・ホイール]と征服王の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rail Zeppelin 2/6: Gordius Wheel and the Memory of the King of Conquerors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magan Shuushuu Ressha 2/6: Gordius Wheel to Seifuku Ou no Kioku</title>
<summary>An incident occurs where Trisha Fellows is murdered by someone aboard the Rail Zeppelin. Lord El-Melloi II undertakes the investigation for the case, but Olga-Marie has doubts about his way of life as it is far from how a Mage should act. Meanwhile, Shishigou and Luvia, under Reines` orders, are conducting their own investigation. The Mystic Eyes Collection Train begins its procession once again, and a mysterious figure appears before Lord El-Melloi II and Gray. The assailant who descends upon the pair with overwhelming power is the materialization of a Heroic Spirit engraved into human history... A Servant.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787071</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219459" update="2019-09-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔眼蒐集列車3/6 巫女と決意と腑海林[アインナッシュ]の仔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rail Zeppelin 3/6: A Sibyl, Decision, and Child of Einnashe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magan Shuushuu Ressha 3/6: Miko to Ketsui to Einnashe no Ko</title>
<summary>While giving the gravely wounded Lord El-Melloi II an arduous treatment, Gray and the others harbor doubts about an existence of a Servant whose Master is nowhere to be seen. Shishigou and Luvia are continuing their investigation in London where they visit Jean-Mario Supinerra and inquire about a serial murder that took place seven years ago. The respite was momentary as the course of the Rail Zeppelin has been altered, and the train plunges into the Forest of Dead Apostles, the Child of Einnashe. Gray, worried about the weakened Lord El-Melloi, decides to assist Karabo`s group that is acting to resume the train`s progress. Furthermore, Melvin, who has arrived at the Mystic Eyes Collection Train after hearing of rumors, joins the entourage. Olga Marie, barricading her lonely self after refusing to help Gray, finds a "certain something" in her own room.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787072</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219460" update="2019-09-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔眼蒐集列車4/6 泡影の魔眼と目覚める探偵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rail Zeppelin 4/6: Mystic Eyes of Transience and an Awakening Detective</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magan Shuushuu Ressha 4/6: Houei no Magan to Mezameru Tantei</title>
<summary>Gray and the Servant Hephaestion clash within the Child of Einnashe. However, they are engulfed in an avalanche, inevitably forcing a cease-fire. While they temporarily sheathe their weapons, they speak to each other about their ideologies about the relationship between Masters and Servants. Shishigou and Luvia find out that Trisha was investigating about the serial murders from seven years ago and about the Holy Grail War, and see the link between her and the Rail Zeppelin. As various speculations intertwine, Adashino begins to disclose her own deductions in place of Lord El-Melloi II aboard the Mystic Eyes Collection Train...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787073</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219461" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔眼蒐集列車5/6 残像とオークション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rail Zeppelin 5/6: The Residual Image and Auctions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magan Shuushuu Ressha 5/6: Zanzou to Auction</title>
<summary>As Adashino`s deductions are playing out, Lord El-Melloi II makes his comeback. He sees a clue to the identity of the true perpetrator of Trisha`s murder from Gray`s testimony, and requests Melvin to delay the Mystic Eyes Auction from starting. His objective is to seek assistance from Olga Marie, and grasp conclusive evidence to overturn Adashino`s deductions. Meanwhile, in London, Shishigou gathers up Flat and Svin in order to proceed with certain preparations. As each of them reflect upon their own ideas, the fated Mystic Eyes Auction finally begins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787074</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219462" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔眼蒐集列車6/6 雷光と流星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rail Zeppelin 6/6: Lightning and Shooting Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magan Shuushuu Ressha 6/6: Raikou to Ryuusei</title>
<summary>Caules Forvedge is suddenly apprehended as the perpetrator. As Lord El-Melloi II causes the Mystic Eyes Auction to pause while disclosing his deductions, Reines, who is supposedly still in London, rushes over to his side. Thus, Lord El-Melloi II points out the name of the true perpetrator.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787075</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="220958" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時計塔と日常と未来への第一歩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Clock Tower, Usual Days, and the First Step Forward to the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokeitou to Nichijou to Mirai e no Daiippo</title>
<summary>Several days after the incident on the Mystic Eyes Collection Train, there was a solemn ritual at Modern Magecraft Theories for Svin`s ascendance to the rank of Pride. Lord El-Melloi II looked upon the ritual full of emotion as this ascendance to Pride was while his student was still in his teens. Meanwhile, Gray could not shake off the uneasiness that Lord El-Melloi II would depart for distant lands to participate in the Holy Grail War. While in thought, she bumps into Melvin in the streets bustling with the approach of Christmas.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787076</identifier>
<identifier>lord-el-melloi-iis-case-files-rail-zeppelin-grace-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
