<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14622" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-06-13</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mutafukaz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="short">MFKZ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ムタフカズ -MUTAFUKAZ-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mutafukaz</title>
</titles>
<url>http://mutafukaz.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="738" type="Animation Work">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="14845" type="Direction">Nishimi Shoujirou</name>
</creators>
<description>After a scooter accident provoked by a mysterious woman`s vision, Angelino, a deadbeat like thousands of others in Dark Meat City, starts getting violent migraines that are accompanied by strange hallucinations. Along with his good buddy Vinz, he tries to figure out what`s happening to him while threatening men in black seem determined to catch him.
Source: Annecy
Note: The movie premiered at the Annecy International Animated Film Festival on 13.06.2017. Regular cinematic release started in France on 23.05.2018 and in Japan on 12.10.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="68">6.60</permanent>
<temporary count="68">6.84</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>229281.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38292</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mutafukaz.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mutafukaz.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mutafukaz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ムタフカズ_-MUTAFUKAZ-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365144</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mutafukaz_ja</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3430" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-04">
<name>Western comics</name>
<description>This anime is based on a western comic book.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="212066" update="2019-01-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2017-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
