<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14631" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aikatsu Friends! Kagayaki no Jewel</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アイカツフレンズ! ~かがやきのジュエル~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">偶像活动Friends～闪耀的宝石～</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15047" type="Sequel">Aikatsu on Parade!</anime>
<anime id="13755" type="Prequel">Aikatsu Friends!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.aikatsu.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="58474" type="Music">Digz Motion Sounds</name>
<name id="18168" type="Character Design">Watanabe Satomi</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="42824" type="Original Work">BN Pictures</name>
<name id="1051" type="Original Plan">Bandai</name>
<name id="18739" type="Direction">Igarashi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="18168" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Satomi</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="18">6.95</permanent>
<temporary count="18">6.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>229694.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39078</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.aikatsu.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Aikatsu_Friends!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アイカツフレンズ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5239</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367011</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21041</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>aikatsu_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94930" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-06">
<name>Coco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94931" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<rating votes="3">2.80</rating>
<name>Yuuki Aine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54473" picture="215912.jpg">Matsunaga Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94932" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<name>Hinata Ema</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54474" picture="215913.jpg">Ninomiya Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94933" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Asuka Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94934" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<name>Minato Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94935" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<name>Kamishiro Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33509" picture="204529.jpg">Tadokoro Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94936" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<name>Chouno Maika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5077" picture="28885.jpg">Miyama Karen</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95229" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-27">
<rating votes="2">8.26</rating>
<name>Enjouji Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Mio and Aine`s manager, her office being in Production Room No. 3 of Star Harmony Academy</description>
<picture>216775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95230" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-27">
<name>Hachiya Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiharu is also the top designer of Sugar Melody.</description>
<picture>216776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95231" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-27">
<name>Mayuzumi Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hair makeup and lesson coach</description>
<picture>216777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97509" type="main character in" update="2018-08-16">
<name>Shirayuri Sakuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66480.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="53351" picture="211867.jpg">Suyama Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97924" type="appears in" update="2018-09-10">
<name>Manami Marin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223519.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="97925" type="appears in" update="2018-09-10">
<name>Shinkai Rinna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223521.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="100983" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-21">
<name>Yuuki Momone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40353" picture="225072.jpg">Takada Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100984" type="main character in" update="2019-04-05">
<name>Shirayuri Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100985" type="appears in" update="2019-02-21">
<name>Hirata Himari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100986" type="appears in" update="2019-02-21">
<name>Inoue Iroha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23517" picture="77564.jpg">Tomioka Misako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102088" type="main character in" update="2019-05-21">
<name>Tenshou Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102089" type="main character in" update="2019-05-21">
<name>Alicia Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102090" type="main character in" update="2019-05-21">
<name>Harukaze Wakaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="58004" picture="234479.jpg">Aira Rin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102104" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Penne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102105" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Yuuki Yoshitsune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38924" picture="188476.jpg">Saitou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102106" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Yuuki Suzune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34880" picture="130561.jpg">Fuku Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102107" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Yuuki Kazune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102108" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Yuuki Nene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102113" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102120" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Chouno Maito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102122" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Haryuu Rokushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102127" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Masuda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102128" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Habara Mamiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38232" picture="140073.jpg">Asai Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102129" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232513.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102130" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Michi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232514.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102175" type="appears in" update="2019-04-13">
<name>Charles Charlotte</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44400" picture="181318.jpg">Wakui Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102177" type="appears in" update="2019-04-13">
<name>Nonomura Nonoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43558" picture="235945.jpg">Takayanagi Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102178" type="appears in" update="2019-04-13">
<name>Tsukino Tsukasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57152" picture="228647.jpg">Shibata Mei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102179" type="appears in" update="2019-04-13">
<name>Yukimura Yuzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232582.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102182" type="appears in" update="2019-04-13">
<name>Minamino Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232585.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="103885" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Natsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Hibiki`s assistant. Along with Hiro and Mana, the three are a part of Lovely Friends.</description>
<picture>235385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103886" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Hibiki`s assistant. Along with Natsu and Hiro, the three are a part of Lovely Friends.</description>
<picture>235386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40590" picture="159151.jpg">Nishida Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103887" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Hiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Hibiki`s assistant. Along with Natsu and Mana, the three are a part of Lovely Friends.</description>
<picture>235387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103889" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Leo Charlotte</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>is the father of the Charlotte children and the husband of Sophie Charlotte. He is the King of Sorbet Kingdom.</description>
<picture>235388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103890" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Sophie Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>is the mother of the Charlotte children and the wife of Leo Charlotte.</description>
<picture>235389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103891" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Aira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103892" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Neve</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36620" picture="134995.jpg">Ayase Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103893" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Nejyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235392.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57976" picture="234256.jpg">Takahashi Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103894" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Shune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235393.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="103895" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Otenki Daijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103896" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Uranai Daijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103897" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103898" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Byakuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Disguised as twins.</description>
<picture>235397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53526" picture="242924.jpg">Hasegawa Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103899" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Kodomo no Fan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57152" picture="228647.jpg">Shibata Mei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103900" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48929" picture="198268.jpg">Yamaguchi Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103901" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Snow Dan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103902" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35750" picture="131611.jpg">Mizuma Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108997" type="appears in" update="2020-04-01">
<name>Kobayakawa Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a cousin and sister figure to Wakaba Harukaze. She also aspires to be a film director.</description>
<picture>245551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32911" picture="230127.jpg">Furuki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108998" type="appears in" update="2020-04-01">
<name>Kouhai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40199" picture="156640.jpg">Nitta Hiyori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109077" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-03">
<name>Yuuki Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109155" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109156" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109172" type="appears in" update="2020-04-07">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109173" type="appears in" update="2020-04-07">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109174" type="appears in" update="2020-04-07">
<name>Obaa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109182" type="appears in" update="2020-04-07">
<name>Gankoyama Onizaemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4742" picture="54426.jpg">Fukumatsu Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="213408" update="2019-03-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙から来たアイドル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu kara Kita Idol</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213409" update="2019-03-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かがやきの原石</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayaki no Genseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213410" update="2019-03-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひびきのショータイム!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibiki no Showtime!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213411" update="2019-03-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かがやけ! あたしの色!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayake! Atashi no Iro!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214783" update="2019-04-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214784" update="2019-04-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215625" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャッフル!? フレンズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuffle!? Friends!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215626" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">君だってMyStar</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi Datte My Star</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215627" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">GoGo☆ソルベット王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go Go Sorbet Oukoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="215628" update="2019-04-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">Oujo Alicia</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">王女アリシア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217109" update="2019-05-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">合言葉はキスイダツカイア!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aikotoba wa Kisuida Tsukaia!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217110" update="2019-05-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイカツ! 禁止令!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aikatsu! Kinshi Rei!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217111" update="2019-05-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心の扉をあけて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Tobira o Akete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217112" update="2019-05-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達かえる♪パーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi Kaeru Party</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217113" update="2019-05-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すべての道はアイカツに通ず!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete no Michi wa Aikatsu ni Tsuuzu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218316" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハニーキャットはギャラクシー☆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honey Cat wa Galaxy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218317" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキ♥フレンズデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki Friends Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218318" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わかば, まるっとやっちゃうぞ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaba, Marutto Yacchauzo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218632" update="2019-07-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミライから, 未来へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai kara, Mirai e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218633" update="2019-07-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビュンビュン! 激走カレン島!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byun Byun! Gekisou Karen Shima!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218634" update="2019-07-11">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなでウミカツ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna de Umi Katsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218635" update="2019-07-11">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなるステージへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Stage e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219208" update="2019-08-08">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくやの思い, かぐやの願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuya no Omoi, Kaguya no Negai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219209" update="2019-08-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">LOVE ME TEAR</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Me Tear</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219210" update="2019-08-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジュエリングフェスティバル前夜祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dueling Festival Zen`yasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219211" update="2019-08-08">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時を超えたステージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Koeta Stage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219587" update="2019-08-22">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりじゃない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori ja Nai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219588" update="2019-08-22">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなみんなフレンズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna Minna Friends!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
