<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14680" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-05-08</startdate>
<enddate>2017-05-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eievui to Colorful Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Eevee and Colorful Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">イーブイとカラフルフレンズ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="230" type="Other">Pocket Monsters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://www.pokemon.co.jp/sp/eievui2017/</url>
<description>A short animation promoting a new line of Eevee merchandise. The short features Eevee and its evolutions.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="14">2.86</permanent>
<temporary count="14">4.78</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>239870.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35551</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pokemon.co.jp/sp/eievui2017/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>pokemonart/status/864153511600295936</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="449" type="main character in" update="2020-01-08">
<name>Eievui</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eevee is a Normal-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves into one of eight different Pokémon through various methods. It also has a Gigantamax form.
Eevee is the game mascot and starter Pokémon in Pokémon: Let`s Go, Eevee!, as well as for the main characters of Pokémon XD: Gale of Darkness and Pokémon Conquest. It is also the rival`s starter Pokémon in Pokémon Yellow, although Professor Oak originally intended to give it to the player.
Eevee is a mammalian, quadruped Pokémon with primarily brown fur. The tip of its bushy tail and its large furry collar are cream-colored. It has short, slender legs with three small toes and a pink paw pad on each foot. Eevee has brown eyes, long pointed ears with dark brown interiors, and a small black nose. Eevee is rarely found in the wild and is mostly only found in cities and towns. However, Eevee is said to have an irregularly shaped genetic structure that is easily influenced by its environment. This allows it to adapt to a variety of habitats by evolving. Eevee is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive Z-Move Extreme Evoboost.
In Pokémon: Let`s Go, Eevee!, the player starts with a special Eevee known as a Partner Eevee. The Partner Eevee has purple eyes and a lighter shade of fur. These design elements likely taken from the anime, which implemented similar traits starting in the Advanced Generation series. The marking on the tip of a female Partner Eevee is heart-shaped. Before Pokémon Sword and Shield, this trait was unique and wasn`t found on other female Eevee. Partner Eevee has higher base stats and access to moves that normal Eevee do not. Partner Eevee is the only Pokémon capable of performing Bouncy Bubble, Buzzy Buzz, Sizzly Slide, Glitzy Glow, Baddy Bad, Sappy Seed, Freezy Frost, Sparkly Swirl, and the Partner Power, Veevee Volley. In Pokémon Sword and Shield, the unique pattern is present on all female Eevee as a true gender difference.
As Gigantamax Eevee, it has become larger and more fluffy. The fur collar becomes longer with several triangular furs pointing straight up. The right ear has three red clouds surrounding it like a circle. Due to the fur becoming fluffier and luxurious, any enemies caught in it will lose the will to fight due to being enamored by its presence. Due to Gigantamaxing, Eevee becomes even more playful and rambunctious, desiring to play with its opponent and often unintentionally crushing them with its size.
Gigantamax Eevee is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Cuddle.</description>
<picture>68375.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="450" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Showers</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vaporeon is one of the evolutions of Eevee that is caused by radiation from a water stone. Upon evolving, it gains fins and gills that give it the ability to live underwater. It has small scales that are hard to see. Its finned tail is similar to a mermaid`s, so it is often mistaken for one. Vaporeon`s cells are similar in structure to water molecules, and this allows it to have a unique control over the water around it. This includes being able to transform itself into liquid as a form of camouflage (this being portrayed in the games as its ability to learn the attack Acid Armor), and detect rain through subtle vibrations in its fins. Its base scale color is aqua with darker aqua that makes a line along the spine from the tail to the neck where it forms into a base for its white frill. A darker-aqua patch on the head is similar in shape to a diving cap, and upon the head are three yellow fins, two resembling ears, and the middle one, a Dorsal fin. Its ability is `Water Absorb`, which allows it to gain HP when struck with a water type move.</description>
<picture>243023.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="451" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Thunders</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jolteon is one of the evolutions of Eevee that is caused by radiation from a thunder stone. Jolteon is covered with spiky, bright yellow fur, with white spiky fur surrounding its neck. Its fur sparks with electricity constantly; it can be soft to the touch or turn into sharp needles that can be fired when it is angered. Jolteon is able to gather negative ions from the atmosphere, using the resulting electricity to create lightning bolts of up to 10,000 volts. Its individual cells also create small electrical charges on their own, which combined with the static electricity caused by its body can result in powerful electric-type attacks. It`s very sensitive which causes it to constantly charge as it quickly changes moods. It can also make lightning and cause small thunderstorms. In the Pokémon video games, Jolteon can absorb electric attacks and turn them into HP (Health Point, or Health) with the ability `Volt Absorb`.</description>
<picture>243024.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="452" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Booster</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flareon is one of the evolutions of Eevee that is caused by exposure to a Fire Stone. It has a red body and thick, yellow fur on its face, head, neck, and tail. Its ears are as long as the Jolteon`s. It stores thermal energy from the sun, causing its body temperature to skyrocket to more than a range of 1600 degrees Celsius, releasing its flames from an internal sack. Its ability is `Flash Fire` which negates fire-type moves against it and increases its attack by 1.5 times damage if hit by a damaging fire attack.</description>
<picture>243025.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="603" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="5">10.00</rating>
<name>Eifie</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Espeon is an evolved cat-like form of Eevee that became available with the Japanese release of Pokémon Gold and Silver. The appearance of Espeon is said to resemble the Japanese mythological creature known as Nekomata which also displays the feline body with forked tail tip and solid colored eyes. An Espeon`s fur is used to sense air currents, allowing it to predict the weather, as well as the actions of its opponent in battle. Its forked tail quivers when this occurs. A red jewel rests on its head, and glows whenever Espeon uses its psychic abilities. Espeon are described as being very loyal to their trainers once they consider them worthy. They are also said to develop precognitive abilities in order to protect their trainers, Espeon become enabled to see into the future to identify potential threats. Eevee evolves into Espeon by having a high happiness level and leveling up during the day. A Sun Shard item can also be used in Pokémon XD, a Sun Ribbon in Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Blue, Red, Explorers of Time, and Explorers of Darkness. Espeon`s name is derived from "ESP" and the suffix "-eon", as with every evolution of Eevee.</description>
<picture>243080.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="604" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Blacky</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Umbreon is one of two Eevee evolutions that first featured in Pokémon Gold and Silver, the other being Espeon. It is called the "Moonlight" Pokémon. It has rabbit-like features displayed strongly in the shape of its head and eyes, a reference to the Japanese idea that you can see the head of a rabbit on the face of the moon. One of Umbreon`s most noticeable features is the yellow rings visible around its body. The Pokédex states that the rings will glow when Umbreon leaps to attack, becomes excited, or when there is a full moon. Umbreon are said to evolve as a result of love for their trainers and the moonlight; forcing one to walk during the day can also cause stress to it. They are described as preferring to lurk in darkness while waiting for their opponents to make the first move. If angered, they can secrete powerful poisonous sweat from their pores.</description>
<picture>243081.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1258" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Leafia</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leafeon is covered with tattered leaves, along with moss-green fur. Besides leaf-like ears and tail, there are a multitude of smaller leaves growing from the knee joint, chest, and back. A larger, curled leaf grows from the middle of its forehead, and is the same soft green color as all of the other leaves. Leafeon has plant-like characteristics alongside its animal nature; as such, it is photosynthetic, and, as a result, it is always surrounded by clean air.</description>
<picture>243407.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1259" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Glacia</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Glaceon, known as the Fresh Snow Pokémon, is one of two evolutions of Eevee that is obtained from training it in a certain location, the other evolution being Leafeon. The location necessary to evolve Eevee into Glaceon is on route 217 in the Sinnoh region. There is an ice covered rock here, but it is also possible to level up anywhere in grass on route 217 to evolve. Being an ice-type, it prefers cold climates, and as a protective measure it freezes its fur completely. This freezing causes the hair to resemble "ice needles."
In the Anime, May`s Eevee evolved into a Glaceon prior to her reappearance in the episode 544 `Restaurant Seven Stars! Tag Battle for a Full Course!` and Bianca got a same Eevee and now evolved into Glaceon nicknamed Iceshocker.</description>
<picture>243408.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61284" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-12">
<name>Nymphia</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sylveon (ニンフィア), the Intertwining Pokémon, is a Fairy type Pokémon and a brand new evolution of the first generation Pokémon Eevee. Its type was kept a mystery until the official reveal. Sylveon possesses abilities to move its antenna-like ribbons on its body which uses it to relieve the feelings of both humans and Pokémon. Also the ribbons act as a leash when it walks with its trainer. Sylveon can learn a new Fairy-type move, Moonblast, that allows it to borrow energy from the moon and attack the opponent with a powerful blast.
Sylveon appears in the short feature Pikachu and Eevee Friends that accompanies the film Pokémon the Movie: Genesect and the Legend Awakened in theaters, wherein it is voiced by Shoko Nakagawa.</description>
<picture>243654.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="222705" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
