<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14693" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchi no Ko no Tame Naraba, Ore wa Moshikashitara Maou mo Taoseru Kamo Shirenai.</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">우리 딸을 위해서라면, 나는 마왕도 쓰러뜨릴 수 있을지 몰라.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Uchi no Musume no Tame Naraba, Ore wa Moshikashitara Maou mo Taoseru Kamo Shirenai.</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">为了女儿，我说不定连魔王都能干掉</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">UchiMusume</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">うちの娘の為ならば, 俺はもしかしたら魔王も倒せるかもしれない.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">If It`s for My Daughter, I`d Even Defeat a Demon Lord</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Заради моєї донечки я навіть Володаря Демонів здолаю</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">为了女儿，我说不定连魔王都能干掉。</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8211" approval="14" total="28">Usagi Drop</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="162292">Pretty nice and charming series. even though its setted in a RPG Fantasy World, its focused on social relations and development. Easygoing and nice watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://uchinoko-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10027" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishida Miyako</name>
<name id="44568" type="Chief Animation Direction">Deguchi Kaho</name>
<name id="11814" type="Chief Animation Direction">Masudate Toshihide</name>
<name id="57478" type="Original Work">Chirolu</name>
<name id="57662" type="Animation Work">Maho Film</name>
<name id="44568" type="Character Design">Deguchi Kaho</name>
<name id="10027" type="Character Design">Nishida Miyako</name>
<name id="11814" type="Character Design">Masudate Toshihide</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="1506" type="Direction">Yanase Yuuji</name>
<name id="52500" type="Music">Yokoseki Kouta</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy adventure slice of life light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr57478 [Chirolu] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr57664 [Truffle] (Vol.1) and http://anidb.net/cr57665 [Kei] (Vol.2 - ).
http://anidb.net/ch100956 [Dale] is a cool, composed, and highly skilled adventurer who`s made quite a name for himself despite his youth. One day on a job deep in the forest, he comes across a little devil girl who`s almost wasted away. Unable to just leave her there to die, Dale takes her home and becomes her adoptive father. Devil or not, http://anidb.net/ch100957 [Latina] is beyond adorable, and the adventurer soon finds himself head over heels with being a parent. But why was she out in the forest to begin with, and why does she carry the mark of a criminal?
Source: J-Novel Club</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="515">4.96</permanent>
<temporary count="520">6.52</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236873.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22006</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://uchinoko-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>If_It's_for_My_Daughter,_I'd_Even_Defeat_a_Demon_Lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>うちの娘の為ならば、俺はもしかしたら魔王も倒せるかもしれない。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22044</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>uchinoko_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=aJT6_qQBYs8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=dbDovK5jB3E</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=jP0CnyAmxc0</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="100956" type="main character in" update="2019-02-20">
<name>Dale Leki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100957" type="main character in" update="2019-09-06">
<rating votes="6">9.09</rating>
<name>Latina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43732" picture="177230.jpg">Takao Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102290" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<name>Antony</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50468" picture="226248.jpg">Fukuhara Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102291" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<rating votes="1">5.74</rating>
<name>Chloe Schneider</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102292" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<name>Kenis Krugel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102293" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<rating votes="2">4.64</rating>
<name>Silvia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102294" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<name>Marcel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47407" picture="235753.jpg">Hirose Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102295" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<rating votes="2">4.58</rating>
<name>Rita Krugel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102296" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<name>Rudy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104368" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Sylvester</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104369" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Amos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104370" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Bosco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20273" picture="175422.jpg">Kijima Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104371" type="appears in" update="2019-07-26">
<name>Cedric</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5410" picture="222917.jpg">Douzaka Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104372" type="appears in" update="2019-07-26">
<name>Douglas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104451" type="appears in" update="2019-08-08">
<name>Smaragdi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104519" type="appears in" update="2019-07-18">
<name>Gregor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104520" type="appears in" update="2019-07-19">
<name>Eldstedt Koushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3965" picture="25836.jpg">Souya Shigenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104633" type="appears in" update="2019-07-26">
<name>Onna Shinkan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104634" type="appears in" update="2019-07-26">
<name>Shisai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38636" picture="228962.jpg">Takeuchi Emiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104787" type="appears in" update="2019-08-08">
<name>Farru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40355" picture="223014.jpg">Kamio Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104809" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Makuda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29850" picture="203454.jpg">Nakamura Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104810" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45696" picture="186024.jpg">Fukuo Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104811" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Yorck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38051" picture="188925.jpg">Yonai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104812" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Josef</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44871" picture="182505.jpg">Inoue Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104813" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Randolph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104814" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Vint</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104815" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Wendelgard</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3833" picture="25459.jpg">Shibahara Chiyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104948" type="appears in" update="2019-08-08">
<rating votes="2">4.76</rating>
<name>Helmine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104949" type="appears in" update="2019-08-08">
<name>Schmidt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104950" type="appears in" update="2019-08-08">
<name>Rudy Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45618" picture="185811.jpg">Nitta Anju</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104951" type="appears in" update="2019-08-08">
<name>Rudy Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38295" picture="222841.jpg">Yamashita Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105061" type="appears in" update="2019-08-16">
<rating votes="1">2.07</rating>
<name>Glaros</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36583" picture="134947.jpg">Kubota Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105156" type="appears in" update="2019-08-22">
<name>Ute</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36232" picture="136070.jpg">Nakajima Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105233" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Frida</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56011" picture="222827.jpg">Otagiri Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105234" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Izabine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46602" picture="224736.jpg">Kubota Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105287" type="appears in" update="2019-09-06">
<name>Cornelio Shifu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105288" type="appears in" update="2019-09-06">
<name>Clarissa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10951" picture="222825.jpg">Hara Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105289" type="appears in" update="2019-09-06">
<name>Hagel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42052" picture="225801.jpg">Ichikawa Taichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105376" type="appears in" update="2019-09-14">
<name>Shihesu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105507" type="appears in" update="2019-09-19">
<name>Teo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40353" picture="225072.jpg">Takada Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105508" type="appears in" update="2019-09-19">
<name>Mov</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238546.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="217922" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青年, ちいさな娘と出会う.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Man and the Little Girl Meet.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune homme rencontre la fillette</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinen, Chiisana Musume to Deau.</title>
<summary>The adventurer Dale Reki is undertaking fairly typical mission when he finds a young devil girl, with a broken horn. Not willing to abandon her in the wilderness, he takes her back to the town he works out of, to see if he can help her find her way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786958</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217923" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちいさな娘, 新たな生活をはじめる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Girl Begins Her New Life.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette entame une nouvelle vie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Musume, Aratana Seikatsu o Hajimeru.</title>
<summary>While helping run errands in town, Latina gets lost and goes on a small adventure of her own, while Dale frantically searches for her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786959</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217924" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青年, 留守にする.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Man Heads Out.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune homme s’absente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinen, Rusu ni Suru.</title>
<summary>A job has Dale traveling to the royal capital, which means leaving Latina at home for several days. Will either of them manage without each other?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786960</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217925" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちいさな娘, その『事件』.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Girl and the "Incident."</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette et l`incident</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Musume, Sono "Jiken".</title>
<summary>Latina starts attending classes at the local temple, where she learns more about human society: for better, and for worse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786961</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218487" update="2019-07-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『うちの娘の為ならば, 俺はもしかしたら魔王も倒せるかもしれない.』アニメ化告知PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (0:38)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Uchi no Ko no Tame Naraba, Ore wa Moshikashitara Maou mo Taoseru Kamo Shirenai." Anime-ka Kokuchi PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218488" update="2019-07-03">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『うちの娘の為ならば, 俺はもしかしたら魔王も倒せるかもしれない.』第1弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:04)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Uchi no Ko no Tame Naraba, Ore wa Moshikashitara Maou mo Taoseru Kamo Shirenai." Dai 1 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218489" update="2019-07-03">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『うちの娘の為ならば, 俺はもしかしたら魔王も倒せるかもしれない.』第2弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (2:02)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Uchi no Ko no Tame Naraba, Ore wa Moshikashitara Maou mo Taoseru Kamo Shirenai." Dai 2 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218647" update="2019-07-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218648" update="2019-07-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218881" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちいさな娘, 雪に感激する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Girl Is Fascinated by the Snow.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette s’emballe pour la neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Musume, Yuki ni Kangeki Suru.</title>
<summary>As snow begins to fall in Kreuz, Latina comes up with an secret plan involving Dale.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786962</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218882" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼き少女, 旅に出る.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Girl Leaves on a Journey.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette part en voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osanaki Shoujo, Tabi ni Deru.</title>
<summary>Some unexpected news has Dale preparing to make the long trip back to his hometown, and Latina decides she wants to go with him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786963</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218883" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼き少女, 港町へ行く.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Girl Visits a Port Town.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette se rend dans une ville portuaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osanaki Shoujo, Minatomachi e Iku.</title>
<summary>Dale and Latina arrive in a port town where they encounter a musician that shares a secret with Latina.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786964</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218884" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青年, 故郷に着く.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Man Arrives at His Home Village.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune homme arrive dans son village natal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinen, Furusato ni Tsuku.</title>
<summary>After visiting with Dale`s cousin, he and Latina arrive in the village of Teathrow where they receive a spicy welcome.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786965</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219378" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青年, 弟の結婚式と幼い少女と.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Man Attends His Brother`s Wedding with the Young Girl.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune homme et la fillette au mariage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinen, otouto no kekkonshiki to osanai shoujo to.</title>
<summary>On the night of his brother`s wedding, Dale comes to terms with his position among the Teathrow, and the course of events that led him to meet Latina.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786966</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219379" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼き少女, クロイツに帰る.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Girl Returns to Kreuz.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette rentre à Kreuz.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osanaki Shoujo, Kreuz ni Kaeru.</title>
<summary>Dale and Latina begin their return to Kreuz, and along the way, pick up some souvenirs for their friends back home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786967</identifier>
<identifier>fr/if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219380" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼き少女とにゃんこパラダイス.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Girl and the Kitty Paradise.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fillette et le paradis des chats.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osanaki Shoujo to Nyanko Paradise.</title>
<summary>Latina`s made all kinds of friends since starting her life in Kreuz, but cats have managed to evade her so far. That changes when she and Dale are introduced to a trader from the east with a house full of furry friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786968</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219381" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼き少女, 願う.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Girl`s Wish.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le souhait de la fillette.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osanaki Shoujo, Negau.</title>
<summary>Rita`s baby is due soon, Latina`s tenure at school is ending, and changes is in the air. What ill the future hold for the young devil girl and her guardian?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786969</identifier>
<identifier>if-its-for-my-daughter-id-even-defeat-a-demon-lord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
