<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14701" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>21</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2020-02-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Radiant (2019)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Radiant S2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラディアン (2019)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Radiant (2019)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">虚空魔境 第二季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13767" type="Prequel">Radiant</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="14899">Season 2 was good, but there needs to be a season 3  because none of the questions for season 1 were technically explained.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="73747">S2 has the same tone as the previous season with magic, goofiness and fun times, but this season does get more serious at various points.  The new characters and adventures were a welcome sight.  Some questions were answered in this season, but a lot remains unanswered, so another season is needed to resolve the lingering questions and to focus on Radiant.  All in all, this was a good season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284604">Slow to start but built to an exhilarating climax which I enjoyed better than the first season where I had just considered the main protagonist annoying. Some of the villains` abilities were overpowered and resolutions predictable lots of loose ends.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://anime-radiant.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="46783" type="Character Design">Kawano Nozomi</name>
<name id="26894" type="Direction">Fukuoka Daiki</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="1234" type="Work">NHK Enterprises</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="53544" type="Original Work">Tony Valente</name>
<name id="4489" type="Direction">Kishi Seiji</name>
<name id="46783" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawano Nozomi</name>
<name id="37306" type="Music">Kouda Masato</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a French comic book series by http://anidb.net/cr53544 [Tony Valente].
http://anidb.net/ch98083 [Seth], http://anidb.net/ch94709 [Melie], and http://anidb.net/ch94708 [Doc] encounter new allies in Caislean Merlin – the stronghold of the Knights-sorcerers, a group that is also after the monster called Némésis. Seth`s adventure accelerates with the addition of http://anidb.net/ch105365 [Ocoho], a girl who hopes to become a Knights-sorcerer, a farewell with Melie and Doc, and a clash with the malicious Merchant-Barons! And all this with the Inquisition still at his heels!
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="148">5.88</permanent>
<temporary count="151">7.18</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>237759.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39355</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.nhk.or.jp/anime/radiant/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://anime-radiant.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Radiant_(TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ラディアン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5442</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367287</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21520</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nep_radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07Z7BTRRX</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3192" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-26">
<name>hidden base</name>
<description>Someone wants to be secretive when he plans to take over the world...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3423" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>religious persecution</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3430" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-04">
<name>Western comics</name>
<description>This anime is based on a western comic book.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3671" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>footage reuse</name>
<description>Footage reuse is the employment of a sequence of frames many times, generally as a side effect of a constrained anime production budget. This can happen by using the same footage once at a time, but many times over the course of the show, or by directly looping it. Types of scenes that tend to get reused include: transformations, such as those typical of superheroes or magical girls, characters that change into powered-up versions of themselves, or robots changing shape; attacks, especially when involving a series of steps that must be followed before the attack can be launched; and any kind of action that involves repeating the same movement.
This tag does not apply if the footage changes significantly between iterations. An example of that is the infamous Endless Eight arc of http://anidb.net/a6367 [the 2009 iteration of Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu]; even as the plot repeated itself, each episode of the arc showed it in different ways.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3823" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-03">
<name>recap in opening</name>
<description>A short recap of the previous episode(s) is included in the opening sequence. This can result in an opening longer than the traditional 1m30s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94706" type="main character in" update="2018-09-22">
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<name>Alma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94708" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Doc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94709" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="24">8.23</rating>
<name>Melie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98083" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Seth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105364" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Alkon Onna Danshaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105365" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Ocoho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10333" picture="170916.jpg">Fuchigami Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105366" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-14">
<name>Gulis-kyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105367" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="2">7.07</rating>
<name>Queen Boudica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105368" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Cristolom-danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105369" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Sagramore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43746" picture="240127.jpg">Kumagai Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105370" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Doussant-danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4687" picture="27301.jpg">Kinoshita Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105371" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<name>Pazz-danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105372" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Furgonde-danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105373" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<name>Furgonde-danshaku Fujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48852" picture="225071.jpg">Kohara Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105374" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Brangoire-kyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105375" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Mordred</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106345" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Myr</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106346" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Jill</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106347" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Diabal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106349" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<name>Verone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221454" update="2019-11-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる冒険へ -Overture-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toward a New Adventure: Overture</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nouvelle aventure: Overture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Bouken e: Overture</title>
<summary>Seth has set out on a new adventure to unravel the mysteries of Radiant. His destination is Caislean Merlin, the city of the Knights-sorcerers. He boards Alma`s airship and, along with Alma and her new helpers, Bossman and Jiji, heads for the continent of Cyfandir. Meanwhile, Dragunov, the Inquisition captain, visits the Inquisition`s holy land at General Torque`s order. He`s prepared to face capital punishment, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789393</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221455" update="2019-11-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧雨の邂逅 -Mist-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Encounter in the Rain: Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontre sous la bruine: Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirisame no Kaikou: Mist</title>
<summary>Seth parts ways with Alma and her helpers, and arrives at the continent of Cyfandir alone. There, he has an unexpected encounter with the Merchant Barons, who have come to this land to exploit its resources and see the sorcerer Seth as an enemy. Seth is backed into a corner by the Merchant Barons` fierce attacks, but finally escapes with Grimm`s help. When Seth finally arrives in the city, he`s surprised to see both sorcerers and ordinary humans living together... and admiring the Knights-sorcerers together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789394</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221456" update="2019-11-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">騎士の都 -Caislean Merlin-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The City of Knights: Caislean Merlin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La capitale des chevaliers: Caislean Merlin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishi no Miyako: Caislean Merlin</title>
<summary>Seth runs into Melie and Doc, but Melie is cold toward him and quickly leaves. So Seth heads to the castle to look for clues about Radiant, but he`s turned away at the gate. Then he encounters a myserious old man named Myr who leads him to the Knights-sorcerers` stables. There he meets an aspiring Knight-sorcerer named Ocoho, who`s preparing to set out on a mission to defeat a Nemesis. Seth is mistaken for a newbie and taken along...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789395</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221457" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">災いをよぶ者 -Dullahan-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bringer of Calamity: Dullahan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celle qui porte malheur: Dullahan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wazawai o Yobu Mono: Dullahan</title>
<summary>When the battle threatens to ruin farmland, Seth does his best to protect the crops. Ocoho is impressed and casts defensive magic to help him, but she`s reprimanded for going against orders. But then Queen Boudica appears and praises Ocoho for protecting the land as the legendary sorcerer Merlin did. The farmers also say that a spirit called the Dullahan started appearing in the area around the same time as the Spectral Nemesis...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789396</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222511" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨音静かに心は遠く -Rain-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silent Rain, Distant Hearts: Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pluie silencieuse, cœurs distants: Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amaoto Shizuka ni Kokoro wa Tooku: Rain</title>
<summary>Seth visits Melie at the inn where she`s staying, but she treats him coldly. Seth had left Artemis on his own because he didn`t want to hurt his friends with the power he couldn`t control, but Melie wanted Seth to have faith in her as his friend; the two of them just can`t see eye to eye. Seth is left with nowhere to go, but then Ocoho asks him to train with her, offering to look in the castle library for information on Radiant in return. But Seth still isn`t sure if he should be making new friends...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789397</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222512" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼[か]の者の名は -Diabal-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Name Is: Diabal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nom de cet homme: Diabel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ka no Mono no Na wa: Diabal</title>
<summary>Ocoho`s search for information on Radiant isn`t going well, so Seth makes up his mind to sneak into the castle archive himself. For some reason, even though he`s never been inside the castle before, he feels as if he knows it. He takes a hidden passage he`d seen before in his dreams, and beyond it, he sees a Nemesis and a young man. The young man reacts with fear upon seeing Seth`s horns and traps him within a barrier. While Seth is trapped, every move he makes is matched by a Spectre Nemesis somewhere in the world outside...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789398</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222513" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペクトル攻防戦 -Spectre-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spectre Battle: Spectre</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille des spectrums: Spectre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Spectrum Koubousen: Spectre</title>
<summary>A Nemesis that looks like Seth has appeared, brought forth by a mysterious man who lurks deep beneath the castle. He is the one who has been making the Spectre Nemesis appear. After making his way beneath the castle, Seth was attacked by a Nemesis and blacked out, finding himself trapped within the realm of his own consciousness. He comes face to face with his memories, which causes him to awaken in his berserk form.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789399</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222514" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時の森のセト -Caillte-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seth in the Forest of Time: Caillte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Seth, dans la forêt du temps: Caillte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki no Mori no Seto: Caillte</title>
<summary>The mysterious man, who claims to know Piodon, is terrified of Seth`s out-of-control form and ends up being blown out of the castle. When Seth disappears, Melie, Doc, and Ocoho follow traces of Fantasia to find him, but they end up in a forest that no one has ever escaped after entering. As they make their way through the forest, they find Myr and his wife Jill, who have been protecting Seth. He has become lost within the realm of consciousness, called Sidh, and refuses to leave because he`s afraid of his own power...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789400</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="223663" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謀略の王宮 -Palace-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Palace of Schemes: Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le palais des complots: Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bouryaku no Oukyuu: Palace</title>
<summary>Ocoho and Melie are blamed for disobeying orders in the previous battle, but Mordred saves them by telling the queen that it was all Lord Brangoire`s mistake. Seth, meanwhile, remains in Caillte`s forest, training so that he can learn to control his power. With the help of Myr and Jill, he learns how to harmonize with Fantasia, but when he tries to control the darkness inside him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789401</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224321" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">騎士の資格 -Quality-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Qualifications of a Knight: Quality</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La qualité de chevalier: Quality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishi no Shikaku: Quality</title>
<summary>Led by Lord Brangoire and Lord de Gulis, the Knights-sorcerers set out to battle a Nemesis that has appeared in the surrounding farmland. Ocoho is the only one who notices that the enormous Nemesis is actually a composite of several Echo Nemesis, which then split apart and begin rampaging as countless individuals. Ocoho calls for help, but no one can hear her, and she`s left with no choice but to disobey orders again. Using a powerful Gysoni spell, she forcibly takes over command from Lord Brangoire...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789402</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224322" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いま世界を感じて -Resonance-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Now, Feel the World: Resonance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À présent, ressens le monde: Resonance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima Sekai o Kanjite: Resonance</title>
<summary>Seth is still unable to control his rampaging power. He tries to suppress it by force, but only ends up closer to being completely engulfed by it. But by thinking about all the bonds and relationships he`s forged up to this point, Seth experiences an awakening and learns to use his power to create rather than destroy. He also learns that if he can use his power of creation correctly, the world that was once filled with pixies could be reborn. So Seth then leaves Myr with a new hope...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789403</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224323" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実は呪いのように -Ocoho-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth Is Like a Curse: Ocoho</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vérité est comme une malédiction: Ocoho</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjitsu wa Noroi no You ni: Ocoho</title>
<summary>As the town bustles in preparation for the upcoming ordination ceremony, Ocoho leaves quietly, avoiding being seen. Lord Brangoire grows suspicious of her behavior and attacks her. Melie stops him, but is shocked to see Ocoho starting to call forth a Spectre Nemesis. Seth stops Ocoho when she appears to go on a blind rampage, but when she returns to her senses, she doesn`t remember anything that`s happened. It`s clear that someone is manipulating her, but who is it?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789404</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224779" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の決意 -Knighthood-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Decision: Knighthood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ta détermination: Knighthood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Ketsui: Knighthood</title>
<summary>The one manipulating Ocoho was Mordred, but Mordred claims that Queen Boudica herself is a traitor with connections to a shady organization called the Faithful of the Hermit. Ocoho is left unsure what she should believe, but Seth`s advice helps her make a decision. On the day of the ordination ceremony, Ocoho exposes the truth and questions Queen Boudica in front of everyone, declaring that some of the knights are traitors.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789405</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225374" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦の大地 -Battlefield-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Battlefield: Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lieu de la bataille décisive: Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen no Daichi: Battlefield</title>
<summary>The ordination ceremony has been called off. Queen Boudica refuses to surrender and leads her forces in a do-or-die resistance. The Knights-sorcerers charge into battle, but they face a crisis when they lose the ability to use magic due to the strange machine supplied by the Merchant Barons. Meanwhile, Seth finds Diabal again underneath the castle, and Diabal tells him they are something like brothers. also, Doc finds a book called "Book of Truth" in the castle archive and hopes it will hold a clue to the location of Radiant, but then...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792546</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225375" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈落へ誘う滅びの調べ -Harmonizium-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Led to the Abyss by a Melody of Death: Harmonizium</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mélodie de la destruction, l`invitation en enfer: Harmonizium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naraku e Sasou Horobi no Shirabe: Harmonizium</title>
<summary>Diabal started cooperating with the Faithful of the Hermit in order to escape Piodon`s pursuit and protect his hiding place. Through the realm of consciousness, Sidh, Seth learns that a war has broken out above ground. He hurries back to the surface, but Melie is caught by Dragunov as bait to lure him. Meanwhile, Ocoho leaves the battlefield to follow Mordred and Sagramore... only to find them boarding the Merchant Barons` airship. When she does the same, Mordred reveals a shocking fact.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792547</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225376" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えゆく命の灯火 -Tragedy-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light of Life Is Extinguished: Tragedy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vie ne tient qu`à un fil: Tragedy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieyuku Inochi no Touka: Tragedy</title>
<summary>Mordred is revealed to have no emotions. He had infiltrated Caislean Merlin as a child and spent his life there creating chaos in anticipation of this day, all on his father`s orders. His father, Baron Doussant, has been working toward the goal of making all infected people into slaves. Back on lang, Queen Boudica flies into a rage and attempts to destroy the machine that`s negating Fantasia, but Santori`s attack drains the last of her energy. Ocoho is captured, and Sagramore crosses swords with their childhood friend, Mordred.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792548</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225578" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒き竜は舞い降りた -Pen Draig-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Dragon Descends: Pen Draig</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arrivée du dragon noir: Pen Draig</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroki Ryuu wa Maiorita: Pen Draig</title>
<summary>Dragunov had been told by General Torque that capturing Seth was his only objective, and that a military intervention was not his wish. But even after Dragunov reports that he has Seth, the Inquisition warships begin to bomb Caislean Merlin. Dragunov defies orders to join his former squadron and try to stop the war. Meanwhile, Seth takes on Santori, but is overwhelmed by his immense strength. Then a mysterious figure descends upon the battlefield...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792549</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226248" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝くは人の意思 -Resistance-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Will of the People Shines Bright: Resistance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La volonté des gens scintille: Resistance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayaku wa Hito no Ishi: Resistance</title>
<summary>The mysterious knight turned out to be Doc trapped in a suit of armor along with several memory stones. The soldiers race to rescue the queen, but Verone`s petrifying ability impedes them. Santori attempts to have some fun in his battle with Seth and ends up causing him to go berserk. Santori then talks about using people as if they were tools, causing him to explode with rage. Ocoho and Melie are also boiling with resentment in their respective battles against Doussant and Liselotte.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792550</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226249" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の声が聞こえない -Myrddin-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Hear Your Voice: Myrddin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je n`entends pas ta voix: Myrddin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Koe ga Kikoenai: Myrddin</title>
<summary>Cornered by Ocoho, the Merchant Barons show their true colors. It seemed this would be the end of the battle, but the when the Inquisitor Ullmina learns that Santori has been lost, she has an even more powerful Harmonizium dropped into the forest. The Fantasia there begins to disappear, and the soldiers under the control of Ullmina`s powerful miracle close in on the castle wall. Seth hurries to the forest, concerned about Myr and Jill, and he finds Myr in a state of despair. His grief over losing what was most precious to him then turns to intense rage...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792551</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226250" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">この大地に花束を -Fantasia-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bouquet of Flowers for This Land: Fantasia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une gerbe pour ces terres: Fantasia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Daichi ni Hanataba o: Fantasia</title>
<summary>Engulfed by despair, Myr sets out to on a rampage to destroy everything. Seth responds to Myr`s rampage by flying further out of control, and ends up captured by Ullmina. As the biggest crisis yet closes in, Ocoho grills the disheartened Queen Boudica on who she truly is. Encouraged by Ocoho`s words, Queen Boudica gets back on her feet to destroy the Harmonizium. With the help of Grimm and Dragunov, Melie rescues Seth, who returns to his right mind and sets out to stop Myr`s rampage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792552</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226251" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来は君とともに -Eternity-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Future Is with You: Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`avenir avec toi: Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai wa Kimi to Tomo ni: Eternity</title>
<summary>The thing that finally stops Myr`s rampage is a memento Seth found, left behind for him by Jill. Seeing new life growing before him, Myr finally finds hope again. After beginning to question the Inquisition`s intentions through this war, Dragunov returns to Bome to question General Torque. The long battle is over. All the people of Caislean Merlin gather as Queen Boudica declares an end to old conventions and appoints a new queen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792553</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
