<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14735" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>8</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-24</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Psycho-Pass 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">サイコパス 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">PSYCHO-PASS 3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">PSYCHO-PASS心靈判官 3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">心理测量者3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15308" type="Sequel">Psycho-Pass 3: First Inspector</anime>
<anime id="13894" type="Prequel">Psycho-Pass: Sinners of the System</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://psycho-pass.com/3rd/index.php</url>
<creators>
<name id="27223" type="Avatar Design">Yu-Pon</name>
<name id="6306" type="Music">Kanno Yuugo</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="2992" type="Direction">Shiotani Naoyoshi</name>
<name id="1963" type="Series Composition">Ubukata Tou</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
</creators>
<description>Two inspectors are newly assigned to the Public Safety Bureau`s Criminal Investigation Division Unit 1. http://anidb.net/ch101314 [Shindou Arata], Japanese and http://anidb.net/ch101315 [Kei Michael Ignatov], East European who has been naturalized in Japan have been friends beyond nationality since their childhood. In the unsolved case over export of the SIBYL Systems and the leakage of technology, Arata`s father committed suicide after he killed Kei`s brother. Since then, they turn out to be the bereaved family members of the offender and victim. Both Arata and Kei become inspectors to look for the truth behind the mysterious case. They deeply trust and care for each other as they team up and lead the rebellious enforces to follow the cases one after another.
Source: Fuji Creative
Note: The first episode was digitally distributed by Amazon Prime Video one day before the regular TV broadcast.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="433">7.76</permanent>
<temporary count="437">7.92</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238842.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21952</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://psycho-pass.com/3rd/index.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Psycho-Pass</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>PSYCHO-PASS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367480</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22282</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>psychopass_tv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1633" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>xenophobia</name>
<description>An intense dislike and/or fear of people from other countries.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="48064" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-27">
<rating votes="270">7.96</rating>
<name>Kougami Shin`ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48307" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-24">
<rating votes="298">6.21</rating>
<name>Tsunemori Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48542" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="87">5.43</rating>
<name>Kunizuka Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67980.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48544" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-20">
<rating votes="87">7.34</rating>
<name>Karanomori Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67975.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49441" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="23">4.54</rating>
<name>Dominator</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dominator is the handgun that enforcement officers point at a suspect to instantly measure the "crime factor" of the individual. If the crime factor is above a certain limit, the gun will automatically fire. If the "crime factor" is below that limit, a safety device will be activated to prevent the user from pulling the gun`s trigger.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>126352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70086" type="main character in" update="2015-09-18">
<rating votes="23">4.82</rating>
<name>Hinakawa Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70419" type="main character in" update="2019-11-16">
<rating votes="160">4.92</rating>
<name>Shimotsuki Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68095.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71380" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="8">3.10</rating>
<name>Sugou Teppei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76595" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="4">6.58</rating>
<name>Sibyl System</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>63084.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="94647" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="18">7.37</rating>
<name>Ginoza Nobuchika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginoza Nobuchika is an Enforcer with http://anidb.net/ch76608 [Public Safety Division 1] at the http://anidb.net/ch76607 [Public Safety Bureau].
He was demoted to Enforcer after his Crime Coefficient rose above regulation levels to 140, after the death of his father http://anidb.net/ch48543 [Masaoka Tomomi] at the hands of http://anidb.net/ch48756 [Makishima Shougo]. As part of the incident, Ginoza lost his left arm and gained a prosthetic, much like his father. Ginoza`s personality and outlook on life also drastically changed. Further, he no longer wears glasses; when http://anidb.net/ch48307 [Tsunemori Akane] asks if he actually needed prescription glasses, Ginoza replied that he wore glasses as he did not like the shape of his face, but he no longer cares about this aspect of his appearance.</description>
<picture>177477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98915" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-10">
<rating votes="11">7.12</rating>
<name>Hanashiro Frederica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101314" type="main character in" update="2019-10-09">
<rating votes="6">6.17</rating>
<name>Shindou Arata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67976.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101315" type="main character in" update="2019-10-09">
<rating votes="6">5.40</rating>
<name>Kei Mikhail Ignatov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67977.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105621" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<name>Round Robin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105622" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="2">3.78</rating>
<name>Daigin Youki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105623" type="main character in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="4">5.77</rating>
<name>Irie Kazumichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67978.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105624" type="main character in" update="2019-10-09">
<rating votes="5">5.00</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105625" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-29">
<rating votes="5">7.82</rating>
<name>Komiya Karina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105626" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<name>Obata Chiya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105627" type="main character in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<name>Todoroki Tenma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67979.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105628" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<name>Serizawa Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105629" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<name>Houhan Seika</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105630" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<name>Saientera Sayako</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221693" update="2019-10-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライラプスの召命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laelaps` Calling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`appel de Laelap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Laelaps no Shoumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221694" update="2019-10-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">DIVE to PSYCHO-PASS 第三期 #00</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dive to Psycho-Pass: Daisan Ki #0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222727" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テウメソスの生贄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teumessian Sacrifices</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sacrifices de Teumesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teumessos no Ikenie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222728" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘラクレスとセイレーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Herakles and the Sirens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hercule et les sirènes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Herakles to Siren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222729" update="2019-10-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コロッセオの政争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Political Strife in the Colosseum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Conflit politique au Colisée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Colosseo no Seisou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223551" update="2019-10-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223552" update="2019-10-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224032" update="2019-11-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アガメムノンの燔祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Agamemnon`s Offering</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`offrande d`Agamemnon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Agamemnon no Hansai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224033" update="2019-11-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カエサルの金貨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caesar`s Gold Coins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les pièces d`or de César</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caesar no Kinka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224034" update="2019-11-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Don`t take God`s name in vain</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Take God`s Name in Vain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Don`t Take God`s Name in Vain</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224035" update="2019-11-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2019-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Cubism</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cubism</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cubism</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
