<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14750" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai demo Yoyuu de Ikinuku You Desu!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">Choyoyu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">超人高校生たちは異世界でも余裕で生き抜くようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">High School Prodigies Have It Easy Even in Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">عباقرة المدرسة الثانوية لا يواجهون صعوبة حتى في عالم آخر</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">超人高校生在异世界也可以活的风生水起！</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14727" approval="2" total="14">Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="173070">I was about to face-palm at the first episode, and then things stepped up quickly and made me understand why everything was laid out the way it was. This started so strong. For the first half of the series I was sitting here wondering why this was rated so poorly.

And then the series just kind of drifted off. It seemed to pull back in the last episode, but it was very disappointing in the sense that it could have been so much more.

If you`re not expecting an incredible series, I think it`s enjoyable. But this honestly could have been 8 episodes long and gotten the same content out of it.

So, watch it if you`re looking for something to fill. Maybe they`ll make a second season and have it be a step up where they focus more on story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="73747">The concept of 7 prodigies being sent to another world and thriving in their new environment was cool, especially the first few episodes as each character helped resolve small and local issues, but as the show progressed, this got over-the-top pretty quickly.  Still, there is fun in this series, but could have been better if it remained grounded rather than always going bigger... a decent watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://choyoyu.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="43227" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yano Akane</name>
<name id="17544" type="Chief Animation Direction">Satou Marina</name>
<name id="21205" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iida Eriko</name>
<name id="35813" type="Animation Work">Project No.9</name>
<name id="43191" type="Original Work">Misora Riku</name>
<name id="7462" type="Direction">Yanagi Shinsuke</name>
<name id="2753" type="Music">Mizutani Hiromi</name>
<name id="43227" type="Character Design">Yano Akane</name>
<name id="4556" type="Series Composition">Akao Deko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr43191 [Misora Riku] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr57612 [Sacraneco].
Seven Japanese high school prodigies have taken the world by storm, exercising their mind-blowing abilities in everything from politics to entertainment. But when their plane crashes one day, these geniuses awaken to find themselves in a different realm-one that`s home to magic and beast folk! While such strange new surroundings might throw an average person for a loop, these prodigies take their situation in stride...and then some! With the greatest minds and talents known to Earth, this dream team is about to turn the other world on its head!
Source: Yen Press</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="454">2.82</permanent>
<temporary count="461">5.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238486.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39523</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://choyoyu.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>High_School_Prodigies_Have_It_Easy_Even_In_Another_World</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>超人高校生たちは異世界でも余裕で生き抜くようです!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367528</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>choyoyu_PR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=TZjmff4PFNA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=WL8FStExZgE</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=bxv7Wm1TCBI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3368" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>covert operations</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3423" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>religious persecution</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3433" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>power corrupts</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4021" parentid="36" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-08">
<name>evil military</name>
<description>The military is depicted as being of a nefarious nature in this anime. Be it through the heartlessness that their soldiers convey, or the ruthless killing of innocents, the military in this anime is not to be messed with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4244" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>healthcare and medicine</name>
<description>The anime contains themes related to healthcare, medicine, or the human body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4271" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-29">
<name>corrupt church</name>
<description>An official religion (not cult or sect) has become evil or was evil to begin with, and tends to be highly influential with political leaders, to strengthen / enforce the church`s power over the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5003" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>imperialism</name>
<description>Imperialism is a type of advocacy of empire. Its name originated from the Latin word "imperium", which means to rule over large territories. Imperialism is "a policy of extending a country`s power and influence through colonization, use of military force, or other means".
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5150" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-11">
<name>asymmetric warfare</name>
<description>Asymmetric warfare is war between conflicting groups whose relative military power differs, or whose strategy or tactics differ significantly.
Asymmetric warfare can describe a conflict in which the resources of two groups differ in essence, and in the struggle, they interact and attempt to exploit each other`s weaknesses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5293" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>crash landing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5838" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>fire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7238" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>attempted rape</name>
<description>Attempted rape is an unsuccessful attempt at http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape]. For AniDB purposes, generally an "unsuccessful" attempt is where both fellatio and penetration did not occur. Discretion should be applied on a case-by-case basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7402" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>corrupt nobility</name>
<description>The nobility is characterized by decadence, sadism, and contempt towards the baseborn.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101386" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Prince Akatsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101387" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="8">3.34</rating>
<name>Lyrule</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101388" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="4">8.29</rating>
<name>Ichijou Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45433" picture="185233.jpg">Kaneko Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101389" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="5">6.05</rating>
<name>Oohoshi Ringo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101390" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="2">7.66</rating>
<name>Mikogami Tsukasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101391" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="5">7.79</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38978" picture="183949.jpg">Hioka Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101392" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="1">3.36</rating>
<name>Sanada Masato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101393" type="main character in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="4">8.17</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Keine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105042" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-15">
<rating votes="2">4.64</rating>
<name>Kumausa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105465" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="6">8.09</rating>
<name>Winona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105466" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="1">3.36</rating>
<name>Elk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105467" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<name>Oslo El Gustave</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105468" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="4">4.24</rating>
<name>Jeanne de Leblan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105469" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="6">3.72</rating>
<name>Roux</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38750" picture="145599.jpg">Hashimoto Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106152" type="appears in" update="2019-10-18">
<name>Jaccoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10393" picture="38280.jpg">Maruyama Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106153" type="appears in" update="2019-10-18">
<name>Klaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23574" picture="64846.jpg">Morishima Shuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106154" type="appears in" update="2019-10-13">
<name>Ulga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31390" picture="151711.jpg">Shiga Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106254" type="appears in" update="2019-10-18">
<name>Inzagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56025" picture="222869.jpg">Katayama Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106555" type="appears in" update="2019-10-28">
<name>Gale Stafford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4764" picture="67960.jpg">Takahashi Ryoukichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106556" type="appears in" update="2019-10-28">
<name>Findolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106694" type="appears in" update="2019-11-02">
<name>Haizerad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106695" type="appears in" update="2019-11-02">
<name>Zest Bernard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42006" picture="232274.jpg">Mizunaka Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106696" type="appears in" update="2019-11-02">
<name>Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53024" picture="232385.jpg">Shimabukuro Miyuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107596" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Emerada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43784" picture="181317.jpg">Kanazawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107597" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Melinda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41766" picture="242448.jpg">Kitou Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107598" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Serentius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20906" picture="223783.jpg">Kitazawa You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107599" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Neuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39784" picture="153564.jpg">Inoue Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107600" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Raisenach</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56039" picture="222895.jpg">Sumi Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107601" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Conrad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55799" picture="220735.jpg">Mine Akihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107602" type="appears in" update="2019-12-21">
<name>Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48852" picture="225071.jpg">Kohara Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108305" type="appears in" update="2020-02-09">
<name>Oscar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108306" type="appears in" update="2020-02-09">
<name>Arclide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108307" type="appears in" update="2020-02-09">
<name>Buchwald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108308" type="appears in" update="2020-02-09">
<name>Tanganika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108309" type="appears in" update="2020-02-09">
<name>Hibari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244356.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108310" type="appears in" update="2020-02-09">
<name>Shura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244358.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218890" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『超人高校生たちは異世界でも余裕で生き抜くようです!』PV第1弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:23)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai demo Yoyuu de Ikinuku you desu!" PV Dai 1 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218891" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『超人高校生たちは異世界でも余裕で生き抜くようです!』PV第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:38)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai demo Yoyuu de Ikinuku you desu!" PV Dai 2 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221327" update="2019-09-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『超人高校生たちは異世界でも余裕で生き抜くようです!』第1話Web予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 - Episode 01 Web PV (1:07)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai demo Yoyuu de Ikinuku you desu!" Dai 1 Wa Web Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221517" update="2019-10-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超人高校生たちは異世界に来てしまったようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">High School Prodigies Have Arrived in Another World!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">وصل عباقرة المدرسة الثانوية إلى عالم آخر!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai ni Kiteshimatta You Desu!</title>
<summary>There are seven young men and women known as "high school prodigies" who are the world`s top leaders in their respective fields of politics, economics, swordsmanship, medicine, espionage, science, and magic.
However, one day a plane carrying these seven meets an unfortunate accident. When next they open their eyes they find themselves in another world with dragons flying in the skies and people who have animal ears.
While normal people may be shocked and lose their composure, these are the high school prodigies. It`s easy for them to survive, even in another world. In fact, their main concern lies with the fact that their talents may upset the order of this new world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789426</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221518" update="2019-10-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝人は本気で金儲けをするようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masato Is Serious About Making Money!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Masato se met à gagner sérieusement de l`argent !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن ماساتو جاد بشأن كسب المال!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masato wa Honki de Kanemouke o Suru You Desu!</title>
<summary>Tsukasa and the others begin taking action to repay Elm Village and the young girl, Lyrule, for saving them. The villagers and Tsukasa`s group begin opening up to one another, but Elm Village is being forced to lead a poor life by the Neutscheland Trading Company, a corrupt organization that controls all trade in the North.
So their world`s top entrepreneur, Sanada Masato, the same man feared as the demon lord of finance, decides to take a stand.
After visiting the trade city of Domunt, he creates his own company in the blink of an eye and uses his outstanding skill to challenge the Neutscheland Trading Company on all fronts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789427</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221519" update="2019-10-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルーは自分の価値を自分で決めたようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Roo Can Decide Her Own Worth!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ruu décide elle-même de sa propre valeur !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن رو تستطيع أن تحدّد قيمتها بنفسها!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roux wa Jibun no Kachi o Jibun de Kimeta You Desu!</title>
<summary>While conducting their business in Dormant, Masato adds a young girl named Roo to their party, and he continues to laugh audaciously in the face of Neutscheland Trading Company`s cowardly plans.
Meanwhile, winter comes to Elm Village and Tsukasa works on a plan out of concern for their safety.
Thanks to the actions of Sarutobi Shinobu, a descendant of ninja and the world`s top journalist, they develop a vague understanding of the forces in this new world, such as Frejyagard Empire, the large nation controlling much of this world. They also learn of the lost faith, the Seven Light Faith, which leads to more mysteries as he searches for a way to return them to their old world.
During all of this, danger descends upon the peaceful Elm Village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789428</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221520" update="2019-10-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">司は異世界を変える覚悟を決めたようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Tsukasa Has Resolved to Change the World!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tsukasa se résout à changer le monde !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أنّ تسوكاسا قد عزم على تغيير العالم!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukasa wa Isekai o Kaeru Kakugo o Kimeta You Desu!</title>
<summary>Thanks to quick thinking on the part of Prince Akatsuki, their world`s top magician, the villagers of Elm Village manage to escape danger. However, Lyrule has been kidnapped and taken away to Findolf, the heinous lord of their region.
The villagers are filled with righteous anger, but there`s no way their village will remain safe if they defy their lord. As a politician, Tsukasa proposes the resolution that would result in the least sacrifices for the villages, however, he ultimately resolves to lend them his aid when they decide to unite to rescue Lyrule and seek his help.
Using their talents and skills, Tsukasa and the others lead the rebellion against the lord, knowing that it would mean fundamentally altering the way things were in this new world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789429</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222674" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暁はゴッド暁になるようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Akatsuki`s Becoming God Akatsuki!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Akatsuki est devenu le dieu Akatsuki !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن أكاتسكي يصبح إلها!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akatsuki wa God Akatsuki ni Naru You Desu!</title>
<summary>The high school prodigies have defeated the villainous lord of Findolf with their overwhelming science. However, that`s only the beginning.
After proclaiming themselves to be messengers of the gods under the Seven-Light Faith, Tsukasa and the others appear before the populace to distribute medical treatment, magic shows, and mayonnaise as miracles of their faith, hoping to organize the people of this new world together.
As the first step toward their goals, Tsukasa and the others took control of the grand city, Dormundt, but the leader of the Dormundt watch, Bernard, harbors some doubts. With the lord defeated, there`s no way Frejyagard Empire will remain quiet.
Bernard laments the trouble looming in their future, but Tsukasa sees great value in his realistic perspective, and seeks to welcome him to their side.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789430</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222675" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リルルは距離を縮めるようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Lyrule`s Growing Closer to Him!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lilulu s`efforce de réduire la distance !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن ليرول تتقرب منه أكثر</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rilulu wa Kyori o Chijimeru You Desu!</title>
<summary>With Dormundt as their new base of operations, Tsukasa begins implementing reform after reform, and they also must begin preparing for a major clash with the Empire.
What concerns Tsukasa the most is the governor of the northern lands, Oslo El Gustave, and the terrifying, tactical spell that he commands - Heaven`s Flames.
Meanwhile, Lyrule still has yet to thank Tsukasa for saving her from Findolf. Recognizing that Tsukasa was starting to avoid her, she resolves to confront him face to face!
At the same time, Roo is facing her own trials off in Elm Village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789431</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222676" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍はシノビの勘がはたらくようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Shinobu Has a Shinobi`s Intuition!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shinobu montre la force de son flair !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن شينوبو لديها حدس شينوبي!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobu wa Shinobi no Kan ga Hataraku You Desu!</title>
<summary>Shinobu and Elch visit the northern village of Coconono. In contrast to their expectations, the villagers spared nothing to welcome them.
The village was kept clean, the villagers were nicely dressed, and everyone was friendly. They all claimed it was due to northern governor, Oslo El Gustave, and offered their praises for him.
Yet while Coconono Village appeared to be a thriving village, Shinobu sensed a bottomless darkness lurking beneath the surface and began her investigations.
At this same time a brigade of imperial knights, led by the female knight Jeanne, arrives to inspect Coconono Village. So in order to obtain more intel Shinobu decides to...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789432</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222677" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">葵は想像以上のスペックを発揮するようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Aoi`s Specs Are Greater Than Imagined!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aoi fait preuve de capacités dépassant l`imagination !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن قدرات أوي أعظم مما هو متوقع!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi wa Souzou Ijou no Spec o Hakki Suru You Desu!</title>
<summary>Gustave gives in to his burning anger toward the Seven Light Faith and unleashes Heaven`s Flames, L`age Soliel.
The city of Dormundt panics at the sudden attack, yet Tsukasa remains completely calm. He had already anticipated all of it, and was confident they could all weather the attack if they did what was required of them.
So following Tsukasa`s emergency manual, Domundt manages to avoid the worst case scenario. However, the Heaven`s Flames aren`t stopping. The fire spirits unleashed by the spell are compelled to continue their attack until the city burns to the ground.
Faced with a predicament even their missiles couldn`t stop, the world`s strongest swordsman, Ichijou Aoi, rises to the challenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789433</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224344" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">司は全てを見通しているようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Tsukasa Has Seen Through Everything!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tsukasa prévoit absolument tous les événements !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن تسوكاسا قد كشف كل شيء!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukasa wa Subete o Mitooshite Iru You Desu!</title>
<summary>After Tsukasa and the others narrowly defeat Gustave`s Heaven`s Flames, he deems the Seven Light Faith a dangerous threat and orders his armies to march at once.
Count Arclide follows his orders and marches to subjugate them, but his army is forced to clash with the Seven Light Faith`s Knights on a freezing, snowy mountain.
Meanwhile, Shinobu joins up with the anti-imperial organization that Jeanne belongs to, the Azure Brigade. After receiving Gustave`s orders for all of his soldiers to assemble, they seize their chance to revolt lay siege to Gustave`s lands.
Though Jeanne demands his surrender, Gustave chooses to fight an intense battle against Shinobu and Jeanne with obsessive loyalty toward his emperor burning within his heart.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789434</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224345" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">林檎は勇気を出して狩人になるようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Ringo`s Worked Up the Courage to Become a Hunter!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ringo prend son courage à deux mains et devient une chasseuse !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن رينغو استجمعت الشجاعة لتصبح صيادة!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ringo wa Yuuki o Dashite Karyuudo ni Naru You Desu!</title>
<summary>After deposing Gustave and incorporating their northern region into their domain, the Seven Light Faith has become a danger the empire cannot ignore.
Though just as Tsukasa was preparing for matters to get even busier as their war against the empire picked up, their doctor, Keine, warns both Tsukasa and Ringo that they`ve been overworking themselves.
With doctor`s orders to rest and recuperate, Tsukasa proposes taking a stroll through the city with Ringo during their time off. But is this a date? While Ringo may be the world`s greatest scientist, she`s ignorant and helpless when it comes to romance. She tries consulting her friends on the matter, but it doesn`t help assuage her fears or anxieties. But then Shinobu teaches her a secret plan.
How will their date ultimately go?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789435</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224346" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桂音は悪い子を決して許したりはしないようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems Keine Can`t Stand Naughty Boys!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Keine ne pardonne pas aux vilains petits garnements !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن كاين لن تسامح الأشخاص الأشقياء!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keine wa Warui Ko o Keshite Yurushitari wa Shinai You Desu!</title>
<summary>Ringo focuses on developing the item Tsukasa requested while he endures the weight of that request. Shinobu continues to gather information, but shows concern for Jeanne when she uncovers the Azure Brigade`s suspicious activity. Meanwhile, a plague strikes the city. Its treatment is beyond the doctors of this other world, and with the group`s reserves of medical supplies running low, the patients are facing the risk of death.
When the local Medical Guild comes to insult the Seven-Light Faith for failing to save their patients, Akatsuki gets mad. That`s when the world`s greatest doctor, Kanzaki Keine responds to his spirit and declares that she will make medicine to save them all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789436</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224347" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超人高校生たちは異世界でも余裕で生き抜くようです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Seems High School Prodigies Have It Easy Even in Another World!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Super Lycéens survivent aisément dans un autre monde !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يبدو أن عباقرة المدرسة الثانوية لا يواجهون صعوبة حتى في عالم آخر!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai demo Yoyuu de Ikinuku You Desu!</title>
<summary>After rescuing Jeanne, Shinobu acknowledges her ideals and invites her to join the Seven Light Faith. Meanwhile, Tanganika, the precious mage of Imperial General Neuro, unveils his hidden power, laying death and destruction to his surroundings in an ample display of the empire`s might. To counter him, the world`s greatest politician, Mikogami Tsukasa, executes his prearranged plan lighting the beacon of revolution in this other world.
"We will defeat the empire and carry out our revolution." Tsukasa then speaks on the new world, the new nation they`ll create before the crowd gathered around him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789437</identifier>
<identifier>high-school-prodigies-have-it-easy-even-in-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
