<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14756" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-12</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Given</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ギヴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Given</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">被赠与的未来</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15102" type="Other">Eiga Given</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13979" approval="1" total="3">Dakaretai Otoko 1-i ni Odosarete Imasu.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="672246">I was really surprised by this shounen ai. I watched it expecting nothing, just wanting to see a bunch of guitar bois. What I got was a really well written relation between the two heroes, some very touching moments and an outstanding feature song that got me to tears. One of my best surprises in 2019.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://given-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="21486" type="Series Composition">Ayana Yuniko</name>
<name id="45916" type="Direction">Yamaguchi Hikaru</name>
<name id="57629" type="Original Work">Kizu Natsuki</name>
<name id="12920" type="Character Design">Oosawa Mina</name>
<name id="12920" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oosawa Mina</name>
<name id="44779" type="Music">Michiru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a BL music manga series by http://anidb.net/cr57629 [Kizu Natsuki].
Somehow, the guitar that he used to love to play and the basketball games that he found so fun just lost their appeal...
That was until http://anidb.net/ch103479 [Uenoyama Ritsuka] randomly met http://anidb.net/ch103481 [Satou Mafuyu]. Ritsuka had started losing his passion for music in his everyday life, but then he hears Mafuyu sing for the first time. The song resonates with his heart and the distance between them starts to change.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="195">6.41</permanent>
<temporary count="198">7.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>234733.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21958</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39533</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://given-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Given_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ギヴン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5374</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22114</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>given_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4785" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>rock music</name>
<description>Rock music is a genre of popular music that originated as "rock and roll" in the United States in the 1950s, and developed into a range of different styles in the 1960s and later, particularly in the United Kingdom and the United States. Musically, rock has centered on the electric guitar, usually as part of a rock group with electric bass guitar and drums. Typically, rock is song-based music usually with a 4/4 time signature using a verse-chorus form, but the genre has become extremely diverse. Like pop music, lyrics often stress romantic love but also address a wide variety of other themes that are frequently social or political in emphasis. The dominance of rock by white, male musicians has been seen as one of the key factors shaping the themes explored in rock music. Rock places a higher degree of emphasis on musicianship, live performance, and an ideology of authenticity than pop music.</description>
<picurl>10250.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="103479" type="main character in" update="2019-06-13">
<rating votes="4">8.55</rating>
<name>Uenoyama Ritsuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38579" picture="225249.jpg">Uchida Yuuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103480" type="main character in" update="2019-06-13">
<rating votes="4">1.76</rating>
<name>Nakayama Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13644" picture="236301.jpg">Nakazawa Masatomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103481" type="main character in" update="2019-06-13">
<rating votes="5">8.34</rating>
<name>Satou Mafuyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40047" picture="225902.jpg">Yano Shougo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103482" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-13">
<rating votes="6">9.10</rating>
<name>Murata Ugetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103483" type="main character in" update="2019-06-13">
<rating votes="4">8.55</rating>
<name>Kaji Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103484" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-13">
<rating votes="2">7.64</rating>
<name>Kashima Hiiragi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56572" picture="236188.jpg">Imai Fumiya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218201" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Boys in the Band</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boys in the Band</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boys in the Band</title>
<summary>Ritsuka Uenoyama meets Mafuyu Sato one day in his normal napping spot. Ritsuka ends up fixing Mafuyu’s guitar, which leads to Mafuyu pestering Ritsuka to teach him guitar over and over. Ritsuka declines over and over but somehow, after seeing how passionate Mafuyu is about learning guitar, Ritsuka starts to remember how he felt when he first started playing music.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787200</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218202" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Like Someone In Love</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like Someone in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Like Someone in Love</title>
<summary>Ritsuka introduces Mafuyu to his other bandmates, Haruki Nakayama and Akihiko Kaji. After some convincing from the other two, Ritsuka finally agrees to teach Mafuyu how to play guitar. Mafuyu is so excited about playing guitar for the first time that he can’t hide his excitement. One day, Haruki and Akihiko tell Mafuyu the most important thing about playing music...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787201</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218203" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Somebody Else</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Somebody Else</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Somebody Else</title>
<summary>Ritsuka is floored after hearing Mafuyu’s singing voice and invites him into the band, but Mafuyu declines. Ritsuka just can’t take no for an answer and keeps trying to invite Mafuyu into the band, but now, Mafuyu is avoiding him. Then during band practice, Haruki asks Ritsuka to actually think about if he ever thought about how Mafuyu felt...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787202</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218204" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fluorescent Adolescent</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fluorescent Adolescent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fluorescent Adolescent</title>
<summary>Mafuyu finally decides to join the band. In order to compose a song to go along with the little tidbit that Mafuyu sang for him, Ritsuka dives back into playing guitar nonstop. Haruki is at his part-time job one day when his friend Koji Yatake comes by and asks him if he and his band would like to appear in a live show he’s putting on. Ritsuka is teaching Mafuyu guitar at school as usual and then invites Mafuyu to go look at effect pedals with him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787203</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218649" update="2019-09-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218650" update="2019-09-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218825" update="2019-09-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218971" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Reason</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reason</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Reason</title>
<summary>It was decided that Ritsuka and the rest of his band were going to do a live show. Haruki and Akihiko were at a bar drinking, talking about Ritsuka and Mafuyu. Since Akihiko had ridden his motorcycle into town, he asks to spend the night at Haruki’s place and Haruki thinks back on the first time they met. That was right around the time Haruki’s old band had disbanded and he had first encountered Ritsuka, who had just entered his third year of middle school...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787204</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218972" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Creep</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Creep</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Creep</title>
<summary>Ritsuka hears a rumor that the person that Mafuyu used to date had died and is a bit shaken. Ritsuka couldn’t build up the courage to ask Mafuyu about it, but then, Akihiko visits his place. Akihiko then suggests that Mafuyu write the lyrics for the song Ritsuka had made. Ritsuka was thinking the same thing, and at the next band practice, asks Mafuyu if he’d do it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787205</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218973" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Tumbling Dice</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tumbling Dice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tumbling Dice</title>
<summary>Ritsuka realizes how he truly feels and ends up taking out his frustrations and confusion on Mafuyu. Ritsuka ends up talking to Akihiko, who tells him that what he’s feeling is completely normal, but Ritsuka still wonders if it’s okay to admit these feelings. As Akihiko watches over Ritsuka and Mafuyu, he remembers his past with Ugetsu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787206</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218974" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Time Is Running Out</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Is Running Out</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Is Running Out</title>
<summary>The North Patria Union tries to quickly exterminate all of the Incarnates before the impending war. The captain of the Coup de Grace, Claude, had appeared in the port town of Port Gulf. Schaal is also there and happens to hear a beautiful singing voice. She heads toward the cave that the voice is coming from and encounters the Incarnate Siren, otherwise known as Beatrice, and her friend Charles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787207</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219602" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬のはなし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Winter Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Hanashi</title>
<summary>On the day of the concert Ritsuka and Mafuyu get into a little spat and one of the strings on Mafuyu’s guitar breaks. Haruki tells Ritsuka to run and buy new strings, and Ritsuka then realizes that Mafuyu’s been trying to do everything he had been asking him to do this whole time. As he replaces Mafuyu’s strings, he tells Mafuyu how he feels. Even though there are still no lyrics done, their time to perform finally arrives, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787208</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219603" update="2019-10-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Wonderwall</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wonderwall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wonderwall</title>
<summary>Ritsuka comes to the realization that he was so worked up at the concert that he kissed Mafuyu. Ritsuka hears that Mafuyu didn’t come to school because he had a fever, so he decides to go visit him. The next day, Mafuyu is feeling better and the band gets together to celebrate his recovery and to try to figure out their future as a band and figure out a name for their band.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787209</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219604" update="2019-10-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Song2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Song2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Song2</title>
<summary>Mafuyu tells Ritsuka that he likes him and Ritsuka is ecstatic to find out that they both like each other but at the same time, he remembers himself saying that band members should never bring relationships into the band. However, they both decide to talk to Haruki and Akihiko about it. Haruki gives them a lecture and Akihiko congratulates them. Meanwhile, Haruki, who likes Akihiko...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>787210</identifier>
<identifier>given</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221433" update="2019-09-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221434" update="2019-09-20">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
