<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1478" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-07-29</startdate>
<enddate>1995-07-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hajimari no Boukensha-tachi: Legend of Crystania</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">First Adventurers: Legend of Crystania</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Lodoss - The Legend of Crystania - Kinofilm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Lodoss - La légende de Crystania - Le film</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Crystania</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はじまりの冒険者たち レジェンド・オブ・クリスタニア</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Legend of Crystania - The Motion Picture</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Lodoss - The Legend of Crystania - Der Film</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Chroniques de la guerre de Lodoss - La légende de Crystania - Le film</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="691" type="Sequel">Legend of Crystania</anime>
<anime id="137" type="Prequel">Lodoss-tou Senki: Eiyuu Kishi Den</anime>
<anime id="169" type="Character">Lodoss-tou Senki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="789" type="Animation Production">Triangle Staff</name>
<name id="814" type="Unknown Relation">Kadokawa Shoten</name>
<name id="1582" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsuda Katsumi</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="4184" type="Direction">Nakamura Ryuutarou</name>
<name id="5648" type="Original Work">Mizuno Ryou</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
</creators>
<description>From the golden pen of Ryo Mizuno, comes an all-new adventure set in the aftermath of the Lodoss Wars!
Ashram, desperate to find a home for his people, is tricked into selling his soul. 300 years later, Pirotesse`s devotion to her king remains unshaken.
In the sacred world of Crystania, amidst a civil war waged by shape-changing warriors, she searches for her beloved Ashram. She meets Redon, a young prince obsessed with avenging his murdered parents. Together, they confront Ashram`s captor - the bloodthirsty Barbas, who aspires to rule Crystania as The God`s King.
Will they free Ashram`s soul... or will Redon`s innocence become the next sacrifice to Barbas` emerging power?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="435">3.35</permanent>
<temporary count="439">5.95</temporary>
<review count="1">1.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>238187.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>482</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>515</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>313</identifier>
<identifier>xmwxdv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Legend_of_Crystania</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>はじまりの冒険者たち_レジェンド・オブ・クリスタニア#.E3.81.AF.E3.81.98.E3.81.BE.E3.82.8A.E3.81.AE.E5.86.92.E9.99.BA.E8.80.85.E3.81.9F.E3.81.A1_.E3.83.AC.E3.82.B8.E3.82.A7.E3.83.B3.E3.83.89.E3.83.BB.E3.82.AA.E3.83.96.E3.83.BB.E3.82.AF.E3.83.AA.E3.82.B9.E3.82.BF.E3.83.8B.E3.82.A2.EF.BC.88.E6.98.A0.E7.94.BB.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152588</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="153" parentid="1609" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>dark elf</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="38072" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="24">7.93</rating>
<name>Pirotessa Merestianna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pirotess is a dark elven noble considered to be one of the more prominent figures in her people`s society. Like most dark elves, she worships Fararis and calls the Forest of Darkness on Marmo island her home. She is the younger sister of Altas, a member of the quest of Rod of Dominatus, eventually cheated by the chief leader of all dark elves, the powerful Ruchiev, who had decided to recreate the kingdom of his kindred. Since she believed that the useless human Ashram should be the one to pay for her beloved brother`s death, she joined the mission of killing the general of Dark Knighthood. Ashram found and bested her in hand-to-hand combat when she ambushed him in his bedroom, but let her go after learning her identity as the sister of his lost old friend. After she learned the truth and the crazy decision of Ruchiev from her fellow assassin, she stalked Ashram to learn about him and discovered his loyalty to the lost emperor, the heroic Beld, and his dedication to Marmo and its people. She decided to protect him from the other assassin and aided him in a "Test" from the Dark Sage. After 10 years, she had been the only one to whom Ashram had showed appreciation and care. She in turn remained fiercely loyal to Ashram as a lieutenant and a leader of his scouts. She was accepted by the subordinates of Ashram as their mistress and sub-general. Pirotess is a skilled adversary, both an adept of the rapier and a skilled magic user. A shaman like Deedlit, she often uses spirits that high elves will not associate with, such as the spirits of darkness.[ol][u]</description>
<picture>73130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="16374" update="2005-09-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<airdate>1995-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
