<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14795" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Africa no Salaryman (2019)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">African Office Worker (TV)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アフリカのサラリーマン (2019)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Africa Salaryman</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">非洲的动物上班族</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12983" type="Other">Africa no Salaryman</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://afusara.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="49347" type="Original Work">Gamu</name>
<name id="58323" type="Direction">Tatamitani Tetsuya</name>
<name id="58323" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tatamitani Tetsuya</name>
<name id="58324" type="Animation Work">Hot Zipang</name>
<name id="30857" type="Series Composition">Momose Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="51109" type="Character Design">pH studio</name>
<name id="58729" type="Music">Yamaguchi Tako</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr49347 [Gamu]`s comedy web manga series.
http://anidb.net/ch105908 [Lion], http://anidb.net/ch105907 [Lizard], and http://anidb.net/ch105905 [Toucan] live the lives of office workers in a capitalist society in Japan, while also dealing with their unique situations as animals living beyond the savanna and the food chain.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="75">3.50</permanent>
<temporary count="76">5.38</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236650.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22001</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39590</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://afusara.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>African_Office_Worker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アフリカのサラリーマン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5440</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367665</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22258</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>afusara_P</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07Z8L4YFS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4259" parentid="2857" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>animal world</name>
<description>All characters of the show are walking-talking animals. Their behaviour and clothing can resemble that of humans. They also may try to mirror human society.
There are no humans present in this world.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3968 [animal protagonist].</description>
<picurl>10254.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="105905" type="main character in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="3">4.82</rating>
<name>Oohashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105906" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="3">4.82</rating>
<name>Kame-shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105907" type="main character in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="3">4.82</rating>
<name>Tokage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105908" type="main character in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="3">4.82</rating>
<name>Lion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105909" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="2">2.19</rating>
<name>Sasshou Hamster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42138" picture="184598.jpg">Kino Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105910" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Caracal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105911" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Ratel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105912" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<name>Gorimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105913" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Mitsuoshie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105914" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-06">
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<name>Shishimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221553" update="2019-09-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの痴漢 / アフリカのドーナツ屋 / アフリカの眼鏡 / アフリカの合コン / アフリカのJK~シシ村~ / アフリカのJK~ゴリ美~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Pervert / Africa Donut Shop / Africa Eyeglasses / Africa Mixer / Africa High-School Girls: Shishimura / Africa High-School Girls: Gorimi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Chikan / Africa no Donuts-ya / Africa no Megane / Africa no Goukon / Africa no JK: Shishi Mura / Africa no JK: Gorimi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221554" update="2019-09-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカのダイエット / アフリカの風呂事情 / アフリカのリモート同棲 / アフリカの社畜 / アフリカのJK~アフリカの友情~ / アフリカのJK~アフリカの風呂事情(JK ver.)~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Diet / Africa Bathing Situation / Africa Remote Cohabitation / Africa Corporate Drones / Africa High-School Girls: Africa Friendship / Africa High-School Girls: Africa Bathing Situation (High-School Girls Edition)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Diet / Africa no Furo Jijou / Africa no Remote Dousei / Africa no Shachiku / Africa no JK: Africa no Yuujou / Africa no JK: Africa no Furo Jijou (JK Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221555" update="2019-09-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカのワイドショー / アフリカの一芸 / アフリカのお花見 / アフリカのパーリナイッ! / アフリカのお花見② / アフリカのJK~JKの本音~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Variety Show / Africa Party Tricks / Africa Flower-Viewing Parties / Africa Party Night! / Africa Flower-Viewing Parties 2 / Africa High-School Girls: What High-School Girls Really Think</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Wide Show / Africa no Ichigei / Africa no Ohanami / Africa no Paarinai! / Africa no Ohanami 2 / Africa no JK: JK no Honne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221556" update="2019-09-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカのOL / アフリカの歯医者 / アフリカのゆるふわキャラ / アフリカのJK~ゆるふわキャラ見本市~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Secretaries / Africa Dentist / Africa Mascot Characters / Africa High-School Girls: Mascot Character Trade Fair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no OL / Africa no Haisha / Africa no Yuru Fuwa Chara / Africa no JK: Yuru Fuwa Chara Mihon`ichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223443" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの就活 / アフリカのコスト削減 / アフリカの就活② / アフリカのJK~でしょーね~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Job Search / Africa Cost Reduction / Africa Job Hunting 2 / Africa High-School Girls: Right?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Shuukatsu / Africa no Cost Sakugen / Africa no Shuukatsu 2 / Africa no JK: Deshou ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223444" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの童話 ハシずきん / アフリカの夏休み / アフリカの陰湿な同僚 / アフリカのJK~シシ村の朝~ / アフリカのJK~ゴリ美の朝~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Fairy Tale: Little Red Toucan Hood / Africa Summer Vacation / Africa Nasty Coworker / Africa High-School Girls: Shishimura`s Morning / Africa High-School Girls: Gorimi`s Morning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Douwa: Hashi Zukin / Africa no Natsuyasumi / Africa no Inshitsu na Douryou / Africa no JK: Shishi Mura no Asa / Africa no JK: Gorimi no Asa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223445" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの出国手続き / アフリカの社員旅行 / アフリカの社員旅行② / アフリカのJK~お土産~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Departure Procedures / Africa Company Trip / Africa Company Trip 2 / Africa High-School Girls: Souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Shukkokutetsuzuki / Africa no Shainryokou / Africa no Shainryokou 2 / Africa no JK: Omiyage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223446" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの休暇明け / アフリカのお掃除ロボット / アフリカの喫煙スペース / アフリカの世界 / アフリカのコインランドリー / アフリカの運動会 / アフリカの夏の思い出 / アフリカの背筋がない / アフリカの標語 / アフリカのホワイジャパニーズピーポー / アフリカの思い出 / アフリカの昼夜の差 / アフリカのJK~ティックチック~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Post-Vacation / Africa Robot Vacuum / Africa Smoking Area / Africa World / Africa Laundromats / Africa Sports Day / Africa Summer Memories / Africa Spineless / Africa Slogans / Africa Japanese Quirks / Africa Memories / Africa Night and Day / Africa High-School Girls: TokTik</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Kyuuka Ake / Africa no Osouji Robot / Africa no Kitsuen Space / Africa no Sekai / Africa no Coin Laundry / Africa no Undoukai / Africa no Natsu no Omoide / Africa no Sesuji ga Nai / Africa no Hyougo / Africa no Whi-Japanese People / Africa no Omoide / Africa no Chuuya no Sa / Africa no JK: Tick Chick</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224444" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの闇金くん / アフリカの婚活 / アフリカのJK~アフリカの街コン~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Loan Sharks / Africa Speed Dating / Africa High-School Girls: Africa Town Mixers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Yamikin-kun / Africa no Konkatsu / Africa no JK: Africa no Machicon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224445" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカのストレスチェック / アフリカのッターン! / アフリカの健康診断 / アフリカのビジネスマナー / アフリカの実況者 / アフリカのJK~ユーチューバー~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Stress Check / Africa Snap! / Africa Physicals / Africa Business Etiquette / Africa Play-by-Play Commentator / Africa High-School Girls: YouTubers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Stress Check / Africa Notturn! / Africa no Kenkoushindan / Africa no Business Manner / Africa no Jikkyousha / Africa no JK: Youtuber</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224446" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカのボーナス / アフリカのBBQ / アフリカのチラシ配布 / アフリカのJK~寿司ネタ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Bonuses / Africa BBQ / Africa Flyer Distribution / Africa High-School Girls: Sushi Toppings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Bonus / Africa no BBQ / Africa no Chirashi Haifu / Africa no JK: Sushi Neta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224447" update="2019-11-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフリカの解雇 / アフリカのサラリーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Africa Dismissal / Africa Salaryman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Africa no Kaiko / Africa no Salaryman</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
