<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14812" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-03-29</startdate>
<enddate>2020-01-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gundam vs Hello Kitty</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">40th Gundam vs Hello Kitty 45th</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガンダムvsハローキティ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="715" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
<anime id="5874" type="Other">Daisuki! Hello Kitty</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://www.gundamvskitty.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="55162" type="Direction">Im Ga-Hee</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="28">3.36</permanent>
<temporary count="28">4.82</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231892.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39674</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.gundamvskitty.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369095</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gundamvskitty</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>channel/UCUWCwmYec08m5aHTYVVZkXQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=0yCR6f5C5UQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Lotw0yxtSUo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=3orqk_vhepA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=fyp40FVEoPM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="3971" type="main character in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="107">7.89</rating>
<name>Amuro Ray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amuro is the hero of our story, and the pilot of the mighty mobile suit RX-78 Gundam. As the series begins, he is a civilian living at the Side 7 research colony, the neglected son of a Federation Forces engineer. When Zeon mobile suits attack the colony, Amuro commandeers the prototype Gundam and defeats the invaders. He soon finds himself part of the substitute crew of the Federation warship White Base, and this moody young man begins to develop strong bonds with his newfound "family." Meanwhile, Amuro`s increasing fighting skills suggest that he has potential far beyond that of ordinary mortals...
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85679.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9127" type="appears in" update="2018-10-04">
<rating votes="170">4.75</rating>
<name>Haro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haro is the mechanical mascot of the Gundam science fiction anime metaseries, and is the only character that appears in more than one timeline.
The original Haro is a little robot companion built by the main character Amuro Ray. It is a cute testament to Amuro`s exceptional talent for machines. Haro`s features include a limited range of speech, and the ability to hover (in environments with atmosphere and low gravity) by flapping its ear-like appendage coverings. Haro can usually be found rolling behind Amuro`s next door neighbor Frau Bow. The ability to detect brain waves is also one of Haro`s functions; in one of the episodes, Haro actually claimed that the brain wave of Amuro was lowered/different.
In Zeta Gundam, a mass-produced Mk-II version of Haro ends up in the hands of that series` main protagonist Kamille Bidan, who initially suspects it to be the original. He repairs the robot, only to have it constantly address him as Amuro.
During the events of Char`s Counterattack, Amuro gives a "third-generation" Haro to Hathaway, the son of his captain Bright Noa.
Haro continues to permeate the Gundam franchise, having appeared in Gundam SEED as Lacus Clyne`s multi-colored horde of simple-speech robot pets, built for her by Athrun Zala. These Haros are roughly 1/4 the size of their Universal Century counterparts and are similar in function, however a few possess certain abilities such as unlocking doors. Lacus`s favorite Haro is a pink machine that she refers to as "Pink-Chan" (often translated as "Mr. Pink" or "Pinky"). Another notable Haro in Lacus`s collection is "Navy-Chan", a navy blue robot on which she paints a mustache bearing a distinct resemblance the facial ornament of the ∀ Gundam of the CC (正歴 Seireki) calendar system. The rest of Lacus` Haros have been seen in yellow, orange, blue, green, and black. The parody comic Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Club Yonkoma states that Athrun has built a total of 35 Haros for Lacus.
In Mobile Suit Gundam 00, Celestial Being had produced unknown numbers of Haros as an assistant of daily maintenance works. Currently at least 6 unique Haros have appeared in the animation production. The Haros in the series took much more maintenance and combat role than any other series` counterpart, usually seeing them operating with various machines, including mobile weapons.</description>
<picture>28615.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10986" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="9">8.30</rating>
<name>RX-78-2 Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam is one of three prototype mobile suits secretly developed by the embattled Earth Federation. After suffering tremendous losses to Zeon`s mobile suits earlier in the war, the Federation set out to create its own, using the very latest advanced technology. The Gundam is the most successful of these prototypes, a close-combat mobile suit protected by tough Luna Titanium armour, and armed with both lethal beam sabers and a devastating beam rifle as powerful as a battleship cannon. It`s also equipped with an advanced computer which learns from its pilot, ultimately enabling it to operate the Gundam automatically. In the hands of accidental pilot Amuro Ray, this one prototype mobile suit proves to be the equal of any Zeon weapon.</description>
<picture>32757.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10989" type="appears in" update="2009-08-09">
<rating votes="3">4.15</rating>
<name>RGM-79 GM</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The GM - pronounced "Jim" - is a mass-produced version of the RX-78 Gundam, introduced just before the end of the war. In order to reduce its cost, the GM omits the Gundam`s expensive Luna Titanium armor, Core Block system, and spare beam saber, and substitutes a short-range beam spray gun for the Gundam`s beam rifle. Still, it`s an effective close-combat mobile suit, and in the final campaigns of the war the GM turns the tide in favor of the Federation Forces.</description>
<picture>32837.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10991" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">1.05</rating>
<name>RB-79 Ball</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Ball is a mass-produced "mobile pod" armed with a recoilless cannon. These inexpensive vehicles, based on civilian space pods, were created to provide fire support for the Federation Forces` GM mobile suits. Large numbers of Balls are deployed during the Federation`s assaults on the space fortresses Solomon and A Baoa Qu.</description>
<picture>32838.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11094" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.15</rating>
<name>Zaku II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Zaku II is the Principality of Zeon`s standard mass-produced mobile suit. Its manoeuvrability and heavy weaponry make it more than a match for the Earth Federation`s conventional forces. At the start of the war, Zeon`s Zakus wiped out the Earth Federation`s space fleet and overran two-thirds of the planet`s surface, and over the following months the Zaku II has been adapted into several variants for space, land, and even underwater combat. However, it proves to be hopelessly outclassed by the Federation`s prototype mobile suits, and Zeon`s developers begin phasing out the classic Zaku in favor of newer mobile suit designs.</description>
<picture>32992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11097" type="appears in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<name>Dom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This land warfare mobile suit. is a radical improvement over the Zaku II and Gouf. While its predecessors were limited to travelling on foot or making brief rocket-assisted jumps, the jet engines in the Dom`s legs turn it into a high-speed hovercraft. With its maneuverability, heavy armor, and powerful bazooka, the Dom is almost unbeatable in ground combat. When Zeon`s dreaded "Black Tri-Stars" use this new model to attack the immobilized White Base, our heroes are hard-pressed to fight them off.</description>
<picture>32996.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11099" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<name>MS-14 Gelgoog</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>With the Gelgoog, the Principality of Zeon at last creates a mobile suit to rival the Earth Federation`s Gundam. The Gelgoog boasts high performance and sturdy armor like that of the Rick Dom, but it`s also equipped with powerful beam weapons. Although it`s the best mass-produced mobile suit to appear in the war, the Gelgoog arrives too late to change the course of the conflict, and due to Zeon`s manpower shortage it`s piloted mostly by inexperienced trainees.</description>
<picture>32998.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36774" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="4">9.15</rating>
<name>Kitty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="214946" update="2019-04-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハローガンダム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hello, Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hello Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218484" update="2020-01-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めぐりあい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meguriai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226049" update="2020-01-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2020-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛・戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soldiers of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Senshi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
