<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14829" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>28</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-03-17</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Luo Xiao Hei Zhanji</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">罗小黑战记</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15253" type="Alternative Setting">Luo Xiao Hei Zhanji (2019)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<picture>232690.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33443</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>罗小黑战记</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="33">
<externalentity>
<identifier>罗小黑战记/8383472?fr=aladdin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4200" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>flash animation</name>
<description>Made in Adobe Flash (formerly known as Macromedia Flash), a software package for rich multimedia and Web animations and applications. Very popular on amateur fanproductions (like the ones found in places such as YouTube)
Sadly, Flash has also earned a bad reputation among the animation purists because it leads to cheap low-quality animation jobs, since anyone with a hint of creativity and a "idea" on its head can easily learn how to produce an animated feature in Flash... and sell it to the masses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4572" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-22">
<name>human-animal relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and an animal (or an animal-like creature like a dragon) plays an important role in the plot of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5891" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Taoism</name>
<description>Taoism refers to a philosophical or religious tradition in which the basic concept is to establish harmony with the Tao (道), which is the mechanism of everything that exists. The word "Tao" (or "Dao", depending on the romanization scheme) is usually translated as "way", "path" or "principle", although the word also means "nature" as in the nature of all things as well as the natural world. Taoism had not only a profound influence on the culture of China, but also on neighbouring countries. While the philosophical Taoism is not institutionalized, the religious Taoism is institutionalized and present in multiple countries. Taoist philosophy is deeply rooted in contemporary China, and is an unavoidable part of modern Chinese life. Taoist propriety and ethics emphasize the Three Jewels of the Tao: compassion, moderation, and humility.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7141" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-16">
<name>goblin</name>
<description>A goblin is a monstrous creature from European folklore, first attested in stories from the Middle Ages. They are ascribed various and conflicting abilities, temperaments and appearances depending on the story and country of origin. They are almost always small and grotesque, mischievous or outright malicious, and greedy, especially for gold and jewelry. They often have magical abilities similar to a http://anidb.net/t780 [fairy] or http://anidb.net/t2646 [demon].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>220782.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7438" parentid="2282" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>cultivation</name>
<description>Cultivation is a Taoist concept that describes extending one`s lifespan through the practice of martial and mystical arts with the goal of cultivating qi/chi, spiritual life force. Cultivation is a common theme in both Wuxia and Xianxia stories</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="108113" type="main character in" update="2020-01-24">
<name>Luo Xiaohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243965.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108114" type="main character in" update="2020-01-24">
<name>Luo Xiaohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68449.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="223779" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Meow!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">喵</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223780" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Run!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">逃</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223781" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Hey!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">嘿</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223782" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">飘</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223783" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2012-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Wow!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">唷~</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223784" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Gen</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">阿根</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223785" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Piyu</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">比丢</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223786" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep in the Mountains</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">深山</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223787" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Diting</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">谛听</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223788" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2014-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Master Lao</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">老君</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223789" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Creek</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">蓝溪镇</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223790" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2014-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Collection of Twelve</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">拾贰集</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223791" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2014-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Spirit Force</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">灵质力</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223792" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2014-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower Fairy</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">花精灵</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223793" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Soul Wind Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">灵风山</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223794" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Immortal and Fairy</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">仙与精灵</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223795" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Peace and Quiet</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">风平浪静</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223796" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Power Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">顶上战争</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223797" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">City Park</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">城中别苑</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223798" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2015-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Spirit Club Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">妖灵会馆</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223799" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission: Sky Pearl</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">目标天明珠</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223800" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2016-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Anime Convention</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">相遇阿呲阁</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223801" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2016-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape and Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">内外与胜负</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223802" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2016-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Unwritten Rule</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">默契的规则</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223803" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2017-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Early Morning Crescent Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">清晨的萌芽</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223804" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2017-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Lawful Ones and Lawless Ones</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">非法者合法者</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223805" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2017-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">What`s This Taste?</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">这是什么滋味</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223806" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2019-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Parting and Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">离别终会相见</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223807" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">罗小白的期末考试</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223808" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8.5: Goodbye, Piyu</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">再见了，比丢</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223809" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10.5: Music Video - Good Night, Meow!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">MV番外——晚安喵</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223810" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24.5: Music Video - Shh!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">MV番外——嘘</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
