<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14822" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-04-05</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yesterday o Utatte</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">イエスタデイをうたって</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sing "Yesterday" for Me</title>
</titles>
<url>https://singyesterday.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17732" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshikawa Maho</name>
<name id="30322" type="Series Composition">Fujiwara Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="8008" type="Original Work">Toume Kei</name>
<name id="49748" type="Work">DMM.futureworks</name>
<name id="30322" type="Direction">Fujiwara Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="30322" type="Series Composition">Fujiwara Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="7866" type="Character Design">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a romance seinen manga series by http://anidb.net/cr8008 [Toume Kei].
After college, http://anidb.net/ch108090 [Uozumi Rikuo], a boy without much ambition in life, takes on a job at a convenience store. The days pass by uneventfully for Rikuo until he meets http://anidb.net/ch108088 [his former love interest and classmate], but especially thanks to the unusual http://anidb.net/ch108089 [Nonaka Haru], and http://anidb.net/ch109134 [her pet crow]...
Source: M-U
Note: Additional 6 episodes will have an exclusive advance streaming on AbemaTV after TV broadcast.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="67">6.66</permanent>
<temporary count="68">6.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>243921.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22975</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39710</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://singyesterday.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sing_"Yesterday"_for_Me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>イエスタデイをうたって</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5631</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367978</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_yesterday</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sing-yesterday-for-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://abema.tv/video/title/481-3</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4431" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-06">
<name>love at first sight</name>
<description>Plot device: When two characters meet for the first time, at least one party, supposedly, immediately falls in love with the other party, and from then on tries to get to know that party better.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="108087" type="main character in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Hayakawa Rou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108088" type="main character in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="5">9.12</rating>
<name>Morinome Shinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108089" type="main character in" update="2020-04-19">
<rating votes="5">5.37</rating>
<name>Nonaka Haru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4432" picture="200731.jpg">Miyamoto Yume</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108090" type="main character in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Uozumi Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36910" picture="214237.jpg">Kobayashi Chikahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109134" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Kansuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40523" picture="192219.jpg">Maekawa Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109135" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Kinoshita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109136" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Morita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109137" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Yuzuhara Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109138" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Minato Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109139" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Takishita Katsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43410" picture="225078.jpg">Horie Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109140" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Sayama Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109141" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Fukuda Takanori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109142" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Fukuda Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="227739" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">社会のはみ出し者は自己変革を目指す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakai no Hamidashi Mono wa Jiko Henkaku o Mezasu</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794606</identifier>
<identifier>sing-yesterday-for-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227740" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">袋小路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukurokouji</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794607</identifier>
<identifier>sing-yesterday-for-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227741" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛とはなんぞや</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Is Love?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to wa Nanzo ya</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794608</identifier>
<identifier>sing-yesterday-for-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227742" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">川は流れて 榀子帰郷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawa wa Nagarete: Shinako Kikyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228402" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228403" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228404" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228405" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228496" update="2020-04-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228497" update="2020-04-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228498" update="2020-04-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
