<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1484" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>155</episodecount>
<startdate>1977-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>1980-10-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lupin Sansei (1977)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">新・ルパン三世</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ルパン三世 PART2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin III: Part II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Lupin III</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Red jacket</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin the 3rd: Series 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin the Third: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Giacca rossa</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Люпет Трети (1977)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shin Lupin Sansei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Lupin Sansei: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shin Lupin III</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">鲁邦三世 (TV第2部)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Lupin III TV 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">l3tv2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">l32</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">lupins2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">lupin2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ルパン三世 (1977)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lupin the 3rd</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Edgar, le détective cambrioleur</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Lupin III - Seconda serie</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1485" type="Sequel">Lupin Sansei: Part III</anime>
<anime id="421" type="Prequel">Lupin Sansei</anime>
<anime id="320" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Cagliostro no Shiro</anime>
<anime id="823" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Lupin vs Fukusei-ningen</anime>
<anime id="15003" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: The First</anime>
<anime id="12084" type="Other">Lupin the Third: Lupin Sansei no Theme</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7469" approval="9" total="9">Magic Kaito</anime>
<anime id="266" approval="5" total="10">Meitantei Conan</anime>
<anime id="3683" approval="3" total="6">Sen`ya Ichiya Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="621" approval="1" total="5">D.N. Angel</anime>
<anime id="450" approval="1" total="4">Mouse</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/tv/data/t_sin_rupin.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="5421" type="Series Composition">Yamatoya Atsushi</name>
<name id="4479" type="Music">Oono Yuuji</name>
<name id="1267" type="Original Work">Monkey Punch</name>
<name id="4117" type="Character Design">Kitahara Takeo</name>
<name id="7752" type="Original Plan">Kimiya Shigeru</name>
</creators>
<description>Lupin III chronicles the adventures of http://anidb.net/ch7622 [Arsène Lupin Sansei], the world`s greatest thief, and his partners in crime: master marksman http://anidb.net/ch7976 [Jigen Daisuke], beautiful and scheming http://anidb.net/ch8458 [Mine Fujiko] and stoic samurai http://anidb.net/ch8474 [Ishikawa Goemon XIII]. Lupin and his gang travel around the globe in search of the world`s greatest treasures and riches and always keeping one step ahead of the tireless http://anidb.net/ch8460 [Inspector Zenigata], who has vowed to bring Lupin to justice.
Source: ANN
Note: The R1 episode ordering differs from the original, mainly due to episode 3, which was moved to episode 26. Reasoning being the Nazi themed content which http://anidb.net/cr40923 [Pioneer Entertainment (USA)] wanted to release only after the viewers made themselves familiar with the franchise. There are other discrepancies in the footage itself due to copyright infringement issues. The episodes 145 and 155 (both by http://anidb.net/cr40 [Hayao Miyazaki]) have been released previously on VHS by Streamline Pictures (US) as "Tales of the Wolf" and "Greatest Capers" (compilation tape)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="462">7.26</permanent>
<temporary count="469">7.43</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>168586.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>885</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1425</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4189</identifier>
<identifier>iocdgs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/tv/data/t_sin_rupin.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=53</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/english/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=171</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Lupin_III_Part_II</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ルパン三世_(TV第2シリーズ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3574</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89480</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1462</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="362" parentid="2793" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-24">
<name>dancing</name>
<description>Dance is when people move their body to music. There are many kinds of dance, like ballet or waltz. Dancing can be done for fun but can be also an art.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2394" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>mischievous</name>
<description>The character enjoys causing small irritations, pranks, and misfortune for others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3248" parentid="362" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-13">
<name>belly dance</name>
<description>Belly dance is any solo, improvised dance based on torso articulation originating from the Middle East. Belly dance takes many different forms depending on region, both in costume and dance style, and new styles have evolved in the West as its popularity has spread globally. In the Middle East, belly dance has two functions: as a social dance, it is performed by ordinary men and women of all ages at celebrations and social gatherings, although in more traditional societies such occasions are gender segregated, with separate parties for men and women; as an art, professionals perform it with an emphasis on stagecraft and special costumes designed to show off the movements to best effect, but they are not seen as respectable in the Middle East, with a strong social stigma attached to female dancers in particular, since the display of their bodies in public is considered sinful. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3489" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>car chases</name>
<description>Car chases occur as part of the action setting in this anime.</description>
<picurl>211263.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3536" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-05-20">
<name>undercover</name>
<description>Be it the spy, the criminal or the police, someone pretends to be a person they aren`t in order to obtain information or something of value.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4945" parentid="7079" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Prague</name>
<description>Prague is the capital and largest city in the Czech Republic, the 14th largest city in the European Union and also the historical capital of Bohemia. It is situated in the north-west of the country on the Vltava river. The city has a temperate climate, with warm summers and chilly winters.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214368.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7079" parentid="2831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Czech Republic</name>
<description>The Czech Republic, also known as Czechia, is a landlocked nation state in Central Europe bordered by Germany to the west, Austria to the south, Slovakia to the east and Poland to the northeast. It is a unitary parliamentary republic, the capital and largest city is Prague.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7622" type="main character in" update="2012-04-11">
<rating votes="2567">8.66</rating>
<name>Lupin Sansei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The grandson of Arsène Lupin is tall, lanky, impertinent, and very sneaky. His prime qualities are listed as "appearing like a god, disappearing like a demon"; in other words, he appears with a flash and leaves with a whisper. Despite being aided by many gadgets, his main talents lie in plotting and evasion of weapons.
While his grandfather was known as the "Gentleman Thief", Lupin III has no qualms about trying to separate a woman from her modesty. He fancies himself as quite the ladies man, but his advances rarely succeeds. His primary weakness is his overconfidence and lust for Mine Fujiko.</description>
<picture>85729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4652" picture="27089.jpg">Yamada Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7976" type="main character in" update="2019-07-18">
<rating votes="1164">8.59</rating>
<name>Jigen Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jigen is Lupin`s marksman. He can perform a 0.3-second quick-draw and is amazingly accurate. He prefers to conceal his eyes using his hat, as it gives him a more enigmatic appearance; when one or both of his eyes are seen, it is occasionally used to demonstrate surprise. In the second anime series, it is revealed that he uses a notch of the hat to aim. However, due to the nature of the series, no single episode could be considered canon; Jigen has been seen shooting excellently without his hat, even in the very series this is mentioned in, he is seen making shots from angles where his hat`s notch would be useless and even during times he is not wearing his hat at all. He is also proficient in many different firearms, such as machine guns, sniper rifles, and even a PTRS Anti-Tank Rifle.
His preferred weapon, however, is a Smith and Wesson M19 Combat revolver, based on the pistol`s stopping power and its dependability against mechanical misfire. He keeps the weapon in a fabric holster specially constructed in the back beltline of his pants. He also feels quite naked without a gun. Jigen also carries a few rounds of special ammunition such as armor piercing ammunition to use a circumstances dictate. As he frequently travels by air, its not been made clear how he successfully gets his weapon through airline checkpoints.</description>
<picture>236414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37" picture="43092.jpg">Kobayashi Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8458" type="main character in" update="2012-04-11">
<rating votes="1342">6.81</rating>
<name>Mine Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4735" picture="29144.jpg">Masuyama Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8460" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-18">
<rating votes="620">7.62</rating>
<name>Zenigata Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Interpol inspector Zenigata has made it his mission in life to arrest Lupin. He would love to arrest the other members of Lupin`s gang, but Zenigata is really after the mastermind himself. Lupin and Zenigata appear to be the worst of enemies, but they are, in a manner of speaking, friends; something Lupin shows openly (often by greeting Zenigata with mock affection), but it is an idea Zenigata is extremely reluctant to entertain. Similarly, he is often awed by Lupin`s genius, but refuses to show it.</description>
<picture>236411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8474" type="main character in" update="2012-04-11">
<rating votes="634">6.81</rating>
<name>Ishikawa Goemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ishikawa Goemon is a fictional character created by Monkey Punch for his Lupin III series. Goemon is the thirteenth generation of renegade samurai, a descendant of the historical figure Ishikawa Goemon. He is usually quiet and participates in Arsène Lupin III`s exploits less frequently than Daisuke Jigen.
While Goemon might be considered one of Lupin`s friends, it starts off more of a professional relationship than friendship. By the second series, Goemon has developed a true loyalty to Lupin, refusing to give away Lupin`s secrets when tortured in one second series episode, for example. However, he easily gets annoyed by Lupin`s antics, especially Lupin`s infatuation with women in general and Fujiko Mine in particular. He will occasionally oppose Lupin directly when Lupin`s jobs or actions do not agree with Goemon`s morals. He has even promised that the last act he will take with Lupin is delivering his deathblow. However, Goemon doesn`t hesitate to help Lupin in serious situations, and readily assists him any time Lupin works for a just cause. Many theorize that Goemon associates with Lupin out of admiration for his profession, as Goemon`s ancestor was a master thief himself.
Goemon has a much more amicable relationship with Jigen. Goemon sees Jigen as a fellow honorable warrior, while Jigen sees Goemon as a trustworthy "foxhole buddy," and the two are frequently paired together during jobs, and usually help keep Lupin in check.
On the odd occasion and increasingly in recent years, Goemon will ally himself with Fujiko, in spite of his distrust of her. As long as their goal is the same and Fujiko makes no attempts to betray him, the two work well together and usually achieve what they seek.
Goemon has an extreme sense of pride in his abilities, and when he cannot accomplish a task, usually feels extreme shame and remorse afterward. Breaking Zantetsuken, as he did in a battle with Flinch from Mystery of Mamo, is a common cause of shame. He will also show chagrin when he succumbs to his weaknesses, as when a woman ran off with his sword in Tokyo Crisis. On many of these occasions, Goemon will leave to meditate or further train to rid himself of his weak points.
Goemon`s most oft-seen pastime is meditation; during inactive moments, even with potential danger near, he is usually seated on the floor with legs crossed, eyes closed. Like most of the Lupin gang he is a trained driver and pilot, although he prefers being a passenger rather than taking the driver seat.
Goemon shows allegiance to Japanese culture as strictly as his travelling and unique lifestyle can allow. He dresses in an hakama and wears fundoshi instead of underwear. His preferred food is Japanese cuisine. Although he may toast with champagne, his drink of choice is sake. In unoccasional moments, he has been seen smoking a traditional bamboo kiseru. His favorite music is enka, or as Jigen calls it, "elevator music".
Although typically a person of mellow aloofness, Goemon has been seen exploding with frustration, admiring beautiful women, and...very rarely...screaming in fright. Such out of character moments are usually treated as humorous takes. His martial arts training gives him many extraordinary talents, i.e., underwater breath control for diving without an aqualung and a limited understanding of the supernatural. He can easily best several trained thugs in unarmed combat and can barehandedly catch an arrow or thrown dagger. His trademark skill is near-superhuman fleetness, enabling him to sword-slice bullets in half before they make contact. It should be mentioned that, despite the deadliness of his weapon, Goemon will never take a human life unless challenged to a duel, and even then only if the opponent reveals a dishonorable nature.
If Goemon has a true weakness, it is that he`s even more weak with women than Lupin is. He readily trusts any woman who seems superficially trustworthy or innocent, often landing him in much trouble. At the same time, he fears sultry women will distract him from his training, and tends to blush or flee when any woman is put in less than modest situation.
Goemon also is very bad with money, and constantly charges Lupin for his services in some fashion. What he does with the money is a usually complete mystery. In $1 Money Wars he gives it to the female leader of a cult, who promptly runs off with it.
Commonly thought to be just a samurai, an episode of Shin Lupin III, ("Goemon`s Revenge") has Goemon visiting his Iga Ninja sensei. This episode depicts him as having had the training of a master ninja, perhaps giving some reason behind his willingness to find thievery as an acceptable practice, in spite of his samurai ways.</description>
<picture>85727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3233" picture="171389.jpg">Inoue Makio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22235" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Adolf Hitler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176944.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66923" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Peter Jakob</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="15968" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネッシーの唄が聞こえる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">50 Ways to Leave Your 50-foot Lover</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tu peux entendre Nessie chanter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nessie no Uta ga Kikoeru</title>
<summary>At Loch Ness in Scotland, the mysterious monster Nessie reveals itself from the lake, charmed by Fujiko’s singing. Seeing this, Doctor Oz decides to use Fujiko to capture Nessie for his personal gain. Will Lupin let Doctor Oz get away with his scheme?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679171</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15969" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">浮世絵ブルースはいかが</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Now Museum, Now You Don`t</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`estampe japonaise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ukiyoe Blues wa Ikaga</title>
<summary>Lupin meets the grandson of master Ukiyoe artist, Toushusai Sharaku and learns that he has been switching his own works with his grandfather’s originals. Unable to switch the last painting due to illness, he asks Lupin to switch it in his stead. Will Lupin be able to pull off the switch and what will happen to the original Ukiyoe paintings?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679181</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15970" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リオの夕陽に咲く花束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buns, Guns and Fun in the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La coupe du monde brésilienne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rio no Yuuhi ni Saku Satsutaba</title>
<summary>An international soccer game is taking place in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil and Lupin has his eyes on the box office and betting takes. Will the box office heist go as planned?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679169</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15971" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第4次元の魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Auntie Ballistics</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une sorcière de la quatrième dimension</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai-4-jigen no Majo</title>
<summary>Fujiko Mine, a mysterious woman who claims to be Fujiko’s aunt, gives Lupin an ultimatum: Find Marshal Rommel’s lost gold or die! First, Lupin must decipher the location of the gold, written in ancient hieroglyphs. Will Lupin be able to locate the golden treasure? Time is running out!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679209</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15972" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">五右ェ門の復讐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Mastery</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’ange de Goemon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goemon no Fukushuu</title>
<summary>Upon returning to Japan, Goemon finds his master on the brink of death. Furthermore, Jinkuro, a fellow disciple, had stolen half of the scroll containing the Secret Arts of the Iga Ninja. Knowing he is no match for Goemon, Jinkuro deliberately gets arrested so he can be put in prison, beyond Goemon’s reach. Will Goemon be able to avenge his master?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679205</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15973" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電撃ハトポッポ作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Electroshock Pigeon Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’affaire du « Blitzkrieg »</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dengeki Hato Poppo Sakusen</title>
<summary>As a master thief, Lupin has many secret techniques up his sleeve, and one of them is his Levitation Technique. In order to get their hands on this technique, a crime syndicate plots a dirty trick, where a fake Lupin tortures a man known as X8 and frames the real Lupin. Will a vengeful X8 believe Lupin’s words?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679223</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15974" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女刑事メロン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lady Detective Melon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Femme policier « Melon »</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Keiji Melon</title>
<summary>Lupin has sent a notice declaring he will steal all the cash from every bank in Paris. Detective Melon, the granddaughter of Inspector Garimard, is chosen to catch Lupin alongside Inspector Zenigata. Inspector Garimard was the original Lupin’s rival, and now their grandchildren are about to square off. Where will the chase lead the two rivals?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679221</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15975" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">十年金庫は破れるか!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Safe Bet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’affaire des coffres-forts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juunen Kinko wa Yabureru ka!?</title>
<summary>Vault maker Marukin Safe Company is forced into bankruptcy after Lupin cracks open their impenetrable safes. To test his own skills, Marukin’s son challenges Lupin to open a safe he has designed, and resorts to rather drastic measures to convince a reluctant Lupin. Furthermore, the safe Lupin must open has no keyhole, dial or even a door! Could this be the first safe Lupin can`t open?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679201</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15976" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン三世颯爽登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of Lupin III</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une bonne mine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Sansei Sassou Toujou</title>
<summary>It’s been a long time since Jigen, Goemon and Fujiko have heard from Lupin. Then one day, they each receive an invitation from Lupin for a reunion aboard the luxury liner Sirloin. Little do they know that the reunion is a trap plotted by a vengeful Mister X! Where is the real Lupin?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679167</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15977" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カリブ海の大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curse of the Jumbo Juju</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rubis sanglant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Carib Kai no Daibouken</title>
<summary>Forward Hees, the world’s richest man, suddenly dies a mysterious death and leaves a large ruby to Fujiko in his will. After inheriting the ruby, Fujiko comes down with the same mysterious fever as Hees. The ruby, in fact, had been stolen from a cult temple in the Caribbean. Lupin must return the ruby in order to save Fujiko, but the cult has something in store for Lupin, as well! Will Lupin and Fujiko be able escape the cult’s wrath?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679191</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15978" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オイルダラーを狙え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sheik-down</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des ambitions ensevelies dans le désert rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oil Dollar o Nerae</title>
<summary>A small Arab nation has received a blackmail notice. Pay a $100 million or have their oil fields blown up. Lupin targets the money, but his plans are hindered when he finds out the culprits are using human bombs. Will the desert winds blow in Lupin’s favor or will everything blow up in his face?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679197</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15979" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モロッコの風は熱く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wind Is Hot in Morocco</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un vent chaud souffle sur le Maroc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Morocco no Kaze wa Atsuku</title>
<summary>Lupin and Inspector Zenigata get kidnapped and the two are forcibly conscripted into the Foreign Legion in Morocco. Lupin and Inspector Zenigata make a run for it, but not before they`re shackled together at the neck. Now the two must form an awkward alliance to pull off their escape. Can Lupin and Inspector Zenigata overcome their differences, at least temporarily?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679225</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15980" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツタンカーメン三千年の呪い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cursed Case Scenario</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le masque de Toutankhamon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tutankhamen Sanzennen no Noroi</title>
<summary>Lupin has stolen the golden death mask of Tutankhamen, the ancient Egyptian pharaoh known as the “boy king.” However, when Lupin tries on the golden death mask he becomes possessed by an ominous curse. Will Lupin be able to break the three-thousand-year-old curse of the pharaohs?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679177</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15981" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラックパンサー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Birthday Pursuit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Panthère noire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Black Panther</title>
<summary>The Black Panther, the world’s largest emerald, gets its name from the black panther that appears inside it when a light shines on the emerald at a particular angle. After capturing this one-of-a-kind emerald, Lupin hides it in a museum to retrieve it at a later time. However, the emerald goes missing and things get even more complicated when two rivaling inspectors take on the case. Will Lupin get his hands on the emerald again?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679199</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15982" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンデレラの切手はどこへ行った</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Princess of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Où est le timbre Cendrillon ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cinderella no Kitte wa Doko e Itta</title>
<summary>According to legend, a stamp named the Cinderella Shadow is said to make its owner a princess. Lupin and his gang pull off the heist, but a girl name Alice who also wants the stamp tags along. A clever and very persistent Alice proves to be a major headache for Lupin. Will the little girl get her royal wish?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679219</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15983" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンは二度死ぬ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Dies Twice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar meurt deux fois</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin wa Nido Shinu</title>
<summary>A hit has been ordered on Lupin and Puma, a formidable hitman who specializes in long-range attacks, is on his trail! Lupin takes his chances with a close range, one-on-one showdown against Puma, but the plan seemingly backfires and Lupin is shot. Will Lupin’s soul rest in peace?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679229</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15984" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金塊の運び方教えます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gold Smuggling 101</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comment transporter les lingots ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkai no Hakobikata Oshiemasu</title>
<summary>Fujiko and a mystery man have an enticing job for Lupin: Stealing a ton of gold bullion from a Swiss Bank, a bank renowned for its tight security. Can it be done? What is the mystery man’s true identity and who will have the last laugh?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679173</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15985" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バラとピストル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shot Through the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rose et le pistolet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara to Pistol</title>
<summary>Linda, a beautiful Spanish dancer, has stolen Jigen’s heart and a vengeful Meyer has taken Lupin’s love Fujiko hostage. Believing the women they love are in danger and unaware that Linda and Meyer are working together, Lupin and Jigen are unwittingly set up to kill each other. With their guns aimed at each other, they pull the trigger. Will love bring both of them down?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679215</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15986" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピサの斜塔は立っているか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shaky Pisa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ne laissez pas tomber la tour de Pise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pisa no Shatou wa Tatteiru ka</title>
<summary>A man is threatening to destroy the Leaning Tower of Pisa with a device that generates artificial earthquakes. The Italian government has no choice but to meet the culprit’s demands and prepares the ransom, but Lupin takes the ransom for himself! With an enraged criminal armed with a destructive device on the loose, what will become of the Leaning Tower of Pisa?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679175</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15987" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベネチア超特急</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Disorient Express</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’Orient-Express</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Venezia Choutokkyuu</title>
<summary>The Trans Europe Superexpress train has departed Venice and is headed to France. Onboard the Superexpress is crime boss Don Marcino’s ill-gotten treasures. Can Lupin and his gang pull off the heist before the train reaches its destination?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679179</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15988" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">追いつめられたルパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell Toupee</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar est coincé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oitsumerareta Lupin</title>
<summary>While trying to snag General Hatler’s prize medallion, which contains a fifty-carat ruby, Lupin inadvertently reels in Hatler’s biggest secret, his toupee! An enraged General Hatler orders Lupin and his gang to be killed. With an order out for his head, Lupin and Fujiko are left with nowhere to run! Has Lupin finally met his match?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679203</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15989" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪盗ねずみ小僧現わる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rats to You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voici le grand chef Mimikozo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitou Nezumi Kozou Arawaru</title>
<summary>The great thief Nezumi-Kozou Jirokichi IV appears before Goemon and reveals that their ancestors competed in the first International Thieves Championship together, but were defeated by Lupin’s grandfather, Arsène Lupin. Nezumi-Kozou proposes the two should team up to avenge their ancestors’ dishonor, but will the Lupin clan claim the win again?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679211</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15990" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の女人館を探れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin in Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sur la trace du mystérieux palace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Nyonin Yakata o Sagure</title>
<summary>Lupin and Jigen are in a remote area pursing a mysterious treasure, when they save a woman being chased by hoodlums. The woman invites the two back to her sister’s manor, which is full of beautiful women. However, the invitation and the beautiful women are a trap to expose the men to aging gas. Will an aged Lupin be forced into retirement?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679207</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15991" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファイルM123を盗め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ZenigataCon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dérobez le dossier M123</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">File M123 o Nusume</title>
<summary>Lupin and Fujiko have been invited to a party hosted by Marcel Dulane, a member of Paris’ high society. However, the elegant party turns out to be a trap. Fujiko is taken hostage and Lupin, with a time-bomb belt strapped to his waist, is ordered to steal a certain file from Scotland Yard. Will Lupin be able to infiltrate Scotland Yard and save Fujiko, all before the bomb belt detonates?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679183</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15992" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">必殺鉄トカゲ見参</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lair of the Land-shark</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lézard au souffle mortel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hissatsu Tetsu Tokage Kenzan</title>
<summary>The warden of an African prison is holding Fujiko captive. Lupin and his gang infiltrate the prison and attempt to break Fujiko out, but they become the target of the Iron Lizards, robotic devices developed to chase down fugitives and loaded with explosives! With the Iron Lizards hot on their tail, will their prison break end with a bang?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679213</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15993" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒトラーの遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Be or Nazi Be</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trésor de guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitler no Isan</title>
<summary>An old man who supposedly knows the secret to Hitler’s legacy lives in East Germany within the Berlin Wall. Lupin and his gang track the old man down, but the old man can’t recall anything about any legacy. In order to bring back the old man’s memories, Lupin and his gang decides to put on an act. Will the old man’s forgotten memories come rushing back?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679217</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15994" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名探偵空を行く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Case of the Risible Dirigible</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mystère en dirigeable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meitantei Sora o Iku</title>
<summary>A Count challenges Lupin to steal a gemstone named Dracula’s Tear from on board his airship, the Hendenburg. However, also on board the Hendenburg are several formidable detectives: Homes III, Detective Archer, Koojisuke Kaneda and Inspector Zenigata. Will Lupin accept the Count’s challenge and will he be able to complete the task before the airship lands, where the police will be waiting for him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679193</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15995" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白夜に向かって撃て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Face the Midnight Sun and Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qui a tiré pendant le soleil de minuit ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byakuya ni Mukatte Ute</title>
<summary>Beautiful Swedish twins, Latica and Anita, are engaged in a battle to the death over the Viking treasure map concealed on their backs. In disguise, Lupin learns the map’s secret, but the map possesses an additional secret. Who will get their hands on the Viking treasure?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679227</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15996" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二つの顔のルパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crude Reproduction, Perfect Frame</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux Edgar !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Kao no Lupin</title>
<summary>Lupin is suffering from Transformation Sickness, an illness that transforms him into a cruel, cold-blooded criminal at the stroke of midnight, and leaves him with no recollection of his murderous crime spree in the morning. In despair, Lupin even contemplates taking his own life, but is the “other Lupin” really Lupin?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679195</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15997" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンフランシスコ大追跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Left My Mind in San Francisco</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Course poursuite à San Francisco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">San Francisco Daitsuiseki</title>
<summary>A criminal gang has hidden a microfilm containing the manufacturing process for artificial diamonds, developed by NASA, in one of Inspector Zenigata’s molars. Determined to get his hands on that microfilm, Lupin must capture Inspector Zenigata, who now believes that he is seeing hallucinations of Lupin everywhere. Can Inspector Zenigata’s mind handle this bizarre reverse chase?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679189</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15998" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大統領への贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sleight Before Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un cadeau pour le président</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daitouryou e no Okurimono</title>
<summary>A rare bottle of Bordeaux, commissioned by Napoleon for his beloved wife, Josephine, is to be given to the President of the United States as a Christmas present. Lupin and his gang decide to steal the wine while it’s being transported over the Atlantic, but Inspector Zenigata stands in their way. Who will be celebrating come Christmas?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679187</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="15999" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モナコGPに賭けろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s Vrooming Who</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Grand prix à Monaco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monaco GP ni Kakero</title>
<summary>Lupin is in Monaco to race his new toy in the Monaco Grand Prix. Or so he thought. Lupin ends up losing both his money and race car in a fixed poker game at the casino. Then, Fujiko tells Lupin about a fixed race, suggesting that Lupin should enter it to turn the tables on the man who cheated him, while also stealing the enormous betting takes. Who will be laughing at the finish line?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679185</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16000" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">非常ベルにルパンは笑う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Laughs While the Alarm Bell Rings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alerte à la banque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijou Bell ni Lupin wa Warau</title>
<summary>Lupin announces he’s going to steal the betting takes at the Kentucky Derby, but the heist falls short and fails. However, it’s all part of the plan. Lupin’s main target is really the Metropolitan Bank’s underground vault. Will Lupin get past their tight security measures and pull off the heist?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679261</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16001" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月影城の秘密をあばけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Expose the Secret of Tsukikagejoo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère du château Tsukikage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukikage-jou no Himitsu o Abake</title>
<summary>Massive riches have been hidden inside Tsukikage Castle. Lupin and his gang must decipher a code to find out the whereabouts of this great treasure. However, the Fuma Ninja Clan is also plotting to take the treasure for themselves. Will Lupin be able to decipher the code and locate the treasure before his rivals do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679237</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16002" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ICPOの甘い罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sweet ICPO Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le doux piège d`Interpol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ICPO no Amai Wana</title>
<summary>The ICPO bureau chief promises to erase Fujiko’s criminal record in exchange for her cooperation in arresting Lupin. The woman who knows everything about him proves to be a formidable opponent and Lupin is captured. Up against an ego-bruised Inspector Zenigata and a determined Fujiko, have Lupin’s heisting days come to an end?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679241</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16003" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">可愛い女には毒がある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Pretty Woman Has Venom</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une femme venimeuse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaii Onna ni wa Doku ga Aru</title>
<summary>After several divorces and a couple of deceased husbands, Jacqueline has amassed a fortune and a collection of impressive jewels. In a twist of fate, Lupin and Jacqueline become close... Too close for Jigen and Goemon’s comfort. Fujiko, on the other hand, who is after Jacqueline’s jewels, gets kidnapped by the Cobra crime syndicate. Blinded by love, will Lupin realize who the true venomous snake is?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679263</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16004" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私が愛したルパン (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin, Whom I Loved (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar, mon amour perdu (partie 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ga Aishita Lupin (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>An illicit auction selling smuggled treasures is taking place. Lupin targets the auction, but is outsmarted by Fujiko, who takes the auction items for herself, as she usually does. In the process, Lupin discovers the auctioneer is Cornelia, the woman he once loved who died saving his life. Has Cornelia really risen from her grave and if so, why?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679265</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16005" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オリオンの王冠は誰のもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Whom Does Orion`s Crown Belong?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qui porte la couronne ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orion no Oukan wa Dare no Mono</title>
<summary>Orion’s Crown has been stolen and is up for grabs at a black-market auction. Lupin has his eyes on both the crown and the auction money, but first he must outsmart the other parties vying for the crown, including Fujiko. Furthermore, Jigen is working for the seller and Goemon is working for a bidder. With an auction full of deceit and trickery, who will ultimately get the crown?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679231</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16006" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミサイルジャック作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Missilejack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Opération détournement de missiles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Missilejack Sakusen</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang steal a suitcase containing Costa Rican diamonds, but the contents turns out to be Inspector Zenigata. The real diamonds are being shipped to Puerto Rico inside a missile and Lupin must find out the precise launch time to intercept it. Will Lupin be able to get his hands on the Costa Rican diamonds and maintain his reputation?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679245</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16007" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた特別装甲車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vanishing Special Armored Car</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La voiture blindée a disparu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Tokubetsu Soukousha</title>
<summary>The Sleeping Lion, a statue made of solid gold, is being transported to a museum by a specially armored, airtight car to mark the 50th anniversary of Australia’s independence. Lupin steals the armored car together with the statue out from under the Sydney Police’s watchful eye, but then discovers that also inside the armored car is a nearly asphyxiated Inspector Zenigata. Will Lupin choose the golden statue over Inspector Zenigata’s life?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679253</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16008" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">香港の夜空にダイヤは消えた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Diamond Disappeared in the Hong Kong Night Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les diamants évaporés dans le ciel de minuit...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hong Kong no Yozora ni Dia wa Kieta</title>
<summary>Lupin and Jigen sneak on board a ship smuggling diamonds. However, what they find on board are several thousand chickens! Lupin and his gang infiltrate the Hong Kong smuggling boss’s lair where diamonds are being illicitly sold, but the diamonds are nowhere to be found. Will Lupin discover the secret of the chickens?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679243</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16009" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンお高く売ります</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Will Fetch a High Price</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar à vendre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Otakaku Urimasu</title>
<summary>Lupin has been put on auction at the Wanted Club and Dr. Mad places the winning bid. Dr. Mad also purchases Fujiko and Jigen from the Wanted Club’s auctions. The three are abandoned on a deserted island with killer cyborgs as part of Dr. Mad’s human reconstruction experiment. Can Lupin, Jigen and Fujiko get off the island alive?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679257</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16010" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジンギスカンの埋蔵金</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Buried Treasure of Genghis Khan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de Gengis Khan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genghis Khan no Maizoukin</title>
<summary>Lupin and Jigen head to Mongolia in search of Genghis Khan’s buried treasures. Meanwhile, Goemon is visiting his ancestor’s grave to pay his respects when he encounters Fujiko, who is in search of Yoshitsune Minamoto’s buried treasure. Will their searches lead to either Genghis Khan or Minamoto’s buried treasures?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679239</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16011" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴリラギャングを追っかけろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chase the Gorilla Gang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la poursuite du Gang des Gorilles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gorilla Gang o Okkakero</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang are attending a party in Africa, waiting for an opportunity to snatch a rare black pearl. However, their plan goes awry when a gang of gorillas crashes the party and steals the black pearl. Lupin and his gang throw a decoy party to lure the gorillas back, but is someone pulling the strings of the gorillas?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679235</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16012" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花嫁になったルパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Becomes a Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar devient une mariée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanayome ni Natta Lupin</title>
<summary>A wealthy shipping magnate and also a bachelor, Onabes’ final voyage is nothing short of extravagant, with a ship full of beautiful women and fine art. Things go as planned when Lupin infiltrates the ship disguised as a woman, but things get complicated when Onabes falls in love and proposes to Lupin. Will Lady Lupin be walking down the aisle?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679249</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16013" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぐや姫の宝を探せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find Princess Kaguya`s Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la recherche du trésor de princesse Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaguya-hime no Takara o Sagase</title>
<summary>Kaguya, a beautiful woman, separately asks Lupin, Jigen and Goemon to gather the tears of the Yeti, a mermaid’s scale, and the liver of a dragon so she can make a secret potion. Unaware that each of them has been given a task, they travel to the far corners of the earth to find these items. Will Kaguya’s beloved prince awake from his sleep?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679247</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16014" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺しはワインの匂い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Killing Is the Smell of Wine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`odeur de la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koroshi wa Wine no Nioi</title>
<summary>Lupin manages to steal crime boss Mulligan’s precious jewels, only have them stolen from him by Fujiko! Mulligan, unaware that Fujiko has his jewels, hires a skilled gunman named Hangman to take them back from Lupin. Showered with Hangman’s bullets, Lupin and his gang return fire with rare wine. Meanwhile, Inspector Zenigata is closing in on Lupin. Will Lupin be able to outrun both Hangman and Inspector Zenigata?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679255</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16015" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吸血鬼になったルパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Becomes a Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar, le vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuuketsuki ni Natta Lupin</title>
<summary>A two-thousand-year-old casket has been excavated. Inside the casket is Camilla, a beautiful woman in a near-death state, holding a golden statuette of the Virgin Mary. Lupin attempts to steal the golden statuette, but things don’t go as planned when Camilla, a vampire awakes from her long slumber. Will Lupin be able to save Fujiko from being sacrificed for Camilla’s revenge?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679233</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16016" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女王陛下のズッコケ警部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Majesty`s Slipshod Inspectors</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Détective de sa majesté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joouheika no Zukkoke Keibu</title>
<summary>Lupin has his eyes on the royal family’s Imperial State Crown, but thanks to Scotland Yard’s Inspector Dover, stealing it won’t be easy. After their initial heist fails, Lupin and his gang plan to take the crown on the day of Princess Mary’s royal wedding. Will Big Ben chime in Lupin’s favor?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679259</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16017" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北京原人の骨はどこに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where Are Peking Man`s Bones</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Où sont les os de l`homme de Pékin ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Peking Genjin no Hone wa Doko ni</title>
<summary>Lupin is in Hong Kong for a vacation when he is asked to find a woman in return for helping him escape from Inspector Zenigata. Lupin discovers the pickpocket who stole his wallet is the daughter of the woman he is looking for, and in her possession are the archeologically significant bones of the Peking Man. With Fujiko also after the Peking Man, will Lupin be able to add the bones to his private collection?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679251</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16018" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私が愛したルパン (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin, Whom I Loved (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edgar, mon amour perdu (partie 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ga Aishita Lupin (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Lupin is reunited with Cornelia, a woman who died by her father’s hands to save Lupin`s life. However, Cornelia’s memories of Lupin have been erased. Her father is Dr. Zel, a Nazi who has succeeded in resurrecting corpses and controlling them. Cornelia is caught between the lies her father tells her and her memories of love for Lupin. Will Lupin be able to save Cornelia?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679267</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16019" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時を駆ける少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Who Travels Through Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Kakeru Shoujo</title>
<summary>Lupin gets called out to New York by Fujita, where he rescues a girl hunted by an organization called Red Spider. Lupin does everything he can to help the poor girl suffering from amnesia; he tries hypnosis on her but to no avail, he gets hypnotized instead. Who is this girl, and why is Red Spider after her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685641</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16020" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンを呼ぶ悪魔の鐘の音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of the Devil`s Bells Calls Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin o Yobu Akuma no Kane no Ne</title>
<summary>Jigen and Gomen have sent a letter saying they are being held captive in a small but terrifying village. Lupin arrives in the village to rescue them, but Jigen and Goemon are acting oddly.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679289</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16021" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花吹雪・謎の五人衆 (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Falling Cherry Blossoms - The Mysterious Gang of Five (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanafubuki Nazo no Goninshuu (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang have stolen the “36 Views of Mt. Fuji,” a famous series of 46 woodblock prints, from the exhibition hall. However, a gang calling itself the Shiranami Five challenges Lupin head-on by stealing one of the prints from him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679275</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16022" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">射殺命令!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shooting Orders!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shasatsu Meirei!</title>
<summary>Here comes Beauty, the assassin hired by ICPO Headquarters to knock off Lupin! Overwhelmed by Beauty’s powerful DumDum bullets, Lupin narrowly escapes with his life thanks to Jigen’s quick thinking.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679297</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16023" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンの大西遊記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Big Saiyuuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin no Daisaiyuuki</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang head to the isolated country of Kimasan, after hearing the country possesses mountains of treasure. They sneak across the border but are quickly captured by Kinkaku and Ginkaku, the giants who rule the country.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679299</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16024" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドロボウ交響曲を鳴らせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Play the Thieves` Symphony</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorobou Koukyoukyoku o Narase</title>
<summary>The World Crime Prevention Devices Association has developed the “killer safe” that sent many safe crackers to their graves. Their ultimate product is the atomic safe, located 100 meters underground, which is said to detect sounds and detonate, blowing thieves to smithereens. Not only that, the bomb goes off when the weight of the elevator going up is heavier than when it went down. But Lupin takes the challenge to steal what it guards, regardless. The end result is ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685637</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16025" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐はルパンにまかせろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leave Revenge to Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu wa Lupin ni Makasero</title>
<summary>Though Joe Spade was once a formidable hitman of renown and  Jigen`s sharpshooter coach, he now comes to beg for Jigen`s help; he had gotten old, flubbed a hit contract, and is now on the run. Jigen decides to help his old mentor and heads to Mareseilles with Lupin, but Lupin has a change of heart because he hates killers. So Jigen heads to Jigen`s ramshakle shack all by himself ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685627</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16026" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エマニエルは天使のささやき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emmanuelle Is an Angel`s Whisper</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La jeunesse éternelle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Emmanuelle wa Tenshi no Sasayaki</title>
<summary>Fujiko discovers that the Holy Scripture for Immortality is hidden within the jungles of Thailand. However, Emmanuelle Poirot, a cold-hearted beauty, is after them too. Lupin, love-struck and being manipulated by Emmanuelle, goes to the temple where the Holy Scripture is hidden and takes on the challenge of stealing it. Stuck between two beauties, whom will Lupin get the treasure for?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679269</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16027" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪い奴ほど大悪党</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bad Guys Are Truly Big Villians</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warui Yatsu Hodo Daiakutou</title>
<summary>Lupin crashes crime boss Markane`s masquerade party, but the party was just a ruse to entrap Lupin. Lupin gets hung by rope in the dark and is made the target of Markane`s murder game in ten rounds, of which players have to hit the target. As more players participate, the richer Markane gets.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685639</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16028" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットの瞳にダイヤが光る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diamonds Gleam in a Robot`s Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot no Hitomi ni Dia ga Hikaru</title>
<summary>Fujiko calls Lupin from Professor Pot’s lab, but since Lupin is half-asleep, Jigen takes the call instead. Fujiko claims Professor Pot has accidentally invented a robot that manufactures diamonds, but Jigen doesn’t believe a word she says and hangs up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679321</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16029" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">国境は別れの顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Border Is the Face of Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokkyou wa Wakare no Kao</title>
<summary>Lupin and Jigen are after the Aurora Droplet, a diamond adorning a prima ballerina’s tiara. During the heist, Jigen is wounded and in a twist of fate, is saved by Monica, the prima ballerina.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679281</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16030" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊船より愛をこめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From the Ghost Ship with Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuureisen yori Ai o Komete</title>
<summary>Lupin steals a statue called the Stone Child from the Metropolitan Art Museum; he and Fujita make their getaway in a Cessna, but they crash at the Bermuda Triangle. They encounter a ghost ship at this grave of many ships and planes. Lupin investigates the ghost ship while Fujita waits, not knowing it was a trap …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685649</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16031" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父っつあんのいない日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day the Old Man Died</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottsuan no Inai Hi</title>
<summary>Lupin and Jigen are surrounded, as usual, as they are trying to escape after a jewelry theft. But somebody shoots at Zenigata and hits him dead on. Lupin learns of the even the next morning in the papers, and Fujiko and Goemon get implicated. However, there`s a conspiracy behind it all …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685655</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16032" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン一世の秘宝を探せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find the Treasure of Lupin I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Issei no Hihou o Sagase</title>
<summary>Lupin the Third learns that his grandfather Arsene Lupin`s secret treasures are buried in his grave. Lupin learns of its location with Fujiko`s microfilm. He learns that the treasures are items that have been acquired by the governments of the U.S., U.K., and the Soviet Union; those three nations hire a fierce assassin, but Lupin tries to thwart their plan; Zenigata enters the scene, and …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685653</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16033" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">半七刑事十年目の約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Detective Hanshichi`s Ten-Year Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanshichi Keiji Juunenme no Yakusoku</title>
<summary>The aging Inspector Hanshichi Mikawa, who failed to capture Lupin 10 years ago, is viewed as a nuisance by his peers at the downtown police station. Lupin has announced he’ll be stealing the golden Kannon statuette.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679273</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラシック泥棒と九官鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Classic Thieves and Mynah Birds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Classic Dorobou to Kyuukanchou</title>
<summary>Lupin, Jigen and Goemon have turned themselves in to the FBI, but it’s all part of the plan. Their real goal is to break out old man Clyde Barlow, who was once known as a genius bank robber, to get his help with their heist of the National Super Bank.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679305</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16035" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名画強奪ウルトラ作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Famous Painting Theft Ultra Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiga Goudatsu Ultra Sakusen</title>
<summary>The prime minister of France has run up a ridiculous tab with Maxim of Paris, and orders the Louvre Museum proprietor to sell a painting to cover his bill. But the proprietor doesn`t want to let it go, and takes the painting out of the museum; it`s a painting that Lupin`s grandfather had stolen from the Louvre back in the day, and it`s just a replica. Pandemonium follows when art connoiseurs and criminals find out what`s going on …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685659</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16036" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マダムと泥棒四重奏[カルテット]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Madame and a Thieves` Quartet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madame to Dorobou Quartet</title>
<summary>Old man Piccolo had taught Lupin the art of thievery 15 years ago. Learning that his widowed wife had all of her belongings impounded by the police, Lupin promises her to get them all back. But the widower thinks her late husband was a musician, and has no idea that he was a thief. How will Lupin manage to get her stuff back without having to reveal his true identity?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685643</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16037" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">万里の長城インベーダー作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Great Wall of China Invader</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Banri no Choujou Invader Sakusen</title>
<summary>Lupin and crew sneak into Peking`s Imperial Palace Museum to steal Emperor Shi`s jade Mahjong set, but winds up getting chased by a gang. A mysterious woman comes to the rescue, who says that she learned Japanese  using an accelerated learning elixir. She says that you can dissolve any book into the elixir, and if ingested, you will have the book memorized. She gives Lupin the elixir as a gift, but the gang is still out there looking for him ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685645</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16038" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">罠には罠を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Trap for a Trap!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wana ni wa Wana o</title>
<summary>Don Kecchi, the wealthiest man in America, is terminally ill and has announced that he`s donating his entire fortune to charity. However, Lupin steals Kecchi`s money and shoots Fujiko right in front of Inspector Zenigata!.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679291</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16039" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不二子に花嫁衣装は似合わない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fujiko Doesn`t Look Good in a Bridal Gown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujiko ni Hanayome Ishou wa Niawanai</title>
<summary>Fujiko decides to marry Huffner for his jewelry collection, disregarding the rumor that Huffner`s brides always die a mysterious death within a few weeks of their wedding. Turns out, he’s also a collector of brides and likes them permanently preserved!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679315</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16040" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シェークスピアを知ってるかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Know Shakespeare?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakespeare o Shitteru kai</title>
<summary>Jigen receives a letter from Sister Angelica and heads to the African country of Borodias. Sister Angelica wants Jigen’s help to rescue Dr. Othello, the leader of the country’s independence movement.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679317</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16041" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花吹雪・謎の五人衆 (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Falling Cherry Blossoms - The Mysterious Gang of Five (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanafubuki Nazo no Goninshuu (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Goemon, siding with the Shiranami Five, challenges Lupin to a one-on-one duel. While Goemon keeps Lupin busy, the Shiranami Five steals the 36 Views, but one of its members, Kikuko Benten, betrays her gang and escapes with the loot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679277</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16042" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空飛ぶ斬鉄剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flying Zantetsuken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soratobu Zantetsuken</title>
<summary>Trouble is all but guaranteed when a crime boss and an arms merchant join hands. The two set their eyes on Goemen’s sword  ,which can split a tank in half! After hiring Fujiko to steal it, they transform the sword into an invincible flying weapon  of war.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679287</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16043" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっつぁんの惚れた女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman the Old Man Fell in Love With</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottsuan no Horeta Onna</title>
<summary>Political fixer Pomade Jaws trusts no one, not even his wife Laura. He`s stored the scandalous secrets of various world leaders inside a voice-activated safe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679303</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16044" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンピューターかルパンか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Will It Be the Computer or Lupin?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Computer ka Lupin ka</title>
<summary>On a wild whim, Inspector Zenigata swipes a throwing coin owned by his great Edo-era ancestor, Heiji Zenigata while he`s viewing the inside of an incredible new safe protected by Professor Hunter`s super computer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679279</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16045" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">インドに自殺の花が咲く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Flower of Suicide Blooms in India</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Indo ni Jisatsu no Hana ga Saku</title>
<summary>Bandit leader Basara is determined to sniff out the location of the diamonds Lupin has hidden somewhere in India. Armed with his sinister invention, the Suicide Ray Gun, he tries to make Lupin talk, even trying his luck with a fake Fujiko.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679285</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16046" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマスは女神の手に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Is in the Hands of the Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas wa Megami no Te ni</title>
<summary>Margaret Tiffany, the owner of Tiffany’s and a TV anchor, hires Lupin and his gang to rob her jewelry store on live TV. Initially, Lupin refuses, but ends up having to go through with it thanks to Fujiko’s wild spending habits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679293</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16047" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不二子! 男はつらいぜ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fujiko! Men Are Tough</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujiko! Otoko wa Tsurai ze</title>
<summary>Lupin is after the Golden Bell, symbol of the monarchy of Beltenberg and precious tourist attraction. However, the bell that sparkles in the belfry is just a brass replica. Though Fujiko insists that the bell made of gold doesn`t exist, Lupin believes to the contrary. Meanwhile, Lupin gets news of Fujiko`s engagement to prince Claude of Beltenberg, whom she had met in Paris.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685621</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16048" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スケートボード殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Skateboard Murder Mystery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Skateboard Satsujin Jiken</title>
<summary>Ellery Queen, the owner of the legendary sapphire called “The Eye of Solomon,” is also the owner of a football team. Lupin, coming for the sapphire as announced, discovers Queen on the brink of death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679309</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16049" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の差し入れはカップラーメン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Meal Is Cup Ramen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Sashiire wa Cup Ramen</title>
<summary>Silver, who once worked with Lupin on a train robbery, stole the money himself, hid it somewhere, and promptly got himself thrown into prison on a rinky-dink charge. Lupin, having learned that Silver is about to be released, goes to the prison intent on making Silver tell what he did with the loot, only to discover that, while Silver was in prison, a new top-of-the-line prison was built over the site where he hid the money. Now, will the operation to trade an execution for the recovery of the money succeed?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685619</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16050" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンの南極北極大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Big South Pole-North Pole Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin no Nankyoku Hokkyoku Daibouken</title>
<summary>Lupin`s target is the Vatican Crown, located at the North Pole. He devises a plan to thwart pesky Fujiko, which is to relocate penguins at the South Pole to the North Pole; Lupin takes a flight to the South Pole to gather penguins, then heads to the North Pole. But Fujiko learns of his antics and with the help of an underground organization called the 
Red Voyagers League, heads to the North Pole. Who will claim the prize of the Vatican Crown?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685635</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16051" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンの大西部劇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Big Western</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin no Daiseibugeki</title>
<summary>The Smith Gang hit-man company was once the best in the business, but they`re suffering now from tough competition. Though the company chairman Smith considers running TV ads to revive his business, he can`t think of a good way to do it. Fujiko gets word that he`s willing to shovel out 300 million dollars for a good idea, so they decide to film a Western in which Lupin gets killed ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685625</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16052" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンの敵はルパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Enemy Is Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin no Teki wa Lupin</title>
<summary>A princess of a small Silk Road country has been kidnapped. Lupin and his gang are persuaded to rescue Princess Yasmin in exchange for a stomach full of holy curry meant for the gods. However, the kidnapping was a trap to lure Lupin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679295</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16053" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂気のファントマ・マークIII</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mad Fantoma Mark III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouki no Fantoma Mark III</title>
<summary>Phantoma Mark III, grandson of the mysterious master thief and disguise artist Phantoma, who terrorized Europe during his heyday, is plotting to take over the world. He demands that Lupin deliver the world’s largest ruby in exchange for Fujiko, whom he is holding captive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679271</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16054" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">花も嵐も泥棒レース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flowers and Storms and a Thieves` Race</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana mo Arashi mo Dorobou Race</title>
<summary>The 3rd Thieves Olympic is about to be held in Japan, and Lupin and Jigen are in it to win it! After winning the first and second Thieves Olympic, if they also win this year’s getaway race, they’ll become the first-ever Triple-Crown winners!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679311</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16055" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン対スーパーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Vs. Superman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Tai Superman</title>
<summary>Look who is flying above New York; it`s Superman! All he does is fly around, but the town is in a panic because of his performance. In the meantime a lot of banks get robbed. The police won`t take it lying down, and Inspector Mclead is placed in charge of the investigation. But there is something even more sinister to this state of affairs …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685647</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16056" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">荒野に散ったコンバット・マグナム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Combat Magnum Scattered in the Wasteland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouya ni Chitta Combat Magnum</title>
<summary>The prime minister of the Duchy of Blanco has a one-of-a-kind gold coin of Hannibal hidden in his chest; well, Lupin and crew are after it. Amidst their scheming, Jigen is challenge to a duel with a man named Stoneman. Jigen had forgotten all about the duel that Stoneman had demanded, five years ago; he`d been on the run from it since …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685657</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16057" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星占いでルパンを逮捕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrest Lupin with Horoscopes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshiuranai de Lupin o Taiho</title>
<summary>The ICPO tries a different approach to capturing Lupin: Astrology. It enlists the help of Marianne, a clairvoyant who can read Lupin’s actions using astrological predictions and her crystal ball.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679319</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16058" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖のカメレオン人間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Terrifying Chameleon Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Chameleon Ningen</title>
<summary>The world’s largest diamond has been discovered in South Africa and Lupin has his eyes on the prize. But as it turns out, stealing it is the easy part!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679313</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16059" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とっつあん人質救出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Old Man Hostage Rescue Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottsuan Hitojichi Kyuushutsu Sakusen</title>
<summary>Zenigata is taken hostage from ICPO headquarters. The terrorists demand to swap him with their boss Napoleon XI, but ICPO refuses. Since Zenigata is no further use to them, the terrirosts are bound to kill him; Lupin must now come to his rescue, but do it delicately so as to not hurt Zenigata`s pride. Thus begins Lupin`s Zenigata-rescue caper ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685623</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16060" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンのお料理天国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Gourmet Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin no Oryouri Tengoku</title>
<summary>Foodie and gourmet aficianado Baron Gourmel says he wants to eat Lupin`s brain. His crew of cooks of course can`t come up with the main ingredient, so they try passing off monkey brain as Lupin`s, which makes really ticks him off. He claims he`d offer his own 70-million dollar jewelry collection to anyone who could capture Lupin. Fujiko hears of it and informs Lupin right away. Meanwhile, the chefs begin planning on cooking Lupin ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685651</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16061" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ICPO(秘)指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ICPO Secret Directive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ICPO Maruhi Shirei</title>
<summary>ICPO Bureau Chief Jasmine is an able commissioner. She uses the governor to spur Zenigata into action, as she has a secret plan to arrest Lupin. But Jasmine`s plan is to make this mission her very last at ICPO so she could get married. Who is Jasmine marrying? Will her plan to arrest Lupin succeed?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685629</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16062" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カジノ島・逆転また逆転</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Casino Island - Inversions and More Inversions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Casino-tou - Gyakuten Mata Gyakuten</title>
<summary>Casino Paradise is an artificial island owned and operated by Domino, a casino tycoon. Domino decides to run for President and brags that with $500 million to spend, the only way he can lose is if Lupin steals his campaign funds!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679301</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16063" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン葬送曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lupin Funeral March</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Sousoukyoku</title>
<summary>Fujiko has invited Lupin and company to a classical concert conducted by Kyoransky from the International Philharmonic. After they get a good look at Kyoransky’s baton, studded with a  a diamond worth at least 200 million yen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679323</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16064" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マダムXの不思議な世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious World of Madame X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madame X no Fushigi na Sekai</title>
<summary>After shaking off Inspector Zenigata’s pursuit, Lupin is stopped by a monstrously huge Fujiko on his way home! The giant Fujiko turns out to be an illusion created by Madame X. Lupin learns Madame X’s hobby is collecting famous people.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679283</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16065" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン対新選組</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Vs. the Shinsen Group</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Tai Shinsengumi</title>
<summary>Isamu Kondo III, grandson of the leader of the Shinsengumi, hires Lupin and his gang to recover a golden cannon sunk by the Shogunate forces in the Tsugaru Strait. After much effort, the valuable golden cannon is finally recovered from the deep ocean.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>679307</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16066" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の夜光仮面現わる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Nightlight Mask Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Yakou Kamen Arawaru</title>
<summary>Nightlight Mask murdered the Duke of Le Mond and stole his diamonds. ICPO is having trouble solving the case, so they induct mystery author Conan Dorill as a special inspector. Dorill deduces that the true identity of Nightlight Mask is Lupin. Learning that Count Johannes is his next target, he and Zenigata lie in wait at the Johannes Mansion, where a costume ball is taking place ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685631</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16067" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔がルパンを招くとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the Devil Beckons to Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma ga Lupin o Maneku Toki</title>
<summary>On a night of thunder and rain, a man gives Lupin a doll. That very night Lupin has a nightmare of being manipulated by a man named Mephistopheles. The next day there is a news report that a diamond called the Phoenix`s Tear had been stolen. Though Lupin had been caught on security camera, he has no recollection of having done the deed. What is going on?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685633</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">131</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人五右ヱ門斬鉄剣の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Goemons - The Mystery of Zantetsuken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari Goemon Zantetsuken no Nazo</title>
<summary>Three incidents of bank robbery using an iron-cutter sword have happened; a total of 1.3 billion yen was stolen. But Lupin and group know they were Goemon`s doing, because the culprit had ruthlessly killed a security guard. Meanwhile, a man calling himself Goemon sends Lupin a challenge, but Goemon wants to settle the score by himself. He heads to the bank to meet his foe, not knowing it`s a trap …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685721</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16108" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しみの斬鉄剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zantetsuken`s Lament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Zantetsuken</title>
<summary>Lupin and crew go to a hot springs for rest and relaxation. Lupin drinks sake, Jigen enjoys classical music and bourbon, while Goemon trains at the cliffs. A girl manifests to Goemon; she`s a pure and simple sort, who captures Goemon`s heart. However, the girl is seeking the secret of the super sword, for the sake of her swordsmith grandfather …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685675</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">127</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">直撃! デッドボール作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Direct Hit! Operation Dead Ball</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chokugeki! Dead Ball Sakusen</title>
<summary>Boss Largo wants Lupin dead; Lupin had just stolen a bundle of the boss`s casino profits. But no run of the mill hitman would suffice to wack Lupin. But Largo sees that Lupin is suffering from a toothache, and gets an idea after seeing a sports newspaper. He heads to a baseball stadium, slips a hypnotic drug to a major league baseball player to make him do the boss`s bidding …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685713</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16110" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">114</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷画 最初の晩餐の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Mystery Painting, "The First Supper"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiga: Saisho no Bansan no Himitsu</title>
<summary>The painting “The First Supper” hides clues to the hiding place of an heirloom that Christ receive from Virgin Mary, 2,000 years ago. This painting has been kept by the clan of Judah for generations, and a woman named Nova, one of the descendants, knows that the painting is hidden at a fortress called Demon Rock. Nova gives Zenigata X-ray eyedrops invented by professor Nestle, hoping to he could find and catch Lupin at Demon Rock …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685687</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16111" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">147</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白夜に消えた人魚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mermaid That Disappeared in the Midnight Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byakuya ni Kieta Ningyo</title>
<summary>Fujiko is the model for Norway`s famous sculptor Vingel`s crystal mermaid statue; she believed when he said he would give it to her the day it was finished, but Vingel gets greedy and sells it to the mayor of the city of Bergen instead. Fujiko asks Lupin to get the statue for her, which is set to become a tourist attraction.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685753</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16112" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もっとも危険な黄金ベッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Most Dangerous Golden Bed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motto mo Kiken na Ougon Bed</title>
<summary>Pestered by Fujiko, Lupin has to steal a golden bed that was originally made by Louis XIV for Josephine. He makes a plan with Jigen and Goemon, but the owner of the bed, Morgan, is a formidable opponent who has WWII military experience. Will Lupin succeed in stealing the bed from under Morgan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685667</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">117</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チューインガム変装作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chewing-Gum Disguise Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chewing Gum Hensou Sakusen</title>
<summary>As usual, Lupin is tossed to and fro and Fujiko. But a man named Buckingham comes to him and sells him “disguise chewing gum” for 50,000 dollars. This is how it works: you chew it, blow a bubble till it pops, then you will become disguised. While they celebrate the closing of their deal at a nightclub, Lupin falls for a dancer called Amore ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685693</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16114" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">153</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神様のくれた札束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bills That Came from God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamisama no Kureta Satsutaba</title>
<summary>It`s said that immense sums of money confiscated from organized crime get transported to a Swiss bank by ICPO, once a year. Naturally Lupin wants a piece of that action, so he steals the armed security vehicle along with Zenigata in it. But Fujiko betrays him, so he has to ride a horse driven carriage instead. Meanwhile Zenigata lies in wait at the border. Now what will Lupin do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685765</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16115" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">128</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">老婆とルパンの泥棒合戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Old Woman and Lupin Thievery Contest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rouba to Lupin no Dorobougassen</title>
<summary>Lupin reads the morning paper, which says that Lupin stole a 100-karat diamond that was being used in a musical. He knows he didn`t do it, so he asks Fujiko and others, but they too have no idea what it`s all about. Lupin sneaks into the theater to find the truth out for himself. There he sees and elderly woman skillfully cracking a safe …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685715</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16116" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">118</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">南十字星がダイヤに見えた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Southern Cross Looked Like Diamonds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minami Juujisei ga Dia ni Mieta</title>
<summary>The island of Rabaul has many remains of Japanese casualties of the Pacific War. It`s said that Captain Cook`s secret treasure is hidden there, worth 1-billion pounds. Of course Lupin and friends go to get it in a helicopter, but the helicopter gets shot down by a Zero plane. Who`s flying the plane that shot them down?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685695</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16117" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">結婚指輪は呪いの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Wedding Ring Is an Accursed Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kekkon Yubiwa wa Noroi no Wana</title>
<summary>Louis XIV and Marie Antoinette`s Hope Diamond has brought much misfortune on its possessors. The diamond is now safeguarded by a maximum security device. Fujiko provokes Lupin to steal that diamond, but as soon as he enters the Smithsonian Museum to steal, he too encounters misfortune …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685673</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16118" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">126</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄へルパンを道づれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Together with Lupin to Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku e Lupin o Michizure</title>
<summary>Lady Black and Fujiko have a bet. Whoever kills Lupin will get the loser`s entire jewelry collection. Lady Black lures Lupin using Fujiko so she could kill him, but why is she so passionate about wanting him dead? Will Lupin survive her murderous plan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685711</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16119" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">146</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン華麗なる敗北</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Splendid Failure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Kareinaru Haiboku</title>
<summary>Genius prodigy boy Romanoff has ten doctrates from Russia`s Public Academy; blustering that no greater than he exists, he challenges Lupin. Since Fujiko is involved, Lupin cannot back down; what will become of this challenge?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685751</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16120" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン 史上最大の苦戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin`s Toughest Battle Ever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin: Shijou Saidai no Kusen</title>
<summary>Lupin has to battle a hitman called Tiger. Lupin tries to dodge him, but Tiger is one step ahead of him. Lupin keeps trying to escape him but Tiger is relentless; he has a way of disappearing and appearing at will. However, there was a trick to the whole thing …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685677</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">作戦名は忠臣蔵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Name of the Operation Is Chuushingura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusenmei wa Chuushingura</title>
<summary>Chief Commissioner of Police Asano slugs the prime minister and gets fired; his duty had been to capture Lupin, but since he had failed, he now joins forces with Zenigata for the task. Meanwhile Lupin goes to see a Kabuki theatrical play, but he isn`t impressed. But Lupin is accosted by an elderly man there, who wants him to steal the treasures of his own household …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685685</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16122" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">135</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">毒薬と魔術とルパン三世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Poison and Magic and Lupin III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokuyaku to Majutsu to Lupin Sansei</title>
<summary>Lupin finds out about the jewel “Poison Trio” of the Borges family and decides to steal it after Fujiko goads him. Galdan, the nephew of Lucricia greets Lupin, and tells him that elderly Lucricia had been arrested and must be broken out of jail. But what is he really after?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685729</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16123" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベルサイユは愛に燃えた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Versailles Burned with Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Versailles wa Ai ni Moeta</title>
<summary>Lupin recieves a letter about Marie Antoinette`s jeweled crown, and sneaks into the palace of Versailles. A young man called Oscar appears, the sender of the letter. Since Zenigata and others have gotten involved, the situation gets taken to Normandy; Zenigata, Goemaon, and Lupin wait there, knowing nothing of the fact that Oscar had received orders to steal the jeweled crown from Lupin …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685661</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16124" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンはシャネルがお好き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Is Fond of Chanel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin wa Chanel ga Osuki</title>
<summary>Lupin was told by Fujiko to steal a pistol of the Wilhem family worth 500 million pounds, but Jigen and Goemon are not interested in the caper. Meanwhile, a man named Jim Benkei, a giant of a man who`s stirred troubled in London, steals Jigen`s favorite Magnum ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685663</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16125" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">137</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華麗なるチームプレイ作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magnificent Team-Play Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kareinaru Team Play Sakusen</title>
<summary>Lupin scopes a jewelry museum where the billion-dollar gem Cleopatra`s Tear is displayed. But Lupin can`t get to it because the display case is secured by high-voltage electricity. Not only that, Zenigata has him surrounded. Will Lupin escape, and get Cleopatra`s Tear?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685733</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16126" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">133</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱いお宝に手を出すな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keep Your Hands Off the Hot Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsui Otakara ni Te o Dasuna</title>
<summary>Lupin learns that a treasure trove lies in a volcano on Cleo Island, but it can only be reached when the mountain isn`t spewing molten lava! He tries to convince Jigen and Goemon to join him but they`re not interested, because the island native Claudia had talked them into obstructing Lupin …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685725</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16127" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">149</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベールをはいだメッカの秘宝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Treasure of Mecca Wore a Veil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Veil o Haida Mecca no Hihou</title>
<summary>Following Fujiko`s information, Lupin heads to Mecca to steal Mohammed`s treasure. But first he is confronted by Patra Lawrence, the grandaughter of the Lawrence of Arabia, who is the chief of Mecca`s special police headquarters; how will Lupin steal the treasure now?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685757</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16128" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">145</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の翼アルバトロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wings of Death - Albatross</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Tsubasa Albatross</title>
<summary>Fujiko joins Lupin and friends who are camping and cooking Sukiyaki; people are hunting Fujiko, and gunfire is exchanged. Fujiko gets captured and Lupin`s Sukiyaki meal gets ruined, but he finds an atomic bomb`s detonator plug inside of the Sukiyaki bowl.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685749</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16129" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">122</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">珍発見 ナポレオンの財宝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rare Find: Napoleon`s Fortune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinhakken: Napoleon no Zaihou</title>
<summary>Zenigata acquires a pie-throwing gun, and is ordered to capture Lupin. Meanwhile Lupin and Fujiko are discussing Napoleon`s treasures. It`s said that the key to solving the mystery of their whereabouts lies in a scarf made by Napoleon`s assistant …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685703</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16130" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">144</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不二子危機一髪救出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fujiko`s Close Call Rescue Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujiko Kikiippatsu Kyuushutsu Sakusen</title>
<summary>Thief brothers Nanja-Monja have been in the business since the days of Arsene Lupin; they decide to induct Lupin as a tourist attraction for the Republic of Karchina. But first they abduct Fujiko, then gather a huge crowd in a stadium with a safe set up in the midst; Fujiko is locked inside it, waiting for Lupin to come get her out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685747</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16131" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">138</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポンペイの秘宝と毒蛇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Treasure of Pompeii and Venomous Snakes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pompeii no Hihou to Dokuhebi</title>
<summary>No thief has ever succeeded in stealing the secret gem of Pompeii`s nunnery; it`s guarded by venomous snakes. Even Arsene Lupin gave up on it, since he hates snakes. But Lupin takes on the challenge. Will Lupin succeed? And what kind of secret gem is it?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685735</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16132" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">132</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊山ヒマラヤの泥棒教団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Himalayan Holy Mountain Thieves` Cult</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reizan Himalaya no Dorobou Kyoudan</title>
<summary>Lupin`s stash of Napoleon`s cash got stolen, but Lupin catches the culprit and tries to make him confess. But Lupin learns he`s one of the followers of the Fandar cult, and heads to their holy land of Fandara. What kind of religious organization is this Fandar cult? Will Lupin get his stash back?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685723</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16133" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">116</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">108つの鐘は鳴ったか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have the 108 Bells Rung</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">108-tsu no Kane wa Natta ka</title>
<summary>On the last day of the year, Lupin is after is the Golden Treasure Ship at Mount Horai. It`s said that the Seven Lucky Gods confered the treasure, and it`s shown in public only once a year when the New Year`s bell gongs at the belfry of Kohoji Temple. The police department is swamped and hires the mafia as security guards, they even invite a killer called Antonio Wolf, who bears a grudge against Lupin. Can Lupin pull off his last theft of the year?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685691</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16134" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">125</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オイルダラーの大謀略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Oildollar Plot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oildollar no Daibouryaku</title>
<summary>Lupin is blackmailed; Fujiko has been kidnapped, and for ransom he must steal a jeweled crown worth a 100 million dollars. Lupin and friends head to the museum in Iraran where their objective lies, and they discover that it is displayed above a fountain of sulfuric acid. Can Lupin steal the crown to save Fujiko`s life, and what is this so-called Oildollar plot?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685709</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16135" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">142</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グランドレース消えた大本命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Favorite Disappeared at the Grand Race</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Grand Race Kieta Daihonmei</title>
<summary>England`s Lord Weather owns a famous horse named Red Arrow. Weather provokes Lupin with a bet, and dares him to steal Red Arrow away from him. Lupin takes the challenge as it`s a matter of pride, but Jigen wants no part of it because he and Weather are gambling buddies. Will Lupin win the bet?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685743</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16136" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">141</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1980モスクワ黙示録</title>
<title xml:lang="en">1980 Moscow Revelation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1980 Moscow Mokushiroku</title>
<summary>Coaxed by Fujiko, Lupin decides to steal the diamond chandelier at the Kremlin Palace. He disguises himself as Zenigata and infiltrates the palace, but government police soldier Natasha captures him and throws him in the slammer. How will Lupin steal the chandelier now?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685741</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16137" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">124</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1999年ポップコーンの旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">1999: A Popcorn Odyssey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1999-nen Popcorn no Tabi</title>
<summary>Professor Pancho has devoted his life to solving the problem of food supply. He and his wife have conceived of a popcorn machine in the U.S. that can increase the quantity of corn by a million times, but producing the actual mechanical device will cost them a fortune. Lupin decides to help them out and invents a rocket that flies on corn fuel, thinking that maybe he and Fujiko will take a trip to the moon …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685707</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16138" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">130</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン対奇人二面相</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Vs. the Mystery Man With Two Faces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Tai Kijin Nimensou</title>
<summary>The master of surrealism, Monsieur Daré had spent three years working on his masterpiece, but news is out that the great object of art got stolen. Inspector Magrey deduces that the culprit is Lupin, and provokes him through television. But Lupin wants to find out the truth; he disguises himself as Magrey to go visit Daré ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685719</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16139" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">120</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フランケンシュタイン ルパンを襲う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frankenstein Attacks Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Frankenstein: Lupin o Osou</title>
<summary>Lupin and friends searched a month for the pirate Kid`s treasure, but they are thwarted by an underground organization called the Red Ghost. Knowing something is afoot, Lupin sends Fujiko and Goemon to investigate. According Fujiko`s report, they are conversing with dead using psychic arts to uncover the whereabouts of the treasure. Meanwhile, Goemon gets ambushed …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685699</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16140" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">136</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴールドバタフライの復讐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge of the Gold Butterfly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gold Butterfly no Fukushuu</title>
<summary>Lupin goes on a safe-cracking rampage and rakes in 10 million francs. He needs the money to purchase the world`s only rare Gold Butterfly at an auction. But Lupin drops the 10 million francs while on the run ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685731</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16141" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五右ヱ門危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goemon`s Close Call</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goemon Kikiippatsu</title>
<summary>Wolf and Rose are a cool hitmen duo with the ambition of rising to the top of the hitman business by killing Lupin. They capture Goemon and torture him to confess about Lupin`s weaknesses. Lupin learns that Goemon is in danger, thwarts Zenigata`s trap to go save Goemon, only to come face to face with the muzzle of Wolf`s gun …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685683</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16142" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼は天使を見た</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wolf Saw an Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami wa Tenshi o Mita</title>
<summary>Lupin is after the various jewels at the World Fair in Los Angeles. Goemon says he`s gotten soft so he decides not to participate in the plan this time. But Lupin learns from Fujiko that a man named Harry Satler is also after the jewels, so he decides to go see who this guy is. But lo and behold, the man he meets is a wizened old man …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685665</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16143" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪奇鬼首島に女が消えた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Horror - A Woman Disappeared on Devil`s Head Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiki Onikubitou ni Onna ga Kieta</title>
<summary>The Heike Clan and Minamoto Clan once battled on Devil`s Head Island at the inland sea of Seto; Fujiko and Lupin go there to find out about the details behind the legend of the battle, which has it that the ghosts of the dead warriors of the Heike Clan haunt the island`s forest. But just as in the legend, Fujiko gets abducted in the forest ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685669</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16144" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">君はネコ ぼくはカツオ節</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re a Cat, I`m a Dried Tuna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi wa Neko Boku wa Katsuobushi</title>
<summary>Vivian dreams of becoming a star some day, but her auditions are a bust. She thinks of using Lupin to become famous; she makes Lupin engage in thievery, and informs reporters to be at the site to catch him in the act. But what he`s supposed to steal is a cat that feeds on pencil shavings;  humiliated by the event, Lupin decides to get back at Vivian …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685671</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16145" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">140</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼は走れ豚は転がれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf, Run, Pig, Fall Down</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami wa Hashire Buta wa Korogare</title>
<summary>Famous gourmand and field mice scientist Salmon Whitney is also known as being the chairman of a Canadian diamond mining operation. Lupin is after his diamonds, which will go on auction in Paris. However, somebody has already stolen them before Lupin could get to them. Who stole them? Will Lupin get the diamonds?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685739</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16146" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">129</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元に男心の優しさを見た</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Jigen, I Saw the Gentleness of a Man`s Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen ni Otokogokoro no Yasashisa o Mita</title>
<summary>The nation of Janaica is troubled with coup d`etats and revolutions, but Lupin, discovering that the president`s mansion houses the missing painting “Nude Venus,” decides to go scope the joint with Jigen. Jigen goes to Janaica first, and is visited by a woman who is on the run from government police …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685717</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16147" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激写 これが不二子だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Shot: This Is Fujiko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekisha: Kore ga Fujiko Da</title>
<summary>Lupin and friends go to have fun at the horse race track, but winning isn`t as easy as stealing. Lupin notices two people who are winning big money hand over fist, and gets suspicious, because they take photos of the finish line when no horses are running, and strange stuff like that. Meanwhile, Zenigata is hired to find a missing camera …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685679</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16148" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">134</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン逮捕頂上作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Climactic Lupin Arrest Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Taihou Choujou Sakusen</title>
<summary>Fujiko informs Lupin that fine quality diamonds from South Africa are stored in a safe of a global syndicate and importer of diamonds. Lupin makes his way as a worker in the boiler room, and easily steals his loot of diamonds from the poorly guarded safe. He flies back to Fujiko, not knowing it was all Zenigata`s trap to catch him …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685727</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16149" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">143</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイアミ銀行襲撃記念日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miami Bank Raid Anniversary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miami Ginkou Shuugeki Kinenbi</title>
<summary>Miami Bank is on the verge of bankruptcy after its last customers closed their accounts. The bank manager Garlic devises a plan to revive the bank, and drums up news that his bank had been raided by Lupin; he also asks Lupin to really do it. Because Garlic is so pesky about it, Lupin caves in and agrees. What will happen?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685745</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16150" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">115</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モナリザは二度微笑う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mona Lisa Smiles Twice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mona Lisa wa Nido Warau</title>
<summary>The Mona Lisa never leaves the Louvre Museum. Hitler and Arsene Lupin tried unsuccessfully to steal her. But Mona Lisa gets sent to Arabia, with Zenigata in charge of security. Lupin wants her for his collection, however, and fireworks ignite between those two. But the story has a surprising twist …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685689</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16151" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">152</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元と帽子と拳銃と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jigen and a Hat and a Pistol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen to Boushi to Kenjuu to</title>
<summary>A month ago, president Gappolini of one of the world`s top five trading company, had died. Gappolini bequeathed a will saying that the heir to the company presidency will be the world`s finest sharpshooter. This really angers vice-president Don Hagero, so he hires expert marksman Minnesota Fats to kill off all sharpshooters in the world. And finally, only Jigen was left …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685763</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16152" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">119</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンを殺したルパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin, Who Killed Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin o Koroshita Lupin</title>
<summary>A crew of four: Lupin, Jigen, Zenigata, and Fujiko break into the Bank of Stockholm. But Fujiko deceives them and tries to take the money all for herself. Lupin goes after her but she gets injured in an avalanche. As Fujiko is about to die at the hospital, she confesses to Lupin about the location of her most precious treasure …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685697</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16153" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">148</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ターゲットは555M</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Target Is 555 Meters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Target wa 555M</title>
<summary>Lupin tries to steal a bunch of diamonds from a diamond auction. But the auction auditorium is at the Marine Tower above a skyscraper, and there is only one transparent elevator to get there; if the elevator isn`t used, the invader will get zapped with high-voltage electricity. What kind of plan will Lupin devise?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685755</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16154" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">150</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピアノ交響曲「動物園」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Piano Symphony "Zoo"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Piano Koukyoukyoku "Doubutsuen"</title>
<summary>As usual, Fujiko instigates Lupin and friends to go steal; this time their target is the Jovich Piano installed in a music hall built around it. There is no door large enough in the hall to carry the piano out. How will Lupin and crew steal the piano?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685759</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16155" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">151</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパン逮捕ハイウェイ作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Arrest Lupin Highway Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin Taiho Highway Sakusen</title>
<summary>Lupin is after the shipment of raw diamonds that arrived at a harbor in Nice; he sneaks into the storage in the middle of the night but Zenigata was on to him, and has him surrounded. Lupin escapes with the help of Jigen and Goemon, but Fujiko gets captured. Now Lupin has to rescue Fujiko and steal the diamonds, but in the meantime Zenigata has a plan to catch him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685761</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16156" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">インベーダー金庫は開いたか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is the Invader Safe Open?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Invader Kinko wa Hiraita ka?</title>
<summary>Catherine rescues Lupin and Jigen, who are pursued by Zenigata as usual. She`s an old acquaintance of Jigen`s, and provokes Jigen to steal a 140-karat diamond from her own mansion. But Jigen is insulted by her condescending ways, even as she gives him the blueprint of her mansion. However, there has to be a reason why she wants her own home robbed …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685681</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16157" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">139</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンのすべてを盗め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steal Everything of Lupin`s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin no Subete o Nusume</title>
<summary>Though the tycoon Steel had replaced all his bodily organs with artificial organs to live, he`s told that he only has a week to live. There is only one way he could prolong his life, which is to receive Dr. Changer`s brain transplant operation. After much computer analysis, results show that Lupin`s brain will be his best choice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685737</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16158" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">155</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば愛しきルパンよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell My Beloved Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Itoshiki Lupin yo</title>
<summary>Robot soldier Lamda flies above the sky of Tokyo, raids a jewelry store. Its creator, professor Oyamada`s daughter Maki and Lupin say that it was just a show to demonstrate the inhumanity of robots. But Zenigata knows that there`s more to the story, and embarks on an independent investigation. He discovers Lupin`s hideout, and …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685769</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16159" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">121</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレの爺さんが残した宝物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Treasure My Grandfather Left Behind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Jii-san ga Nokoshita Takaramono</title>
<summary>Lupin finds a piece of paper in a silk hat, an heirloom of Arsene Lupin. It`s information regarding an opal statue of Venus, and since Lupin figures its ownership is his birthright, he heads to Gregoire`s castle. But will they let Lupin have the statue that easily?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685701</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16160" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">154</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘクサゴンの大いなる遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hexagon`s Great Legacy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hexagon no Ooinaru Isan</title>
<summary>The city of Grand Hexagon lies at the border of France and Spain; just like its name, the city is designed with six sides. But at the center of the city is Raika Bank storing fifty tons of gold bullion; an alarm will go off if even one bullion is missing. The bank president, however, has another identity ...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685767</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="16161" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">123</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泥棒はパリで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paris Is for Thieves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorobou wa Paris de</title>
<summary>The young girl Francoise lives near Lupin; she watches Lupin and Fujiko talking, and falls for him. But her father scolds her and tells her to stay away from thieves, but Francoise devises a plan to approach Lupin anyway …
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685705</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="31253" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1977-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31254" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1977-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35760" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35761" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37246" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37247" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182657" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1979-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182658" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1979-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217700" update="2019-05-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin III`s Greatest Capers</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
