<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1485" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>1984-03-03</startdate>
<enddate>1985-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lupin Sansei: Part III</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ルパン三世 PART3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pink jacket</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin III Part III</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin S3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin III TV 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin III Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">lupins3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lupin the 3rd: Series 3</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Giacca rosa</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Люпен Трети - част трета</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">鲁邦三世 PartIII</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">lupin3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ルパン三世PARTIII</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lupin the Third: Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Lupin III - Terza serie</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">鲁邦三世 PartⅢ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10882" type="Sequel">Lupin Sansei (2015)</anime>
<anime id="1484" type="Prequel">Lupin Sansei (1977)</anime>
<anime id="705" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Harimao no Zaihou o Oe!!</anime>
<anime id="810" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Twilight Gemini no Himitsu</anime>
<anime id="815" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Moeyo Zantetsuken</anime>
<anime id="976" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Walther P38 - In Gedenken an die Walther P38</anime>
<anime id="977" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Fuuma Ichizoku no Inbou</anime>
<anime id="986" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Lupin Ansatsu Shirei</anime>
<anime id="987" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Russia yori Ai o Komete</anime>
<anime id="989" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Babylon no Ougon Densetsu</anime>
<anime id="1024" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Bye Bye Liberty - Kiki Ippatsu!</anime>
<anime id="1421" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Ai no da capo - Fujiko`s Unlucky Days</anime>
<anime id="1941" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Alcatraz Connection</anime>
<anime id="2014" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Hemingway Paper no Nazo</anime>
<anime id="2136" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: 1$ Money Wars</anime>
<anime id="703" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Dead or Alive</anime>
<anime id="2138" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Otakara Henkyaku Daisakusen!!</anime>
<anime id="2139" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Honoo no Kioku - Tokyo Crisis</anime>
<anime id="2405" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Nusumareta Lupin</anime>
<anime id="3420" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Tenshi no Tactics - Yume no Kakera wa Koroshi no Kaori</anime>
<anime id="4634" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Seven Days` Rhapsody</anime>
<anime id="5367" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Kiri no Elusive</anime>
<anime id="5698" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Green vs Red</anime>
<anime id="6065" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Sweet Lost Night - Mahou no Lamp wa Akumu no Yokan</anime>
<anime id="7288" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: The Last Job</anime>
<anime id="8713" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Chi no Kokuin - Eien no Mermaid</anime>
<anime id="9458" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Touhou Kenbunroku - Another Page</anime>
<anime id="9937" type="Side Story">Lupin Ikka Seizoroi</anime>
<anime id="10021" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Princess of the Breeze - Kakusareta Kuuchuu Toshi</anime>
<anime id="2137" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Napoleon no Jisho o Ubae</anime>
<anime id="704" type="Side Story">Lupin Sansei: Kutabare! Nostradamus</anime>
<anime id="6432" type="Other">Lupin Sansei vs Meitantei Conan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/tv/data/t_rupin_part3.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3480" type="Series Composition">Iioka Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="1267" type="Original Work">Monkey Punch</name>
<name id="4479" type="Music">Oono Yuuji</name>
<name id="6858" type="Character Design">Aoki Yuuzou</name>
<name id="3478" type="Work">Tokyo Movie Shinsha</name>
<name id="829" type="Work">Yomiuri TV</name>
</creators>
<description>The never-ending adventures of http://anidb.net/ch7622 [Lupin Sansei] continues, as once again he travels the world pulling off any heist he can think of, while being assisted by the cool gunslinger http://anidb.net/ch7976 [Jigen Daisuke], the stoic swordsman http://anidb.net/ch8474 [Ishikawa Goemon], and from time-to-time by the beautiful femme fatale http://anidb.net/ch8458 [Mine Fujiko], when she isn`t backstabbing him in order to get money and treasures for herself. But as always, Lupin and his gang still have http://anidb.net/ch8460 [Inspector Zenigata] persuing them, who has vowed to never stop chasing Lupin in order to have him arrested.
— written by Mortsyn</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="258">6.22</permanent>
<temporary count="263">6.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>153690.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>887</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1426</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4190</identifier>
<identifier>mcpabd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=331</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/tv/data/t_rupin_part3.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/english/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=171</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Lupin_III_Part_III_episodes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ルパン三世_PartIII</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3858</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1467</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2394" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>mischievous</name>
<description>The character enjoys causing small irritations, pranks, and misfortune for others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3536" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-05-20">
<name>undercover</name>
<description>Be it the spy, the criminal or the police, someone pretends to be a person they aren`t in order to obtain information or something of value.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7622" type="main character in" update="2012-04-11">
<rating votes="2567">8.66</rating>
<name>Lupin Sansei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The grandson of Arsène Lupin is tall, lanky, impertinent, and very sneaky. His prime qualities are listed as "appearing like a god, disappearing like a demon"; in other words, he appears with a flash and leaves with a whisper. Despite being aided by many gadgets, his main talents lie in plotting and evasion of weapons.
While his grandfather was known as the "Gentleman Thief", Lupin III has no qualms about trying to separate a woman from her modesty. He fancies himself as quite the ladies man, but his advances rarely succeeds. His primary weakness is his overconfidence and lust for Mine Fujiko.</description>
<picture>85729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4652" picture="27089.jpg">Yamada Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7976" type="main character in" update="2019-07-18">
<rating votes="1164">8.59</rating>
<name>Jigen Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jigen is Lupin`s marksman. He can perform a 0.3-second quick-draw and is amazingly accurate. He prefers to conceal his eyes using his hat, as it gives him a more enigmatic appearance; when one or both of his eyes are seen, it is occasionally used to demonstrate surprise. In the second anime series, it is revealed that he uses a notch of the hat to aim. However, due to the nature of the series, no single episode could be considered canon; Jigen has been seen shooting excellently without his hat, even in the very series this is mentioned in, he is seen making shots from angles where his hat`s notch would be useless and even during times he is not wearing his hat at all. He is also proficient in many different firearms, such as machine guns, sniper rifles, and even a PTRS Anti-Tank Rifle.
His preferred weapon, however, is a Smith and Wesson M19 Combat revolver, based on the pistol`s stopping power and its dependability against mechanical misfire. He keeps the weapon in a fabric holster specially constructed in the back beltline of his pants. He also feels quite naked without a gun. Jigen also carries a few rounds of special ammunition such as armor piercing ammunition to use a circumstances dictate. As he frequently travels by air, its not been made clear how he successfully gets his weapon through airline checkpoints.</description>
<picture>236414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37" picture="43092.jpg">Kobayashi Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8458" type="main character in" update="2012-04-11">
<rating votes="1342">6.81</rating>
<name>Mine Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4735" picture="29144.jpg">Masuyama Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8460" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-18">
<rating votes="620">7.62</rating>
<name>Zenigata Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Interpol inspector Zenigata has made it his mission in life to arrest Lupin. He would love to arrest the other members of Lupin`s gang, but Zenigata is really after the mastermind himself. Lupin and Zenigata appear to be the worst of enemies, but they are, in a manner of speaking, friends; something Lupin shows openly (often by greeting Zenigata with mock affection), but it is an idea Zenigata is extremely reluctant to entertain. Similarly, he is often awed by Lupin`s genius, but refuses to show it.</description>
<picture>236411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8474" type="main character in" update="2012-04-11">
<rating votes="634">6.81</rating>
<name>Ishikawa Goemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ishikawa Goemon is a fictional character created by Monkey Punch for his Lupin III series. Goemon is the thirteenth generation of renegade samurai, a descendant of the historical figure Ishikawa Goemon. He is usually quiet and participates in Arsène Lupin III`s exploits less frequently than Daisuke Jigen.
While Goemon might be considered one of Lupin`s friends, it starts off more of a professional relationship than friendship. By the second series, Goemon has developed a true loyalty to Lupin, refusing to give away Lupin`s secrets when tortured in one second series episode, for example. However, he easily gets annoyed by Lupin`s antics, especially Lupin`s infatuation with women in general and Fujiko Mine in particular. He will occasionally oppose Lupin directly when Lupin`s jobs or actions do not agree with Goemon`s morals. He has even promised that the last act he will take with Lupin is delivering his deathblow. However, Goemon doesn`t hesitate to help Lupin in serious situations, and readily assists him any time Lupin works for a just cause. Many theorize that Goemon associates with Lupin out of admiration for his profession, as Goemon`s ancestor was a master thief himself.
Goemon has a much more amicable relationship with Jigen. Goemon sees Jigen as a fellow honorable warrior, while Jigen sees Goemon as a trustworthy "foxhole buddy," and the two are frequently paired together during jobs, and usually help keep Lupin in check.
On the odd occasion and increasingly in recent years, Goemon will ally himself with Fujiko, in spite of his distrust of her. As long as their goal is the same and Fujiko makes no attempts to betray him, the two work well together and usually achieve what they seek.
Goemon has an extreme sense of pride in his abilities, and when he cannot accomplish a task, usually feels extreme shame and remorse afterward. Breaking Zantetsuken, as he did in a battle with Flinch from Mystery of Mamo, is a common cause of shame. He will also show chagrin when he succumbs to his weaknesses, as when a woman ran off with his sword in Tokyo Crisis. On many of these occasions, Goemon will leave to meditate or further train to rid himself of his weak points.
Goemon`s most oft-seen pastime is meditation; during inactive moments, even with potential danger near, he is usually seated on the floor with legs crossed, eyes closed. Like most of the Lupin gang he is a trained driver and pilot, although he prefers being a passenger rather than taking the driver seat.
Goemon shows allegiance to Japanese culture as strictly as his travelling and unique lifestyle can allow. He dresses in an hakama and wears fundoshi instead of underwear. His preferred food is Japanese cuisine. Although he may toast with champagne, his drink of choice is sake. In unoccasional moments, he has been seen smoking a traditional bamboo kiseru. His favorite music is enka, or as Jigen calls it, "elevator music".
Although typically a person of mellow aloofness, Goemon has been seen exploding with frustration, admiring beautiful women, and...very rarely...screaming in fright. Such out of character moments are usually treated as humorous takes. His martial arts training gives him many extraordinary talents, i.e., underwater breath control for diving without an aqualung and a limited understanding of the supernatural. He can easily best several trained thugs in unarmed combat and can barehandedly catch an arrow or thrown dagger. His trademark skill is near-superhuman fleetness, enabling him to sword-slice bullets in half before they make contact. It should be mentioned that, despite the deadliness of his weapon, Goemon will never take a human life unless challenged to a duel, and even then only if the opponent reveals a dishonorable nature.
If Goemon has a true weakness, it is that he`s even more weak with women than Lupin is. He readily trusts any woman who seems superficially trustworthy or innocent, often landing him in much trouble. At the same time, he fears sultry women will distract him from his training, and tends to blush or flee when any woman is put in less than modest situation.
Goemon also is very bad with money, and constantly charges Lupin for his services in some fashion. What he does with the money is a usually complete mystery. In $1 Money Wars he gives it to the female leader of a cult, who promptly runs off with it.
Commonly thought to be just a samurai, an episode of Shin Lupin III, ("Goemon`s Revenge") has Goemon visiting his Iga Ninja sensei. This episode depicts him as having had the training of a master ninja, perhaps giving some reason behind his willingness to find thievery as an acceptable practice, in spite of his samurai ways.</description>
<picture>85727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3233" picture="171389.jpg">Inoue Makio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="19285" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">こんにちは地獄の天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good Afternoon, Hell`s Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konnichiwa Jigoku no Tenshi</title>
<summary>Lupin sneaks into an old castle to steal a collection of priceless angel paintings, owned by the late Malcolm Hurst. Inside the castle, Lupin meets a mysterious girl named Flora, who knows the whereabouts of the angel paintings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681645</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19286" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖母マリヤの脱出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Virgin Mary`s Getaway Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seibo Mariya no Dasshutsu Sakusen</title>
<summary>A mysterious cult that idolizes a solid gold Virgin Mary statue abducts Fujiko and they’re planning to burn her at the stake as a witch. However, her kidnapper and the cult leader look vaguely familiar to Lupin. Have they crossed paths before?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681655</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19287" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大いなる罠を暴け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Expose the Great Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooinaru Wana o Abake</title>
<summary>Inspector Zenigata concocts an extravagant plan to finally capture Lupin by luring him in with a fake meteor made from 6 tons of pure gold. Low and behold, his plan backfires and Lupin and his gang make off with the meteor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681643</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19288" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">テレパシーは愛のシグナル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Telepathy Is Love`s Signal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Telepathy wa Ai no Signal</title>
<summary>Lupin and Jigen are out at sea attempting to retrieve the gold inside a sunken pirate ship. However, a female pirate gang interrupts their retrieval mission and both parties leave empty handed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681647</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19289" update="2017-02-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去を消した男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross His Name Off the List</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako o Keshita Otoko</title>
<summary>Onihei Azumaya, the next President of the Federation of Economic Organizations, is actually Mamushidayu, a fraudster who underwent plastic surgery and altered his face. Lupin, who was once duped by Mamushidayu into stealing diamonds, decides its payback time. Will Lupin get his revenge and finally get his share of diamonds after all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681679</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19290" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">五右ェ門無双</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goemon Daydream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goemon Musou</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang are in South Africa to receive a nautical chart from a retired Nazi that shows the location of a sunken Nazi treasure. However, two young German soldiers interrupt the exchange and a skirmish ensues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681649</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19291" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神ガーブと呼ばれた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Is Called the Death Garb</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami Garb to Yobareta Otoko</title>
<summary>Unsurprisingly, Fujiko had once betrayed her heist partner Garb, known as the Grim Reaper and left him for dead. Garb, who has seemingly returned from the dead, is determined to kill Fujiko and has an uncanny ability to dodge bullets with ease.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681653</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19292" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ショータイムは死の香り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Show Time Is Death Feeling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Show Time wa Shi no Kaori</title>
<summary>It’s the Mafia Boss’ birthday party and everyone is gambling away. Lupin’s next target is the casino’s safe. While attending the party, Lupin meets a girl named Jenny, an aspiring Broadway dancer, who is willing to help him pull off the heist to sell her name. Will the heist turn out to be a Broadway hit or a flop?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681675</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19293" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りの荒野を走れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Act of Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Kouya o Hashire</title>
<summary>Lupin breaks out a man named Parker from a Mexican prison in order to steal the treasure Parker had hidden away somewhere. However, not a single piece of truth comes out of Parker’s mouth. Meanwhile, Fujiko is busy seducing Parker to find out the treasure’s whereabouts and is scheming to take the treasure for herself. Parker agrees to split his treasure with her, but Parker isn’t the type to keep promises either. With so many lies swirling about, will Lupin find Parker’s treasure and who is the biggest liar of them all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681677</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19294" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">金塊はルパンを呼ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gold Is Beckoning Lupin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkai wa Lupin o Yobu</title>
<summary>Notorious gangster, Al Capone left behind five tiles that reveal the location of his massive gold hoard when put together. Out of the five tiles, Lupin and Fujiko have three in their possession.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681641</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19295" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪のり変装曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Play a Joke on the Variation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warunori Hensoukyoku</title>
<summary>Lupin and Fujiko attend a lavish party full of wealthy women in order to steal their jewelry. However, the castle tower where the party was being held turns out to be a rocket ship. The hijacked rocket transports the party to a small island and the guests
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681665</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19296" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば黄金伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Golden Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Ougon Densetsu</title>
<summary>An ancient burial mound has been discovered and etched on its walls are ancient mythical creatures with jewel-encrusted eyes. Lupin makes off with the blue dragon’s crystal eye and kidnaps the archeologist in charge. The archeologist reveals that when the blue dragon’s crystal eye is brought together with two other ancient crystals, they reveal a map to the legendary Golden Paradise. Lupin and his gang are determined to find the Golden Paradise, but has the archeologist told them everything he knows?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681681</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19297" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コピー人間は高くつく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Copy-Man Comes Expensive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Copy Ningen wa Takaku Tsuku</title>
<summary>Lupin has a horrible case of athlete’s foot and visits Dr. Budweiser, who is also a cloning expert, for treatment. The doctor takes a sample of Lupin’s skin under the guise of treating his Athlete’s foot, but the doctor has another plan up his sleeve.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681657</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19298" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄金のリンゴには毒がある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Apple Has Poison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougon no Ringo ni wa Doku ga Aru</title>
<summary>The Golden Apple, known as “Eve’s Apple” is being transported to New York City onboard a luxury cruise ship and Inspector Zenigata has a gut feeling Lupin is after it. Inspector Zenigata’s hunch is on the mark as Lupin and Jigen are onboard the ship.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681671</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19299" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘拐ゲームはお好き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Play the Abduction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuukai Game wa Osuki</title>
<summary>Mrs. Alda, a wealthy heiress is kidnapped and Lupin shows up to claim the ransom money. However, the real mastermind behind the kidnapping is Mrs. Alda herself. After she gets the ransom money, she erases Lupin’s memory and frames him for the crime.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681667</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19300" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺しが静かにやってくる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Killer Comes Along Quietly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koroshi ga Shizuka ni Yattekuru</title>
<summary>Lupin learns he needs a pure hearted girl to find an ancient Persian treasure and his computer chooses a girl named Lori. After getting some hands on training from Jigen and Goemon, the two are headed to Jordan to find the treasure.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681669</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19301" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バルタン館のとりこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prisoner of a Valtan Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vartan Yakata no Toriko</title>
<summary>Lupin steals a painting of Lupin I’s beloved from Baltan Gallery in Paris. However, the painting turns out to be a forgery and Lupin has a clue as to who is painting the forgeries. With his daughter Sophie held hostage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681663</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19302" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルビーは血の汗を流す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ruby Sheds Bloody Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ruby wa Chi no Ase o Nagasu</title>
<summary>Lupin manages to steal the Dracula Heart ruby form a mysterious woman known as Mother. The Dracula Heart ruby is known to bleed once every century and whoever drinks its blood maintains their youth for another 100 years.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681661</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19303" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘宝は陰謀の匂い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lay a Plot with the Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hihou wa Inbou no Nioi</title>
<summary>A mysterious message appears in the newspaper and Lupin takes it as a sign from this late grandfather, Lupin I, to reclaim his diamond keepsake.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681659</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19304" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルパンが戦車でやってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lupin Has Come with a Tank</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lupin ga Sensha de Yattekita</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang are in the small city of San Pico in Central America. However, the city was in the midst of a war between the Government Forces and the Guerilla Army. Leading the Guerilla Army is Jigen’s old army pal, Giranco.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681651</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19305" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">結婚するって本当ですか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are You Really Getting Married?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kekkon Surutte Hontou Desuka</title>
<summary>Lupin is over the moon when Fujiko promises to marry him if he steals the ICPO’s gold for her. Lupin pulls off the heist right under Inspector Zenigata’s nose, but the two soon find themselves locked up in jail. Lupin pleads with Inspector Zenigata to let them marry before they are executed. Out of pity, Inspector Zenigata allows the wedding to take place. Will wedding bells ring for Lupin and Fujiko?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681673</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19307" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ターゲットは白銀の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target Was Gone Beyond the Snow Field</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Target wa Hakugin no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang blow up Fontaubert Bank’s underground safe to steal 5 tons worth of gold, but someone has beat them to it. The thieves are a pair of disguise artists named John and Mary. While searching for the pair, Lupin is captured by Inspector Zenigata. The two seek shelter from the snowstorm in an elderly couple’s mountain cabin, but soon a flood of unwanted visitors come barging in. Will Lupin find the missing gold and will his plot roll out as planned?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681709</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19308" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗号名(コードネーム)はアラスカの星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Code Name Is Alaska Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Code Name wa Alaska no Hoshi</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang were pursuing Flight 107, when Soviet Union planes suddenly shoot it down for wandering into its territory inadvertently. To Lupin’s despair, the now sunken Flight 107 was carrying a ring called the Star of Alaska, or in Lupin’s mind, his engagement ring to Fujiko. Fujiko had told Lupin that she’d marry him if he gets the Star of Alaska for her, but Lupin soon finds out the CIA and KGB are also after the Star of Alaska. What secret does the Star of Alaska hold and is it truly at the bottom of the ocean?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681693</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19309" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハディスの涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tears Stood in Hades` Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hades no Namida</title>
<summary>The 100-carat blue diamond, known as Hades’ Tear is auctioned off at 1 billion dollars along with its accompanying Hades statue to the KL Foundation of Kingsland. Lupin and Jigen make off with Hades’ Tear with ease, but they soon find out the blue diamond is nothing but a blue-tinted glass ball. The KL Foundation reveals that although it’s a glass ball, it holds Kingsland’s national secrets, and hires Lupin to smuggle it back to Kingsland. Teaming with a girl named Maria, Lupin decides to deliver Hades’ Tear to Kingsland, but is he actually being duped?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681735</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19310" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鷲の舞い降りる時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eagle Alights on the Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Washi no Maioriru Toki</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang steal the Eagle of Helazard from a luxury cruise ship, but Fujiko betrays them at the last moment and makes off with the Eagle. Fujiko may have stolen the Eagle, but Prince Fallon of Helazard has stolen her heart, creating a love triangle with Lupin in the mix. Prince Fallon believes the Eagle is the key to overthrowing Tolfa, the dictator of Helazard and restoring the kingdom. Will Fujiko choose Prince Fallon over Lupin, and will the prophecy prove to be true?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681711</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19311" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベイルート移動銀行強奪作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strategy of Beirut Mobile Bank Robbery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beirut Idou Ginkou Goudatsu Sakusen</title>
<summary>The Swiss Bank’s Beirut branch is a mobile branch. It also has the odd distinction of being the safest bank in the world, despite being in the world’s most dangerous place. It’s also the branch where all the oil money from the Arab world gets deposited. Will Lupin manage to pull off the heist of this impenetrable bank and get out safely with Inspector Zenigata on his tail?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681685</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19312" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライバルに黄金を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Give the Gold to the Rival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rival ni Ougon o</title>
<summary>A mysterious army steals 3 tons worth of gold under Inspector Zenigata’s watch. His superiors are convinced Lupin stole the gold and holds Inspector Zenigata responsible. No only does Inspector Zenigata hold onto his job by the skin of his teeth, he ends up in the hospital with serious injuries from a failed assassination attempt on him. Feeling sorry for Inspector Zenigata and also to clear their name, Lupin and his gang decide to help retrieve the gold. Will Inspector Zenigata accept Lupin’s warm gift?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681717</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19313" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピラミッドの保険金を奪え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plunder the Pyramid of Insurance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pyramid no Hokenkin o Ubae</title>
<summary>Count Bone and Lord Wave operate the Rondo Insurance Company. The two seem like perfect English gentlemen, but they make their money through dirty tactics. Lupin plans to insure a fake pyramid and steal its insurance money. Will Lupin be able to beat the two at their own game?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681723</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19314" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友よ深く眠れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pray for the Repose of Your Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo yo Fukaku Nemure</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang are after Taniyama’s treasure from an ancient Chinese dynasty. Realizing that Lupin is after his treasure, Taniyama hires a lone assassin named Seiryuu to counter Goemon, knowing full well that Seiryuu is Goemon’s childhood friend. Promised that Taniyama will help him find his clan’s killer, Seiryuu stands in Lupin and his gang’s way. Can Goemon best his childhood rival and will Seiryuu discover his clan’s killer?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681687</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19315" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1000万ドルの鍵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">10 Million Dollar Key</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1000-man Dollar no Kagi</title>
<summary>John Decker, an oil tycoon from Colorado hires Lupin to steal the US presidential limousine and promises to pay 10 million dollars in return. Lupin breaks into Chase Manhattan Bank to steal the presidential limousine’s spare key, but it seems his client has a more sinister plot in mind, with Lupin ultimately taking the blame. Will Lupin end up saving the President of the United States?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681703</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19316" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺を愛したレティシア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letiethia Loved Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore o Aishita Leticia</title>
<summary>Goemon has been thrown into prison for a crime he did not commit. He is charged with cutting off the Little Mermaid’s arm. Roman, the Chief of the Copenhagen Tourist Bureau says he’ll release Goemon as soon as the arm is returned. Even though Lupin knows something is fishy, he signs on to retrieve the Little Mermaid’s arm from the Santa Maria wreckage with the help of Letizia, the dolphin. However, what the masterminds are truly after is the content hidden inside the Little Mermaid’s arm. How far will Lupin go to retrieve the arm and to avoid his pals getting arrested by Inspector Zenigata?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681715</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19317" update="2017-02-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイヤに炎は似合わない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fire Is Not Suitable for a Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dia ni Honoo wa Niawanai</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang break into a vault full of uncut diamonds. However, the diamonds suddenly catch on fire and guess who is being blamed for it! Lupin quickly discovers the diamonds are fakes and it was all a ploy to raise the price of diamonds at the expense of his reputation. With the price of diamonds at an all time high, where are real diamonds and will Lupin get his revenge against the man who framed him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681683</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19318" update="2017-02-17">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カクテルの名は復讐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Name of the Cocktail Is Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cocktail no Na wa Fukushuu</title>
<summary>A massive amount of gold is being transported in the cover of darkness, but on this rainy night, Lupin is busy being bartender to a beautiful woman named Sara. Lupin serves her a cocktail named Revenge, with the promise of killing the man who took over her father’s bank and murdered him. Will revenge and thievery make the perfect cocktail?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681699</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19319" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺たちは天使じゃない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are Not Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oretachi wa Tenshi ja Nai</title>
<summary>How could Lupin and his gang refuse when a church priest asks them to retrieve the Dove’s Eggs, the church’s jewels, for the sake of Spoonland’s children? The real Dove’s Eggs were swapped with fakes during the country’s civil war and are now in Prime Minister Hatcher’s possession. With Lupin’s announcement to steal the eggs, Prime Minister Hatcher appoints Inspector Zenigata and promises him the rank of knighthood bestowed by the Queen, if he successfully guards the eggs and arrests Lupin. Now, Inspector Zenigata is determined to arrest Lupin more than ever! Will Lupin and his gang pull off the charitable heist or will Inspector Zenigata become Sir Koichi Zenigata?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681689</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19320" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばシンデレラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Cinderella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Cinderella</title>
<summary>Queen Gretchen of the Kingdom of Monaka dies from a car accident. As a fan of her years as a Hollywood actress, Lupin mourns her passing. Meanwhile, Fujiko is convinced the King had a hand in her death, and her female intuition proves to be right. The King intends to marry a new Cinderella. Lupin and Fujiko plot to steal the royal treasures and avenge Queen Gretchen, but things don’t exactly go as planned. Who will have their happily ever after ending?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681725</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19321" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戒厳令の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night Under Martial Law</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaigenrei no Yoru</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang have learned a coup d’état is about to take place in one of the Caribbean countries. Amidst the chaos, they plan to steal the dictator’s treasure. They manage to sneak into the dictator’s mansion with ease, but the treasure was long gone. Meanwhile, Jigen is shot by a mysterious woman while in disguise. Where did the treasure disappear to and will the mysterious woman’s wish come true?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681721</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19322" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニューヨークの幽霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ghost of New York</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New York no Yuurei</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang are in New York City to steal a pinball machine made of solid gold. Lupin, Jigen and Fujiko board a casino cruise ship and discover that they’ll need Goemon’s Zantetsuken sword to pull off the heist. Meanwhile, Goemon is out fishing on the banks of the Hudson River when he reels in a human skeleton.  Suddenly, Goemon finds himself haunted by a young beautiful ghost named Lily. Will Goemon’s ghostly admirer help or hinder the heist?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681691</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19323" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆転 逆転 また逆転</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reversal. Reversal and Again Reversal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakuten Gyakuten Mata Gyakuten</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang steal an exquisite painting of a young girl from a Renoir art exhibit. Using the painting as bait, Lupin and his gang plan to steal Ghellon’s impressive art collection. However, Ghellon, the wealthiest man in Mexico is also known as the Merchant of Death with good reason. With the tables turned with each move, will Lupin make off with Ghellon’s precious collection?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681701</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19324" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父っつあんが養子になった日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pops Was Adopted into the Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottsuan ga Youshi ni Natta Hi</title>
<summary>Mexico’s richest woman, Madame Tequila owns a black diamond named the Black Pig of Mexico. Realizing that Lupin is after her diamond, Madame Tequila appoints Inspector Zenigata to guard it. However, what Madame Tequila doesn’t tell Inspector Zenigata is that she also has a 10 billion dollar insurance policy on the diamond. After seeing Inspector Zenigata’s valiant attempt at capturing Lupin, Madame Tequila decides to adopt Inspector Zenigata as her heir. And she’s not taking no for an answer! Will Inspector Zenigata call Madame Tequila, “Mother”?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681737</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19325" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月へハネムーンに行こう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Honey-Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki e Honeymoon ni Ikou</title>
<summary>Lupin is over the moon, now that he’s won Fujiko’s hand in marriage after stealing Marie Antoinette’s wedding dress and ring. Lupin is planning a romantic honeymoon to the moon, but first he needs to track down a rocket scientist to do that. Will the church organ play Lupin and Fujiko’s wedding march?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681697</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19326" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">原潜イワノフの抹殺指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kill the Atomic Submarine Ivanov</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensen Ivanov no Massatsu Shirei</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang steal the Ivanov, the Soviet Union’s newest atomic submarine from the Port of Arkhangelsk. Lupin lightheartedly stole it to salvage some sunken treasure off the coast of Bermuda, but he becomes entangled in a fierce tug of war between the KGB and CIA when Fujiko decides to sell it to the highest bidder. Despite the hostilities between the two spy agencies, perhaps Goemon has found a way for everyone to get along?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681739</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19327" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の翼はスクラップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Worn-Out Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Tsubasa wa Scrap</title>
<summary>At Fujiko’s request, Lupin steals the Hina dolls given to the US Vice President by the Deputy Prime Minister of Japan. However, the doll heist was a trap laid out by Fujiko and her partner, Barracuda. Inside one of the Hina dolls is proof of a secret military transaction between the US and Japanese government, which they can use to extort both governments. Betrayed by Fujiko, Lupin and his gang are stuck on a deserted island. Will the gang make it off the island and what will become of Goemon’s Zantetsuken sword?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681731</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19328" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アラスカの星は地獄への報酬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Alaska Star Is a Ticket to Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alaska no Hoshi wa Jigoku e no Houshuu</title>
<summary>A ring called the Star of Alaska holds a single wheat seed inside it. The seed is a new species of wheat that can grow in minus 40 degrees and the CIA and KGB are determined to get their hands on it. Lupin and his gang take Barbara, a woman who holds the key to the whereabouts of the Star of Alaska, under their care, but Jigen has a personal score to settle with her husband, George. Will history repeat itself and what will become of the Star of Alaska?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681695</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19329" update="2017-02-17">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才少年の危険な遊び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boy Genius Plays a Dangerous Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai Shounen no Kiken na Asobi</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang were scoping out their next target, Macintosh Jewelry, the world’s most expensive jewelry store, when they end up inadvertently saving a young boy who was being kidnapped. Turns out, the boy is a genius and he possesses the data to a revolutionary invention that can turn seawater into fresh drinking water. In order to get his hands on the data, the owner of Macintosh Jewelry kidnaps Fujiko and demands the boy in exchange. Can Lupin protect the boy’s secret from Macintosh and who is the smartest of them all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681705</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19330" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一枚のお宝で大混戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In a Panic over the Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichimai no Otakara de Daikonsen</title>
<summary>Lupin has lottery fever, or to be specific, has his eyes set on the 50 million dollar jackpot. However, Lupin discovers the lottery is rigged. Tony, the President of the Lottery Commission manipulates the lottery machines to pull a certain number. Knowing the lottery is rigged and not wanting to play a game of chance, Lupin decides to manipulate the lottery machines before the jackpot draw. However, an elaborate security system stands between him and the lottery machines. Will Lupin become the lucky 50 million dollar jackpot winner?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681719</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19331" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンゲームに乾杯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Toast to the Con-Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Con Game ni Kanpai</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang have Pinkerton’s unbreakable safe, minus the key. Lupin breaks into the prison where the late Pinkerton was once held and finds the key hidden in his former prison cell. Now the gang has both the safe and key. However, Carlos, a mob boss and Pinkerton’s younger brother, steals the safe from their hideout. Meanwhile, Fujiko and her new man are also after the safe. Who is the biggest con artist of them all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681729</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19332" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父っつあん大いに怒る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pops Boils over with Rage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tottsuan Ooi ni Ikaru</title>
<summary>A young girl named Anne tearfully tells Inspector Zenigata how Lupin has brought on her family’s misfortunes. Inspector Zenigata is even more determined to capture Lupin, but when he learns Anne has been shot dead by Lupin something snaps inside of him. Lupin and his gang will soon learn that Inspector Zenigata is a force to be reckoned with, when he’s raging mad. But is Anne really dead?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681713</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19333" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マンハッタン・クライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Manhattan Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manhattan Crisis</title>
<summary>Lupin and his gang make off with the New York Mafia’s secret cash hoard. However, the suitcases were filled with old newspapers and as retribution, the mafia puts a hefty bounty on Lupin’s head. Not only does Lupin have Inspector Zenigata after him, it seems as though all of New York is trying to cash in, too! Will Lupin get his hands on the Mafia’s cash hoard or will he end up as fish food at the bottom of the Hudson River?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681707</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19334" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボクたちのパパは泥棒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Papa Is a Thief</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi no Papa wa Dorobou</title>
<summary>Once a year, jewelers from around the country descend on New York City for a jewelry tradeshow, bringing with them their entire inventory. Combined, the jewelry is said to be worth 20 million dollars. Lupin and his gang plan to steal the whole lot, but things go awry when some children claim Lupin is their father. Jigen and Goemon find it hugely amusing, but they soon find themselves stuck in the same mess. Will the gang be able to juggle fatherhood and their thieving careers?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681727</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="19335" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一枚の迷画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Famous Picture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichimai no Meiga</title>
<summary>The mafia killed a young boy’s father to steal his massive fortune. Realizing that his life is in danger, Ken’s father paints a picture that contains a treasure map to his fortune and is killed shortly after. Goemon pities the young boy who is afflicted with an incurable illness, and swears to retrieve his father’s painting for him. Will Goemon be able to keep his promise and will Lupin decipher the painting’s hidden secret?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681733</identifier>
<identifier>lupin-the-third-part-3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124482" update="2018-12-15">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1984-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124483" update="2018-12-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1984-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210969" update="2018-12-15">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1985-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
