<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1517" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>1967-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>1967-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gokuu no Daibouken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Adventures of Goku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Adventures of the Monkey King</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Goku`s Great Adventures</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">悟空の大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Goku`s Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">The Monkey - Le grandi avventure di Goku</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2199" type="Alternative Setting">Saiyuuki</anime>
<anime id="7340" type="Other">Boku no Son Gokuu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/36.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="833" type="Unknown Relation">Mushi Production</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="4382" type="Music">Uno Seiichirou</name>
<name id="7924" type="Direction">Sugii Gisaburou</name>
<name id="7924" type="Chief Direction">Sugii Gisaburou</name>
</creators>
<description>In this film, because of complaints from children that Goku is depicted as too much of an eager student, he is instead portrayed as a very naughty modern boy. It then received so many complaints from the PTA about its bad language that it was forced out of the show after all.
Source: Official Site</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="27">5.22</permanent>
<temporary count="27">6.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>151156.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1502</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2687</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1763</identifier>
<identifier>xojmue</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/36.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gokū_no_Daibōken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>悟空の大冒険</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89632</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>522</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1546</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3752" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>Journey to the West</name>
<description>Journey to the West is a classic Chinese mythological novel. It was written during the Ming Dynasty based on traditional folk tales. Consisting of 100 chapters, this fantasy relates the adventures of a Tang Dynasty priest Sanzang and his three disciples, Monkey, Pig and Friar Sand, as they travel west in search of Buddhist Sutra. Several anime are loosely based on its story, most famously Dragon Ball.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31062" type="main character in" update="2011-04-10">
<name>Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4018.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="34061" picture="94378.jpg">Ute Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31063" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-10">
<name>Ryuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4019.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4735" picture="29144.jpg">Masuyama Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31064" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-10">
<name>Sanzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4020.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3380" picture="187130.jpg">Nozawa Nachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31065" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Sagojou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4021.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1935" picture="21204.jpg">Aikawa Kin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31066" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-10">
<name>Hakkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4022.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3790" picture="50436.jpg">Takiguchi Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="16381" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊感大王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great King of Inspiration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikan Daiou</title>
<summary>Sanzo and the others come across a big river called the Tsuten River. They ask a boatman ferrying a small boat to carry them across. However, the boatman takes Sanzo away. Goku follows them hurriedly, and sneaks into the hideaway of the king, who rules the river.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16382" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第6の妖怪ハリケーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sixth Monster Hurricane</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 6 no Youkai Hurricane</title>
<summary>In a thick fog, the sixth monster Hurricane uses his huge eyes to block Goku`s magic. With Tatsuko`s help, Goku escapes from jail. Hurricane suffers from a weakness in his eyes.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16383" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of Goku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu Tanjou</title>
<summary>A long time ago, a stone monkey is born in Mt. Kaka of Gorai-koku on the Chinese Continent. His name is Son-Goku. He has been born rambunctious, and he thinks of taking over the castle in Gorai-koku just for fun.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16384" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">坊さんナンバーワン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Number One Monk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousan Number One</title>
<summary>Goku is saved by Sanzo-hoshi. He helps Goku out of Mt. Gogyo on his way to Tenjiku in order to get a sacred sutra. As soon as Goku emerges from the rocks, he runs away. When he finds Sanzo-hoshi being attacked by a monster, however, he cannot help coming back to save Sanzo.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16385" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">博士は何にしびれたか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Carried the Doctor Away?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakase wa Nani ni Shibiretaka</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends get lost in the mad scientist Doctor Dokkanko`s bomb experimenting facility. The doctor thinks that Sanzo is an industrial spy and captures him. Goku and others try to rescue Sanzo. They have a hard fight, but the bomb that is the doctor`s last resort fails...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16386" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おナカの中の中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside the Inside of Stomach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onaka no Naka no Naka</title>
<summary>Sanzo and the others are going up a river heading for Tenjiku when a mud snail monster attacks them. When Goku punishes it, it says, "It`s not my fault. It`s the man in my stomach." So Goku goes inside the mud snail`s stomach, and finds a bear that says, "You must blame the man in my stomach."
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16387" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">バラモンの足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Baramon`s Feet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baramon no Ashi</title>
<summary>A huge foot suddenly appears from the sky and tries to trample Sanzo and the others down. It turns out to be a huge centipede.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16388" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">王様はユーレイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King Is a Ghost</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ousama wa Yuurei</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends are involved in a plot to assassinate the prince of Furiten. It is likely that Plankton of the Federation of Global Villains is connected to the plot. But a monster is also involved...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16389" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">プイプイ教の大魔神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Demon God of the Pui-Pui Religion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Puipui no Daimashin</title>
<summary>Sanzo`s party goes fishing to a port in the country, but Sanzo eats some highly poisonous seaweed there by mistake. He is said to have only an hour to live because of the poison.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16390" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">あれが天竺の灯だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Is the Light of Tenjiku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Are ga Tenjiku no Akari Da</title>
<summary>Sanzo`s party continues the journey to Tenjiku. Then they save an old man who is also on his way to Tenjiku. When they come to a crossroads, the old man says that Tenjiku must take the bleak road, but Goku and his friends take the road blooming with flowers. That road turns out to be a villain`s trap.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16391" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかしな? おかしな?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strange? Strange?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashina? Okashina?</title>
<summary>When Gilde captures Sanzo, Goku and others go around the globe following them...then Hakkai wakes up.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16392" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘラクレスの手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hercules`s Hands</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heracles no Te</title>
<summary>Gigantic hands? Although Goku has once broken off his friendship with Sanzo and the others, he goes to rescue captured Sanzo when he finds out what the Monster Union is up to.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16393" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">火輪童子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fire Ring Child</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bihanawa Douji</title>
<summary>Rain forces Sanzo to stay on, so he takes shelter in a small shrine in a big tree. Goku, who cannot keep still, goes scouting with Tatsuko. When they find a wizard school in the mountains, Goku at once challenges the head wizard to a fight...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16394" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">59作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation 59</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">59 Sakusen</title>
<summary>A king who loves toys summons the evil scientist Plankton from a television to meet Goku and his friends. Although he is once defeated, Goku sneaks into the castle hidden in a wooden horse. Then he takes over the castle as planned, but one of Plankton`s monsters suddenly appears and destroys the ramparts...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16395" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">金角 銀角</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kinkaku &amp; Ginkaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkaku Ginkaku</title>
<summary>Kinkaku and Ginkaku, who live in the Renge Cave, eat a village girl as a sacrifice once a year on a night with a full moon. This year, Min-min, the daughter of the village headman, is chosen for the sacrifice. Then Goku, who happens to be staying in the village hotel, sympathizes with her, and sets out to destroy the monsters.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16396" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">キント雲はいただき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Be Taking Kinto-Un</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinto-Un wa Itadaki</title>
<summary>Goku`s dream comes true: he becomes the king of Gorai-koku. Then he is invited to heaven by the celestial emperor, but he behaves violently there. He has a fight with the celestial army, and is captured once but runs away. Then Buddha captures Goku and shuts him in a rock as punishment for causing a disturbance in heaven. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16397" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラゴンの牙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dragon`s Tusk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dragon no Kiba</title>
<summary>A tusk-shaped rock suddenly attacks Goku and his friends. The Monster Union has incited the attack. Then Tasuko comes to rescue them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16398" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宝の地図はペケペケ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Treasure Map Is No Good</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takara no Chizu wa Pekepeke</title>
<summary>The pig monster Hakkai, who drives a sports car named Kinto-un, and Sagojo, who is a treasure-hunting freak, join Goku and Sanzo on their journey. Goku becomes involved in trouble related to Sagojo`s treasure map, but when the treasure they dig out turns out to be ancient currency made from stones...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16399" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガツガツムシャムシャ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gatsu-Gatsu, Musha Musha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gatsugatsu Mushamusha</title>
<summary>The monster King Gatsu-Gatsu and Queen Musha-Musha rob a country. The prince and princess of that country are disguised as bandits who assault carriages. Goku and his friends sympathize with them, and head for the castle to destroy the monsters.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16400" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハネ一族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hane Tribe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hane Ichizoku</title>
<summary>A swarm of ants attacks Goku and his friends. When they run into a windmill, they find themselves trapped by an old woman of the Hane tribe.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16401" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">荒野の妖怪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster in the Wilderness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouya no Youkai</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends come to a town in the wilderness. On the advise of a sheriff, who happens to pass by, they stay in a house on the top of the hill. It turns out to be a trap set by bounty hunter Makarony.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16402" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">メデュウスの髪の毛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Medusa`s Hair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Medusa no Kami no Ke</title>
<summary>The fifth monster "Medusa`s Hair," which is said to be the cruelest monster of all, torments Goku and his friends with its hair. Its weakness lies unexpectedly in a huge pot.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16403" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">カジババと40にんの盗賊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gajibaba and Forty Thieves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kajibaba to 40 Nin no Touzoku</title>
<summary>Sanzo is being followed persistently by Okesa Monk, the leading expert of Buddhist priest`s clothes. So he hides in a big safe, but then the notorious looters Gajibaba and the forty thieves take away the safe..
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16404" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">かげろうの谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Valley in the Haze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagerou no Tani</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends find a peaceful quiet village in the mountains as they go through a thick fog. They are welcomed, so they decide to stay in the village. That night, however, a monster attacks them. This peaceful village is in fact an illusion that the monster had created.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16405" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">あけてビックリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Surprise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akete Bikkuri</title>
<summary>Goku feels pity for the girl Mimi, who comes from the country of beauties, so he destroys the monster in Skeleton Castle and takes back the bomb in the golden coffin for her. However, it turns out that the country of beauties is to blame. Tatsuko is surprised to hear the truth from a monster. Then she is showered with a hail of bombs...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16406" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボクはコブコブよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Kobu-Kobu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Kobukobu yo!</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends fight against the great king Kobu-Kobu, who lives in the mountain marsh. Kobu-Kobu is a tough enemy who can use the marsh water as he likes, and is immune to lightning. However, when Goku aggressively shakes his Kinso-bo...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16407" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">つらら大王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Icicle King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsurara Daiou</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends step into a snow-covered mountain, where they are hit by a blizzard. When they reach a hotel, however, they find themselves trapped by a goblin with a blank face, which works under the Great Icicle King. Goku is shut inside the ice at once, and Sanzo and the others are taken away.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16408" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">どっちもどっち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neither Is Better Than the Other</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Docchi mo Docchi</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends come to a town where an old party and a new party are opposed to each other. They become involved in big trouble concerning the election of the village headman by the two parties. Everything depends on the last vote by Goku and his friends. Gradually the competition gets out of their control...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16409" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨に歌えば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Singing in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame ni Utaeba</title>
<summary>Kankara is a scorching country where everything is dried up. Just as Goku and his friends jump into a spring they have finally found, they are arrested for stealing water. The drought, in fact, has resulted from a nasty scheme of Kankara Minister and Thunder Minister, who are trying to make money by selling water.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16410" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハートでいただき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captured by Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heart de Itadaki</title>
<summary>Goku fights against the mad scientist Plankton. Plankton takes Goku and his friends for spies, and sends beautiful Micron to them. Hakkai and Sanzo are completely fascinated by her. Goku, however, ...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16411" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪連合のさいご</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the Monster Union</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Rengou no Saigo</title>
<summary>The great monster is a combination of six big monsters that had been defeated. It is overwhelmingly strong. Sanzo and the others are captured by the Great Monster King, and Goku is also in imminent danger. However, with the help of the Buddha, he destroys the great monster and also the Great Monster King...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16412" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おいらゴウケツだい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Outstanding</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oira Gouketsudai</title>
<summary>Goku fights desperately to rescue Hakkai, who has been abducted. The abductor Gidarla Minister, however, is impressed with Goku`s excellent fighting, and asks him to destroy the monster that haunts the marsh in his country.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16413" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぼちゃの化物-のろわれた王様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pumpkin Monster, The Cursed King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabocha no Bakemono: Norowareta Ousama</title>
<summary>Sanzo, Hakkai, and Sagojo drink water from a waterfall because it is unbearably hot. The village people tell them that the fall is called "Pumpkin Waterfall," and whoever drinks its water turns into a pumpkin. Moreover, the doctor only cures those who pay a lot of money...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16414" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">人食いジャングル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Man Eating Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitogui Jungle</title>
<summary>They are forced to pass through the jungle if they want to take a short cut to Tenjiku by going beyond the mountains. Three monsters live in the jungle, the blue lion, the white elephant, and the eagle. The monsters believe that they can live longer by eating great monks.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16415" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴミまで愛して</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Your Garbage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomi made Ai Shite</title>
<summary>Goku and his friends pass a dirty village named "Flowering Village." In fact, this village has been turned ugly by a salamander that hates beautiful things.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16416" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベロリベロベロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Peroi Pero-Pero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Perori Peropero</title>
<summary>Sanzo`s party goes to a fighting ring where an old woman appears and appeals against the ill treatment of bulls. However, nobody listens to her. Then the old woman, who has collected the tongues of dead bulls, brings out a monster called Berori Bero-Bero.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16417" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">われらガードマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are Guard Men</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warera Guard Men</title>
<summary>A contest is held to choose Princess Mandolin`s bodyguard because the boss of moles is trying to catch her. Goku participates in the contest and becomes her bodyguard.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16418" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">奥様は妖怪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Monster Wife</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okusama wa Youkai</title>
<summary>A female monster that can transform creatures into dolls turns Hakkai, Sagojo, and Sanzo into dolls. Goku, who has been scouting, gets Tatsuko`s urgent message, and heads for the amusement park on the top of the mountain, which is the monster`s headquarters...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16419" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀糸仙人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Silver Thread Hermit (Ginshi-sennin)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginshi Sen`nin</title>
<summary>Sanzo`s party has to go through a forest where a vampire called Ginshi-sennin lives. While Goku is away scouting, Sanzo and the others are captured by Ginshi-sennin. The vampire gives Goku, Hakkai, and Sagojo to his three sons, and tries to suck Sanzo`s blood...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126635" update="2011-01-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126636" update="2011-01-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126637" update="2011-01-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126638" update="2011-01-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126639" update="2011-01-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilot film</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126667" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Non-Broadcasted Version of Ep.1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
