<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1536" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2004-09-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bakuretsu Tenshi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Exploding Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Explosive Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Взрывной ангел</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Anjo Explosivo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BakuTen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">爆裂天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Ангелы Смерти</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เทพธิดามหาประลัย</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Ангели на смъртта</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Burst Angel</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3386" type="Side Story">Bakuretsu Tenshi: Infinity</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1322" approval="18" total="19">Hikari to Mizu no Daphne</anime>
<anime id="6275" approval="11" total="11">Canaan</anime>
<anime id="6113" approval="5" total="14">Ga-Rei: Zero</anime>
<anime id="68" approval="5" total="6">Bubblegum Crisis</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="244867">Really good series :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/0403.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="735" type="Original Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="4314" type="Animation Character Design">Horiuchi Osamu</name>
<name id="4157" type="Music">Nishida Masara</name>
<name id="1391" type="Direction">Oohata Kouichi</name>
<name id="1602" type="Animation Work">Gonzo Digimation</name>
<name id="9387" type="Animation Character Design">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="1602" type="Work">Gonzo Digimation</name>
</creators>
<description>* A high-tech action series produced by http://anidb.net/cr735 [Gonzo].
The year is 20XX. Under the Maintenance of Public Order Act only a select few are permitted to carry firearms.
Tokyo has been converted, including major districts such as Shinjuku, Shibuya, Roppongi and Akihabara. Everyone now suffers a life of oppression and the constant threat of violence.
A mutual opposition in the underground plans to rebel against this malevolent syndicate. However, the people, and their names, as well as their occupations remain unknown.
The main female characters are http://anidb.net/ch10008 [Jou], http://anidb.net/ch10009 [Meg], http://anidb.net/ch10010 [Sei] and http://anidb.net/ch10007 [Amy]. These energetic and courageous teenagers with skills of professionals will deal with anyone who stands in their way — the gunfighter`s way.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3991">4.48</permanent>
<temporary count="4050">6.96</temporary>
<review count="9">7.34</review>
</ratings>
<picture>8233.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3560</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>109</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1347</identifier>
<identifier>kvxeyy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/bakuretu-tenshi/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.imagicatv.jp/content/bakuten/TV/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Burst_Angel</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>爆裂天使</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>378</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319949</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6717</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5991" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>dark mood</name>
<description>Similar to `Dark Atmosphere`, but more focused on the actual characters rather than the setting. A dark mood can easily result from a dark atmosphere.
A dark mood is more than just occasionally feeling angry or down, it`s usually a permanent character trait that sours the character`s relationships with others.
However it arises, at least one character in this anime can see little good in the world or the people in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10007" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<rating votes="11">3.80</rating>
<name>Amy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amy is a young computer/techno whiz. She was saved and recruited by Sei after Amy`s hacking drew attention from the authorities in her own country. It was through her hacking skills that Sei managed to recruit Jo and Meg. She often argues with Meg in a friendly way and loves scarfing down Kyohei`s various treats. Her hair is light brown, and worn in pigtails. She is often seen carrying a pink stuffed animal that contains a laptop.</description>
<picture>30190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10008" type="main character in" update="2011-05-04">
<rating votes="35">6.83</rating>
<name>Jou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jo`s physical appearance is of that of a young teenager of 17 years old. Consisting of silver hair, red eyes, and a glowing tattoo located on her left arm and shoulder blade, they resemble wings and are occasionally called "The Wings of the Devil". They only appear when Jo is under a significant amount of stress while fighting. She also carries a pair of .44 Magnums with markings similar to the tattoo designed on left arm. Jo is often seen wearing a red leather jacket lined with gold fur and a yellow or red scarf. Aside from her jacket, she also wears a black top, black shorts, and chaps with her gun holster over the top.
Jo pilots a cybot called Django, which she uses to carry out various missions for Sei and to help out her friends when they`re in need, mainly Meg. Jo also puts Meg over anything else, which she stated when telling Meg that she fights for her. When she is not fighting, she enjoys watching horror or gore related movies. Jo would eventually rediscover her past as a genetically engineered war machine in human form. After being forced to surrender with Meg and others held hostage, Jo returns to the secret labs for reprogramming and conditioning at RAPT R&amp;D. Jo`s counterpart, Maria, frees her and Meg to only prove who was the strongest by re staging the fight they were unable to finish. After the fight between Maria and Jo, which pushes both of them to their limits, Maria loses her will to fight and is restored to her true humanity. Reunited with the group, Jo decides that she has to destroy RAPT. Against Meg`s will who is highly opposed to the idea after seeing her go through a lifetime of combat, Jo knocks Meg out for her own safety, bids her farewell, and leaves her jacket behind for her to remember her by.</description>
<picture>30192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10009" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<rating votes="28">6.04</rating>
<name>Meg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Megumi, called Meg, has red hair (although in her first appearance chronologically in episode 14: "Wild Kids", she is portrayed as having black hair) and dresses like a cowgirl. She carries a small revolver, and, at times, a large anti-tank rifle. Meg is highly prone to be captured only to be rescued by Jo. She is the very best of friends with Jo and is 100% loyal only to her. It is suggested that her feelings for Jo are romantic.
Meg was once an orphan in New York City with several other children until she encountered Jo. Since then, Meg and Jo teamed up and became bounty hunters. The other children appeared to have been adopted by a police officer.
After she finds out Jo`s origin, she feels Jo no longer should fight. Jo however knocks her out and leaves her jacket to her. At the end of the series, Meg makes her way to the ruined RAPT HQ and sees Jo`s scarf hanging on a piece of debris. Meg then says her final goodbye to Jo. The final scene is Meg in Jo`s outfit, in a scene very much paralleling the beginning of the opening title, only with a red Django behind her.</description>
<picture>30193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10010" type="main character in" update="2011-05-05">
<rating votes="22">6.70</rating>
<name>Sei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sei is the kind leader of the group who is the one that hires Jo and Meg to become members of Bai Lan. She wears a long blue jacket and has her black hair in a bun. Her grandfather runs Bai Lan (White Lotus) and comes from a very powerful Chinese family. Sei was born and raised as a traditional Chinese girl and was trained in various ways of her clan/syndicate. After her grandfather stepped down as leader of the clan, their current clan members made a partnership with RAPT to preserve their clan. However, such actions not only disgusted Sei, she was also forced to do many things for RAPT in Bai Lan`s name. She eventually rebelled against her own organization under the advice of her grandfather.</description>
<picture>30194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15568" type="main character in" update="2011-05-04">
<rating votes="6">2.96</rating>
<name>Tachibana Kyouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student attending a certified culinary school who is proficient in Chinese, Italian and Japanese cooking. Kyohei is often seen wearing his chef uniform and riding a small motor scooter which is destroyed by Jo on more than one occasion. He is hired by Sei as a cook for the girls because their last cook had left. He continues working for the team to save up to go to France and become a patissier.</description>
<picture>44193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15569" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Angelique</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15570" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="9">3.62</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with a distinct resemblance to Jo who, like Jo, was artificially created. She expresses a desire to hurt Jo, and so attempts to take Meg for her own. She`s discovered to be Jo`s "sister" and when both fight their energies are capable of entering a pocket of alternate space and reality. After Jo defeated her, she lost the drive to fight and regains her humanity to save Jo and Meg from RAPT forces. She was killed in heavy gunfire from RAPT Cybots.</description>
<picture>44195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15571" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-07">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Ichimonji Hayao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15572" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<rating votes="6">4.59</rating>
<name>Katsu Takane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A loud-mouthed, bike-riding Police Officer from Osaka. Takane is often seen riding a chopper and wears a uniform resembling that of a schoolgirl. She carries a large wooden sword, which she swings around often; as it symbolizes her leadership of an all girl biker gang, who often act as her deputies. She`s also efficient at throwing handcuffs and subduing her target. Takane is quick to lose her temper and hates being in debt to anyone. She is also the daughter of the Police Chief of Osaka. After crossing paths with the team, she becomes attached to the team and assists them anyway she can as debt to Jo even if it means disobeying her father.</description>
<picture>203719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31754" type="appears in" update="2011-05-02">
<name>Django</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>70810.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="46102" type="appears in" update="2012-12-06">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Sam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10303.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5977" picture="30601.jpg">Omoro Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46103" type="appears in" update="2012-12-06">
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<name>Shirley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10304.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2032" picture="186151.jpg">Yoshizumi Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46104" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Mafia no Boss</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46105" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hongou-sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4628" picture="224317.jpg">Kobayashi Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46106" type="appears in" update="2014-02-03">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Won</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46107" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Taxi Untenshu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3965" picture="25836.jpg">Souya Shigenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46108" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Ryan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2233" picture="21784.jpg">Takewaka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46109" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="309" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46110" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46111" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="3">5.05</rating>
<name>Kazami Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5815" picture="30271.jpg">Oono Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46112" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Jay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A representative from Kokuren and Bai-lan`s Japanese counterpart. His father and Sei`s grandfather arrange for he and Sei to wed so that the white and black lotus can join together once again. However, Sei`s grandfather respectfully declines Jay`s request to have both the Bai Lan and Kokuren seals displayed together. Angry, he and his men attack Sei to try and obtain the Bai Lan seal by force. Jay obtains the seal and almost escapes, but he is stopped by Jo after shooting down the dragon head of the yacht making it crash onto Jay`s boat.</description>
<picture>132413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46113" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Lee Jii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20" picture="16599.jpg">Kitagawa Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46114" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nino Leo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46115" type="appears in" update="2018-04-16">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Iriki Tougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46116" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Tetsuzou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1942" picture="50629.jpg">Amada Masuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46117" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2089" picture="151696.jpg">Morota Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46118" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46119" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Charlie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1677" picture="223670.jpg">Matsumoto Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46120" type="appears in" update="2012-06-18">
<name>Masa-yan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66289" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Lava</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="16770" update="2005-09-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17846" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="23">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄が静かにやって来る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell Comes Silently</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`enfer approche doucement</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`inferno arriva all`improvviso</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ад тихо приближается</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Helvetti on tulossa kaikessa hiljaisuudessa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku ga Shizuka ni Yattekuru</title>
<summary>Kyouhei’s job hunt lands him in the middle of more action than he could’ve ever expected when he meets his beautiful new bosses: Sei, Amy, Meg, and Jo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="17868" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">情無用のガン・ファイター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heartless Gunfighter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pistolero sans pitié</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Duellanti senz`anima</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Безжалостный стрелок</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Sydametön pistoolisankari</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nasakemuyou no Gun Fighter</title>
<summary>When Meg’s kidnapped by a mysterious Cybot, Jo and Kyo rush into the most dangerous part of town to set her free.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="18046" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野獣の吠える街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City Where the Beast Howls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ville où rugissent les bêtes</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La città dove ululano le bestie feroci</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Город, где воют чудовища</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kaupunki jossa peto ulvoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yajuu no Hoeru Machi</title>
<summary>Random Cybots, RAPT, and a stealthy bounty hunter complicate the girls’ mission to bring in Wong.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="18253" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄弟 暁に死す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Brothers Die at Dawn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les frères meurent à l`aube</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fratelli, morte all`alba</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Братья: смерть на заре</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Veljekset tapaavat Kuoleman ammunkoitteessa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai Akatsuki ni Shisu</title>
<summary>Meg’s fighting for her life, thanks to a runaway freight train and a mutant monster gone berserk. A mysterious man from Wong’s past puts everything into sharper perspective.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="18933" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪神蠢く館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mansion Where Lurks the Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le manoir où grouillent les démons</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il palazzo infestato dagli spiriti del male</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Чертог, где таится демон</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kartano jossa paha henki kiemurtelee</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jashin Ugomeku Yakata</title>
<summary>Meg is undercover at an elite girls’ school, investigating a student’s descent into insanity - and some kind of demon is on the loose.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19213" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この花園を血で洗え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wash This Garden with Blood!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lavez cette école dans le sang</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Lavate questo giardino con il sangue!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Цветочный сад, омытый кровью</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Pese tämä puutarha verellä</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Hanazono o Chi de Arae</title>
<summary>A secret society conjures an ancient demon and it has its sights set on Meg! If Jo can’t break the curse, Meg may not make it out of this mission alive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19796" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Noir comme le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cielo nero</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Чёрное Небо</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Musta taivas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Sora</title>
<summary>A giant bird snatches up Meg before Jo’s very eyes! A secret weapon injected into Kyo raises the stakes for Sei, and a deal to save Meg leaves Jo hanging in the balance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20396" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷だらけの逃亡者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wounded Outlaw</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fugitive blessée</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il fuggitivo pieno di ferite</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Израненный беглец</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Haavoittunut lainsuojaton</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizudarake no Toubousha</title>
<summary>Traps and cops are everywhere, but Jo and Kyo have to reach Tokyo Tower before the Crow Monster has its way with Meg.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="20713" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーティ・オブ・ザ・ドラゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Party of the Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête du Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il party del dragone</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вечеринка у Дракона</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Lohikäärmeen juhla</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Party of the Dragon</title>
<summary>The situation turns ugly after the announcement of Sei’s arranged marriage to a member of the Black Lotus Clan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21180" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電脳番外地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uncharted Cyberspace</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La zone électrique perdue</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La straordinaria terra dei computer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Неизведанное кибер-пространство</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kartoittamaton kyberavaruus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dennou Bangaichi</title>
<summary>After Amy sneaks off to the electronics store with Kyo, they find themselves sucked into a world filled with cybernetic creatures determined to make them stay!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21190" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東の天使 西の鷹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel of the East, Hawk of the West</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ange de l`est et le faucon de l`ouest</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`angelo dell`est, il falco dell`ovest</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ангел Востока, Сокол Запада</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Idän enkeli, lännen haukka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higashi no Tenshi, Nishi no Taka</title>
<summary>Jo’s protecting a star athlete, chasing a giant bug, and trying to save a hijacked train - all at the same time. Her hands are full, but a hotshot detective arrives and navigates the chaos with ease.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21389" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">通天閣は涙に濡れて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsutenkaku Tower, Drenched with Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tour Tsutenkaku baignée de larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Lo Tsutenkaku bagnato di lacrime</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Башня Слёз</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kyynelten uittama Tsuutenkaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuutenkaku wa Namida ni Nurete</title>
<summary>Jo’s hauled in by an elite Hawk Squad Cop, and the city of Osaka is feeling the iron fist of RAPT. Meanwhile, Sei is digging deeper into the mystery behind the mutant creature.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21390" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血戦! 浪速愚連隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bloody Battle! Naniwa Hoodlums</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un peuple se lève ! Combat sanglant !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Scontro sanguinoso! La gang di Naniwa</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кровавая Битва</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Verinen taistelu! Naniwan sekalainen joukko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Naniwa Gurentai</title>
<summary>With Meg held hostage, Sei finds her options limited when dealing with Iriki - any brash moves could spell a fatal end for her colleague.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22026" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワイルド・キッズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wild Kids</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Enfants sauvages</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ragazzi di strada</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Дикие Дети</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Villit lapset</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wild Kids</title>
<summary>Flashback: Young Meg and her friends are homeless thieves, and they’ve caught the attention of a trained killer who will change Meg’s life forever.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22027" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海と水着と大海獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Ocean, Swimsuits, and a Sea Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mer, des maillots de bain et un monstre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Oceano, costumi da bagno e il grande mostro marino</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Море, Купальники и Морское Чудовище</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Meri, uimapuvut ja jättimäinen merieläin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi to Mizugi to Daikaijuu</title>
<summary>The girls’ day at an amazing water park turns into a nightmare when a greedy park executive decides to sabotage the grand opening.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22036" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔境戦鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">War Demon of the Haunted Realm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ogre vil tapi dans l`ombre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il mondo misterioso del demone combattente</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Потусторонний демон войны</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Demonitaistelija kirotussa maailmassa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makyou Senki</title>
<summary>Jo’s suffering from painful visions, and she’s on the run after a routine Jango session leads to a violent attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22037" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 二人の天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Clash! The Two Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux anges, une collision !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Scontro! I due angeli</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Поединок! Два ангела</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Taisto! Kaksi enkeliä</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Futari no Tenshi</title>
<summary>A ghost from the past confronts Jo as she battles for her life, and a brilliant adversary from another dimension gives her a run for her money!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22038" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死身の同級生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Immortal Classmate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ami immortel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il compagno di classe immortale</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Бессмертный одноклассник</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kuolematon luokkatoveri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujimi no Doukyuusei</title>
<summary>A simmering gang war pits brother against brother and man against machine. Kyo must prevent mayhem and save an old classmate from his own destruction.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23398" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謀略 24時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">24 Hour Plot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une ruse, 24 heures</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Congiura 24 ore su 24</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Заговор "24 часа"</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">24:n tunnin strategia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bouryaku 24-jikan</title>
<summary>Takane falls victim to a mind control device, and it’s up to the girls to rescue her from the clutches of the sinister men behind the mystery.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23589" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2004-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24403" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">皆殺しのハイウェイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Massacre Highway</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`autoroute de la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`autostrada assassina</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Резня на шоссе</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Joukkotuho moottoritiellä</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minagoroshi no Highway</title>
<summary>A new cybernetic police unit meant to keep the peace goes haywire and turns its malfunctioning glare to Takane!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24508" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使, 爆裂!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burst, Angels!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anges et explosions</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Angel, Burst!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ангелы! Взрывайтесь!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Enkeli, räjähdä!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi, Bakuretsu!</title>
<summary>Sei devises a plan to free Tokyo from the dominating clutches of RAPT, but she’ll have to reassemble the team to pull it off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24773" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉄の墓標に弾丸を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bullets in the Iron Grave Post</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tirez sur le tombeau métallique</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Pallottole sulla lapide di ferro</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пули в железное надгробие</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Ammu luoti rautaiseen hautakiveen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tetsu no Bohyou ni Dangan o</title>
<summary>Another terrorist attack rocks the city, but the girls won’t be saving Tokyo this time - they’ve been de-commissioned!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24811" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋する悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beloved Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un démon amoureux</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il demone che ama</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Влюблённый дьявол</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Demoni jota rakastat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Akuma</title>
<summary>Cornered by a strange woman from Jo’s past, Meg finds herself in the clutches of evil. Glenford tightens his grip on Tokyo as dark clouds move in overhead!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24812" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い海の処刑場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Execution Ground on the Red Seas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Exécution sur une mer rouge de rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il luogo dell`esecuzione sul rosso mare</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Место казни на красном море</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Teloitusalue punaisella merellä</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Umi no Shokeijou</title>
<summary>It’s a battle between Angels when Maria and Jo face off in the ultimate fight of their lives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="72141" update="2009-12-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72142" update="2009-12-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72143" update="2009-12-23">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72144" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72318" update="2007-04-30">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72319" update="2007-04-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72320" update="2007-04-30">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special #6</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
