<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1554" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-01</startdate>
<enddate>2005-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mai-HiME</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">My Hime</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">My Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dancing Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Моя принцесса</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Май-Химэ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Танцующая принцесса</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">ماي-هيمي</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">ศึกศาตราเจ้าหญิงแห่งดวงดาว</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Танцуващата принцеса</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mai Hime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mh</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">舞-HiME</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">My-HiME</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">My-HiME</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">My-HiME</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ไม-HiME ศึกศาสตราเจ้าหญิงแห่งดวงดาว</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3216" type="Alternative Setting">Mai-Otome</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8069" approval="56" total="92">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
<anime id="5786" approval="5" total="14">Sekirei</anime>
<anime id="11572" approval="5" total="11">Mahou Shoujo Ikusei Keikaku</anime>
<anime id="8160" approval="4" total="6">Fate/Zero</anime>
<anime id="2481" approval="2" total="7">Uta Kata</anime>
<anime id="8" approval="1" total="5">Aquarian Age: Sign for Evolution</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="17">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="391160">It gets good around ch. 7, epic in its second part. But its over-sweet-happy-end is not `meh` is horrible, a Titanic-class disaster.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177393">Surprisingly funny and heart-warming</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="297941">This anime contains some clichés that make it look only mediocre in the first few episodes (people with "special powers" et al), but it turns out to be a very well-constructed, dramatic, serious and funny story that ends in quite an epic way. Definitely a recommendation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="215397">A very good anime, with plenty of fun, intrigue and of course echhi...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="79448">Starts as a pure fun with girls and robots doing cute silly stuff, then descends into some intense drama (that would only seem intense if you had enjoyed the first part of the show), and ends with absolutely BEST last episode ever - you will laugh your asses off.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="467099">didn`t really expect a whole lot from this series and it did take around 5 episodes before i really go into it but it turned out to be quite an interesting watch. The only gripe i have is with cop-out cheesy ending oh well still worth watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="5572">Good anime just wish it was based of manga if it was it would have been AWESOME. Good to watch though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="305044">Very realistic characters and an exceptional drama. Amazing show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="250906">Best, ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="150297">one of the best anime project SUNRISE ever made.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/my-hime/</url>
<creators>
<name id="706" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hisayuki Hirokazu</name>
<name id="706" type="Character Design">Hisayuki Hirokazu</name>
<name id="707" type="Direction">Ohara Masakazu</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="4250" type="Series Composition">Yoshino Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch5913 [Tokiha Mai] and her sickly younger brother, http://anidb.net/ch5933 [Takumi], have received a scholarship to attend the prestigious Fuuka Academy. On the way there, the ferry they are travelling on becomes the site of a destructive battle between two girls wielding apparently supernatural powers. This is only the beginning of their troubles, as Mai learns that she herself possesses these powers — the powers of a HiME.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7417">6.95</permanent>
<temporary count="7523">8.00</temporary>
<review count="16">7.46</review>
</ratings>
<picture>5470.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4155</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>673</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>98</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>8062</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1493</identifier>
<identifier>hafpby</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/my-hime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>My-HiME</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>舞-HiME</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321262</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6958</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>65</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B078KJHXZK</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="165" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>painting</name>
<description>Painting is the practice of applying paint, pigment, color or other medium[1] to a surface (support base). The medium is commonly applied to the base with a brush but other implements, such as knives, sponges, and airbrushes, can be used.
In art, the term painting describes both the act and the result of the action. Paintings may have for their support such surfaces as walls, paper, canvas, wood, glass, lacquer, clay, leaf, copper or concrete, and may incorporate multiple other materials including sand, clay, paper, gold leaf as well as objects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="736" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-13">
<name>tea ceremony</name>
<description>A tea ceremony is a ritualised form of making tea. The term generally refers to either chayi Chinese tea ceremony, chado Japanese tea ceremony, tarye Korean tea ceremony. The Japanese tea ceremony is more well known, and was influenced by the Chinese tea ceremony during ancient and medieval times. One can also refer to the whole set of rituals, tools, gestures, etc. used in such ceremonies as tea culture. All of these tea ceremonies and rituals contain "artificiality, abstractness, symbolism and formalism" to one degree or another.
These rituals can be found worldwide, although are centred on Asia and Europe, including the Victorian-era `high tea` or afternoon tea ritual, where the ritual of being seen to have the right equipment, manners, and social circle, was just as important as the drink itself.</description>
<picurl>160817.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1590" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>biker</name>
<description>A person who is skilled at riding a motorcycle/motorbike and does so on a regular basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2620" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-21">
<name>battle royale</name>
<description>Many characters are removed from their normal lives or lifestyles and thrown into a game where they are forced to battle each other until one survivor remains. Much like the famous film `Battle Royale`.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3094" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>befriend attack</name>
<description>A befriend attack is a pounce performed by someone in an attempt to hug someone else. This is an exuberant display of affection, often used for comedic effect. Sometimes, the target of such attacks learn to dodge them, usually by simply sidestepping them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3161" parentid="2726" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>enjo-kousai</name>
<description>Enjo-kousai means "compensated dating" and is a practice which originated in Japan where older men give money and/or luxury gifts to attractive women for their companionship, and possibly sexual favours. The female participants range from school-age girls to housewives. A common misconception is that enjo-kousai always involves some form of sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>222239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3192" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-26">
<name>hidden base</name>
<description>Someone wants to be secretive when he plans to take over the world...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3250" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-02">
<name>regeneration from death -- TO BE SPLIT AND REMOVED</name>
<description>This tag is meant for removal. The characters it would apply to should be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2209 [regeneration] and/or http://anidb.net/t1396 [immortality], as appropriate. Please tag the relevant characters with those two tags and remove this tag from their respective anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3833" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>there can be only one</name>
<description>The long-term plot of the program revolves around a group of characters whose numbers are being slowly whittled away by one means or another, usually by killing each other. In the case of some reality shows, this is a process of elimination intended to result in a single winner. In other shows, this is a dramatic device, designed to generate tension and conflict with which to drive the overall plot of an episode or Story Arc (if any); in these cases it is sometimes combined with Anyone Can Die to especially heighten the resulting excitement, even when the apparent main character may be protected by Contractual Immortality. Compare Gotta Kill Them All.
Named for one of the catchphrases that came out of the Highlander franchise.
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3981" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-27">
<name>ninja maid</name>
<description>This is an old tag for anime which had characters that were maids and also ninjas, or at least able to use ninjutsu. The tag will be removed once all maids in question are properly tagged. See also the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninja,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninja and maid] and the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninjutsu,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninjutsu and maid].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4809" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>superstition</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5505" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-15">
<name>deus ex machina</name>
<description>When the story has been spun so wildly and the plot has been driven so deeply, when all resources are exhausted and the linear truth stands so proudly at the end of the road, ready to bring the never-ending adventure to its epic conclusion...
The writers kick you in the behind and say "Screw that!! Suddenly... UFOs!!! No, wait, Werewolf UFOs!!! Bet you didn`t see that coming!"
It`s the old-Greek form of solving your broken story because it was too much work to do it all over again, or you`ve already shown stuff that compromises what you wanted to do. It`s finding out about a better dragon on a whole different planet because you`ve already been revived 3 times and that`s the cap. It`s breaking a spaceship and "oh wait, there`s an exact copy built in secret by an unknown guy on the other side of the planet, and you can use it free of charge". It`s Doraemon`s pouch, on every single episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5651" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-06-22">
<name>against destiny</name>
<description>Screw destiny and all the others who try to discourage them; they`re not going to fulfill the prophecy of world destruction because they`re the Big Bad`s descendant, or become a sacrificial magician. They`re going to become who they want to be. (source: TV Tropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5732" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-01-21">
<name>evil american</name>
<description>The US plays the evil role. Usually through their actions towards another country while playing the role of the World Police.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5807" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2007-08-08">
<name>cosmic reset</name>
<description>All events that occurred up to a certain point are mysteriously undone, as if the Universe pressed a rewind button. This usually means some characters are being given another chance to unknowingly play out events differently, perhaps to prevent certain consequences from the previous time line`s actions. Occasionally they become doomed to repeat portions of their life over and over again until an individual event or series of events are performed correctly in just the right way, as seemingly to gain the Universe`s approval.</description>
<picurl>36685.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5840" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>birthday</name>
<description>All about the birthday celebration of at least one of the protagonists in this anime.
This includes a birthday party with a birthday cake and other food and presents — lots of them.</description>
<picurl>161031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6066" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>improvised weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be split and deleted. Please apply any applicable http://anidb.net/tag/?parentid=7405&amp;reltb=chartb [weaponized object tags] to the relevant characters, or create new tags if necessary, and delete this tag from the anime/character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6068" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-20">
<name>human sacrifice</name>
<description>Human sacrifice is the act of killing one or more human beings as part of a ritual. Throughout the majority of human history, primitive societies have engaged in human sacrifice, generally as a religious act, such as an offering to please or appease deities, spirits, or the deceased. Other uses that have been seen include magic rituals, usually related to black magic or the summoning of demons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35" type="main character in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="45">7.63</rating>
<name>Kuga Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuki is typically portrayed as a serious, rational blue-haired female, as a foil to the lighthearted Mai Tokiha. Natsuki`s beauty is the target of several jokes, usually involving her becoming embarrassed in a situation. She usually has Shizuru Fujino as a close friend. Natsuki always uses some type of gun as her weapon and she is usually associated with wolves, silver and the element ice. She also has a habit of flicking her hair with her right hand. Running gags include her hobby of collecting lingerie, her fondness of mayonnaise, and her tendency to become irritated easily.</description>
<picture>23004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5913" type="main character in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="38">6.87</rating>
<name>Tokiha Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mai is depicted with short red hair and a rather large bust. She is typically cast as a sisterly friend of Mikoto, the guardian of her brother Takumi Tokiha, a close friend to Natsuki Kuga but usually at odds with her, and a potential love interest of Yuuichi Tate and Reito Kanzaki. She is associated with fire, and in all series wields 4 large golden rings with magatama as weapons. She also uses a mitsu tomoe as her symbol. She has a fear of spiders in both anime and manga. Running gags include Mikoto burying her face in Mai`s chest or Mikoto otherwise being possessive of her, Mai`s bust size, and her cooking abilities.</description>
<picture>23005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5914" type="main character in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="12">3.07</rating>
<name>Tate Yuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuichi is a member of the Fuuka Academy Student Council. He first appears in Episode One on the same ferry that Tokiha Mai is taking and the two quickly form bad impressions of each other. Munakata Shiho calls him her older brother even though they are not related by blood. He works with the Student Council doing odd jobs for them (prompting Mai to label him a "lackey") and sits next to Mai in class.
Yuuichi used to be a member of the Fuuka kendo club and regularly made it into the nationals until he was suffered a severe injury to his knee at some point in the past, though the exact circumstances and nature of the injury are never explained in the anime.</description>
<picture>23006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5915" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="5">1.73</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Reito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reito Kanzaki is the Vice President of Fuuka Academy`s Student Council alongside President Fujino Shizuru. A calm person, he is popular with the female students of the school, but shows romantic interest in Tokiha Mai. Reito`s calm and reserved personality often clashes with that of Executive Committee head Suzushiro Haruka, whose annoyance with him is made evident several times. Reito shows kindness by taking Mai`s brother Takumi and his roommate Akira with him on official business to a fancy restaurant free of charge.</description>
<picture>23007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5916" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="5">5.53</rating>
<name>Harada Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harada Chie is a classmate of Mai Tokiha; whom she sits directly behind, and Yuuichi Tate. She offers her friendship on Mai`s first day, introducing herself by poking Mai`s sides playfully. She uses her cell phone`s camera frequently to give interviews and is always searching for new gossip around the school, which develops into a running gag about her character. She and Aoi Senou appear in an omake as super deformed versions of themselves to give a rundown of their class, classifying Mai as being in the "Biggest Breast Ranking".</description>
<picture>23008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5917" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="24">6.25</rating>
<name>Fujino Shizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The always-calm president of the Fuka Academy Student Council, Shizuru at first appears in episodes involving important school events, or in scenes featuring the Student Council`s homeroom, often calmly sipping tea. Making an entrance as a playful, charming and slightly sarcastic individual, she takes care of significant school affairs single-handedly, even patching up for the academy director when required, but tends to leave all the "dirty work" for the executive committee.
She wears a differently colored uniform to denote her status as Student Council President, something fellow Student Council leaders Reito Kanzaki and Haruka Suzushiro also do. Her beauty and distinctive Kyoto-accent have earned her quite a few fans within the academy - And all mostly female. She occasionally lends Natsuki Kuga use of the Student Council`s computer in order to look up information relating to the HiME.</description>
<picture>23009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5918" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="12">5.11</rating>
<name>Suzushiro Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hot-tempered Haruka Suzushiro is a member of the Fuuka Academy Student Council. She is first introduced when interrogating Mai Tokiha. She has a tendency to mispronounce or misspell words.
She is Yukino Kikukawa`s best friend and often protected the younger girl in earlier years, but also bosses her around. She has a strong (and mostly one-sided) rivalry with Shizuru Fujino, who she often refers to as "bubuzuke" (tea with rice). Much of her strong dislike of Shizuru comes from the result of the Student Council Elections in which they both ran, where Shizuru won in landslide of 817 with only 12 votes for Haruka. However, Haruka recovered from this loss and became the passionate and commanding Executive Director of the Suzushiro Executive Team, and often deals with the dirty work or otherwise humiliating tasks that the Student Council would rather not do.</description>
<picture>23010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5919" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="20">5.44</rating>
<name>Miyu Greer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyu initially appears as a girl in Mai Tokiha`s class and the adopted daughter of Joseph Greer, the resident priest of Fuuka Academy. She is friendly towards Mai, making strange comments about the exact temperature and amount of precipitation, and is very protective of Alyssa Searrs.</description>
<picture>23011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5920" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="9">4.86</rating>
<name>Higurashi Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In My-HiME Akane is a classmate of Natsuki Kuga and works part-time as a waitress with Mai Tokiha and Midori Sugiura at the Linden Baum diner. She is shown to be dating Kazuya Kurauchi, Mai`s classmate, who also works at the diner. She is also seen text messaging Kazuya during class with her cellphone. It is implied by Chie that Kazuya and Akane have difficult family lives, though this is not elaborated on.</description>
<picture>23012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5921" type="appears in" update="2009-05-17">
<rating votes="5">5.49</rating>
<name>Senou Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoi enjoys teasing Mai with Chie Harada. She is also fond of cute younger students.</description>
<picture>23013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5922" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="10">4.86</rating>
<name>Kikukawa Yukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukino appears as the secretary of the Fuuka Student Council and Haruka Suzushiro`s best friend and confidant. She is in the same class as Mai Tokiha and Yuuichi Tate. She is frequently seen with her laptop computer and occasionally runs the communications network of the Executive Council. An introvert, Yukino frequently corrects Haruka`s mispronounced or misspelled words as and attempts to calm the hot-headed Haruka down during crises. Yukino has been friends with Haruka since they were small children, and was often defended by Haruka when she was unable to defend herself from bullying. As such she feels great loyalty towards Haruka and often accompanies her during her (sometimes ill-planned) attempts to protect the school.</description>
<picture>23014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5923" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="2">3.99</rating>
<name>Takeda Masashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masashi Takeda is the chief of the kendo club. He is in love with Natsuki Kuga, despite the fact that she does not return these feelings. He tends to appear in situations where Natsuki is in a compromising position (such as having her skirt blown up by the wind after her panties are stolen). He tries to make Yuuichi Tate return to the kendo club in vain. Takeda is mainly a joke character in the anime series, appearing mainly as comic relief in early episodes of the series.</description>
<picture>23015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5924" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="2">3.02</rating>
<name>Kurauchi Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuya is Mai`s classmate and coworker, and Akane Higurashi`s boyfriend.</description>
<picture>23016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5925" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.77</rating>
<name>Ota Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yayoi is very short, and has a sort of admiration for Akira Okuzaki. She is usually seen with Sayuri and Miya.</description>
<picture>23017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5926" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="3">5.45</rating>
<name>Suzuki Miya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miya is part of a trio of friends with Yayoi and Sayuri.</description>
<picture>23018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="391" picture="228518.jpg">Itsuki Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5927" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="2">3.58</rating>
<name>Ichinose Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayuri is part of a trio of friends with Yayoi and Miya.</description>
<picture>23019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5928" type="main character in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="23">3.62</rating>
<name>Minagi Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikoto is depicted with very short black hair with braids, along with yellow eyes. She is usually very physically strong and agile. She is always paired with Mai Tokiha as a roommate or close friend. Common running gags are Mikoto burying her face in Mai`s chest and possessiveness of Mai; her catlike actions, occasionally causing her to be likened to a demon; her huge appetite, especially for Mai`s food; her tendency to collapse when hungry; and her seeming naivete.</description>
<picture>23020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5929" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="10">6.03</rating>
<name>Yuuki Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In My-HiME, Nao is a middle school student at Fuka Academy and the roommate of Mai Tokiha`s friend Aoi. Although she first appears in the second episode, when a rampaging Mikoto Minagi knocks her down, she is not formally introduced until the seventh, as Mikoto`s classmate. At first, she appears to be a child prostitute as she approaches a man who had arranged to meet her over the Internet (where she uses the nickname "Juliet") and they go to a secluded spot. However, before things go any further, she traps the man with the aid of her "Child" familiar and robs him.</description>
<picture>23021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="83" picture="38901.jpg">Nanri Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5930" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="11">3.38</rating>
<name>Munakata Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiho Munakata is a childhood friend of Yuuichi Tate, whom she affectionately calls her brother (onii-chan) despite the fact that they are not related. She is in the Fuka Middle school, and quickly makes friends with Mai Tokiha and Mikoto Minagi. She is a miko at her grandfather`s shrine. She is very possessive of Yuuichi and is in love with him, and even expresses to Mai that she wishes to marry him. The fact that her hairstyle makes her look like an octopus is something of a running gag in the early episodes of the series, as well as her sporadic movement of her hair and its reaction to her moods.</description>
<picture>23022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5931" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-04">
<rating votes="5">4.15</rating>
<name>Okuzaki Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira is the roommate of Mai Tokiha`s younger brother Takumi Tokiha and attends the Fuka Middle school with him. Akira`s strong-willed and forceful personality contrasts with Takumi`s kind and (relatively) feminine attitude and is extremely private, setting up a curtain and strict boundaries for the room. Akira is also a student of Ishigami, the art teacher.</description>
<picture>23023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5932" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="11">6.26</rating>
<name>Okuzaki Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5933" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="6">2.37</rating>
<name>Tokiha Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takumi is depicted as a kind, soft spoken boy, and is the younger brother of Mai Tokiha. He is usually a close friend and foil of Akira Okuzaki, and has health problems that require attention.</description>
<picture>23024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2871" picture="23214.jpg">Takahashi Yuugo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5934" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="11">4.76</rating>
<name>Homura Nagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagi makes his first appearance in the first episode of the My-HiME anime commenting that another HiME has arrived. He is first seen conversing with Mashiro Kazahana and Fumi Himeno after the latter two meet Mai Tokiha for the first time and he comments on Mai`s HiME status.</description>
<picture>23025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5935" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="13">4.02</rating>
<name>Alyssa Searrs</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alyssa first appears in the Fuuka Academy choir, where she is well known around the school for her wonderful singing voice and is commonly called the "Golden Angel". Mikoto Minagi and Mai Tokiha encounter her on a hillside singing with Miyu Greer during a day off, where they exchange a few words. Alyssa is frequently seen clinging to Miyu, and rarely speaks unless spoken to, coming off as very shy and timid. She is in the Fuuka elementary school.</description>
<picture>23026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5936" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="14">6.09</rating>
<name>Kazahana Mashiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mashiro is depicted as a small girl with lavender hair. She normally has a leadership role; in My-HiME she is the chairwoman of Fuka Academy.</description>
<picture>23028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5937" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="8">5.02</rating>
<name>Himeno Fumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fumi is a maid serving Mashiro Kazahana, the Director of Fuka Academy. Since Mashiro needs a wheelchair, she is almost always accompanied by Fumi, who propels the wheelchair.</description>
<picture>23029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5938" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="3">4.32</rating>
<name>Sagisawa Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youko is the school nurse and a friend of Midori`s from college. Drives a Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution.</description>
<picture>23030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5939" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="15">6.62</rating>
<name>Sugiura Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Midori first appears as one of Mai`s co-workers at the Linden Baum diner. She claims to be 17 years of age, even though she is really 24, and no one believes her. She is friends with school nurse Yohko Sagisawa from their college days, and she eventually becomes a teacher at Fuka Academy. A DVD special reveals that Yohko met Midori on the first day of college when Midori sat down and started chatting amiably. Yohko suggests that Midori has a "thing" for older men.</description>
<picture>23031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5940" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="7">3.09</rating>
<name>Sanada Yukariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukariko is the resident nun of the Fuka Academy Church, and along with Father Joseph Greer she gives council to students seeking advice. She was raised in a convent and has had little contact with men for most of her life.</description>
<picture>23032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5941" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="2">3.02</rating>
<name>Sakomizu Kaiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakomizu is a teacher easily identified by his afro. He enjoys gardening and serves as an informant to Natsuki.</description>
<picture>23033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5942" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="2">2.38</rating>
<name>Ishigami Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5943" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="2">3.18</rating>
<name>Joseph Greer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father Greer is the priest at the Fuka Academy church.</description>
<picture>23035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7084" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-21">
<rating votes="39">8.26</rating>
<name>Yumemiya Arika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yumemiya Arika is the protagonist of the My-Otome anime and manga series. She is first introduced in the first episode where she travels through the desert to Windbloom to find out more information about her mother, whom she was told was an Otome. After seeing the power of the 3rd Column, Shizuru, she decides to follow her mother and become an Otome. She is sometimes nicknamed Anty (Arinko-chan in Japanese) because her name, Arika, could be "蟻か" in Japanese, which means ant. The way her head turns into an ant`s head is a way to show how she feels when someone calls her this nickname (which must have followed her all her life).</description>
<picture>25344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8545" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="28">7.91</rating>
<name>Nina Wang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27727.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21241" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<rating votes="5">5.01</rating>
<name>Kuga Saeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21255" type="appears in" update="2010-09-01">
<rating votes="3">4.35</rating>
<name>Nonomiya Kiyone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nonomiya Kiyone attends the middle school section of Fuuka Academy and is a member of the choir along with Alyssa Searrs. She is attacked by an Orphan, an event for which Sister Sanada Yukariko blames herself.</description>
<picture>54280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21432" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="2">3.10</rating>
<name>John Smith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>John Smith works for the Searrs Foundation. His job is to tie up loose ends previously made by Searrs.</description>
<picture>54618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21447" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="5">5.01</rating>
<name>Mai no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42974" picture="172121.jpg">Yano Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21448" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Mai no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54664.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34999" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-29">
<rating votes="12">6.34</rating>
<name>Kagutsuchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>the basis of the character kagutsuchi is originated from ancient japanese mythology involving Izanami and Izanagi. He is the god of fire</description>
<picture>76157.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="16865" update="2010-03-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23158" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="35">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは☆乙女の一大事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Girl`s Most Important Event</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est un grand bouleversement dans la vie d’une jeune fille !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เหตุการณ์สำคัญของสาวน้อย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Otome no Ichidaiji</title>
<summary>For brother and sister Mai and Takumi Tokiha, a trip to their new school turns bizarre when a girl with a large sword turns up in the water. And when the ship is suddenly attacked, Mai finds herself with unbelievable powers!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23168" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23169" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23170" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23171" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23172" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23173" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23174" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23175" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short PV 08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24815" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="24">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒミツの放課後</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After-School Secrets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Secrets après la classe</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความลับหลังเลิกเรียน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu no Houkago</title>
<summary>After an awkward first morning at school, Mai tries to adjust to life at Fuka Academy! Right when she thinks she’s settled, the attacker from the previous night appears on campus. But things get worse when a strange creature attacks Takumi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24864" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の舞 / 星の誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance of Flames / Star`s Oath</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La danse des flammes</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การร่ายรำแห่งเปลวเพลิง / คำอธิษฐานต่อดวงดาว</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Mai / Hoshi no Chikai</title>
<summary>With a new power and a new destiny, Mai must accept the abilities and burden that come with being a HiME. But the future that awaits her is a dangerous one. A meeting with the headmistress leads to much-needed answers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25067" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風のイ・タ・ズ・ラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischief of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les farces du vent</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ส-า-ย-ล-ม เล่นตลก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Itazura</title>
<summary>Something is up around campus—girls’ underwear has gone missing! Orphans are causing trouble around campus and only the HiME can stop them. But can Mai and Natsuki work together?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25169" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨--. 涙......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rain - Tears...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pluie... Larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ฝนกับน้ำตา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame. Namida......</title>
<summary>An Orphan is attacking buses around the city, but Mai can’t focus on the enemy when she has to worry about Takumi’s health. But will Yuichi be the shoulder she can cry on when it becomes too much?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25294" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もえる十七歳(^^;)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Passionate Age of 17</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ardeurs des 17 ans</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สาววัย 17 ผู้ลุกโชน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeru Juunana Sai (^^;)</title>
<summary>When Yuichi asks Mai and Takumi to help out with a wedding at Shiho’s family shrine, things take a turn for the awkward. Shiho asks Mai not to steal Yuichi from her, and on top of that, Midori Sugiura reveals something unbelievable!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25765" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷子の仔猫たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost Kittens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaton égaré</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เหล่าลูกแมวหลงทาง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maigo no Koneko-tachi</title>
<summary>Mikoto follows a classmate to discover she’s hiding a dangerous secret. But when she gets caught up in the trouble, what will it mean for Mai and the other HiME?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25998" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="27">9.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たいせつなもの.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Precious Thing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chose la plus précieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สิ่งสำคัญ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taisetsu na Mono.</title>
<summary>A day at the school festival turns dark when Orphans begin to attack. Powers are revealed, lives are claimed—what is in store for the girls burdened with the powers of the HiME?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26182" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海とオトメとなつきのヒミツ♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sea, the Maidens, and Natsuki`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mer, les jeunes filles et le secret de Natsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทะเล กับหญิงสาว และความลับของนัตสึกิ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi to Otome to Natsuki no Himitsu</title>
<summary>It’s summertime which means it’s time to hit the beach! But there’s more going on when Mai discovers Natsuki lurking around in the middle of the night. What are her true motives?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26183" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケーキ大戦!!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cake Wars!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La guerre des gâteaux</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สงครามเค้ก!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cake Taisen!!!!</title>
<summary>To make up their not-so-great grades in home economics, the girls and their classmates participate in a cake-baking contest. In this contest hosted by Midori, things are sure to heat up. But trouble doesn’t take a break—even for cake!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26184" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光と闇の輪舞(ロンド)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance of Light and Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ronde des ténèbres et de la lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="th">บทเพลงบรรเลงซ้ำของแสงสว่างกับความมืด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari to Yami no Rondo</title>
<summary>Something is happening to girls around campus, and people are blaming…a vampire?! But this attacker is after specific girls—the HiME!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26185" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使のほほえみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Smile of an Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un sourire angélique</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รอยยิ้มของนางฟ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Hohoemi</title>
<summary>Plots uncovered, questions asked—Natsuki finds the group behind the vampires only to get herself kidnapped. With a little unexpected help, can Mai make it in time to save her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26186" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~たまゆらの夜~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Tamayura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nuit du Tamayura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ค่ำคืนแห่งทามายูระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamayura no Yoru</title>
<summary>Love is in the air in preparation for the Tamayura Festival! But do the HiME have time to find love and figure out what Alyssa and Miyu are planning to do next? Mai finds herself with mixed feelings about her priorities and where her heart lies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26394" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれる学園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Targeted Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`école prise pour cible</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เป้าหมายคือโรงเรียน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareru Gakuen</title>
<summary>While everyone tries to wrap their heads around the explosion last night, armed tanks suddenly appear on campus! Alyssa and Miyu do whatever it takes to seek out the HiME on campus—will the girls escape, or do they make their final stand?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26395" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="36">9.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天翔ける ﾐ☆ 女子高生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A High School Girl Soars to the Heavens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une lycéenne à travers la galaxie</title>
<title xml:lang="th">นักเรียนหญิงม.ปลาย ทะยานสู่อวกาศ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amagakeru Joshikousei</title>
<summary>The HiME come together to take back Fuka Academy. With little time before the next attack, they must act quickly to save their classmates and stop Alyssa’s plans. But the cost of survival, what it will take to save them all—who will make the sacrifice?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26396" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Parade♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Parade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Parade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Parade</title>
<summary>With Mai’s return, normalcy has settled in. Midori gathers the girls and urges them to join forces. But after a night of karaoke and fun, they learn what new battle awaits them, and the HiME festival begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26397" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うそつきな, 唇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deceitful Lips</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des lèvres trompeuses</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปากที่หลอกลวง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usotsuki na, Kuchibiru</title>
<summary>Finally, the truth about HiME and their purpose has been laid out. But to save the world, the girls must fight one another to take away each other’s precious one. What choices will they make, and who will win this battle royal?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26398" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">--はじまり.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le commencement</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จุดเริ่มต้น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari.</title>
<summary>A mysterious figure attacks Mai but disappears before they can find out who it is. Natsuki shares her past, and one of the girls attacks another! Will they follow the destiny Nagi spoke of, or can they make their own path?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26399" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こころの迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Labyrinth of the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les méandres du coeur</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จิตใจที่คดเคี้ยว</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Meikyuu</title>
<summary>Between the impending festival and caring for Takumi, Mai is reaching her breaking point. Tension rises for the HiME as the pressure of whether to fight or not begins to grow. Mai lashes out at Mikoto—what will become of them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26400" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="28">9.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の舞 / 涙の運命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance of Flames / Tears of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La danse des flammes / Un destin fait de larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การร่ายรำแห่งเปลวเพลิง / ชะตากรรมแห่งหยาดน้ำตา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Mai / Namida no Unmei</title>
<summary>Nao attacks Takumi in an act of revenge. As Mai and the others hurry to protect him, the mysterious girl in white appears once more. A sword is drawn, a Child is slain.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26401" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒き君, 目覚めるとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Obsidian Prince Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le prince noir se réveille</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เจ้าชายแห่งความมืดตื่นขึ้นแล้ว</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroki Kimi, Mezameru Toki</title>
<summary>Reito takes in a broken Mai while Natsuki learns a harsh truth about her mother. A new HiME is revealed, and more truths come to light. In this unavoidable fight, who can be trusted?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26402" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くずれゆく......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collapse...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Effondrement</title>
<title xml:lang="th">พังทลาย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuzureyuku......</title>
<summary>The school is falling apart, both students and teachers leaving. Midori shares the secret to saving the remaining HiME, but the only option is to continue fighting. Mai makes a decision—but what are her motives?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26403" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛情と友情, 非情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love and Friendship, Heartlessness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amour et amitié insensibles</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความรักและมิตรภาพ ที่สูญสิ้น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aijou to Yuujou, Hijou</title>
<summary>Midori makes the decision to awaken Miyu but is met with resistance from Mikoto. The fight between HiME continues, and more precious ones are lost. The final battle approaches.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26404" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コイ・ハ・タタカイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love is a Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’amour est un combat</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความรักคือการต่อสู้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi wa Tatakai</title>
<summary>The choices we make can determine our fate. There is no way to go back. Anything that seems like another chance could turn out to be a mere illusion. What is it that Mai really wants—is the answer out there?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31437" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の刻へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moment of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jusqu`à l’heure du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ก้าวสู่ชะตากรรม</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Koku e</title>
<summary>Mai and Natsuki prepare to end this fight once and for all and go their separate ways. Miyu faces off with Mikoto, and Mai finds herself at the door of the Obsidian Prince.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31438" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="29">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">shining★days</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Days</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shining★Days / Les beaux jours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shining Days</title>
<summary>Can destiny be changed?  Can sacrifices be undone? Mai fights the final battle against Mikoto and Reito. With so much lost, is the world still worth saving?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35756" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17 Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35757" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15 Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35758" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16 Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35759" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18 Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42128" update="2005-10-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42129" update="2005-10-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45046" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞衣とはじめてのブラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mai`s First Bra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mai to Hajimete no Bra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45047" update="2006-08-08">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風華学園へようこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Introduction to the Private Fuuka Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuka Gakuen e Youkoso</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45048" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高等部1-A紹介</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Class A introduction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutoubu 1-A Shoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45049" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静留・なつきを語る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shizuru talking about Natsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizuru Natsuki o Kataru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45051" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みことのいちにち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mikoto talking about her day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikoto no Ichinichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45052" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">詩帆のお兄ちゃんとドキドキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shiho talking about Onii-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiho no Onii-chan to Dokidoki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45053" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奈緒の『世界を釣る』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nao`s Fishing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nao no Sekai o Tsuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45054" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あかねの告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akane`s Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akane no Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45121" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞衣の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mai`s Thoughts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mai no Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45122" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なつきの想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsuki`s Thoughts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuki no Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45123" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">命の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mikoto`s Thoughts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikoto no Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45124" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風華のひみつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuuka`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuka no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45125" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なつき, 静留を語る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsuki Tells of Shizuru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuki, Shizuru o Kataru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45126" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「黒曜宮にて」神崎黎人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"At the Obsidian Shrine" Kanzaki Reito</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokuyouguu nite" Kanzaki Reito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45127" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お姉ちゃんへ 鴇羽巧海より</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To My Older Sister, From Tokiha Takumi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onee-chan e Tokiha Takumi yori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45128" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">晶の問い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akira`s Question</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akira no Toi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45129" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風花邸幻想 ~真白と二三~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kazahana Mansion Illusion ~Mashiro and Fumi~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazahana Yashiki Gensou: Mashiro to Fumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45130" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">碧の『運命なんかぶっとばせ!』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Midori`s "Going Against Fate!"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midori no "Unmei Nanka Buttobase!"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45131" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーファンのひみつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orphan`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orphan no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45132" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スノウ・マン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Snow Man</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45133" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">M. I. Y. U</title>
<title xml:lang="en">M. I. Y. U</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">M. I. Y. U</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45134" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楯祐一の『気になるアイツ』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tate Yuuichi`s "Worrisome Fellow"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tate Yuuichi no "Ki ni Naru Aitsu"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45135" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Childhood Friends ~雪之と遥~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Childhood Friends - Yukino and Haruka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Childhood Friends: Yukino to Haruka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45136" update="2006-06-08">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紫子の『尼僧物語』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukariko`s "Priestess Story"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukariko no "Nisou Monogatari"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45137" update="2006-08-06">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽子と碧の『われらが青春の日々』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Youko and Midori`s "Our Days of Youth"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youko to Midori no "Warera ga Seishun no Hibi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45138" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遥の生徒会長立候補演説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haruka`s Student Council President Speech</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruka no Seito Kaichou Rikkouho Enzetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46218" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandub - Episode 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46219" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandub - Episode 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46220" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandub - Episode 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46221" update="2011-01-14">
<epno type="5">P30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandub - Episode 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116139" update="2010-03-07">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒の舞 / 最後の晩餐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Dance / The Last Supper</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro no Mai / Saigo no Bansan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116857" update="2010-03-12">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞-HiME 対 舞-乙HiME 萌え? 史上最大の決戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mai Hime vs. Mai Otome - "Moe"? The Greatest Battle!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121171" update="2010-08-13">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121172" update="2010-08-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179546" update="2016-08-27">
<epno type="2">S29</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Days</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
