<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="156" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2002-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Final Fantasy Unlimited</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">FFU</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">FF:U -ファイナルファンタジー:アンリミテッド-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Final Fantasy: Unlimited</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Final Fantasy: Unlimited</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Final Fantasy Unlimited</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Последняя фантазия: Всемогущий</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Final Fantasy: Unlimited</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Final Fantasy: Unlimited</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/0101.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1462" type="Chief Direction">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="1419" type="Character Design">Nakajima Atsuko</name>
<name id="1522" type="Character Design">Nakazawa Kazuto</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="5510" type="Character Design">Hirata Tomohiro</name>
<name id="22610" type="Character Design">Kusanagi Takuhito</name>
<name id="1462" type="Character Design">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="3688" type="Series Composition">Tomioka Atsuhiro</name>
<name id="2019" type="Music">Hamaguchi Shirou</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
<name id="22905" type="Character Design">Murao Minoru</name>
<name id="43715" type="Original Work">Square</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, a black pillar appeared in the Sea of Japan — a gate that led to another world, used by monsters to invade this world.
Dr. http://anidb.net/ch18302 [Hayakawa], a professor famous for his research in the field of geology, got sent to the other world with his wife http://anidb.net/ch18303 [Marie]. They returned safely, and wrote the book: The Day of Conjunction. Soon thereafter, they left for the other world again.
Years later, their now 12-year-old twins http://anidb.net/ch18276 [Yuu] and http://anidb.net/ch18275 [Ai] explore a closed-down subway station, where according to "The Day of Conjunction", a train that travels to the other world departs. To search for their parents, they board the train. Following Ai and Yuu, the 22-year-old http://anidb.net/ch18277 [Lisa] also boards the train.
But who is this mysterious woman? And what awaits the twins in the other world?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1663">2.48</permanent>
<temporary count="1689">5.82</temporary>
<review count="3">4.72</review>
</ratings>
<picture>3322.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1157</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>709</identifier>
<identifier>ryeedp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/ffu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Final_Fantasy:_Unlimited</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>FF：U_〜ファイナルファンタジー:アンリミテッド〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4937</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1539" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-26">
<name>loner</name>
<description>A characters who avoids or does not actively seek human interaction or prefers to be alone, either because they prefer solitude and independence and are content to have very limited social interaction, or because they are forced to be isolated because they are rejected by society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3513" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>special bullet</name>
<description>Custom made bullets that have special effects (and often shapes, too), which take action when hitting the enemy/ally.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3771" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>recycled animation -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag overlaps recaps, http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks], and http://anidb.net/t3671 [footage reuse]. For that reason, it is set to be split. If you can, please apply the correct tag to the anime that have it, and remove this one from them; guidance on how to use each of those tags can be found in their description. If what the anime contains is a mere recap, please don`t apply any tag at all, and remove this tag from it instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18274" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Chobi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chobi is one of the birds of happiness that lives in Wonderland. He becomes emotionally attached to Yu after Yu finds a Chocobo feather in the forest. Chobi joins them on their journey and always knows when the Subway will be arriving next.</description>
<picture>48843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18275" type="main character in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Ai Hayakawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ai Hayakawa is the daughter of Joe and Marie Hayakawa, who travelled to Wonderland with her younger (said because she is more mature, they are actually the same age) twin brother, Yu, in search of their lost parents. She is an energetic and intensely curious little girl who is very positive and outgoing. But, her good moods don`t last too long. Ai loves creepy, cute things like her gift from Fabula, Poshepocket, with whom she fell in love with at first sight.</description>
<picture>48845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18276" type="main character in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Yuu Hayakawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuu Hayakawa is Ai`s younger twin brother. Always sure to introduce himself when he meets someone new, he shows no signs of shyness, even towards someone like Kaze (who is surrounded by such an unapproachable aura). Yuu tends to act like an adult in that he always proceeds with caution along their journey. But he also has an innocent, childish side that can be seen in such acts as mindlessly chasing cute animals like Chocobo. Through the use of Penna, he can converse with Chobi.</description>
<picture>48846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18277" type="main character in" update="2019-07-29">
<rating votes="2">8.71</rating>
<name>Lisa Pacifist</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ai and Yu first meet the 22-year-old Lisa Pacifist in the subway, where she decides to help the twins search for their parents in Wonderland. She is able to manipulate spirits found in nature through the use of her Kigen Arts and uses this power to protect the two twins from the various monsters of Wonderland. Ai believes that Lisa came to Wonderland in search of her boyfriend, but her true reason for coming is still a mystery...</description>
<picture>48847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18278" type="main character in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Kuroki Kaze</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known to the villains as Black Wind or Kaze, this silent, expressionless man defeats monsters once he thaws the `Magun` on his right arm, which fires summons. All of his memories of the past have been lost, and he walks through life without knowing who or what he is. The only thing he is sure about in his life is his fight with Makenshi, longing to settle things finished between them.</description>
<picture>48848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18279" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Makenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Also known as White Cloud (白い雲, Shiroi Kumo) to Kaze, Makenshi (魔剣士) is a silent mysterious figure working for Gaudium at his leisure, but seems to have his own agenda. He has no interest in fighting Kaze, and only acts in self-defence whenever Kaze engages him.</description>
<picture>48849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18280" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Poshepocket</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Poshepocket is the living pocket creature of Wonderland. He can store away huge amounts of objects in his mouth and also spit up very useful items. From time to time, whenever he feels like it, he mutters in unintelligible speech.</description>
<picture>48949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18281" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Lou Lupus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lou Lupus is a little girl whose homeland was destroyed by Omega, the surviving member of a race that has the ability in transform into a werewolf when they gaze into a reflection of their own eyes. As Lou was the last of her kind, she used a mirror to invoke her transformation and use her super-high frequency wave howling attack. She traveled in search of a place where she belongs, meeting the twins and Lisa on the Subway when they are attacked by Omega. But after Kaze saves them, she falls in love with him and decides her place is by Kaze`s side, mortally wounded in the final battle with the Earl as a result before she offers what little life she had to help him.</description>
<picture>48850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="667" picture="32842.jpg">Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18282" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Knave</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Knave is the leader of the Comodeen, the rebel faction against Earl Tyrant, but is a romantic by nature. He wields a bazooka and a gatling gun.</description>
<picture>48851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4686" picture="171399.jpg">Hori Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18283" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Cid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cid is a member of the Comodeen. A genius inventor, Cid can make anything, which includes the Wonderland Watch that Chobi wears, the Subway, and even a Submarine. He gives each of his inventions a woman`s name and loves them dearly. However, due to his love for them, if they receive even the slightest scratch, his personality changes drastically, and he attacks the opponent in a rage. Normally, he is a pleasant young man who uses gentle and polite speech, even towards the kids Ai and Yuu.</description>
<picture>48852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18284" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="1">6.64</rating>
<name>Miles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miles is a high-ranking female member of the Comodeen. She`s tanned and has purple hair. She`s a tough girl and helps Ai change her clothes the 1st time they meet each other. She`s usually seen carrying out the attacks for the Comodeen. She also seems to have a crush on Cid, who kissed her when he is turned into a frog and was transformed back. Since then, she gets very flustered and happy whenever Cid talks to her.</description>
<picture>48853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18285" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Fungo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fungo is a refugee welcomed into the Comodeen. In his first appearance, he steals and eats Ai`s backpack, leading them to the Comodeen`s base when caught. As the group set off in Cid`s submarine to catch up to the interdimensional train, he steals Yuu`s backpack with intent to eat it. Seemingly not good for anything, it is revealed that he does have one special ability: the good news is that Fungo can sense danger before it happens; the bad news is that Fungo can only sense danger seconds before it happens. It is revealed in Cactus: The Wandering Sea that he can understand Cactuars.</description>
<picture>48948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18286" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Tyrant Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Earl Tyrant is the main antagonist of Final Fantasy: Unlimited and the ruler of Wonderland. though he has the appearance of a spoiled child, the Earl is actually an avatar of Chaos, the entity that attacked the worlds that Wonderland is composed of. The Earl enforces his iron-fisted rule of Wonderland through his four Lords of Gaudium, installing negative emotions among minon and denizen alike for nourishment while going after the pieces of Omega to become a god and rule all existence.</description>
<picture>48854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18287" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Oscha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oscha is one of the four Lords of Gaudium. The most mysterious of the four, he serves as Tyrant`s primary advisor. Oscha appears as living shadow of a figure with no legs and arms, though arms do protrude from his near-formless body from time to time. He wears a white mask over his face, and his mad eye can usually be seen when the camera pans up close to him. It is apparently revealed that Oscha is in truth a part of Chaos like the Earl, and does the job of ensuring that Chaos is fed constantly with dark emotions. Oscha is able to bring things to life; such as seen with his work on Crux, the puppet used to spy on the protagonists, and also revive dead people; such as seen with Madoushi.
From the very beginning, Oscha knew of Ai and Yu`s true nature, creating Crux and altering the clock on Chobi`s neck to pinpoint the twins` exact locations while having them experience the various horrors and tragic event across the series, maturing them so when they can be fused with the Earl, Chaos would reach its zenith and evolve. But the plan failed and Oscha falls down into Chaos as his mask is cracked, but he survived. In FFU:After, Oscha helped to revive the Gaudium and search for new Deathlords, leaving Soljashy to make Chaos Rulers, the Earl`s successor, out of the Hayakawa Twins.</description>
<picture>48855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18288" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Fungus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Appearing as a mushroom humanoid, Fungus is one of the four Lords of Gaudium and is always seen with a pipe in his mouth. Originally from a world of mushrooms, Fungus was a general until a mysterious mushroom-eating mold manifested on his world by Chaos. Only Fungus survived and became a servant of the Earl. Fungus is virtually immortal, and will always reappear after losing a fight against Kaze, though as a 1/10th miniature of himself and must wait for some time before regaining his original stature.
When the Lords of Gaudium were sent to find the innate pieces of Omega, Fungus failed to find any. Fungus was desperate to impress the Earl, losing his trust from each losing battle. However, Oscha offers to give Fungus a edge against Kaze by bring him to what remained of his homeworld. There Fungus draws power from his homeworld during his fight with Kaze, regenerating into a giant. However, though he was winning, the Earl and Oscha planned to dispose of the useless Fungus by using the same mold that destroyed his world to finish the job and infect him. Seeing him in misery, Kaze ended his suffering with Fungus thanking him in his final moments and acknowledging him to be the better man.</description>
<picture>48856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18289" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Herba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Herba is one of the Four Lords of Gaudium with the appearance of a humanoid plant woman. She is considered Earl Tyrant`s favorite and usually sits besides him on his throne. She carries an umbrella and is usually accompanied by her pet Hug-Hug. She has a habit of adding the word, "baby" behind a person`s name if she likes them. She draws her power from plants. In the end of the anime, Herba falls into Chaos, but in FFU:After, it`s revealed that she actually survived to become Princess Herba. She assumes her role as Chaos` agent by using her plants to feed Chaos until the Hayakawa twins Yu and Ai assume their chosen role as Chaos Rulers.
Furthermore, she was responsible for transforming Dolk, Lisa Pacifist`s lover and part of the C2 Organization which she works for, into Soljashy, the first Lord of Gaudium under her. Soljashy is part of Herba`s plot to feed Chaos. She retreated into Wonderland after manipulating Lisa to open the portal to that world.</description>
<picture>48857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18290" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Pist Shaz 11 Sei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pist Shaz XI is another of the four Lords of Gaudium, Pist played the role as an annoying villain quite well. A shark-humanoid with a body of water, its mouth is at the back. An arrogant, over-confident and boastful individual, Pist is also unfortunately intelligent, collecting the data from previous battles and analyzes them to prepare for the next one. He drives a convertible with a pool inside, and goes by his annoying laugh - shashasha! Pist resides in an underwater castle made of corals somewhere. Arriving to Gaudium while still busy on his project, Pist decides to handle Kaze, succeeding to steal Kaze`s Magun`s power but failed to use the Magun as his own. Though he lost, Pist`s revealing Omega`s stirring made up for it.
Pist later played a bigger role after the demise of Fungus, completing his masterpiece: The Ocean Puzzle, a Rubik`s Cube like dimension that entrapped the protagonists, sending them to a part on Wonderland where they had to pass a challenge to continue or be destroyed. However, the protagonists manage to survive each of his puzzles, forcing him to confront them when they arrived to Telos.
Using Blue Elenium, a compound made of Elenium, Pist was able to alter the summons called upon by Kaze; in this case, he turned the Giga Phoenix into a destructive summon that starts to destroy Telos, much to the Earl`s dismay. However, Makenshi appears and destroys the summon with his Mist powers, and Pist was forced to retreat in spite of Telos` destruction ensured. Back in his lair, Pist was almost about to gather all the Omega crystals within his Ocean Puzzle when Makenshi intervened. Though confident in himself, Makenshi defeats Pist by turning him into Mist, using Pist as Mist Dragon to destroy the Ocean Puzzle, causing all the Omega crystals but Clear to be destroyed, forestalling the Earl`s evil plans.</description>
<picture>48858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18291" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Madoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madoushi is the older brother of Makenshi, looking similar except for his red clothes and hair. Originally his younger brother`s only friend, Madoushi taught Makenshi everything he knew in the art of combat. Much to Madoushi`s dismay, however, Makenshi outdid him in swordsmanship. As a result, Madoushi felt himself to be in his younger brother`s shadow and wanted to see who was stronger, even after he died when Chaos attacked their world to prove himself stronger.
He initially appears as part of Oscha`s plot to stall the protagonists on the Ocean Puzzle, however it was to feed Chaos with Makenshi`s horror of facing his own brother as Madoushi had intended to see once and for all who was the greater brother. But Makenshi was reluctantly forced to take his brother down for good. Makenshi still thinks about Madoushi, wondering if his brother intended the fight to go that way.
After Chaos is defeated, Crux discovered Madoushi`s grave in the ruins of Misteria. There she discovers a crystal that contained Madoushi`s power, and by instinct sought to give it to Makenshi. With the crystal, Makenshi receives his brother`s power.</description>
<picture>48859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18292" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Crux</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Crux is a small fairy marionette brought to life by Oscha whose job it is to spy on Kaze the Hayakawa twins Yu and Ai. She will then report her findings to Oscha or whichever of the Lords of Gaudium is around.
Crux`s entire vocabulary is made up of "kukuruyu". Periodically abused by the Lords of Gaudium, Crux developed feelings for Makenshi when he saved her life. Crux rebelled against Oscha and helped the protagonists during the battle against Chaos Tyrant.
After the battle, Crux carried Makenshi away and tended to his wounds. She later becomes his traveling companion. Crux was damaged by Crux Number-2 when she found Madoushi`s grave. Crux received a gem from Makenshi`s older brother Madoushi, which contains his very power, from his grave. From this Makenshi learns the mist powers of his brother, and Crux is able to transform into the Cross Sword, Makenshi`s secondary weapon.</description>
<picture>48860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18293" type="appears in" update="2011-04-20">
<name>Soljashy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Wonderland Consultant", Soljashy was formally Dolk of the C2 Organization, the agency that sent Lisa searching for the Hayakawa professors. He and Lisa were once in love, but he has been captured by Herba and now works for Chaos as Soljashy. He fights by sticking his business cards onto objects, transforming them into monsters. Despite everyone`s attempts to restore Soljashy to his former self, the man who was once Dolk is no more — Soljashy is merely a parasitic entity using Dolk`s body and feeding on the man`s life. The real Soljashy is the briefcase his host carried. Soljashy is charged with the task of having Ai &amp; Yuu assume their "rightful" positions as the Chaos Rulers by any means needed, even using those they care about to his advantage.
He succeeds in making Gaudium and Chaos a beacon of hope and light for those in despair, winning the loyalty of most of the world while promoting egotism for Chaos to feed. However, he is mortally wounded by Makenshi and blasted by Kaze. Dolk is freed, though on the brink of death due to Soljashy taking most of his life. Kaze kills Dolk despite Lisa`s pleas. Dolk becomes the soil Chain Gold.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18294" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Fabula</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Referring to herself as a guide, Fabula plays the role of the storyteller, giving a brief synopsis of the previous episode at the beginning, and "prophecizing" (basically giving a preview) the next episode. Living within an oyster shell filled with pearls and that are able to sprout wings, Fabula rarely gets herself involved.
Ai encounters Fabula during the Hayakawa twins` stop at the Village of Fruit world. Ai had lost her bag, which was stolen and eaten by Fungo. There, Fabula gives her PoshePocket to replace her bag, and disappears immediately after giving Ai some advice. She makes another appearance when Omega attacked the subway where Lisa Pacifist and the twins rode to obtain its piece inside the train. Using her house, Fabula carried the Ghost Train`s last card to safety, carrying them to the Comodeen`s base.
At the end of the anime, she hints on a continuation of the story, and gives a cryptic message to Ai when she and her family returned to their world after Earl Tyrant`s defeat.</description>
<picture>48861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18295" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Chocobaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chocobaba is the old lady who loves Chocobos. In response to Lisa, Yuu, and Ai`s questions she responds with nothing but, "I have no clue", or "At least that`s the rumor". They cannot have much of a conversation with her.</description>
<picture>48862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3968" picture="22867.jpg">Mizuhara Rin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18296" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Chocoimo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chocoimo is Chocobaba`s (slightly) younger sister. She commands a flock of Chocobos and is on a journey in search of the legendary Ciel. Her stock phrases are, "Let me see..." and "Or something like that", make her no different from Chocobaba in conversation problems.</description>
<seiyuu id="3968" picture="22867.jpg">Mizuhara Rin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18297" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<name>Sagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagi is a little boy who appears in the room where Dead Peppers grew in Herba`s Mansion. He actually turns out to be the manifestation of a Sagiso Flower that Lisa had raised as a child and was forced to leave when she moved to her mother`s home, with Lisa feeling guilty for not recognizing Sagi until it was too late. In the language of flowers, the Sagiso means "my thoughts will follow you into your dreams".</description>
<picture>53355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18298" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Aura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aura was Kaze`s younger sister in their world of Windaria. When Chaos destroyed their world, Aura was mortally wounded. She offered to turn herself into Soil for Kaze to use to fight Chaos as Gun Dragon. Aura apparently had a relationship with Makenshi. She only appears in the series in flashbacks.</description>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18299" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<name>Bolbol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bolbol is a tailor living in Teros who uses the Flying Water to create clothing allowing the wearer to fly... and charges ridiculously exorbitant prices for it. He has been known to offer his handiwork free of charge, but only on two known occasions: creating a cape for Lou, and a full body suit with gloves for Clear.</description>
<picture>53354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18300" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Omega</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The absolute antagonistic plot device of FF:U, Omega is a mysterious being who can destroy everything around it simply by being nearby, though whether it is truly malevolent or not is unknown. Prior to the series, Omega`s body is scattered into many pieces across Wonderland in the form of living, but dormant crystals. However, when a piece of Omega is active, it is intent to find its "siblings" and fuse with them to recreate Omega, attacking anything that would interfere. Due to Omega`s power, its pieces are targeted by the series` antagonists as part of the Earl`s plan.</description>
<picture>48863.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18301" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-14">
<name>Clear</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bluish iridescent boy with green hair, Clear is a quiet and shy person who`s actually the heart of Omega. He ended up in Teros where he stayed until Bolbol made him a cloak of Flying Water to cover his entire body and hold his power at bay. Clear hates himself for destroying everything he touches.
It was by fate that he encounters Ai after she had fallen off the submarine in the Ocean Puzzle. Clear tried to steer clear of Ai out of fear of killing her by accident. At that moment, Pist sends his minions; three strange creatures, to hunt down Clear. They manage to find him, but Clear successfully flees with Ai. Safe in a cave, Clear introduces himself to Ai as a part of Omega, in search of his "siblings", which are the Omega pieces. Kaze then discovers the two and attempts to destroy Clear because of his nature, but Ai objects. Just then, Pist`s three minions appeared again, and caught Ai. Clear manages to save her, but his glove came off in the struggle, unleashing his destructive power. Ai was then saved by Lisa and Yuu on Chobi, leaving Clear behind to be caught.
Later, when Clear was last piece of Omega in existence, he was fused with his Flying Water suit to create a stable crystal for Earl Tyrant to absorb. In the series aftermath, Clear`s crystal is retrieved by Crux and given to Makenshi in FF:U After, who entrusts it to Ai in the After Spiral. Clear was inserted into the Airship Sylvia to serve in the ship`s Flying Water Recycling System.</description>
<picture>53356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18302" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Joe Hayakawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Originally an ordinary geologist, Joe Hayakawa became one of the world`s leading researchers in the field of Wonderland physics after the Pillar of Darkness appeared. After traveling once to Wonderland, he came back and published the book called "Day of Conjunction", about his experiences.</description>
<picture>48865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18303" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<name>Marie Hayakawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marie Hayakawa is the mother of Ai and Yuu, she is Joe`s wife who she assists him in his research. When Joe and Marie once again go back into Wonderland, their whereabouts become unknown.</description>
<picture>48866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18304" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-31">
<name>Kupo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1272" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイ -クリアとのであい-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ai: Meeting with Clear</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ai - Rencontre avec Clear</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Аи. Встреча с Клиром</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai -Clear to no Deai-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1273" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔道士 -きりとくものたいけつ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Madoushi: The Battle of Kiri and Kumo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Madoushi - La bataille de Kiri et Kumo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мадоси. Битва братьев</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madoushi -Kiri to Kumo no Taiketsu-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1274" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カエル -ちっちゃなだいぼうけん-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frog: The Smallest Great Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Grenouille - L`épopée miniature</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Лягушка. Самое опасное приключение</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaeru -Chitchana Daibouken-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1275" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氣現獣 -えがおのむこうに-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kigen Summon: Behind the Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Invocation du Kigen - Derrière le sourire</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Дракон Кигэндзитсу. Прочь улыбки</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kigenjuu -Egao no Mukou ni-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1276" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェーン -うごきだすうみパズル-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jane: The Moving Ocean Puzzle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jane - Le jeu du puzzle de l`océan</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Джейн. Океаническая головоломка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jane -Ugokidasu Umi Puzzle-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1277" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オメガ -さいかいとたびだち-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Omega: Reunion and Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Omega - Retrouvailles et séparations</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Омега. Воссоединение и исчезновение</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omega -Saikai to Tabidachi-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1278" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オスカー -おわりなきしごと-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oscar: The Endless Project</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Oscar - Le travail sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Оска. Бесконечный труд</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oscar -Owarinaki Shigoto-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1279" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メテオ -いまわしききおく-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meteor: Abominable Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Météore - L`abominable souvenir</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Метеор. Ужасные воспоминания</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meteo -Imawashiki Kioku-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1280" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソイル -マガンのしんぞう-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soil: The Heart of the Magun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terre - Le cœur du magun</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Соил. Сердце Магана</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soil -Magun no Shinzou-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1281" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フングス -えいえんのいのち-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fungus: Eternal Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fungus - La vie éternelle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Фунгус. Вечная жизнь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fungus -Eien no Inochi-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1282" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下鉄 -じげんトンネルのてき-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Subway: Enemy of the Dimensional Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Métro - L`ennemi du tunnel dimensionnel</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Подземка. Враг тоннеля измерений</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikatetsu -Jigen Tunnel no Teki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1283" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シエル -チョコボとのわかれ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ciel: The Departure of Chocobo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ciel - Le départ du chocobo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Поднебесный. Прощание с чокобо</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ciel -Chocobo to no Wakare-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1284" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氣現術 -いのちまもるもの-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kigen Arts: The Saviour of Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kigen - Celui qui protège les âmes</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кигэндзитсу. Спаситель душ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kigenjutsu -Inochi Mamorumono-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1285" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">屋敷 -サギソウのおもいで-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mansion: The Memory of Sagiso</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Citadelle - Les souvenirs d`une orchidée</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Особняк. Воспоминания орхидеи</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yashiki -Sagisou no Omoide-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1286" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シド -ちかすいみゃくのぼうけん-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cid: The Adventure of the Underground Waterway</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cid - La rivière souterraine</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сид. Вояж по подземным каналам</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cid -Chikasuimyaku no Bouken-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1287" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風 -いのちかがやくとき-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaze: The Glory of Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kaze - À la gloire de la vie</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кадзе. Торжество жизни</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze -Inochi Kagayaku Toki-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1288" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔剣士 -しろきエチュード-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Makenshi: The White Etude</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Makenshi - L`étude en blanc</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Макенси. Белое Облако</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makenshi -Shiroki Etude-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1289" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">混沌 -はくしゃくのしょうたい-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaos: The Earl Unveiled</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaos - Le comte dévoilé</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Хаос. Разоблачение Графа</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konton -Hakushaku no Shoutai-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1290" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">果実 -あまいかおりのまち-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fruit: The Town of Sweet Scent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fruit - La ville au doux parfum</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Плод. Город сладких ароматов</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kajitsu -Amai Kaori no Machi-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1291" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テロス -とびみずをめざして-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teros: In Search of Flying Water</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Teros - En quête de l`eau volante</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Терос. В поисках летучей воды</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teros -Tobimizu o Mezashite-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1292" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔銃 -くろきかぜのおとこ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magun: Man of the Black Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Magun - L`homme du vent noir</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Маган. Чёрный Ветер</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magun -Kuroki Kaze no Otoko-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1293" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モーグリ -なつかしいおもいで-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moogle: Long Lost Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Moogle - Les souvenirs perdus</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мугл. Давно утерянные воспоминания</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moglie -Natsukashii Omoide-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1294" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異界 -やみへのたびだち-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wonderland: Journey into the Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des merveilles - Voyage vers les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Страна Чудес. Путешествие во тьму</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikai -Yami e no Tabidachi-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1295" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サボテン -さまよえるうみ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cactus: The Wandering Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cactus - La mer vagabonde</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кактус. Блуждающее море</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saboten -Samayoeru Umi-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1296" update="2010-05-19">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユウ -ガウディウムのひみつ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yu: The Secret of Gaudium</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yu - Le secret de Gaudium</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ю. Тайна Гаудиума</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuu -Gaudium no Himitsu-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45067" update="2005-12-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">German DVD Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84515" update="2016-02-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84591" update="2016-02-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91213" update="2008-06-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
