<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1586" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-12-21</startdate>
<enddate>1991-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shuten Douji</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Star Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shuten Doji: The Star Hand Kid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shutendoji</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shutendouji</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">手天童子</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shuten Doji</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="892" type="Animation Work">Studio Signal</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="6622" type="Music">Anzai Fumitaka</name>
</creators>
<description>Jiro Shutendo has always seemed a bit unusual. He lives in a nice house, goes to school, and even has a girlfriend... but somehow he still feels different from his friends and schoolmates. As Jiro looks into the mirror one day, he is shocked to find two little horns growing out of his head! It had never occured to Jiro that he`s not human at all to start with. More trouble brews as mysterious creatures suddenly kidnap Jiro`s girlfriend Miyuki. When Jiro tries to save her, his true nature and supernatural powers manifest. He must now travel through time and space to discover the origin of his birth and defeat the mysterious creatures that are wreaking havoc. It`s an all out battle between darkness and light, and Jiro is the ultimate warrior.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="152">4.05</permanent>
<temporary count="152">5.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>240371.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2804</identifier>
<identifier>ihqsrp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shutendoji_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>手天童子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88687</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2572</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2685" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>Heian period</name>
<description>Last division of classical Japanese history, covering the time period from 794 to 1185.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37427" type="main character in" update="2011-10-06">
<rating votes="2">7.61</rating>
<name>Shutendou Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4932" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37428" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-06">
<rating votes="3">8.08</rating>
<name>Shiratori Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37429" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Shiba Ryuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37430" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-06">
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<name>Shiba Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4594" picture="77604.jpg">Takagi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37432" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="2">9.61</rating>
<name>Goki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37433" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="2">8.52</rating>
<name>Senki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37434" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Hyoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3259" picture="151716.jpg">Tanaka Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37435" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<name>Tanemura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37436" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Majari Younen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1658" picture="203223.jpg">Kobayashi Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37440" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Kitani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37441" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Jawanbou Kukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3305" picture="47438.jpg">Arakawa Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37442" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Kaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65615.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37443" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Ooyama Naojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37444" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Shiratori Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37445" type="appears in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Ricky</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37446" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Doctor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3360" picture="24707.jpg">Yada Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37447" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<name>Beth Alonzo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65688.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37448" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="2">6.41</rating>
<name>Mohammed Persis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5058" picture="43359.jpg">Yoshida Rihoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37449" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Castello Sonya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37450" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<name>Pacheko Leo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37451" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Alfard</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>65727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37453" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<name>Iron Caesar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37454" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="2">1.49</rating>
<name>Ramsey Gil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37455" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Zimmerman Lloyd</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3259" picture="151716.jpg">Tanaka Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="38371" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1989-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憑鬼の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter of Hyoki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouki no Shou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38372" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1990-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">降魔の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter of Goma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouma no Shou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38373" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1991-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉄鬼の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter of Tekki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tekki no Shou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38374" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1991-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼獄の章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter of Ongoku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ongoku no Shou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
