<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1596" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1979-03-17</startdate>
<enddate>1979-03-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">SF Saiyuuki Starzinger (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">SF Saiyuki: Starzinger (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">SF西遊記 スタージンガー (1979)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1595" type="Prequel">SF Saiyuuki Starzinger II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
</creators>
<description>Princess Aurora, the only survivor of her planet destroyed by evil mutants, is resolved to put an end to the mutant menace in the galaxy along with three enhanced human cyborgs Jesse Dart, Porkos and Aramus, she travels space in the Cosmos Queen to the Dekkos System to fight the final battle.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="32">3.88</permanent>
<temporary count="33">5.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>2011.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3629</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17165</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>146638</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>n103</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3459" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-20">
<name>space monsters</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3752" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>Journey to the West</name>
<description>Journey to the West is a classic Chinese mythological novel. It was written during the Ming Dynasty based on traditional folk tales. Consisting of 100 chapters, this fantasy relates the adventures of a Tang Dynasty priest Sanzang and his three disciples, Monkey, Pig and Friar Sand, as they travel west in search of Buddhist Sutra. Several anime are loosely based on its story, most famously Dragon Ball.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16615" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<name>Jan Coogo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jan Kugo grew up alone and abandoned, but dreamed of becoming a space pilot, despite knowing that his background would make this difficult. When he learned that a certain professor Dodge needed a subject for a scientific experiment, aiming at creating a super strong cyborg, Kugo volunteered.
Jan Kugo is short-tempered and violent, carefree and fearless. He enjoys battle and kills without hesitation. But though seemingly ruthless and sometimes cruel, deep down he has a heart of gold.
He flies the vessel Starcrow and wields the Astro-lance.
His character is based on the monkey-demon, Sun Wukong.</description>
<picture>46149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16616" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Sir Jogo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most intelligent of the three cyborgs accompanying Orora Hime on her travel. When in doubt he asks his portable computer (which often displays TOEI logo while elaborating a problem).
He flies the vessel Starcopper (equipped for both space and underwater travels) and fights with the Laser-Trident.
His character is based on the water-demon, Sha Wujing.</description>
<picture>46151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3252" picture="24231.jpg">Tomiyama Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16617" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Don Hakka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Before joining the crew of Queen Cosmos, Don Haka had the role of protector of his planet and people. He is a cheerful, constantly hungry cyborg with a big heart.
He flies the vessel Starbood (equipped with a powerful drill to be able to travel underground as well as in space) and fights with a mace, that turns into a flail when swung.
His character is based on the pig-demon, Zhu Bajie.</description>
<picture>46152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3301" picture="24327.jpg">Tomita Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16618" type="main character in" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Aurora-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aurora-hime used to live on the Earth`s moon, which was then a peaceful place. During an attack by space monsters, the moon was devastated, leaving Aurora as the only survivor.
When the energy of the galaxy begins to weaken, Aurora is chosen by Earth`s professor Kitty to travel to the Great King planet to restore it, due to her ability to channel the energy.
Her character is based on Xuanzang.</description>
<picture>46153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17444" update="2010-04-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116351" update="2010-02-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
