<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1611" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-02-21</startdate>
<enddate>1995-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">DNA2: Dokoka de Nakushita Aitsu no Aitsu (1995)</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Algo acerca de ti que perdí en algún lugar OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">dna2 ova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">DNA^2 OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">D・N・A²~何処かで失くしたあいつのアイツ~ (1995)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">DNA2 OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">DNA² OAV</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="81" type="Prequel">DNA2: Dokoka de Nakushita Aitsu no Aitsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="866" type="Original Work">Katsura Masakazu</name>
<name id="3331" type="Character Design">Takahashi Kumiko</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="3568" type="Direction">Sakata Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="14119" type="Music">Takano Fujio</name>
</creators>
<description>Junta`s great granddaughter goes back in time in order to ascertain that http://anidb.net/ch15952 [Junta] stays the Mega-Playboy — to ensure her continued existence in the future. She is accompanied by an old man, who has his own nefarious reasons for wanting to keep Junta the Mega-Playboy forever.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1203">4.12</permanent>
<temporary count="1211">6.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>88382.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3215</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3630</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dna2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3053" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-23">
<name>allergy to potential love interests</name>
<description>A character will be found responding to potential love interests, usually of the opposite gender, as if allergic to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15952" type="main character in" update="2014-05-07">
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<name>Momonari Junta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school boy with a peculiar allergy to girls: he vomits when sexually aroused. He gains the ability to transform into the Mega-Playboy practically at will, after being shot by Karin`s first DCM bullet. Junta also gains psychic powers along with his Mega-Playboy charm, this includes the ability to teleport and telekinesis.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>44849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15953" type="main character in" update="2010-03-18">
<rating votes="20">7.66</rating>
<name>Aoi Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sixteen-year old DNA Operator from the overcrowded future, sent back in time in order to prevent the advent of the Mega-Playboy using DNA Control Medicine. All she wants out of life is a nice husband, a cute pet, and a sweet home.
From Wikipedia</description>
<picture>44850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15954" type="main character in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="10">5.38</rating>
<name>Kurimoto Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ami when not at school, spends most of her time working in her father`s resturant, Kurinoan. She is Junta Momonari`s childhood friend and secretly loves him, but tries to hide it from everyone, including herself. She is the only girl who doesn`t bring about an allergic reaction in Junta, and additionally the only girl immune to the Mega-Playboy`s ability to seduce women. The last is something Karin considers a key part in the plan to stop the Mega-Playboy: if Junta and Ami stay together, she can nullify the Mega-Playboy`s charms and the future won`t be overcrowded.</description>
<picture>44907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="167" picture="16972.jpg">Kasahara Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15955" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-18">
<rating votes="12">4.70</rating>
<name>Saeki Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Miss Fukoma High and the most popular girl in Junta`s school. Tomoko is also the ex-girlfriend of Ryuji. She falls in love with Junta because of his Mega-Playboy powers (in fact, these powers manifest for the first time in front of her). Apart of this, she`s a quite lonely girl; her mother died and her father works abroad.</description>
<picture>44852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15956" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="12">5.36</rating>
<name>Takanashi Kotomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotomi is a shy friend of Ami`s who has a gas problem. Whenever she gets nervous, and her stomach gets upset, she farts. She also falls for the Mega-Playboy. Junta helps her overcome her problem, so that she can compete in a rhythmic gymnastics competition.
From AnimeNfo</description>
<picture>44908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2142" picture="170565.jpg">Shiina Hekiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15998" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-21">
<rating votes="2">1.03</rating>
<name>Sugashita Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuji is Tomoko`s boyfriend in the beginning of the series, but later loses her to the Mega-Playboy, turning him utterly against Junta. Through an odd quirk of events he eventually gains some rather unique abilities. He uses these "powers" to ruin Junta`s reputation... Ryuji is very rich, and lives in an extremely large mansion. He also has several "henchmen" whom he employs to do his dirty work.
From AnimeNfo</description>
<picture>44995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69066" type="appears in" update="2014-07-31">
<name>Yokomori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3299" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69067" type="appears in" update="2014-07-31">
<name>Oharu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1811" picture="222844.jpg">Yamada Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17464" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一つのタイムマシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Time Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une autre machine temporelle.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un`altra macchina del tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouhitotsu no Time Machine</title>
<summary>In order to do "follow-up reports" on Junta, Karin`s back from the future, and she`s out to have a blast! Junta and Ryuji seem to be doing fine, and their DNA is returning to normal. But it seems there`s another actor on this stage, and he`s arriving from the future, too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>680629</identifier>
<identifier>dna2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="17465" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">100年後の忘れもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Something Forgotten 100 Years Later</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quelque chose oublié 100 ans plus tard.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un qualcosa lasciato 100 anni nel futuro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">100 Nengo no Wasuremono</title>
<summary>Mori, the man from the future, reveals his master plan to Karin, but she isn`t about to let him have his way! Meanwhile, Junta confronts his own descendent, come to visit him from the future. But she doesn`t seem to be on great grandfather`s side!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>680631</identifier>
<identifier>dna2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="17466" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくはあなたを忘れない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Never Forget You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne t`oublierai jamais.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Non ti dimenticherò mai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Anata o Wasurenai</title>
<summary>The final confrontation begins. Mori has total control over Junta, and things seem grim. It`s up to Karin to remind Junta that his DNA doesn`t control him--and she`d better do it fast, because his Mega-Playboy genes aren`t playing around!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>680633</identifier>
<identifier>dna2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122331" update="2010-09-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122332" update="2010-09-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
