<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1612" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2004-06-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shinkon Gattai Godannar!! Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shinkon Gattai Godannar Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Marriage of God &amp; Soul Godannar!! Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">신혼합체 고단나 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shinkon Gattai Godannar 2nd</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">godannar2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SGG S2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神魂合体ゴーダンナー!!-SECOND SEASON-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Marriage of God &amp; Soul Godannar!! (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Godannar!! (suite)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1104" type="Prequel">Shinkon Gattai Godannar!!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/godannar2/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="910" type="Animation Work">AIC A.S.T.A</name>
<name id="665" type="Character Design">Kimura Takahiro</name>
<name id="3718" type="Series Composition">Kawasaki Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4234" type="Direction">Nagaoka Yasuchika</name>
<name id="5209" type="Music">Watanabe Chuumei</name>
</creators>
<description>Recap: Five years ago, while battling an alien force known as the Mimetic Beasts, Dannar pilot http://anidb.net/ch12088 [Saruwatari Goo] first met http://anidb.net/ch12089 [Aoi Anna]. Today, on the day of their wedding, the ceremony is interrupted when the Mimetic Beasts strike again. As Goo struggles in his battle against the alien threat, http://anidb.net/ch12091 [Saruwatari Anna] stumbles upon a top secret robot known as the Neo Okusaer and uses it as a last-resort to save her fiancé. Once again Dannar and Neo-Okusaer combine to become the mighty robot Godannar. (Source: ANN)
After the previous events, when Anna is shocked to see http://anidb.net/ch34988 [Mira], Goo`s former partner, piloting the Neo Okusaer, and the Mimetic Beasts have started a worldwide attack on mankind...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="515">5.26</permanent>
<temporary count="521">7.00</temporary>
<review count="2">7.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>78597.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1104</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1337</identifier>
<identifier>gzelam</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Godannar</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神魂合体ゴーダンナー!!_SECOND_SEASON</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>320008</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6704</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/166</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2004/godannar_ss</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-16">
<name>smoker</name>
<description>This character likes to smoke cigarettes, cigars or a pipe.</description>
<picurl>227708.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2259" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>naked apron</name>
<description>A character wearing nothing but an apron appears in the show.</description>
<picurl>162045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>bridge bunnies</name>
<description>A term and English nickname describing the attractive girls who manage the various functions aboard a ship`s/starship`s bridge area. 
Although it originated in reference to characters from Macross, it does not exist among Japanese fans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12088" type="main character in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="3">8.81</rating>
<name>Saruwatari Goo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The hero of the story and pilot of Godannar. Prior to the start of the series, he rescues Anna in a battle with the Mimetic beasts. Five years later, Goh and Anna are to be married just as the Mimetic beasts begin to move once again, he is infected by the Insania virus, due to exposure from repeated battles with the Mimetic Beast. His body is covered in a cocoon, waiting to emerge as a Mimetic Beast. He is placed in suspended animation for seven years until he is given a cure—Mira`s blood, which stops his body from transforming. Since he was placed in suspended animation, his hair covered the length of his body. Anna made a promise to him, during the last few episodes, to cut his unkempt hair. She is the first person he sees upon being revived.</description>
<picture>191874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12089" type="appears in" update="2014-10-07">
<rating votes="5">4.66</rating>
<name>Aoi Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl whom Goo rescues at the beginning of the anime.</description>
<picture>61138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12091" type="main character in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="12">6.58</rating>
<name>Saruwatari Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high school student and skilled robot pilot, she was to be married to Goh before the re-emergence of the Mimetic beasts interrupted their ceremony. Becomes the pilot of Neo Okusaer, and later Go Okusaer. She, Goh and Lou form the Godannar Triple Drive when Celleblader fuses with Godannar. After Goh is cured of the Insania virus, using Mira`s blood, she is the first person he sees when he wakes up. She made a promise near the end of the series to cut his hair because it was become long and unkempt. Since his hair was not cut for seven years, it was extremely long: covering the length of his body.</description>
<picture>191875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34983" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<rating votes="4">6.24</rating>
<name>Ellis Valentine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34984" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Saruwatari Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34985" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="7">5.03</rating>
<name>Ekaterina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34986" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Shadow</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34987" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="3">6.30</rating>
<name>Shukuyuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34988" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="8">5.31</rating>
<name>Mira Ackerman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34989" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Moukaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35034" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="3">6.30</rating>
<name>Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35035" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Kouji Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35036" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35037" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Kagemaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35038" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Yanagisawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35045" type="appears in" update="2016-09-29">
<name>Aoi Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35046" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-20">
<rating votes="14">6.80</rating>
<name>Aoi Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65973.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35047" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="15">8.39</rating>
<name>Fujimura Shizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35048" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="6">7.21</rating>
<name>Hayashi Nanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="402" picture="17249.jpg">Katou Nanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35049" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="8">5.51</rating>
<name>Lou Roux</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70536" type="appears in" update="2014-10-07">
<name>Neo Okusar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>10696.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="70538" type="appears in" update="2014-10-07">
<name>Godannar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>10698.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="70539" type="appears in" update="2014-10-07">
<name>Godannar Twin Drive Mode</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>10699.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="70540" type="appears in" update="2014-10-07">
<name>G Gunner</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>10700.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="70541" type="appears in" update="2014-10-07">
<name>Go Okusar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>162437.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85110" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<rating votes="2">6.95</rating>
<name>Momozono Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85111" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<rating votes="2">6.95</rating>
<name>Takaya Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="83" picture="38901.jpg">Nanri Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85112" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Sugiura Hina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85113" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Shino Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85114" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Kukrachyov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85115" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Knight Valentine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85116" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Volspina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191847.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85117" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Goddiner</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191852.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85118" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Genesister</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191853.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85119" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<rating votes="2">3.40</rating>
<name>Morimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85120" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Shibakusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7432" picture="69009.jpg">Horikawa Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85121" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<rating votes="4">6.38</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3003" picture="23748.jpg">Hosokawa Seika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85122" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="6">7.47</rating>
<name>Sasakure Konami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85125" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Sugiyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85126" type="appears in" update="2016-09-27">
<name>Dragliner</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191870.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85141" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Nekota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85180" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Rouza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85182" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Celleblader</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191956.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85183" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Blade Gainer</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191957.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85184" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<name>Cosmo Diver</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85185" type="appears in" update="2016-09-28">
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<name>Blade Gainer Twin Drive Mode</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>191961.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="18833" recap="true" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蘇る魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reviving Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Renaissance de l`âme</title>
<title xml:lang="th">วิญญาณที่หลับไหล</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Tamashii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18834" update="2016-12-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">その名はゴーオクサー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Its Name Is Go Okusaer!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Son nom est Go-Okusaer</title>
<title xml:lang="th">นามนั้นคือ โกอ๊อคซ่า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonona wa Gou Okusaer!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18835" update="2016-12-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouvelle confession</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คำสารภาพรักครั้งใหม่</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18836" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TONKO MY LOVE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tonko, My Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tonko, mon amour</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทงโกะที่รัก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonko My Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18949" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の微笑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ice-Cold Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sourire de glace</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รอยยิ้มเยือกแข็ง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Bishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19210" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェネシスター暴走!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Genesister Out of Control!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Genesister ne répond plus</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เจเนซิสเตอร์คลั่ง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genesister Bousou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19418" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">桃花哀歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorrowful Song of the Plum Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La complainte des fleurs de pêcher</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ลำนำดอกท้อ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touka Aika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23428" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴーダンナー出撃禁止命令!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Godannar Ground Order!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Godannar, à terre !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คำสั่งห้ามโกดันน่าออกปฏิบัติการ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Godannar Shutsugeki Kinshi Meirei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23441" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! ダンナーVSガイナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash! Dannar vs. Gainer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choc ! Dannar contre Gainer !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดันน่าปะทะไกเนอร์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Dannar VS Gainer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23995" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンナーベースSOS!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dannar Base S.O.S.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dannar base, SOS !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดันน่าเบส SOS</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dannar Base S.O.S.!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24825" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Mortal Combat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la fin du combat mortel</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ที่สุดของการต่อสู้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou no Hate ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25506" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠のふたり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Couple</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le couple éternel</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สองเราชั่วนิรันดร์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Futari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25507" update="2011-12-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">来たるべき明日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Inevitable Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lendemain inéluctable</title>
<title xml:lang="th">วันพรุ่งนี้ที่ควรมาถึง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitarubeki Asu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120413" update="2010-07-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
