<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1640" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>38</episodecount>
<startdate>1984-08-11</startdate>
<enddate>1993-03-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cream Lemon</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">くりぃむレモン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Offenders of the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pandora, An Erotic Trilogy</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Brothers Grime X-Rated Cartoons</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Cream Lemon Vol. 1 - Le Mirroir des Perversions - Possesions diaboliques</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">くりいむレモン</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Cream Lemon</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Sonhos Molhados</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4198" type="Alternative Setting">Cream Lemon New Generation</anime>
<anime id="4210" type="Side Story">Cream Lemon: Lemon Angel</anime>
<anime id="7805" type="Side Story">Shin Seiki Cream Lemon</anime>
<anime id="7817" type="Side Story">Tabidachi: Ami Shuushou</anime>
<anime id="281" type="Other">Project A-ko</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="188" approval="3" total="6">Cool Devices Series</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="75334">Different storys: sci-fi, fantasy, slice of life, romance.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://creamlemon.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Co-Production">AIC</name>
<name id="3670" type="Character Design">Kitakubo Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="664" type="Character Design">Ousaka Hiroshi</name>
<name id="22795" type="Original Work">Yui Toshiki</name>
<name id="23505" type="Original Work">Moriyama Tou</name>
<name id="29737" type="Original Work">Amagi Kei</name>
<name id="3670" type="Original Plan">Kitakubo Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4151" type="Direction">Ide Yasunori</name>
<name id="1936" type="Direction">Hirano Toshihiro</name>
<name id="32245" type="Character Design">Mibashi Ayako</name>
<name id="35421" type="Character Design">Motoyama Yuuji</name>
<name id="4287" type="Music">Makaino Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>A collection of short stories, ranging from soap opera (the Ami series) to fantasy (Rall series) to horror (Cream Lemon Dark) to parody (Pop Chaser). It does deal with a lot of heavy perversions ranging from S&amp;M, male rape (by a bunch of females, that is), bondage, torture, yuri (lesbian love) and incest.
~ Description compiled from Hentai Neko and Anime Web Guide
Note 1: Project A-ko was originally intended to be a part of this series.
Note 2: There are several different versions of episode ordering after episode 16 or most commonly after episode 25. That is because episodes 1-16 are bearing the Cream Lemon title, then there are 9 episodes that were released as Shin Cream Lemon (New Cream Lemon), 6 episodes from the so called Ami Series and other special episode releases. AniDB has the episode ordering used on the story section of the official Cream Lemon homepage: http://creamlemon.jp/story/</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="221">5.30</permanent>
<temporary count="234">6.41</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>12986.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4251</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3552</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7083</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17079</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17078</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17077</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17076</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17075</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17074</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3239</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>607</identifier>
<identifier>jaiwyd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://creamlemon.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cream_Lemon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>黒猫館</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>くりいむレモン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>125592</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>125591</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>크림레몬</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="893" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>dominatrix</name>
<description>A dominatrix is a woman, typically a paid professional, who takes the dominant role in BDSM activities. A dominatrix may be of any sexual orientation, which does not necessarily limit the genders of her submissive partners. The role of a dominatrix may not even involve physical pain toward the submissive; her domination can be verbal, involving humiliating tasks, or servitude. The umbrella term for BDSM activities involving a dominatrix is female dominance, female domination, or simply femdom.
Source: Wikipedia.</description>
<picurl>230370.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2225" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>whipping</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2696" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>threesome</name>
<description>Tag for any scene where sexual acts take place with three people of any gender. Should not be used if more than three.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2699" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>sixty-nine</name>
<description>At least one sex position from a group generically called sixty-nine or 69 is featured, characterised by a mutually inverted alignment of two people of any sex in which both perform oral sex simultaneously. Putting it another way, the top of the head of one person points more or less towards the feet of the other, and the head of each is at the height of the other`s genitals, and both perform cunnilingus or fellatio, whichever is appropriate in each case. The name stems from this mutual inversion, which resembles the numbers 6 and 9.</description>
<picurl>162104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2732" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-04">
<name>female rapes female</name>
<description>Both the perpetrator and victim are female; a same-sex rape results.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2899" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-21">
<name>strapon</name>
<description>Employs the use of an artificial phallus so that the female can engage in the penetrating role during intercourse. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t6455 [double-sided dildo].</description>
<picurl>185955.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3299" parentid="6268" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>double fellatio</name>
<description>Double fellatio is when oral sex is performed on the penis simultaneously by two individuals.</description>
<picurl>168623.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6355" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-06">
<name>water sex</name>
<description>Sexual acts taking place in water: i.e. sea, pool, bath, shower, etc.</description>
<picurl>178296.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81320" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="2">3.97</rating>
<name>Caron</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6820" picture="151692.jpg">Miyuki Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81321" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="3">9.72</rating>
<name>Hayakawa Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4204" picture="86092.jpg">Tsunoda Narumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81322" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Komatsuzaki Rie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2362" picture="22137.jpg">Andou Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81323" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Kouno Ryuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3277" picture="192234.jpg">Hashimoto Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81324" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Mako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81325" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34450">Sasaki Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81326" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Nonomura Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2063" picture="127833.jpg">Oikawa Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81327" type="appears in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Bunny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184706.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81328" type="appears in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>School Principal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81329" type="appears in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Zack</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100948" type="main character in" update="2019-04-20">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Watashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230377.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17811" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">媚・妹・Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Be My Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bii Mai Baby</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17814" update="2007-07-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エスカレーション ~今夜はハードコア~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escalation - Hardcore Tonight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Escalation; Kon`ya wa Hardcore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17815" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エスカレーション2 ~禁断のソナタ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escalation 2 - Forbidden Sonata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Escalation 2: Kindan no Sonata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17816" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エスカレーション3 ~天使たちのエピローグ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escalation 3 - Angels` Epilogue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Escalation 3: Tenshi-tachi no Epilogue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17817" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1985-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">POP チェイサー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pop Chaser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pop Chaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17818" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔人形(madol)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evil Doll (Madol)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maningyou (Madol)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17819" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いけないマコちゃん Mako・セクシーシンフォニー後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Do It Mako-chan! Mako Sexy Symphony Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikenai Mako-chan: Mako Sexy Symphony Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17820" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami III</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17821" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なりすスクランブル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nalice Scramble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nalice Scramble</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17822" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超次元伝説 ラル・~ラモー・ルー逆襲~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Dimensional Legend Rall - Lamu Ru`s Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujigen Densetsu Rall: Lamu Ru Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17823" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1987-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">森山塔スペシャル 5時間目のヴィーナス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moriyama Tou Special - 5th Period Venus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moriyama Tou Special: 5 Jikanme no Venus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17824" update="2007-07-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サマーウィンド ~少女たちが運んだ夏~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Wind - Girls` Transported Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Summer Wind: Shoujo-tachi ga Hakonda Natsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17825" update="2008-10-28">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美・それから 第1部 ~哀しみの中で~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami From Then On Part 1 - Within Sadness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami Sore kara Dai 1 Bu: Kanashimi no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17826" update="2011-07-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">STAR TRAP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Star Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Star Trap</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17839" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SF・超次元伝説ラル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SF Super Dimensional Legend Rall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SF Choujigen Densetsu Rall</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17849" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆめいろBUNNY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream-Colored Bunny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume-iro Bunny</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17933" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホワイト・シャドウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">White Shadow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17934" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">e・tude ~雪の鼓動~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Etude - Snowy Heartbeat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Etude: Yuki no Kodou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17935" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美・AGAIN</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami Again</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17936" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパーバージン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Virgin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Super Virgin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17937" update="2011-07-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハプニングサマー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happening Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happening Summer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17938" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒猫館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Cat Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuronekokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17939" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いけないマコちゃん MAKO・セクシーシンフォニー前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Do It Mako-chan! Mako Sexy Symphony Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikenai Mako-chan: Mako Sexy Symphony Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17998" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人のハートブレイクライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two People`s Life of Heartbreak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Heartbreak Life</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17999" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">e・tudeII ~早春コンチェルト~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Etude 2 - Early Spring Concerto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Etude II: Soushun Concerto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18000" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">森山塔スペシャルII 放課後XXX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moriyama Tou Special 2 - Afterschool XXX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moriyama Tou Special II: Houkago XXX</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18001" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美・それから 第2部 ~忘れたいのに~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami From Then On Part 2 - Even Though I Want to Forget</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami Sore kara Dai 2 Bu: Wasuretai no ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18002" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1989-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美・それから 第3部 ~抱かれたいのに~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami From Then On Part 3 - Even Though I Want to Hold You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami Sore kara Dai 3 Bu: Dakaretai no ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18003" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1990-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美・それから 第4部完結編 ~微笑みの中で~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami From Then On Part 4 (Conclusion) - Within a Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami Sore kara Dai 4 Bu Kanketsuhen: Hohoemi no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18004" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1990-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">森山塔ベストヒット そうかもしんない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moriyama Tou Best Hit - I Guess So</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moriyama Tou Best Hit: Soukamoshinnai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18005" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1990-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">唯登詩樹ベストヒット ヨーロッパの印象</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toshiki Yui Best Hit - Impressions of Europa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshiki Yui Best Hit: Europa no Inshou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18006" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1990-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜麻木硅ベストヒット チェリーなゆううつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amagi Kei Best Hit - Cherry Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amagi Kei Best Hit: Cherry na Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18007" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1989-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔道都市アスタロト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic City Astalot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madou Toshi Astalot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18008" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い性 ~アンジェ&amp;ローズ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Green Nature - Angie &amp; Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Sei: Angie &amp; Rose</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18009" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1993-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">続・黒猫館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to Black Cat Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zoku Kuronekokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18010" update="2008-10-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻のくりぃむレモン パート0</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Vision of Cream Lemon - Part 0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Cream Lemon Part 0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67447" recap="true" update="2013-02-07">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1987-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業アルバム くりいむレモン名場面集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation Album - Cream Lemon Best Scenes Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou Album: Cream Lemon Meibamenshuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67448" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美・イマージュ ~白い影~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami Image - White Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami Image: Shiroi Kage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67449" update="2008-08-23">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1987-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DARK ~ダーク~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dark</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97360" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2005-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">くりいむレモン マニアックス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cream Lemon ManiaX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cream Lemon ManiaX</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110872" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1988-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クライマックス 全集 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Climax Complete Works 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Climax Zenshuu 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
