<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1641" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2004-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kenran Butou Sai: The Mars Daybreak</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Рассвет Марса</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">현란무답제: The Mars Daybreak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kenran Butou Sai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">daybreak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kenran</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kbs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kb</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">絢爛舞踏祭 ザ･マーズ･デイブレイク</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mars Daybreak</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mars Daybreak</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="438710">this is realy good,so give it a try.i tired it cuz sammy,recommended.lol i alwaiz look for that dragon ball Z avatar.anyway its rly good so def. watch it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="460977">Solid plot, good action scenes, great backgrounds, lovable characters and absolutely amazing mecha/tech designs.

Must see for everyone.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kenran/</url>
<creators>
<name id="664" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ousaka Hiroshi</name>
<name id="664" type="Character Design">Ousaka Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
<name id="4597" type="Original Plan">Sony Computer Entertainment</name>
<name id="8516" type="Direction">Mori Kunihiro</name>
<name id="6763" type="Story Composition">Asakawa Miya</name>
</creators>
<description>On a Mars covered in ice and oceans, people have learned to survive by building large floating city-ships in which they can live. And by using submarines to travel beneath the ice and harsh winds that rage overhead, humanity has been able to develop a global community. But during a distant galactic war, Earth looked to Mars as important water resource to support their war efforts. Now that the war is over, Earth still values the wealth of resources that Mars provides, and is reluctant to release their firm control over it.
Continuous oppression breeds contempt, and rebellions occurred. And with each failure, the independence movement learned and grew more organized. During this confusion, pirates appeared to prey on the wealth and abundant resources of Earth`s occupying forces. The Earth government decides to organize a special military unit equipped to fight on Mars — to settle and suppress both the independence movement and pirates once and for all.
Source: MIKOMI</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1419">6.10</permanent>
<temporary count="1430">7.39</temporary>
<review count="3">7.21</review>
</ratings>
<picture>85910.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3642</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1086</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1325</identifier>
<identifier>fnvvzj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kenran/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/kenranbutohsai</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kenran_Butohsai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>絢爛舞踏祭_ザ・マーズ・デイブレイク</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>381</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319968</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6702</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="898" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-17">
<name>submarine</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2765" parentid="2660" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Mars</name>
<description>Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System after Mercury. In English, Mars carries a name of the Roman god of war, and is often referred to as the "Red Planet" because the reddish iron oxide prevalent on its surface gives it a reddish appearance that is distinctive among the astronomical bodies visible to the naked eye. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, having surface features reminiscent both of the impact craters of the Moon and the valleys, deserts, and polar ice caps of Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214389.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21034" type="main character in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="6">7.63</rating>
<name>Gram River</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21035" type="main character in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="11">6.59</rating>
<name>Vestemona Lauren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21036" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="6">5.21</rating>
<name>Elizabeth Liati</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21037" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="3">7.87</rating>
<name>Yagami Arian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21038" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<name>Kato Takigawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21039" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="3">3.63</rating>
<name>Achilles Polandwood</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21042" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="9">6.95</rating>
<name>Enora Taft</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3087" picture="23993.jpg">Murata Akino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21043" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="4">6.65</rating>
<name>Neli Omaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34613" picture="128892.jpg">Tamura Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21044" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="3">5.70</rating>
<name>Sala Shesha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21045" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="5">4.95</rating>
<name>Higashibara Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21047" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="2">7.71</rating>
<name>Clara de Sirene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2184" picture="49347.jpg">Hyoudou Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21048" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<name>Poipoider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21049" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<name>Chrysalis Milch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21050" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="3">7.13</rating>
<name>Kubernes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21057" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<name>Grandpa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>53913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21058" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="3">3.30</rating>
<name>Selena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21059" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="3">5.70</rating>
<name>Anna Grace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21060" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="1">2.31</rating>
<name>Niall Poe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21061" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<name>Veronica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21062" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="11">6.72</rating>
<name>Ester Ein Astrada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21194" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Shie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6933" picture="51989.jpg">Teppouzuka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21195" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Anya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3103" picture="66844.jpg">Houjou Fumie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21197" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Bon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21198" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Garma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3271" picture="171421.jpg">Emori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21199" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Kamal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21201" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Doze</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21202" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Mathers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21203" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Regardie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21204" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Crowley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21206" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="5">5.29</rating>
<name>Rosetta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21207" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<name>Dolittle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21208" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="2">2.88</rating>
<name>Rich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21209" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Joseph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21210" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Lauren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3276" picture="24272.jpg">Nakagi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21211" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<name>Doctor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21226" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Jiai Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54220.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21227" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Buyuu Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54219.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21228" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Kibou Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54218.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21229" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Shiyoku Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54221.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21230" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Mermaid</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54222.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21231" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Yoake no Fune</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>54223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21232" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Giyuu Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54219.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21235" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>F Kyuu Frame</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54232.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21236" type="appears in" update="2010-08-30">
<name>Squirt</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>54231.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21238" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<name>Ginbuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20906" picture="223783.jpg">Kitazawa You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21239" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<name>Uro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21240" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<name>Fuuko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21242" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<name>Abbot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21243" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<name>Bronson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3866" picture="167550.jpg">Harasawa Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21244" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<name>Cornel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17727" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">襲撃! 明けの船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raid! The Ship of Aurora</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Raid ! Le vaisseau de l`Aurore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuugeki! Ake no Fune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17728" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛攻! ラウンドバックラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Furious Attack! Round Buckler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attaque violente ! Round Buckler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moukou! Round Buckler</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17883" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ショウ 憧れの出撃!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jr. Dream Deployment!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rêve de Junior se réalise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shou: Akogare no Shutsugeki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18159" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">接触! グラムとベスと潜水艦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Contact! Gram, Vess and the Submarine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Contact ! Gram, Vess et un sous-marin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sesshoku! Gram to Vess to Sensuikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18868" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンナ奮闘! 夢の我が艦隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anna`s Struggle! The Fleet of our Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat d`Anna ! La flotte de ses rêves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anna Funtou! Yume no Waga Kantai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19027" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嗚呼! 栄光と情熱の革命よ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ah! Revolution of Glory and Passion!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hélas ; O Révolution de gloire et de passion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa! Eikou to Jounetsu no Kakumei yo!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19043" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵か味方か!? 傭兵海賊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend or Foe!? The Mercenary Pirate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ami ou ennemi ? Le pirate mercenaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki ka Mikata ka!? Youhei Kaizoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19340" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絢爛! 豪華舞踏会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gorgeous! Extravagant Ball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Paillettes ! Soirée VIP</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenran! Gouka Butoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19602" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキッ! 水着だらけの大銭湯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thump! Swimsuit-riddled Bathhouse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gloub ! Baignade et maillots</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doki! Mizugi Darake no Daisentou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19714" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">観光! 火星先住移民のロマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sightsee! Romance of the First Martian Immigrant</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tourisme ! La romance des Aborigènes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kankou! Kasei Senjuu Imin no Roman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19920" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突破せよ! 地球軍包囲網</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breakthrough! Federation Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Revirement ! Coup de filet des militaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toppa Seyo! Chikyuugun Houimou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20421" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪奇! 幽霊船漂流地帯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bizarre! The Ghost Ship Drift Zone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mystère ! La zone du vaisseau fantôme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21150" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大胆不敵! 海底の花よめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daring, Fearless! Bride on the Bottom of the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bravoure ! La promise du fond des mers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21386" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大脱獄! 愛と情熱の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Jailbreak! Beyond Love and Passion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande évasion ! Aux limites de la passion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21889" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眼下の敵! 深く静かに潜航せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Enemy Under Eyes! Dive Deep, Quietly</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ennemi du dessous ! Plongée silencieuse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22433" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入! 博物都市船, 叡智の城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter! Hakubutsu Ship, Eichi`s Castle!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Infiltration ! La citadelle du savoir</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22520" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叛乱! 宇宙最強の海賊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebellion! The Universe`s Greatest Pilot!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mutinerie ! Le plus grand pirate de l`univers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22664" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">船長に求婚!? ドクターと呼ばれた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marriage Proposal to the Captain!? The Man Who is Called "Doctor"</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un prétendant ! On l`appelle le docteur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翔べ希望号! あの門を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly, Kibougou! Over that Gate!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22757" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">果たし合い! グラムとベス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel! Gram and Vess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatashiai! Gram to Vess</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22758" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば友よ! 男の夢は永遠に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good-bye My Friend! A Man`s Dream Lasts Forever</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23668" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発見! オリンポス秘宝伝説の聖地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Discovery! Sanctuary of the Olympus Treasure Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakken! Olympus Hihou Densetsu no Seichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24020" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神の石! 前人未踏の争奪戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">God`s Stone! Free-For-All Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami no Ishi! Zenjinmitou no Soudatsusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24021" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球軍強襲! 夜明けの船突入作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Earth Forces Attack! The Ship of Aurora`s Breakthrough Tactic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuugun Kyoushuu! Yoake no Fune Totsunyuu Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24022" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">駆けろグラム! 囚われの仲間を救え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Gram! Rescuing the Captured Comrades</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakero Gram! Toraware no Nakama o Sukue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24405" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火星の夜明け! マーズ・デイブレイク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dawn of Mars! Mars Daybreak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasei no Yoake! Mars Daybreak</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68844" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68845" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
