<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1645" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-03-25</startdate>
<enddate>2004-08-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Interlude</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Interludium</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">インタールード</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Interlude</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Interlude</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4178" approval="14" total="22">Zegapain</anime>
<anime id="14" approval="1" total="4">RahXephon</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/animeister/interlude/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59087" type="Original Work">Sonozaki Tooru</name>
<name id="1152" type="Work">Happinet Pictures</name>
<name id="1977" type="Chief Animation Direction">Inoue Eisaku</name>
<name id="2168" type="Direction">Nagamine Tatsuya</name>
<name id="1977" type="Animation Character Design">Inoue Eisaku</name>
<name id="6392" type="Direction">Hosoda Masahiro</name>
<name id="2168" type="Direction">Nagamine Tatsuya</name>
<name id="2533" type="Music">Kameyama Kouichirou</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>For a close-knit foursome of high school friends, life is all about sleeping in class, strawberry milk, and after-class karaoke. However, our http://anidb.net/ch9745 [unnamed main protagonist] is troubled by nightmares of death and disaster. Only when he begins to realize that his memories of people and events are different from those of http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko], http://anidb.net/ch19493 [Chimu] and http://anidb.net/ch19495 [Harusa], his three female friends, does he begin to wonder. Later, when the waking dreams start... a short moment of him seeing something that noone else sees... an http://anidb.net/ch9747 [attractive young lady], who stares back at him in amazement from an empty subway station, does he begin to wonder about his sanity. That evening, the four encounter and follow a shadow with no person, only to encounter a gang of stumbling zombies. And then he wakes up that morning from yet another bad dream, but the threads of reality have become a bit too frayed, and he begins to see a way in which he can travel over to the reality of his nightmares.
Source: MIKOMI</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1279">4.98</permanent>
<temporary count="1293">6.88</temporary>
<review count="4">6.12</review>
</ratings>
<picture>240637.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3619</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1085</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1370</identifier>
<identifier>tseomc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/animeister/interlude/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://corp.toei-anim.co.jp/english/film/interlude.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Interlude_(visual_novel)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>インタールード_(ゲーム)#OVA.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319445</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6797</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/369</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3195</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>interlude</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1282" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>pet</name>
<description>A domestic animal kept for pleasure or companionship.</description>
<picurl>221616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4308" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-26">
<name>delayed death</name>
<description>The Final Battle has begun. The two opponents square off, and one of them hits the other with a series of mighty blows that would fell a mountain. But what`s this? Nothing seems to be happening! That`s when your opponent tells you that You Are Already Dead, right before your head explodes, your body separates in two, or you disintegrate into a fine mist. If you`re unlucky, only one of those happens. Sometimes, you may also discover that you were Made of Explodium.
A common trope in martial arts series, this involves some form of Finishing Move that does not take effect immediately. When used with martial arts, it may involve Pressure Point attacks or some form of Ki Attacks. Assassins may use Universal Poison to achieve a similar effect. In video games, Damage Over Time abilities often have this effect.
When used with swords there are a number of common variations, often shown with a Diagonal Cut. In sword duels, the two sides charge each other and attack. There will be a pause as the two pose, then one (or both) will fall down. Another one is for a Master Swordsman to perform a series of lightning-fast slashes, and then slowly and dramatically sheath their sword (with an audible *click*) before their attacks take effect.
This trope is not necessarily limited to martial arts, either. In more modern settings, gunshot wounds can often have this effect, since getting shot typically feels like getting punched hard and it is not uncommon for victims to take some time to realize it. This can be exploited for dramatic effect in war movies, where fatally wounded soldiers wander the battlefield before succumbing.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9745" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Shujinkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite being a reliable and sincere person, the unnamed protagonist has yet to respond to http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tama] whether he loves her or just considers her a friend. Nevertheless he takes his nightmares seriously and intends to protect her with all he can do. But when dream and reality begin to merge and he wonders whether he is going insane he develops a determination to find out the truth regardless of the consequences, and finding the http://anidb.net/ch9747 [mysterious girl] he saw on the train platform becomes the most important thing for him.
In the game version of Interlude the protagonist is named Aizawa Naoya (相沢 尚也); in the anime version he is kept nameless so that his family relations remain a secret until late in the story: http://anidb.net/ch19492 [Fuyuki Ikuo] is his older brother, http://anidb.net/ch19483 [Saegusa Miyako] is his sister-in-law (and Ikuo`s wife). Miyako`s younger sister http://anidb.net/ch19491 [Saegusa Mutsuki] calls him "onii-chan" though they aren`t real siblings.</description>
<picture>29548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9747" type="main character in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="5">7.56</rating>
<name>Watsuji Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Watsuji Aya is a mysterious girl with long black hair. The course of events has made her an insecure, withdrawn girl who is hard to get through to.
When her http://anidb.net/ch39751 [mother] died in a car accident strange things began to happen in her life: The next day her mother was alive again - but then people around Aya began to vanish one by one. Despite now living all alone in an empty town she tries to live on as if nothing happened, attends school, and practices archery, hoping that somehow her world will return to normalcy, and trying to prevent going insane. http://anidb.net/ch9745 [The unnamed protagonist] who happens to see her on a station platform is the first person whom she meets after a long time.</description>
<picture>29550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9748" type="main character in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="4">4.41</rating>
<name>Tamaki Maiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki Maiko (nicknamed "Tama" by her friends; "Tamago Musume" = "egg-girl" is a wordplay on her name) is a childhood friend of the http://anidb.net/ch9745 [unnamed protagonist]. Her attitude towards him is expressed by her own word creation "Madako" that she hopes him to say to her ("Mai-chan, dai-suki, koi shiteru" = "Mai-chan, I like you, I love you") which she even writes on the blackboard in their classroom. Maiko is carefree and slightly immature, energetic and loud (e. g. in the karaoke box). She loves strawberry milk and ice cream since kindergarten; despite having a slim body she has a complex about her bottom (and is jealous of http://anidb.net/ch19484 [Marufuji Izumi]`s body because of this). She considers the protagonist her property and is known for spasms of jealousy in public when some "tit monster" (i. e. an adult woman) gets too close to him. She frequently sleeps during class, thus being an endless source of frustration for http://anidb.net/ch39723 [Shimizu-sensei]. Her curiosity of all things paranormal makes her interested in the rumors of shadow beings recently having appeared in town.
Actually Maiko died during the downfall of human society; her current existence in this world is merely a memory of the protagonist revived by the means of the http://anidb.net/ch39798 [Pandora Project].</description>
<picture>29551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19483" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="4">5.62</rating>
<name>Saegusa Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saegusa Miyako has just recently been assigned as the new student counselor (albeit the http://anidb.net/ch9745 [unnamed protagonist] believes to remember that an older woman had been chosen for this position). A mysterious woman who is aware of the existence of shadow beings in this town as both the unnamed protagonist and http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko] happen to observe.
Her job at school only serves as excuse so that she can be close to the unnamed protagonist and fix any malfunctions of the virtual world (symbolized by extracting the shadow out of the http://anidb.net/ch39676 [tortured girl]`s body) before her brother-in-law will notice anything. She is fully aware of the heavy load she has agreed to put on the shoulder of her younger sister http://anidb.net/ch19491 [Mutsuki] and questions the meaning of the http://anidb.net/ch39798 [Pandora Project] because of this.</description>
<picture>50994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25" picture="16608.jpg">Watanabe Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19484" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-16">
<rating votes="4">4.65</rating>
<name>Marufuji Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marufuji Izumi is a 23 years old city hall public servant, co-worker and friend of http://anidb.net/ch19485 [Minegishi Kaoruko] and http://anidb.net/ch19486 [Takase Yuuki] whom she teams up with for their investigation of the events in this town. Her breasts are at least G-cup size; she is very sensitive about any allegation they might not be natural. She often drinks more alcohol than she can handle.
http://anidb.net/ch9745 [The unnamed protagonist] meets her by chance in a fully occupied train (and saves her from a molester - never wearing a bra attracts all kinds of people to her).</description>
<picture>50996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3398" picture="224826.jpg">Kingetsu Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19485" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-16">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Minegishi Kaoruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although she might look younger (her exact age is unknown), Kaoruko Minegishi is http://anidb.net/ch19484 [Izumi]`s senpai at work in this town`s office, and on par with her in terms of looks and breast size. Like her friend she`s a gentle person but a mysterious character with eccentric hobbies such as doing cosplay of game characters. Being curious and a Sci-Fi fan she starts investigating the mysterious shadow creatures that have been observed in the town, and her shooting skills might come in handy for this.</description>
<picture>78570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3834" picture="25805.jpg">Toyoshima Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19486" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="4">3.44</rating>
<name>Takase Yuuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takase Yuuki is one of the office workers in the 2nd citiy affairs department, together with http://anidb.net/ch19484 [Marufuji Izumi] and http://anidb.net/ch19485 [Minegishi Kaoruko]. She tartly banters Izumi about attracting debauchees by not wearing a bra but reacts as scared and helpless as her friend in critical situations.</description>
<picture>78698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19491" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="4">5.62</rating>
<name>Saegusa Mutsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saegusa Mutsuki is a shy girl who attends the second year of middle school. During the course of events she became involved in the work of her http://anidb.net/ch19483 [older sister] and her http://anidb.net/ch19492 [brother-in-law].</description>
<picture>50989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19492" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<name>Fuyuki Ikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuyuki Ikuo is the supervisor of the 2nd city affairs department in the city hall, and as such the superior of http://anidb.net/ch19484 [Marufuji Izumi], http://anidb.net/ch19485 [Minegishi Kaoruko] and http://anidb.net/ch19486 [Takase Yuuki]. Ikuo is a good-looking, respectable, kind and charming person (and thus well liked by his subordinates). He loves sweet food, especially ice cream; he shows interest in the http://anidb.net/ch9745 [unnamed protagonist]`s story as he has already heard about the rumors of shadow creatures recently appearing in the town.
But all of this is just a fake vita allowing him to hide the secret that`s buried inside the city hall. Actually Ikuo is the older brother of the unnamed protagonist, the husband of http://anidb.net/ch19483 [Saegusa Miyako] (two facts that were deleted from the protagonist`s memory) and more importantly, he`s the creator and supervisor of the http://anidb.net/ch39798 [Pandora Project].</description>
<picture>78660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19493" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="3">5.04</rating>
<name>Kimura Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kimura Chika is a classmate of http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko] and http://anidb.net/ch9745 [the unnamed protagonist].</description>
<picture>78659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19494" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<name>Sugiura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugiura (exact name unknown) is an inhabitant of the shadow town under the full moon. A dubious man of uncertain age (who calls himself a romancer and heavy drinker and is not above groping http://anidb.net/ch19484 [busty women] on occasion). But when it comes to protecting helpless people against monsters he has a heart of gold, shows no signs of fear and skillfully uses his rifle to shoot down zombies and shapeless black beings.
These ghost-like beings named "minions" are manifestations of an "open seam" in the virtual world of the http://anidb.net/ch39798 [Pandora Project] through which "the laws of physics of a crumbled reality intruded into this world". By shooting down as many minions as possible Sugiura (being in the know about the project) tries to delay the inevitable destruction of this world as long as possible.</description>
<picture>78710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19495" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-21">
<rating votes="4">5.89</rating>
<name>Fujinobe Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujinobe Haruka is a classmate and best friend of http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko] and http://anidb.net/ch9745 [the unnamed protagonist]. Despite her outward appearance making her look like a delinquent she`s actually considered a honor student.</description>
<picture>78760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39676" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">4.59</rating>
<name>Joshi Seito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A high-school girl who sits in the http://anidb.net/ch19483 [school counselor]`s room and reports that she is hearing a voice inside of her body that`s growing louder.
The school counselor thrusts her hand into the girl`s shoulder and extracts a huge shadow from her body, to the bewilderment of both http://anidb.net/ch9745 [the unnamed protagonist] and http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko] who both happen to observe this incident.</description>
<picture>78646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13940" picture="171402.jpg">Hirotsu Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39677" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Danshi Seito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39678" type="appears in" update="2011-12-16">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Master</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The master of the café where http://anidb.net/ch9745 [the protagonist] meets with http://anidb.net/ch19484 [Marufuji Izumi], http://anidb.net/ch19485 [Minegishi Kaoruko], http://anidb.net/ch19486 [Takase Yuuki] and their superior http://anidb.net/ch19492 [Fuyuki Ikuo] (who treats the protagonist to an ice cream) in order to find out what actually happened the day before. Seeing this muscular man wearing a waitress uniform is quite something.</description>
<picture>78572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39723" type="appears in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="2">3.97</rating>
<name>Shimizu-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shimizu-sensei (nicknamed "Lady" by her students) is the class teacher of http://anidb.net/ch9745 [the unnamed protagonist], http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko], http://anidb.net/ch19495 [Fujinobe Haruka] and http://anidb.net/ch19493 [Kimura Chika]. She may appear a bit strict but only wants the best for her students. Her endless scoldings of and detention penalties for Maiko appear to have no effect on her problem child though (assuming the girl actually listens to these ticking-offs).</description>
<picture>78647.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39751" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Aya no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aya`s mother only appears on photographs (in her family`s home, and during her funeral) but has several spoken lines (in flashback scenes of her http://anidb.net/ch9747 [daughter]).
She died in a car accident but only when she mysteriously returned to life on the next day (and nobody considered this strange) Aya`s reality began to crumble.</description>
<picture>3210.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3969" picture="48838.jpg">Oomoto Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39789" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Daishou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The General (exact name unknown) is a resident of the shadow town under the full moon. Together with http://anidb.net/ch39790 [his minion] he hunts people in this town, especially those who came there because they know too much about the Pandora Project. His body shows traces of his life style (bandages on head and leg), and he uses a crutch for walking.</description>
<picture>78685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39790" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Buta-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Pig (his exact name is unknown) is an inhabitant of the shadow town under the full moon. As http://anidb.net/ch39789 [the General]`s henchman he is eager to not only kill people but then roast and eat them. His weapon for hunting is a heavy crossbow whose bolts even penetrate concrete walls.</description>
<picture>78686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39795" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Hedgehog</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hedgehog is http://anidb.net/ch19491 [Saegusa Mutsuki]`s pet puppy.</description>
<picture>78702.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39796" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Hedgehog</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hedgehog is the glowing girl`s companion and tool for executing her commands.
These (English) commands include:* "house" (= return to its master, used in situations when Hedgehog is in danger)
* "reboot" (= reset the memory of all beings within the virtual world of the target)
* "delete" (= remove the target from the current virtual world)
* "wipe out everything" (= destroy the virtual world)

"Harinezumi" (針鼠), meaning "hedgehog" or "porcupine", is http://anidb.net/ch19494 [Sugiura]`s nickname for this being whereas http://anidb.net/ch19491 [Mutsuki] uses the English word "hedgehog" (ヘッジホッグ).</description>
<picture>78703.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39797" type="appears in" update="2012-01-25">
<rating votes="2">2.68</rating>
<name>Saegusa Mutsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saegusa Mutsuki as nucleus of the http://anidb.net/ch39798 [Pandora Project].
Her dreams create the virtual world for all remaining humans. For the sake of her older sister http://anidb.net/ch19483 [Miyako] who considers this http://anidb.net/ch39798 [project] mankind`s hope, the young girl took over the burden of isolating all negative emotions of the community and taking them on herself by (by moving them to the shadow city under the full moon which serves as "trash can" of the virtual world); the fire hound http://anidb.net/ch39796 [Hedgehog] serves as symbol for executing commands.</description>
<picture>78704.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39798" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<name>Pandora Project</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>"Pandora - the first woman created by the gods. She was never to open the box she was given. When Pandora opened the box, all the evils inside where let out to inflict themselves upon the world. But tucked in at the bottom of the box, under the evils,was a small ray of... hope."
When the world collapsed and life in a world where "the laws of physics have died" became unendurable for them, a group of twelve remaining members of the human race made the choice to live in a dream world instead. The Pandora Project, suggested and overseen by scientist http://anidb.net/ch19492 [Fuyuki Ikuo] and assisted by his wife http://anidb.net/ch19483 [Saegusa Miyako], let all brains of the surviving humans be connected and participate in a world created by the dreaming girl, http://anidb.net/ch39797 [Saegusa Mutsuki], who permanently removes all sad or desperate memories from their respective dreams in the process so that all other dreamers will have only happy memories. In doing so, this Pandora Project put a woman into "the box".
But mysteriously, certain tragic fragments of the http://anidb.net/ch9745 [unnamed protagonist]`s previous life keep reappearing (including his memory of his childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch9748 [Tamaki Maiko] having died in his arms) regardless how often Mutsuki deletes them. And in trying to make sense of all this he finally opens Pandora`s Box (and tears down the curtain of this theater play) by choosing reality (in the person of http://anidb.net/ch9747 [Watsuji Aya] whose world has become a meaningless facade due to Mutsuki`s actions) over this dream world (where Aya is forgotten but Maiko is still alive and acts according to his memory of her), thus making this project an interlude between destruction and hope.</description>
<picture>78707.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17742" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17866" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2004-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<summary>The unnamed main character has been having strange dreams, seeing strange things, and meeting strange people. He investigates these events and finds a strange girl named Aya. With her help, he discovers that his world may not in fact be real and many of the people he thinks he knows may not exist anymore.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573956</identifier>
<identifier>interlude</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="23384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2004-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<summary>The unnamed main character has been having strange dreams, seeing strange things, and meeting strange people. He investigates these events and finds a strange girl named Aya. With her help, he discovers that his world may not in fact be real and many of the people he thinks he knows may not exist anymore.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573958</identifier>
<identifier>interlude</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="23544" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2004-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
<summary>The unnamed main character has been having strange dreams, seeing strange things, and meeting strange people. He investigates these events and finds a strange girl named Aya. With her help, he discovers that his world may not in fact be real and many of the people he thinks he knows may not exist anymore.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573960</identifier>
<identifier>interlude</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
