<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1663" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2004-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mutsu Enmei Ryuu Gaiden: Shura no Toki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Time of Shura</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Время битв</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Syuratoki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shura no Toki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Shuratoki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SNT</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">陸奥圓明流外伝 修羅の刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shura no Toki - Age of Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">L`ère des Shura</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">قتال الطيف</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6613" approval="7" total="16">Katanagatari</anime>
<anime id="90" approval="3" total="3">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="18949">Great tales of the Shura, those martials arts peaceful warriors.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="164299">This is a must see for anyone who appreciate nice fight scenes!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="379645">I have just one word to say-UNREAL!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="129591">Sometimes I really dont understand why some epic anime series can`t be appreciated. This is one of them great plot with 3 different stories and masterly done fight scenes. Shounen funs must see it....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="326893">Most of the fight scenes in this series are just phenomenally done.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="564644">One of the most Poetic shows I`ve ever seen covering Meiji Era. There is a lot more to experience other than great fighting scenes and regular shounen elements.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/syuratoki/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7829" type="Character Design">Hamatsu Takehiro</name>
<name id="3634" type="Series Composition">Takegami Junki</name>
<name id="7829" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hamatsu Takehiro</name>
<name id="9047" type="Original Work">Kawahara Masatoshi</name>
<name id="13267" type="Music">Minobe Yutaka</name>
<name id="21225" type="Direction">Misawa Shin</name>
<name id="839" type="Animation Work">Studio Comet</name>
</creators>
<description>Legends tell of an invincible martial art known as Mutsu Enmei-Ryu, an unarmed style that allows the user to defeat any number of armed opponents using incredible speed and strength. This is the story of three generations of those who bear the name Mutsu, and their encounters and battles with the strongest fighters of their era.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1641">6.62</permanent>
<temporary count="1669">7.74</temporary>
<review count="3">7.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>1528.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3768</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1413</identifier>
<identifier>fikscn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/syuratoki/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mmv.co.jp/special/shura/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shura_no_Toki_–_Age_of_Chaos</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>陸奥圓明流外伝_修羅の刻</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>376</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6713</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3515" parentid="2898" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>shinsengumi</name>
<description>The Shinsengumi were a special police force of the late shogunate period.</description>
<picurl>191098.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50187" type="main character in" update="2012-10-28">
<rating votes="3">9.83</rating>
<name>Mutsu Yakumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50191" type="main character in" update="2012-10-28">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50192" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Miyamoto Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17844" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雲の如き男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man Like the Clouds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme nuage</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الرجل شبيه الغيمة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumo no Gotoki Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18100" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天下無双の器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unrivaled Ability</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`étoffe d`un Hercule</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مقاتل بسرعة البرق</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkamusou no Utsuwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18102" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">烈風の鎖鎌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sickle and Chain of Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le kusarigama au vent violent</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">إنفجار المنجل والسلسلة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reppuu no Kusarigama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18661" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retrouvailles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18991" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の兵法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Tactics</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une sombre stratégie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Hyouhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19455" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三本松の果し合い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at the Three Pines</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel aux trois pins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanbonmatsu no Hatashiai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19634" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いを極めし者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Man Standing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un homme d`expérience</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai o Kiwameshi Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19668" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天斗と圓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takato and Tsubura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Takato et Tsubura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takato to Tsubura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20706" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その男, 梟雄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man. The Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un homme effrayant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Otoko, Kyouyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20712" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陸奥を巡る権謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mutsu in the Mist of Machinations</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ruses autour de Mutsu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mutsu o Meguru Kenbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21035" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たぎりおちる滝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waterfall Boiling Over</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cascade aux chutes effroyables</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tagiriochiru Taki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21199" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寛永御前試合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kanei Era Shogunate Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tournoi Kanei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kan`ei Gozenjiai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21761" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">継ぐもの...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Successor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le successeur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsugu Mono...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22302" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化物(けもの)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monstre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kemono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22303" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れる龍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sleeping Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dragon endormi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemureru Ryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22501" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大海の志士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patriot of the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un homme et la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taikai no Shishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22852" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新撰組</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shinsengumi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Shunsengumi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsengumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22853" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">龍の化身</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Avatar of the Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`incarnation du dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu no Keshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22854" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漆黒の海戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pitch Black Naval Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille navale dans un noir d`encre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikkoku no Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23117" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">示現流の刺客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassin of the Jigen Ryuu!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`assassin de l`école Jigen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen Ryuu no Shikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23742" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我が友, 坂本龍馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Friend, Sakamoto Ryoma</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon ami Ryoma Sakamoto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waga Tomo, Sakamoto Ryouma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27445" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば友よ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell my friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`adieu à un ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Tomo yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34127" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La promesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34128" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪の如く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comme la neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki no Gotoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34129" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the North</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au nord</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kita e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34130" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼と修羅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon and The Shura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ogre et le Shura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni to Shura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46545" update="2006-02-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46546" update="2006-02-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
