<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1682" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>44</episodecount>
<startdate>1976-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>1977-01-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Daikuu Maryuu Gaiking</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Force Five: Gaiking</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">大空魔竜ガイキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dino Mech Gaiking</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Gaiking</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">El Gladiador</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3704" type="Alternative Setting">Gaiking: Legend of Daiku-Maryu</anime>
<anime id="8532" type="Other">Toei Robot Girls</anime>
<anime id="10001" type="Other">Robot Girls Z</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3513" approval="1" total="2">Kagaku Ninjatai Gatchaman</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/gaiking2/</url>
<creators>
<name id="984" type="Unknown Relation">Dynamic Planning</name>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="5269" type="Character Design">Shirato Takeshi</name>
<name id="2380" type="Series Composition">Maruyama Masao</name>
<name id="4109" type="Original Work">Sugino Akio</name>
<name id="3962" type="Music">Kikuchi Shunsuke</name>
</creators>
<description>Tsuwabuki Sanshirou, a professional baseball player, hurt his dominate arm by the attack of monsters sent by the Black Horror Squad of Zeller, and he quitted baseball. He was recruited by Dr. Daimonji, and he saw the members of Combat Force that protected the earth and the large parent ship, Daiku Maryu (Great Sky Dragon). He potentially had special natural power, and joined Combat Force. He become a pilot of the large robot, Gaiking, and fought against the Black Monsters of Zeller.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="63">5.47</permanent>
<temporary count="64">6.25</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>145639.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1294</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>956</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1594</identifier>
<identifier>senkat</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/gaiking2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>大空魔竜ガイキング</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89489</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>193</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="64082" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎のブラックホール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Black Hole</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Black Hole</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72577" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みたか必殺魔球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Did You See It? The Magical Killer Pitch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitaka Hissatsu Makyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72578" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダリウス大帝の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of Emperor Darius</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Darius Taitei no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72579" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">光る目のハニワ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Haniwa Statue with Flashing Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikaru Me no Haniwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72580" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">男一匹ヤマガタケ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yamagatake the Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko Ippiki Yamagatake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72581" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえったムー帝国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrection of the Mu Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaetta Muu Teikoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72582" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の逆デスクロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dreadful Reverse Death Cross</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Gyaku Desk Rose</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72583" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発狂した大空魔竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Insane Demon Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakkyou Shita Oozora Maryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72584" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナスカ地上絵の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Nazca Lines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nasuka Chijoue no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72585" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スカイラー死へのジャンプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skyler Jumps to His Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Skyler Shi e no Jump</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72586" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">泣くなハチロー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Cry, Hachiro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakuna Hachirou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72587" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">応答せよ! ミドリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Respond! Midori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Outou seyo! Midori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72588" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠に吠える赤サソリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Scorpion Howling in the Desert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku ni Hoeru Aka Sasori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72589" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大空魔竜の逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Daikyu Maryu Strikes Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oozora Maryuu no Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72590" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">これぞミラクルドリル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is the Miracle Drill!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Korezo Miracle Drill!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72591" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミドリ 永遠の別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Forever, Midori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midori Eien no Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72592" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">吠えろネッサー大海中戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Howl, Nessar! Ocean Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoero Nessaa Daikaichuusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72593" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙船ノアの方舟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spaceship Noah`s Ark</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuusen Noah no Hakubune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72594" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">弟よ・明日に歌え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother, Sing for the Future!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otouto yo Ashita ni Utae!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72595" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄戦士の復しゅう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hellish Warrior`s Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku Senshi no Fukushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72596" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙のデビルジャガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tears of Devil Jaguar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida no Devil Jager</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72597" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底王国の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Underground Kingdom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitei Ookoku no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72598" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の月世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku no Gessekai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72599" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">巨石島の守り神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoseki Tou no Mamorigami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72600" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地のはての死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi no Hate no Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72601" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙をかける天馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu o Kakeru Tenba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72602" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">南十字星に誓う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minamijuujisei ni Chikau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72603" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙にとどけゼウスミサイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu ni Todoke Zeus Missile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72604" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">晴れ姿 ヤマガタケ土俵入り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haresugata Yamagatake Dohyouiri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72605" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">密林の大恐竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsurin no Daikyouryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72606" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復しゅうのダブルイーグル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no Double Eagle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72607" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙から来た幽霊船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu kara Kita Yuureisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72608" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大魔人ヒミラー出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daimajin Himmler Shutsugen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72609" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛烈! 火車カッター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouretsu! Hisha Cuter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72610" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば栄光のマウンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Eikou no Mound</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72611" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えよ! ゴールデンレオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeyo! Golden Leo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72612" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">占領された大空魔竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senrousareta Oozora Maryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72613" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐を呼ぶ神の手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi o Yobu Kami no Te</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72614" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊急発進! エベレストに向え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkyuu Hasshin! Everest ni Mukae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72615" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バラの宇宙船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara no Uchuusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72616" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャイアントカッター逆さ斬り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giant Cutter Sakasa Kiri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72617" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネス湖の大恐竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nesu Ko no Daikyouryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72618" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まぼろしの火星城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Kaseijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72619" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">壮烈! 地球大決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souretsu! Chikyuu Daikessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102047" update="2009-05-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102048" update="2009-05-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126463" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Jim Terry productions movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
