<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="169" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-06-30</startdate>
<enddate>1991-11-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lodoss-tou Senki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lodoss OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Les chroniques de la guerre de Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Crónicas de la guerra de Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">로도스도 전기</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Crônicas da Guerra de Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">罗德岛战记ova</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RoLW</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RoLW OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ロードス島戦記</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Record of Lodoss War</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Record of Lodoss War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Chroniques de la guerre de Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Cronache della Guerra di Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Kronika wojny na Lodoss</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Ο Πόλεμος του Lodoss</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="607" type="Same Setting">Mahou Senshi Louie</anime>
<anime id="137" type="Alternative Setting">Lodoss-tou Senki: Eiyuu Kishi Den</anime>
<anime id="1478" type="Character">Hajimari no Boukensha-tachi: Legend of Crystania</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5503" approval="18" total="31">Druaga no Tou: the Aegis of Uruk</anime>
<anime id="98" approval="17" total="36">Kenpuu Denki Berserk</anime>
<anime id="538" approval="6" total="8">Majutsushi Orphen</anime>
<anime id="13831" approval="4" total="11">Goblin Slayer</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="414179">Watching this reminded me, how far anime degraded since then. Good plot, touching relations, character development, dynamism, just epic. And this female elf is exactly how elf should be.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="163070">A classic fantasy series with a little bit of everything. Great action and characters, a little bit of romance and comedy thrown in. Great series for fans of RPGs. This is a good choice for people new to anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="406294">This is a great anime overall! And even better if you are a friend of the epic adventure/fantasy medieval-like style. I personally enjoyed watching it. The atmosphere captured perfectly the dark yet epic feeling of such a story. Watch Lodoss-tou Senki, listen to Summoning and drink some beers! Guarantee.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="106569">I`ve watched this for the first time with the release of the blu-ray, and wow.

This was how many years before LOTR movie?
Just absolutely amazing!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="357829">One of the best fantasy anime if not the best. If you don`t expect anime to must have jokes of course.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/1990-1989/works_ova_lodoss.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="7072" type="Music">Hagita Mitsuo</name>
<name id="2217" type="Character Design">Yuuki Nobuteru</name>
<name id="8420" type="Original Work">Yasuda Hitoshi</name>
<name id="2217" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yuuki Nobuteru</name>
<name id="5106" type="Direction">Sakai Akio</name>
<name id="1962" type="Direction">Yamada Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="6534" type="Direction">Kawasaki Hirotsugu</name>
<name id="4408" type="Chief Direction">Nagaoka Akinori</name>
<name id="4408" type="Direction">Nagaoka Akinori</name>
<name id="6604" type="Series Composition">Watanabe Mami</name>
<name id="5648" type="Original Work">Mizuno Ryou</name>
<name id="11073" type="Direction">Makino Shigeto</name>
</creators>
<description>A long time ago, there was a tremendous war between the goddess of Creation and the goddess of Destruction, which made the earth tremble. Both goddesses perished in the war and created what people called a cursed land - Lodoss. Something evil is happening in the land of Lodoss. Parn, a reckless young warrior, along with his newfound friends, takes on a quest to find out the source of this evil and becomes involved in the greatest epic struggle between good and evil since the war of the goddesses.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2757">6.40</permanent>
<temporary count="2776">7.42</temporary>
<review count="6">6.52</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224051.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>394</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>207</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>304</identifier>
<identifier>wvgsfd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/1990-1989/works_ova_lodoss.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Record_of_Lodoss_War</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ロードス島戦記</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88588</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1479</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B073K1P1WP</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="153" parentid="1609" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>dark elf</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7141" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-16">
<name>goblin</name>
<description>A goblin is a monstrous creature from European folklore, first attested in stories from the Middle Ages. They are ascribed various and conflicting abilities, temperaments and appearances depending on the story and country of origin. They are almost always small and grotesque, mischievous or outright malicious, and greedy, especially for gold and jewelry. They often have magical abilities similar to a http://anidb.net/t780 [fairy] or http://anidb.net/t2646 [demon].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>220782.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3229" type="main character in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="11">3.39</rating>
<name>Parn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3230" type="main character in" update="2009-03-01">
<rating votes="53">8.72</rating>
<name>Deedlit</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deedlit is a high elf who comes from the Forest of No Return, her peoples` homeland, where they reside in solitude.
Deedlit is a special figure among her race because she is the last high elf to be born within the last 1,000 years, being just about 160 years old. She is considered, as a result of her rare status, to be the last hope for the high elven people to prosper and flourish once more. She received the best education from her mentors in her homeland, including how to wield a blade, as well as how to cast shaman magic to harness the power of spirits.
Deedlit was restless in her homeland, and decided that staying there was simply a very slow path to extinction. Because of that, she left the forest, seeking out the "Tree of Truth", a means to find out how to help her people to become something more than what they are in their reserved state. She believes she has found it in the form of Parn.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>20108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10496" type="main character in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="5">5.05</rating>
<name>Ghim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ghim is a dwarven warrior who is exclusively a fighter, and has in his possession what appears to be a Battle Axe of Returning, an axe which he can throw, and will return to him after each throw, as his axe always returns after being thrown.
It is never hinted at as to what the age of Ghim is, but judging from his appearance, he seems somewhat old, and could be between the ages of 175 and 220.
Ghim`s purpose is apparent right from the beginning of the series, as he is looking for a girl who is like a daughter to him and wishes to get her back from her kidnappers.
He is devoted to Neese, the high priestess of Marfa, the goddess of all creation and acts as a father figure for Leylia, Neese`s adopted daughter, and a priestess of Marfa herself.
Ghim becomes a sort of mentor for Parn, teaching him how to hold his weapon, as well as how to wield it. He teaches Parn what he is able to, but ultimately allows King Kashue to take on the role of his teacher, when Parn`s studies would need to be furthered by someone who actually uses a sword.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>31474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4438" picture="26713.jpg">Sakaguchi Yoshisada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38071" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-29">
<rating votes="12">7.65</rating>
<name>Ashram</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Black Knight", Ashram is a highly skilled warrior and the former retainer and right-hand aide of Emperor Beld. He served Beld during the War of Heroes, and was sent in the front to deal with any possible resistance. After the death of Beld at the hands of Karla the Grey Witch in the OVA (or Kashue in the TV series), Ashram took up his blade, The Demon Sword Soul Crusher and returned to Marmo to regroup. Later on, Ashram seeks to dominate Lodoss rather than conquer it, as he looks for one of the governor`s treasures, the Scepter of Domination. After the destruction of the scepter, Ashram is believed to have died in the fires of Fire Dragon Mountain, but it is later revealed that one of the agents of Wagnard sacrifices his powers (stripped by Wagnard himself) in order to save his life. In the English version, he is voiced by John Knox.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>73108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38072" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="24">7.92</rating>
<name>Pirotessa Merestianna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pirotess is a dark elven noble considered to be one of the more prominent figures in her people`s society. Like most dark elves, she worships Fararis and calls the Forest of Darkness on Marmo island her home. She is the younger sister of Altas, a member of the quest of Rod of Dominatus, eventually cheated by the chief leader of all dark elves, the powerful Ruchiev, who had decided to recreate the kingdom of his kindred. Since she believed that the useless human Ashram should be the one to pay for her beloved brother`s death, she joined the mission of killing the general of Dark Knighthood. Ashram found and bested her in hand-to-hand combat when she ambushed him in his bedroom, but let her go after learning her identity as the sister of his lost old friend. After she learned the truth and the crazy decision of Ruchiev from her fellow assassin, she stalked Ashram to learn about him and discovered his loyalty to the lost emperor, the heroic Beld, and his dedication to Marmo and its people. She decided to protect him from the other assassin and aided him in a "Test" from the Dark Sage. After 10 years, she had been the only one to whom Ashram had showed appreciation and care. She in turn remained fiercely loyal to Ashram as a lieutenant and a leader of his scouts. She was accepted by the subordinates of Ashram as their mistress and sub-general. Pirotess is a skilled adversary, both an adept of the rapier and a skilled magic user. A shaman like Deedlit, she often uses spirits that high elves will not associate with, such as the spirits of darkness.[ol][u]</description>
<picture>73130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107856" type="main character in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Slayn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107857" type="main character in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Etoh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107957" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Woodchuck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107958" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Karla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107959" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Fahn-ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107960" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kashue-ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107961" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Wort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1599" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火竜山の魔竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon Dragon of Fire Dragon Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Dämonendrache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dragon maléfique de la montagne de feu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il drago della montagna di fuoco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karyuusan no Maryuu</title>
<summary>Parn’s group takes a back entrance into the mountain where they run into Ashram, his Dark Elf companion, and the great dragon who intends to leave no intruder unscathed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1600" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Desert King</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Wüstenkönig</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le roi du désert</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il re del deserto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku no Ou</title>
<summary>The mercenary king of Flaim, King Kashue, makes a grand entrance at the celebration of the princess’s rescue. But a prisoner released by Karla crashes the party, and Parn is sent on a journey to learn more about her motives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1601" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灰色の魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Grey Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die graue Hexe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sorcière grise</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La strega grigia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hai-iro no Majo</title>
<summary>Blocked from the capital of Alania, Parn’s group takes a dangerous shortcut to Valis. Meanwhile, the princess of Valis attempts the long journey to Alania. When their paths cross, a familiar face from Ghim’s past is brought to light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1602" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒衣の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der schwarze Ritter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chevalier noir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il cavaliere nero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokui no Kishi</title>
<summary>Just when Parn meets a kind elf in the woods, a Dark Elf attacks. Soon, his group winds up in a prison where a thief informs them about the invading forces from the land of Marmo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1603" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の出発[たびだち]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blazing Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufbruch in Flammen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`embrasement</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Partenza tra le fiamme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Tabidachi</title>
<summary>Attacking a goblin in self-defense, Parn sparks their retribution against his village and worsens his family’s standing. But when some brave companions arrive to help, a larger task unfolds and a journey begins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1604" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説への序章[プロローグ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue to the Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Prolog einer Sage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prologue à la légende</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il libero cavaliere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu e no Prologue</title>
<summary>In search of more information on the Grey Witch, a young knight named Parn and his five companions travel through perilous ruins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1605" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">支配の王錫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scepter of Domination</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Zepter der Herrschaft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sceptre de la domination</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Lo scettro del potere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shihai no Oushaku</title>
<summary>Learning that his sword is not enough to rule all of Lodoss, Ashram seeks a magic scepter in a mountain guarded by the dragon Shooting Star. Meanwhile, Kashue’s forces head toward the same dragon which has been terrorizing villages.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1606" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼熱の大地[ロードス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lodoss: The Burning Continent</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lodoss - Der brennende Kontinent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lodoss en feu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Terra incandescente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakunetsu no Lodoss</title>
<summary>While Karla watches passively, the fight at the castle continues. Parn, Ashram, and Wagnard go head to head in a deadly confrontation that destroys the scepter. With nothing left to control Kardis, what can be done to save Lodoss?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1607" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士の鎮魂歌[レクイエム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Requiem for Warriors</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Requiem eines Kriegers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Requiem pour un guerrier</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Requiem per un guerriero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi no Requiem</title>
<summary>A mistaken identity leads to a run-in with a couple of mercenaries. Meanwhile, Ghim travels to find Karla and free Leylia from her control. After she tries to sway Parn to join her crusade of neutrality, Ghim faces her head-on.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1608" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 暗黒の島[マーモ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle! Marmo: The Dark Island</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Entscheidungsschlacht von Marmo - Die dunkle Insel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille de Marmo</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Scontro decisivo sull`isola delle tenebre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Ankoku no Marmo</title>
<summary>As Wagnard lowers the sacrificial altar deep below the castle, the great dragon Narse awakens. Meanwhile, Ashram is the first to face Wagnard as Parn makes his way to save Deedlit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1609" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">英雄戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War of Heroes</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Krieg der Helden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La guerre des héros</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La battaglia degli eroi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiyuu Sensou</title>
<summary>Drawn by trickery into an all-out battle, the forces of Lodoss and Marmo collide. While Parn and Ashram cross blades, old friends Fahn and Beld face off once and for all, turning the tides of power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1610" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔導師の野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wizard`s Ambition</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Ambitionen des Zauberers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ambition du sorcier</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`ambizione dello stregone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madoushi no Yabou</title>
<summary>With the Scepter of Domination at hand, Wagnard seeks a High Elf to sacrifice to the goddess of destruction, Kardis. With the entire island as well as Deedlit’s life at risk, all paths lead to Marmo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1611" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗黒王の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sword of the Dark Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schwert des dunklen Imperators</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée du roi des ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La spada del re oscuro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ankoku Ou no Ken</title>
<summary>After Beld’s forces wreak havoc in Valis, Parn’s group splits—some helping the injured while others report back to King Fahn. The king tells Parn the story of a heroic knight who saved a princess at the cost of disgrace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11562" update="2008-01-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2003-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Making of Record of Lodoss War</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49156" update="2006-04-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49157" update="2006-04-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
