<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="170" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Tenshi Angelic Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Battle Doll Angelic Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Арената на Ангелите</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">机动天使</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KTEL</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AL</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動天使エンジェリックレイヤー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Angelic Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Angelic Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Angelic Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Арена Ангелов</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Angelic Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Angelic Layer</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12" type="Same Setting">Chobits</anime>
<anime id="2733" type="Alternative Setting">Tsubasa Chronicle</anime>
<anime id="4046" type="Alternative Setting">Tsubasa Chronicle Dai 2 Series</anime>
<anime id="6258" type="Character">Kobato.</anime>
<anime id="4514" type="Other">Clamp in Wonderland 2 1995-2006</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8513" approval="23" total="24">Busou Shinki Moon Angel</anime>
<anime id="9237" approval="16" total="18">Busou Shinki</anime>
<anime id="9960" approval="13" total="15">Gundam Build Fighters</anime>
<anime id="3324" approval="13" total="13">Plawres Sanshirou</anime>
<anime id="12563" approval="5" total="6">Frame Arms Girl</anime>
<anime id="10417" approval="4" total="6">Selector Infected WIXOSS</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="324041">Awesome show. Totally loved it ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="554022">Fun, light hearted show, with some serious relationship/personal struggle elements.  Definitely Clamp and it`s story based, not authenticity of fighting based.  Easily re-watchable.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281436">Surprisingly i liked this, I would recommend it for most people. It`s also got a bit of comedy in there which always helps.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="508260">Easily one of my all time favorite shows, it has a flow not unlike some well known sports series like Hajime no Ippo or Slam Dunk.  However, the story and characters are uniquely CLAMP and draw you in beyond just the fight scenes.  Add together nearly every major seiyuu from the early 2000s and a heavily improved story, it is the epitome of an Anime that improved upon the Manga.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/angelic-layer</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="1857" type="Series Composition">Ookouchi Ichirou</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="6062" type="Character Design">Komori Takahiro</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="1603" type="Direction">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch3660 [Suzuhara Misaki] is a sixth grader who has just moved to Tokyo to live with her aunt. She stumbles across a merchandising phenomenon known as Angelic Layer in which a person can purchase a doll and custom design it. Once their doll is finished, they can link to it through new technology and have it move however they want, as long as its within the confines of a field known as a layer. In these fields there are battles to see who is the best at Angelic Layer that occur at tourist traps or at special tournaments; Misaki meets a strange man known only as http://anidb.net/ch5369 [Icchan] who gets her involved in the games. The man for some reason believes that she has high potential to become one of the greatest players of all time...
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2580">5.75</permanent>
<temporary count="2605">7.30</temporary>
<review count="9">7.38</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224053.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>400</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>52</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>228</identifier>
<identifier>jueaex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/angelic-layer</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Angelic_Layer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ANGELIC_LAYER</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>200</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234286</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7472</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3283" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>fighting dolls</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2263" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="724">7.91</rating>
<name>Kudou Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139561.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2343" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-02-03">
<rating votes="1032">7.69</rating>
<name>Mouri Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mouri Ran is one of the main characters in Detective Conan. She is the daughter of Mouri Kogoro, a famous but lazy detective. She is also friends with Kudo Shinichi, another famous detective, who is still in high school. She is the captain of the high school karate team, and is very strong willed.</description>
<picture>65742.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="3660" type="main character in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="22">8.79</rating>
<name>Suzuhara Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaki is a very timid, sweet-tempered, and kind 12-year-old girl who has just moved to Tokyo to live with her aunt. She had been living with her grandparents in Wakayama while she went to elementary school, but saved up money that her mother had been sending her while she was away so she could afford to go to middle school in Tokyo. She worries about the fact that she is small and nonathletic, and is sometimes mistaken to be in elementary school, but sees Angelic Layer as a way to prove to others and herself that there is nothing wrong with being small. She started playing Angelic Layer after seeing the white angel Athena on a video screen outside of Tokyo Station. Her angel is Hikaru and she is known as the "Miracle Rookie". She is nicknamed Misakichi (みさきち) by her friend Tamayo to make her name sound cute.</description>
<picture>1936.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5369" type="main character in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="7">8.49</rating>
<name>Mihara Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mihara Ichirou nicknames himself Icchan (いっちゃん) to hide his true identity from Misaki. He is 28 years old and oftens acts extremely eccentric, spontaneous and immature for his age. (often jumping out of random places shouting "Icchan go BOOM!" to scare Misaki and Ogata), but nonetheless is ingenious and dead serious when it comes to Angelic Layer. In the manga, Icchan is the president of the Piffle Company that creates the Angelic Layer toys. In the anime, Icchan is the "father" of Angelic Layer and creator, having developed the game over seven years with the help of Shuko Suzuhara. Icchan had been an employee at a hospital trying to treat Shuko`s neurological condition and were developing the angels as part of research to create prosthetic limbs which could be controlled by brain waves. However, research funds were cut off after the hospital thought that the research was costing too much. As a result, Icchan and Shuuko created Angelic Layer in order to help fund and conduct further research.
Crossover: Icchan is the late husband of Chitose Hibiya and the creator of the persocoms in the hit manga Chobits. He made two special persocoms, the Chobits, for his wife to be their children, since she could not have children herself. They were named Freya and Elda, later known as Chi. The Chobits were created from the findings gathered from the research performed for Angelic Layer project. The cause of his death in Chobits is that he died of an illness.</description>
<picture>1937.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5370" type="main character in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="6">7.54</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Hatoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatoko is a 5 year old known as the "Miracle Kindergartner" and is Misaki`s best friend and Angelic Layer mentor. Even at a very young age, she is extremely intelligent, mature, and hard-working. She is an expert at Angelic Layer, often winning her games in mere seconds. She wins all ten of her games at the Tokyo prefecture games, and is the defending champion of the Kantou regional games. She is fiercely competitive, working to increase her angel`s speed and power often. She also likes to poke fun at her brother Kotaro for his apparent ineptness when it comes to his crush on Misaki. Hatoko also treats Misaki like her student rather than her nee-chan (sister) and is also her mentor. Hatoko`s angel is Suzuka.</description>
<picture>1935.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5404" type="main character in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="5">2.48</rating>
<name>Suzuhara Shuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuuko is Misaki`s mother and Shouko`s elder sister. She is 31 years old.
In the anime, it is explained that Shuuko left a 5-year-old Misaki to be taken care of her grandparents under the guise of work, when in reality she was going to Tokyo in order to find a way to cure the neurological disease she had been inflicted with. This disease inhibits nerve signals from reaching to or from her legs. Ichiro Mihara was a doctor attempting to work with her to find a cure when the two started Angelic Layer as a way to do research and raise funds when their original research funding was cut off. Shuuko, or "Shu" as she is called when playing Angelic Layer, is the undisputed champion with her angel Athena, having won each of the past three national championships. Over the past seven years, she has avoided meeting Misaki, afraid of what Misaki would think of her.
In the manga, however, Shuuko has no such disease and is merely extremely shy about socializing with those she loves. She also works for the company behind Angelic Layer.</description>
<picture>1940.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5405" type="main character in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotarou is a 13 year old middle school classmate of Misaki, whom he has a crush on, as well known as Hatoko`s brother. He is always being assaulted by Tamayo and her various martial arts techniques, which he has been a victim of since he was four years old. He becomes jealous of Ohjirou`s advances towards Misaki, going so far as to try to attempt to play a quasi-match of Angelic Layer against Ohjirou, despite the fact that he had never played it before. His family owns a karate dojo and Kotarou has practiced karate some himself, showing Misaki some of his knowledge in hopes that Misaki can use it to help Hikaru win. In the manga, he and Misaki later fall in love and date.
He also resembles Hiromu Shinbo from Chobits.</description>
<picture>3993.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5406" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="8">7.70</rating>
<name>Kisaki Tamayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamayo is 13 years old and is a friend and classmate of Misaki. She nicknames Misaki "Misakichi" and is rather eccentric. One of her favorite activities is practicing her martial arts techniques on her unwilling friend Kotarou. She always loudly cheers for Misaki at Angelic Layer matches and defends her against those who question her ability.
The various martial arts Tamayo has mastered after eight years of hard training are: wrestling, karate, K-1, kenpou, boxing, judo, capoeira, and taekwondo.
In the anime, it is later revealed that Tamayo has always held intimate feelings for Kotarou, while in the manga, she only saw him as a close friend. She offers to be Misaki`s "second" in her national game match against the Angelic Layer Company`s angel due to Hatoko becoming ill before Misaki accepts Oujiro`s offer to be her second.
In the anime she finally ends up with Kotaro after finally telling him how she feels (despite the fact Kotaro initially liked Misaki). However, in the manga, Tamayo falls in love with Oujiro Mihara.</description>
<picture>3992.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5407" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Mihara Oujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oujirou is 17 years old. He`s http://anidb.net/ch5369 [Icchan`s] younger step-brother. He has been involved with Angelic Layer for many years, in a large part because it was what brought him and Icchan together after their parents married each other. Oujirou competes in Kobe and has been the champion of the Kansai Regional games, as well as being the runner-up in the national tournament for two consecutive years. He has a desperate desire to defeat http://anidb.net/ch5404 [Shuuko Suzuhara`s] angel Athena to get over a childhood crush he had on her. His angel is Wizard.
In the anime it is revealed that he is falling in love with http://anidb.net/ch3660 [Misaki], but he develops a love for both Shuuko and Misaki.
In the manga, he has no feelings for Misaki or Shuuko, but likes http://anidb.net/ch5406 [Tamayo].</description>
<picture>1941.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18135" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Asami Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shouko is Misaki`s aunt and Shuuko`s younger sister. She`s 26 years old. She demands that Misaki and her friends call her "Miss Shouko" instead of "aunt" ("obasan" in Japanese) because she is still "an attractive young newscaster." She often covers Angelic Layer events for the local news station that she works for. Misaki lives with Shouko when she moves to Tokyo.
Her hairstyle bears a resemblance to that of Shimizu Takako in Chobits.</description>
<picture>48656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18136" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="1">4.15</rating>
<name>Ogata Masaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ogata (age 24) is one of Icchan`s subordinates in the Angelic Layer control room and lab. Icchan often ensnares Ogata into situations that result in Ogata getting "penalized." These penalties involve a range of embarrassing or terrible things, such as having a live octopus being stuck down his pants or being made to eat spaghetti through his nose. Icchan also named a remarkably ugly angel after him as a penalty.</description>
<picture>48657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18137" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Saitou Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaede is a 15 year old quiet and wise girl from Kanagawa and is friends with Sai Jounouchi. Her parents divorced and she lives with her father. She received an angel egg as a gift from someone in her father`s company. Her personality does not appear to be one suited for Angelic Layer, as pointed out by her father when he comments that he never believed that he would see Kaede compete in a fighting game. Despite this, she is very adept at Angelic Layer. She treats her angel, Brunashe, as her own daughter.
She also appears in Chobits as Minoru Kokubunji`s late older sister.</description>
<picture>48658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18138" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-10">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Jounouchi Sai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>16 year old Jounouchi Sai, known as the "Ice Machine," started playing Angelic Layer at the request of her terminally ill sister Rin. Rin designed what the angel would look like, but died before Sai could create her. As a result, Sai states that her reason for playing Angelic Layer is "to become strong." Sai is from Kanagawa Prefecture and was the runner-up in the Kantou Regional games in the past year. She is friends with Kaede, who went to the same middle school as Sai. Her angel is Shirahime.</description>
<picture>48659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18139" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Arisu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arisu is a talented genius Angel-builder who aids her sister in creating Angels. She follows in her sister`s steps as a talented Kung Fu artist, and creates very strong and agile angels. Arisu does not make Angels for herself, suggesting that she is not good at guiding them. Arisu designed Mao and Unpyo to be stronger than Suzuka, but Unpyo loses to Suzuka in record time, which mortifies her and her sister. After sabotaging Hikaru with a transmitter, Arisu is caught by Ohjiro Mihara and is told that Angelic Layer is meant to show true talent and that anyone can be brilliant, thus forcing her to give up cheating to win. She is very sensitive about the Angels she builds, and accuses her sister of not liking the Angels she made after their loss to Hikaru. Arisu creates a balance oriented Angel for herself near the end of the anime, called Arisu, and vows to beat Hikaru in a friendly battle. At the end credits, in the last episode, Arisu is shown fighting the angel Queen with Alice.
Arisu`s name is translated in the Japanese anime credits as "Alice".</description>
<picture>48660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18140" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madoka is a strong competitor in the Kantou Regional games who fights against Suzuka and Hikaru, losing to both. Madoka is a Kung Fu artist, using martial arts as her angel`s chief fighting tactics. She has a strong desire to defeat Kobayashi Hatoko`s angel, Suzuka to recover her family`s "lost pride". While spectating Hikaru`s fight against another contestant, she and her sister make it clear to Saito Kaede and Jonouchi Sai that she will not lose to anyone until after Suzuka is defeated. Arisu and Madoka sabotage Hikaru with a transmitter that will block Misaki`s thoughts from reaching her doll in the hopes of winning, but are caught by Mihara Ohjirou. After losing, Madoka obtains a new outlook on why people play Angelic Layer and realizes that it was made to be fun for any person, to the slight annoyance of her sister. Madoka`s angels are created by her younger sister, Arisu.</description>
<picture>48661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18141" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="3">5.96</rating>
<name>Ringo Seto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ringo is a 14 year old pop idol from Tochigi who plays Angelic Layer over the objections of her manager. In order to become strong and beat Hikaru, she studies Hikaru`s past battles, notably against Suzuka because she didn`t lose quickly. Ringo likes living freely and often escapes from her manager to get out of doing work. When Misaki was fighting her male classmate Ryo Misaki in a set of Angelic Layer matches, Ringo encouraged Misaki on between matches. Ringo`s angel is Ranga.</description>
<picture>48662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18142" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Ringo no Manager</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4217" picture="151698.jpg">Yanagisawa Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18143" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Shibata Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18144" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="1">4.15</rating>
<name>Shibata Hijiri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32890" type="main character in" update="2011-05-29">
<rating votes="3">3.26</rating>
<name>Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Angel</description>
<picture>72488.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1612" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">システムダウン!? 嵐の船上決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">System Down? A Battle Onboard a Boat Amidst a Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Systemversagen! Entscheidungskampf auf stürmischer See</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">System Down! Combat décisif sur un bateau en pleine tempête.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Sistema Caiu?! Uma Batalha Na Tempestade!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">System Down!? Arashi no Senjou Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1613" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵がいっぱい! あこがれの全国大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lots of Formidable Opponents! The Much Anticipated National Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Viele starke Gegner! Die Landesmeisterschaft beginnt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les jeux nationaux, de nombreux adversaires.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Muitos Oponentes Formidáveis! A Grandeza Do Torneio Nacional!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki ga Ippai! Akogare no Zenkokutaikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1614" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたに決めた! ミサキの選んだヒト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Choose You! Misaki`s Chosen Person</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Du sollst an meiner Seite sein! Misakis Auserwählter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celui que Misaki a choisi.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu Escolho Você! A Escolha De Misakichi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata ni Kimeta! Misaki no Eranda Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1615" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決勝戦! ヒカルのラストアタック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Match! Hikaru`s Last Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das große Finale! Hikarus letzter Angriff</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La finale ! la dernière attaque de Hikaru.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Batalha Final! O Última Ataque De Hikaru!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kesshousen! Hikaru no Last Attack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1616" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白姫 vs 鈴鹿! アイスマシーンの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shirahime vs Suzuka! The Ice Machine`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Shirahime gegen Suzuka! Das Geheimnis der Eismaschine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hatoko contre Sai Jonouchi.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Shirahime Vs Suzuka! O Segredo Da Máquina De Gelo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shirahime vs Suzuka! Ice Machine no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1617" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あきらめない! そして天使[エンジェル]は生まれた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never Give Up! And Then an Angel was Born</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich gebe nicht auf! Und ein neuer Angel ward geboren</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je n`abandonnerai pas et un ange est né.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Nunca Desistir! Um Angel Nasceu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akiramenai! Soshite Angel wa Umareta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1618" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌え! みさき デウスはアイドル!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sing Misaki! The Deus is an Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sing, Misaki, sing! Der Deus ist ein Popidol!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chante Misaki ! L`adversaire est une star !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Cante, Misaki! O Deus É Um Ídolo?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utae! Misaki - Deus wa Idol!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1619" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純白のブランシェ 楓のほほえみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pure White Blanche - Kaede`s Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blanche, Unschuld in Weiß - Kaedes Lächeln</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Blanche si pure. Le sourire de Kaede.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Branca E Pura Buranshe! O Sorriso De Kaede!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junpaku no Blanche - Kaede no Hohoemi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1620" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みさき vs ミサキ? 危険な同級生[クラスメイト]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misaki vs Misaki? The Dangerous Classmate</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Misaki gegen Misaki - Ein gefährlicher Mitschüler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Misaki contre Misaki. Une camarade dangereuse.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Misaki Vs Misaki?! Um Perigoso Colega De Classe!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki vs Misaki? Kiken na Classmate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1621" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みさきと虎太郎 ♡ 二人のわくわくデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misaki and Kotaru - The Two`s Exciting Date</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Misaki und Kotaro, ein aufregendes Date</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Misaki et Kotaro, le rendez-vous.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Misaki E Kotaro! Um Encontro Excitante!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki to Kotarou - Futari no Waku-waku Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1622" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギリギリの戦い... みさきのラストチャンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight to the Limit... Misaki`s Last Chance</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf Messers Schneide - Misakis letzte Chance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un combat difficile ! La dernière chance de Misaki.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Lutando No Limite...! Última Chance De Misaki!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giri-giri no Tatakai... Misaki no Last Chance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1623" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着! ヒカルとマオの真剣勝負</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Match! Hikaru and Mao`s Real Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Es wird ernst, Hikarus und Maos großer Kampf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Conclusion ! un combat important pour Hikaru et Mao.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Acabe Com Ela! A Partida Decisiva De Hikaru E Mao!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku! Hikaru to Mao no Shinkenshoubu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1624" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光速の鈴鹿! 鳩子のライバル宣言!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light-Speed Suzuka! Hatoko`s Declaration of Rivalry</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die blitzschnelle Suzuka - Hatokos Kampfansage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quel défi ! Un combat avec Hatoko.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Suzuka, A Velocidade Da Luz! Declaração De Rivalidade De Hatoko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousoku no Suzuka! Hatoko no Rival Sengen!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1625" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いじわる姉妹! 狙われたヒカル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mean Sisters! And the Targeted Hikaru</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die fiesen Schwestern, Hikaru wird zum Ziel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des sœurs malveillantes ! Hikaru est visée.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Irmãs Malvadas! Hikaru É O Alvo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ijiwaru Shimai! Nerawareta Hikaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1626" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使の翼よ! 私とヒカルをいざなって</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angels Wings! Pull Me and Hikaru Together</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mögen die Schwingen der Engel mich und Hikaru ans Ziel tragen!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ailes de l`ange ! Guidez-nous Hikaru et moi !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Que As Asas De Um Anjo Guiem A Mim E A Hikaru!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Ysubasa yo! Watashi to Hikaru o Izanatte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1627" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">負けたくない! ヒカルを信じて...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Want to Lose! Please Believe in Hikaru</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich will nicht verlieren - Ich glaube an dich, Hikaru</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne veux pas perdre. Je crois en Hikaru...</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu Não Quero Perder! Estou Acreditando Em Hikaru!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maketakunai! Hikaru o Shinjite...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1628" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の再会 涙に濡れたエンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fateful Reunion - An Angel Soaked with Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schicksalhaftes Wiedersehen! Ein tränennasser Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réunies par le destin ! Des anges mouillés de larmes.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Reunião Familiar! Um Angel Ensopado De Lágrimas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Saikai - Namida ni Nureta Angel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1629" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使が舞いおりた日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day the Angel Descended</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tag, an dem ein Engel herabschwebte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ange tombé du ciel.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Dia Que O Anjo Desceu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi ga Maiorita Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1630" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みさきに届け! この想い虹を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reach Out to Misaki! This Feeling is Over the Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Greif nach dem Glück, Misaki! Die Erfüllung am Ende des Regenbogens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dis-le à Misaki ! Cette pensée traverse l`arc-en-ciel.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Declaração Para Misaki! O Sentimento Sob O Arco-Íris!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki ni Todoke! Kono Omoi Niji o Koete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1631" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたは誰? みさきのドキドキレッスン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Are You? Misaki`s Heart-Pounding Lesson</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer bist du? Eine Lektion in Nervenstärke</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qui est-tu ? L`expérience palpitante de Misaki.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Quem é Você?! A Lição Emocionante De Misaki!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata wa Dare? Misaki no Doki-doki Lesson</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1632" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法の壁を破れ! みさき vs 王二郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Break into the Magical Wall! Misaki vs Ohjiro</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Durchbrich die magische Barriere! Misaki gegen Ohjiro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fais tomber le mur magique ! Misaki contre Ojiro.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Quebrando A Barreira Mágica! Misaki Vs Ohjiro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou no Kabe o Yabure! Misaki vs Oujirou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1633" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれヒカル! はじめてのファイト!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Try Our Best, Hikaru! The First Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tu dein Bestes, Hikaru! Heute ist dein erster Kampf!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Courage Hikaru pour ton premier combat !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Vamos Lá Hikaru! A Primeira Batalha!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganbare Hikaru! Hajimete no Fight!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1634" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突然の二人きり 秘密のダブルデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suddenly Alone Together - The Secret Double Date</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Und plötzlich sind wir ganz für uns! Zwei unverhoffte Rendezvous</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Double rendez-vous secret.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">De Repente Juntos E Sozinhos! O Segredo Do Encontro Duplo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsuzen no Futari Kiri - Himitsu no Double Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1635" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめまして! 私だけのエンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Do You Do? My Very Own Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hallo wie gehts? Mein eigener Angel!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Enchantée ! C`est mon ange à moi.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Prazer Em Conhecê-la! Seja Meu Único Angel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimemashite! Watashi Dake no Angel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1636" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の海! 誰かが誰かに恋してる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Summer Sea! Someone is in Love with Someone</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sonne, Sand und Meer! Jemand hat sich verliebt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mer en été ! Quelqu`un est amoureux de quelqu`un.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Verão Na Praia! Quem Está Apaixonado Por Quem?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no umi! Dareka ga dareka ni koi shiteru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1637" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵はいっちゃん? 戸惑いの二回戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Enemy is Icchan? The Stuttering Second Match</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freund oder Feind? Die zwei Gesichter von Onkelchen Icchan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Icchan est-il un ennemi ? Un jeu étrange.</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Icchan É O Meu Oponente?! O Confuso Segundo Round!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki wa Icchan? Tomadoi no Nikai Sen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38113" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38228" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38229" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125221" update="2010-11-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">10th Anniversary Song - Be My Angel ~memorial wing~</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
