<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1734" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>40</episodecount>
<startdate>1977-06-04</startdate>
<enddate>1978-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Chou Denji Machine Voltes V</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Super Electromagnetic Machine Voltes V</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Super Electron Machine Voltes V</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ultra Electromagnetic Machine Voltes V</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Robot Romance Trilogy (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Voltes V</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Roman Robo Series 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Voltes 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">超電磁マシーン ボルテスV</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Vultus V</title>
<title xml:lang="tl" type="official">Voltes V</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1814" type="Other">Chou Denji Robo Com Battler V</anime>
<anime id="1815" type="Other">Toushou Daimos</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="274570">One of the epic old anime 

I don`t recommend seeing this if you want good animation and everything is so old school you might get bored of it but story is nice can be watch by all ages.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="192559">One of my first anime that I watched when I was small. Both sides are very creative and background story is likeable. This is the kind of anime that I recommend  for a remake</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="4444" type="Music">Tsutsui Hiroshi</name>
<name id="5441" type="Character Design">Kanayama Akihiro</name>
<name id="6544" type="Character Design">Sasakado Nobuyoshi</name>
<name id="5725" type="Chief Direction">Nagahama Tadao</name>
<name id="6526" type="Original Work">Yatsude Saburou</name>
<name id="1062" type="Character Design">Hijiri Yuki</name>
</creators>
<description>In the future evil horned aliens from the planet Boazan decide to add the citizens of earth to their empire. The Boazan race are a curious mixture of high scientific achievement and medieval culture in which hornless Boazanians are considered slaves. One aristocratic child was born without horns, but was fitted with fake ones. He became a great scientific genius, and was next in line for the throne of Boazan. The cunning Zambojil, however, found out the truth and the genius became a slave, and Zambojil became emperor. The genius led a rebellion of slaves but had to flee to earth. Knowing that Zambojil would want to enslave earth, he set about working with the Earth defense forces including General Oka and Professor Hamaguchi to create the ultimate weapon: the Chodenji Machine Voltes Five! Taking the name Go Kentaro, the Boazan genius married an earthwoman and had three children, Kenichi, Daihhiro and Hiyoshi. These three, together with General Oka`s daughter, Megumi, and the former rodeo star Mine Ippei would pilot Voltes Five.
The second of Tadao Nagahama`s Romance Super Robot Trilogy. (#1: Chou Denji Robo Combattler V, #3: Toushou Daimos)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="142">6.62</permanent>
<temporary count="145">6.99</temporary>
<review count="1">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>128047.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1272</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1069</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600</identifier>
<identifier>fvjvrs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>超電磁マシーン_ボルテスV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3651</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89472</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>844</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="39741" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の戦士への鎮魂曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Father`s Last Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Requiem per un soldato coraggioso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Senshi e no Chinkonkyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39742" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の鷹メカの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mechanical Eagle</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Lo sparviero meccanico</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Taka Mecha no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39743" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙からの侵略者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invaders From Outer Space</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Invasori dallo spazio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu kara no Shinryakusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39744" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墓標が教えた作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Modest Help From The Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Aiuto Dall`Oltretomba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bohyou ga Oshieta Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39745" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底城の陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Conspiracy Against Prince Zardoz</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La congiura contro il principe Heinnel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiteijou no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39746" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底城攻撃開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Traitor Within</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Bandiera di battaglia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiteijou Kougeki Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39747" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">子犬よ明日へ歩め!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Voltes V Learns a Lesson From a Puppy</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Verso il domani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koinu yo Ashita e Ayume!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39748" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謀略の父が地球を狙う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Triumph Of Human Love</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Mio Padre, Il Traditore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bouryaku no Chichi ga Chikyuu o Nerau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39749" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">策略の秘密基地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zuhl`s Evil Scheme</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La base segreta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuryaku no Himitsu Kichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39750" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボアザン星の大攻防戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War Of Two Worlds</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Battaglia dei Boazani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boazan Sei no Dai Koubousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39751" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢が招いた大ピンチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jamie`s Dream Forbode Disaster</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un Sogno Terribile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume ga Maneita Dai Pinch!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39752" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵・新将軍の挑戦状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Enemy, General Ozlack From Boazania</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La follia dell`imperatore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki, Shin Shougun no Chousenjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39753" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャングルの追跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Draco`s Capture</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`inseguimento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jungle no Tsuiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39754" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファルコン壊滅の危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destruction Of Big Falcon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il dottor Barion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Falcon Kaimetsu no Kiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39755" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大宇宙へ出撃せよ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Forth To Boazania</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Avanti a Boazan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiuchuu e Shutsugeki seyo!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39756" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">苦闘への前進</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fate Of Planet Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una Battaglia Disperata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kutou e no Zenshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39757" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切り者の計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Death Of The Boazanian Advisor, Zuhl</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il complotto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri Mono no Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39758" update="2007-07-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔のシャドウ必殺剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Skill To Catch a Butterfly</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Gardo, L`Animale Guerriero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ma no Shadow Hissatsu Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39759" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球を賭けた一騎打ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zandra`s Sacrifice</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una battaglia per la Terra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu o Kakete Ikkiuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39760" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">自爆!! 超電磁ボール!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ultra Electromagnetic Beast Cannon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Esplosione suicida</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jibaku!! Choudenji Ball!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39761" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">血で書いた数字の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Letter Written In Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il messaggio di sangue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi de Kaita Suuji no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39762" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の飛行メカとの合体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volt-In With The Mysterious Mechanical Eagle</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Contatto con oggetto non identificato</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Hikou Mecha to no Gattai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39763" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父と子の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trap of Slave Island</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un uomo chiamato Sakab</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi to Ko no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39764" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">岡防衛長官空に散る!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Commander Robinson`s Falling Star</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La morte di Okanin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oka Bouei Choukan Sora ni Chiru!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39765" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝陛下のプレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Present from the Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`arma dell`imperatore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei Heika no Present</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39766" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボルテス起死回生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Voltes Revived from the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Rinascita di Vultus V</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Voltes Kishikaisei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39767" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボアザン星の勇士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boazanian Fighter`s Tragedy</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ghilvan di Boazan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boazan Sei no Yuushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39768" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえるボルテスV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Recovery of Voltes V</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il ritorno di Vultus 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Voltes V</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39769" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦艦三笠が危機を呼ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Model Ship Brings Big Falcon To a Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La corazzata Mikasa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkan Mikasa ga Kiki o Yobu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39770" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボルテス合体不可能</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Voltes Docking Unsuccessful</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il punto debole di Vultus 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Voltes Gattai Fukanou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39771" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父・剛健太郎の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery Of Armstrong`s Past</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il segreto di Kentarus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi, Gou Kentarou no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39772" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔の細菌攻撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Draco`s Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Guerra batteriologica</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ma no Saikin Kougeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39773" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">崩れゆく邪悪の塔!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Liberation</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La fine di Zambazir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuzure Yuku Jaaku no Tou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39774" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いななけ! 愛馬アイフル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mark And His Thoroughbred Horse, Alpha</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un cavallo di nome Eiffel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inanake! Aiba Eiffel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39775" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば! 敵司令官ハイネル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Battle For Planet Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Addio, principe Sirius</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba! Teki Shireikan Heinel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39776" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">憎しみの炎が危機を呼ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Deadly Seeds Of Hate</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il rapimento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nikushimi no Honoo ga Kiki o Yobu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39777" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新隊員タッコちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Voltes Team`s New MemberR, OCTO-1</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un nuovo membro: Takko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Taiin Takko-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39778" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父よ! 地球は近い!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father! The Earth is Near!!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fuga verso la terra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi yo! Chikyuu wa Chikai!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39779" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父の胸の中でなけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dr. Armstrong`s Rescue</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il ritorno di Kentarus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi no Mune no Naka de Nake!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39780" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛も涙もふりすてろ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Urgent Need For Rigid Training</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un Addestramento Troppo Duro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai mo Namida mo Furisutero!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40364" update="2010-05-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Digest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40365" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 1 30s Dr. Smith</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102039" update="2010-08-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1977-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102040" update="2010-08-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1977-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150214" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 8 Kid on Jumbo Machinder</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150215" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 7 Kid fighting</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150216" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 6 15s Weak kid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150217" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 5 30s Weak kid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150218" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 4 15s Kid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150219" update="2013-10-06">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 3 30s Kid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150220" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Toy Commercials 2 15s Dr. Smith</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150221" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150222" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD CM 30s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150223" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Pilot ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150224" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ep1 Pilot ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150225" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
