<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1744" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-01-26</startdate>
<enddate>1996-01-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sonic the Hedgehog</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソニック・ザ・ヘッジホッグ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6394" type="Same Setting">Sonic: Night of the WereHog - Sonic &amp; Chip Kyoufu no Kan</anime>
<anime id="662" type="Character">Sonic X</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="82150">The plot is laughable and the animation nothing special. The climax is a letdown too and the ending itself is the typical stuff of any anime. It was targeted at children so don`t expect anything too fancy. On the plus side, the game references are good and all the moves are portrayed nicely and even if Tails is annoying (and don`t get me started on that Sera) Sonic and Knuckles are okay. Great music and a nice theme song.
If you want something for nostalgia factor that`s a quick and mindless watch, this is for you, but you`ll probably only enjoy it if you are a Sonic fan.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="8172" type="Music">Tada Mitsuhiro</name>
<name id="4789" type="Character Design">Ninomiya Tsuneo</name>
<name id="10970" type="Original Work">Sega Enterprises</name>
<name id="683" type="Series Composition">Sekijima Mayori</name>
<name id="28199" type="Direction">Ikegami Kazunori</name>
</creators>
<description>When Dr. Eggman (Robotnik in the US version) holds the president and his daughter hostage, Sonic must comply to the evil scientist`s demand of going to Eggmanland to stop Black Eggman and deactivate the city`s generator before it reaches critical mass. Little does Sonic know that it`s a trap to activate Hyper Metal Sonic, a robot counterpart built by Eggman to destroy our hero.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="293">4.10</permanent>
<temporary count="295">6.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>2492.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>221</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2263</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3271</identifier>
<identifier>nztwav</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sonic_the_Hedgehog_(OVA)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6750</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32618" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="4">9.40</rating>
<name>Doctor Eggman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3790" picture="50436.jpg">Takiguchi Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32620" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="22">9.04</rating>
<name>Sonic the Hedgehog</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32623" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-22">
<rating votes="8">5.81</rating>
<name>Tails</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2142" picture="170565.jpg">Shiina Hekiru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="35711" update="2011-12-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エッグマンランドヘむかえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey to Eggmanland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Egg Man Land e Mukae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35712" update="2005-04-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソニックVSメタルソニック!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sonic VS Metal Sonic!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonic vs Metal Sonic!!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
