<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1751" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>23</episodecount>
<startdate>1988-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>1989-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Grimm Meisaku Gekijou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Grimm Masterpiece Theatre</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Grimm Masterpiece Playhouse</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Grimm`s Fairy Tales II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Grimm Masterpiece Theater</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Новый театр шедевров братьев Гримм</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新グリム名作劇場</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Grimm`s Fairy Tale Classics (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Grimms Märchen (2. Staffel)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Raconte-moi une histoire (suite)</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Los cuentos de los hermanos Grimm</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Pohádky bratří Grimmů (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">(2) אגדות האחים גרים</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Grimm legszebb meséi (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Приказките на братя Грим</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="947" type="Prequel">Grimm Meisaku Gekijou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/shin_grimm_meisaku.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3653" type="Character Design">Seki Shuuichi</name>
<name id="6388" type="Character Design">Mori Yasuji</name>
<name id="5877" type="Character Design">Takano Noboru</name>
<name id="7437" type="Character Design">Sakamaki Sadahiko</name>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="1119" type="Work">Asahi Housou</name>
<name id="10642" type="Music">Shimazu Hideo</name>
<name id="10149" type="Original Work">Grimm Kyoudai</name>
</creators>
<description>Every episode is a stand-alone retelling of a different fairy or folk tale. Not all of them are based on the fairy tales collected by the Brothers Grimm.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="49">5.69</permanent>
<temporary count="49">6.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>85874.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2242</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4061</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/1550/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Grimm's_Fairy_Tale_Classics</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3774</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235421</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>618</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="26674" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水晶の玉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crystal Ball</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kristallkugel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La boule de cristal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suishou no Tama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26675" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おくさま狐のご婚礼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wedding of Miss Fox</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Hochzeit der Füchsin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les noces de dame renard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okusama Kitsune no Gokonrei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26676" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の庭と冬の庭の話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story of a Summer Garden and a Winter Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schöne und das Biest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Niwa to Fuyu no Niwa ni Hanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26677" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャベツろば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Donkey Cabbage</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Krautesel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyabetsu Roba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26678" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラプンツェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rapunzel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rapunzel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rapunzel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26679" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">森のなかのばあさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Old Woman in the Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die alte Frau im Wald</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mori no Naka no Obaa-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26680" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どまんじゅう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Grave Mound</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Grabhügel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Domanjuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26681" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼と狐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wolf and the Fox</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Wolf und die Füchsin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le loup et le renard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookami to Kitsune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26682" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホレのおばさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother Holle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Frau Holle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maman Holle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Holle no Oba-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26683" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">六羽の白鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Six Swans</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die sechs Schwäne</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les six cygnes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rokuwa no Hakuchou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26684" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">千びき皮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tousand Animal Hides</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Allerleirauh</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mille fourrures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senbiki Gawa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26685" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉と弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother and Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Brüderlein und Schwesterlein</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ane to Otouto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26686" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名人四人兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Skillful Brothers</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die vier kunstreichen Brüder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meijin Yonnin Kyoudai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26687" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガラス瓶の中の化け物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spirit in the Bottle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Geist in der Flasche</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`esprit dans la bouteille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Glass Bin no Naka no Bakemono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26688" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉄のストーブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Iron Stove</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Eisenofen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le poêle à charbon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tetsu no Stove</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26689" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熊の皮をきた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Wearing a Bearskin</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Bärenhäuter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Peau d`ours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuma no Kawa o Kita Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26690" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">兎とはりねずみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hare and the Hedgehog</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hase und Igel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lièvre et le hérisson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usagi to Hari Nezumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26691" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉄のハンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iron Hans</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eisenhans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tetsu no Hans</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26692" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇敢なチビの仕立て屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Brave Little Tailor</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das tapfere Schneiderlein</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuukan na Chibi no Shitateya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26693" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みそさざいと熊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wren and the Bear</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Zaunkönig und der Bär</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misosazai to Kuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26694" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精の名前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairy`s Name (Rumplestiltskin)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rumpelstilzchen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei no Namae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26695" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">池に住む水の魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Witch in the water</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Nixe im Teich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ondine dans son étang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ike ni Sumu Mizu no Majo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26696" update="2007-03-05">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神の名づけ親</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death`s Godfather</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gevatter Tod</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort diabolique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami no Nazuke Oya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121454" update="2010-08-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121455" update="2010-08-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
