<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1759" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-09-11</startdate>
<enddate>2005-02-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fuujin Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ветряные истории</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">風人物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Windy Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Windy Tales</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3195" approval="24" total="36">Kamichu!</anime>
<anime id="2659" approval="17" total="27">Aria the Animation</anime>
<anime id="11281" approval="1" total="1">Kaze no Matasaburou (2016)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="107433">This is a very calm and relaxing show. Its unique art style and slow-paced story progression may feel a bit repulsive or cheap at beginning, but this series really should be given a chance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="752362">A subtle and aesthetically profound slice of life series. Calming, relaxing, sure. But it is also engaging and evocative. 

It`s about wind. It`s about experiencing life, like clouds being pushed through the sky. 

True art and beauty, and an experience that every slice of life or `healing` anime fan needs to see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/contents/works_sp/1180_/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="6004" type="Character Design">Arakawa Masatsugu</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
</creators>
<description>Nao is a second grade student in junior high school, whose also the leader of the Digital Camera Club - which only consists of two members.
Her favourite place for taking pictures is the roof of the school building, where she prefers to photograph the sky and clouds only. One day, she`s going to the roof as usual and finds a cat which is able to control the wind to fly. Nao is so surprised that she slips off of the roof...
There is also Miki, the best friend of Nao and the second member of the Digital Camera Club, Mr. Taiki, the one who taught the cat how to handle the wind, there`s Ryoko, who holds some love towards Mr. Taiki, as well as Jun, who is going to help Nao and Miki finding the flying cat again and there`s Yukio, the wife of Mr. Taiki`s dead brother.
In the hidden "village of the wind driver" - which is located in the suburbs of the metropolitan - the festival of the wind begins.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="653">6.78</permanent>
<temporary count="658">7.24</temporary>
<review count="2">7.25</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4396.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1524</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1417</identifier>
<identifier>imqxcx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/fuujin-monogatari.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fuujin_Monogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>風人物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>484</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321257</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6961</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-08">
<name>beauty in simplicity</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="57915" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="3">5.92</rating>
<name>Ueshima Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57916" type="main character in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="1">5.70</rating>
<name>Kataoka Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="93" picture="142975.jpg">Hanamura Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57917" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<name>Nomura Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57918" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-19">
<rating votes="1">5.70</rating>
<name>Yoshino Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16992" picture="46181.jpg">Iwamura Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105965" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-07">
<name>Taiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2790" picture="83142.jpg">Sugiyama Ooki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105966" type="appears in" update="2019-10-07">
<name>Yukio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105967" type="appears in" update="2019-10-07">
<name>Makino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2894" picture="170603.jpg">Nakamura Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23159" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風猫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wind Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chat volant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze Neko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24266" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風の祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Festival of Winds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Festival du Vent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze no Matsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24765" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ランニングガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Running Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille qui court</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Running Girl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25039" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どんぐりはムササビ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Acorn the Flying Squirrel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Donguri est un écureuil volant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Donguri wa Musasabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27581" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">保健室物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Infirmary Story</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire de l`infirmerie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokenshitsu Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35212" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">缶けり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kick the Can</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tape-canette</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kan Keri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35213" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">台風が来た</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Typhoon Came</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un Typhon arrive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taifuu ga Kita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35214" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大掃除はチュウの予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Cleaning: Premonition of a Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand-ménage - Prémonition d`un baiser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oosouji wa Chuu no Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35224" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父のオートバイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father`s Motorcycle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La moto de Papa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi no Ooto Bai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35225" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球最後の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Earth`s Last Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dernier jour de la Terre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Saigo no Nichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35226" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜のころ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossom Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le temps des cerisiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Koro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35227" update="2005-03-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーディション顛末記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audition: The Factual Record</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire de l`audition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Audition Tenmatsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35228" update="2006-09-08">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪緒ふたたび</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukio, Once Again</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yukio revient</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukio Futatabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121456" update="2010-08-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121457" update="2010-08-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
