<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1764" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2000-07-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eiga Ojamajo Doremi #</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pop and the Queen`s Cursed Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ojamajo Doremi # Movie: Pop and the Magical Cursed Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">映画 おジャ魔女どれみ#</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1763" type="Parent Story">Ojamajo Doremi #</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20041208022754/http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/doremi/theater.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
<name id="2190" type="Direction">Igarashi Takuya</name>
<name id="5654" type="Music">Oku Keiichi</name>
</creators>
<description>One day Pop was out scavenging with Hana-chan, and found a beautiful rose inside the Queen`s garden. Curious, she picked the rose and brought it home. Unwittingly, that rose can cause all wishes to become true, whether good or bad. Good wishes will turn the rose white and bloom, while bad wishes will turn the rose black and wither. After a heated argument with her sister Doremi, Pop wishes that Doremi loses all her magic and be turned into a mouse. Hilarity ensues, as Doremi and the others try to put everything back to normal.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="112">5.57</permanent>
<temporary count="113">6.44</temporary>
<review count="1">9.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>78437.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3796</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2940</identifier>
<identifier>anduuy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20041208022754/http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/doremi/theater.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162086</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3993</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14734" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="22">5.09</rating>
<name>Harukaze Doremi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Doremi is the protagonist. Doremi reflects a typical mahou shoujo: lively to the point of being noisy, a poor student, clumsy and careless but very compassionate, and has shown to be boy-crazy in earlier seasons. Her favorite food is steak (which she is unable to obtain throughout the entire series). She proclaims herself to be "the unluckiest pretty girl in the whole world." Her name is a play on the first 3 notes of the musical scale DoReMi. Her fairy is Dodo, and is very much like Doremi.</description>
<picture>64455.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14735" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="22">6.40</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Hazuki is a friend of Doremi since kindergarten, is a shy, passive and sweet girl. Hazuki cares about her family very much, especially her mother; she did not really like the dresses she got from her mother, but would do everything that she was asked to do. Hazuki has a large fear of ghosts and tries to counter it with thoughts of Majo Rika; this seldom works. In the end, she chose a specially reputated secondary school rather than staying with Doremi. Her fairy is Rere.</description>
<picture>64456.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1940" picture="21213.jpg">Akiya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14736" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="14">5.87</rating>
<name>Senoo Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senoo Aiko is an outgoing tomboy who has split-curled hair. She is a transfer student from (Osaka in Japanese) and speaks in Kansai-ben, a Japanese dialect originating in Osaka. Her parents are divorced, so she lives with her father, a taxi driver, while her mother, a nurse, works in Osaka. She loves both her parents very much and wishes for them to get back together, even going so far as to attempt forbidden magic to do so. She is also one of the most athletic students in the school, but also has a short temper. In the end, she left with her parents back to Osaka and is living happily with them and her grandpa. Her fairy is Mimi.</description>
<picture>64457.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14737" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="30">8.67</rating>
<name>Segawa Onpu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Segawa Onpu is a famous idol who became a witch apprentice of Majo Ruka, rival of Majo Rika. She is adored by many, mostly boys. She is cool and enigmatic at first, but her kind and selfless heart becomes more apparent as she spends more time with Doremi and her friends. She lives with her mother, who used to be a singer herself before an accident occurred (and has now become her daughter`s agent). Her father is constantly away from home as an engineer. Her fairy is Roro.</description>
<picture>64460.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14739" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="5">3.19</rating>
<name>Makihatayama Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makihatayama Hana was a baby born from the Witch Queen Rose, a large blue flower in the Witch Queen Garden that produces a new baby every 100 years as successor to the throne. Hana is given to Doremi to be cared for after she stumbles across her. In Ojamajo Doremi DOKKAAN, she transforms herself into an 11-year-old so she could attend school with her "mothers" and takes on the name of Hana Makihatayama. Of all her "mothers", Doremi`s personality is more apparent in her. Hana returns to the Witch World with Majo Rika and the fairies in the end.</description>
<picture>42444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14740" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="21">7.03</rating>
<name>Harukaze Pop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Pop is Doremi`s younger sister. She attends Sonatine Kindergarten for the first half of the series and then moves on to Misora First Elementary School in the latter half. She loves to annoy Doremi. She acts older than her age, and has more responsibility than her older sister. Deep inside, she is still a kid at heart who secretly admires Doremi. Her fairy is Fafa.</description>
<picture>64458.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39655" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="58">8.23</rating>
<name>Segawa Onpu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64461.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46646" type="appears in" update="2012-07-02">
<name>Dodo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4480.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1912" picture="21099.jpg">Tokumitsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46647" type="appears in" update="2012-07-02">
<name>Rere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4481.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5897">Mizuki Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46648" type="appears in" update="2012-07-02">
<name>Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4482.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="8393" picture="224321.jpg">Saitou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46649" type="appears in" update="2012-07-02">
<name>Roro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4483.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86443" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="7">8.19</rating>
<name>Harukaze Doremi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Doremi is the protagonist. Doremi reflects a typical mahou shoujo: lively to the point of being noisy, a poor student, clumsy and careless but very compassionate, and has shown to be boy-crazy in earlier seasons. Her favorite food is steak (which she is unable to obtain throughout the entire series). She proclaims herself to be "the unluckiest pretty girl in the whole world." Her name is a play on the first 3 notes of the musical scale DoReMi. Her fairy is Dodo, and is very much like Doremi.</description>
<picture>64449.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86444" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<name>Fujiwara Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Hazuki is a friend of Doremi since kindergarten, is a shy, passive and sweet girl. Hazuki cares about her family very much, especially her mother; she did not really like the dresses she got from her mother, but would do everything that she was asked to do. Hazuki has a large fear of ghosts and tries to counter it with thoughts of Majo Rika; this seldom works. In the end, she chose a specially reputated secondary school rather than staying with Doremi. Her fairy is Rere.</description>
<picture>64453.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1940" picture="21213.jpg">Akiya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86445" type="main character in" update="2018-03-18">
<name>Senoo Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senoo Aiko is an outgoing tomboy who has split-curled hair. She is a transfer student from Osaka and speaks in Kansai-ben, a Japanese dialect originating in Osaka. Her parents are divorced, so she lives with http://anidb.net/ch46535 [her father], a taxi driver, while http://anidb.net/ch46538 [her mother], a nurse, works in Osaka. She loves both her parents very much and wishes for them to get back together, even going so far as to attempt forbidden magic to do so. She is also one of the most athletic students in the school, but also has a short temper. In the end, she left with her parents back to Osaka and is living happily with them and her grandpa. Her fairy is http://anidb.net/ch46648 [Mimi].</description>
<picture>64452.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86446" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="8">8.57</rating>
<name>Harukaze Pop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Pop is Doremi`s younger sister. She attends Sonatine Kindergarten for the first half of the series and then moves on to Misora First Elementary School in the latter half. She loves to annoy Doremi. She acts older than her age, and has more responsibility than her older sister. Deep inside, she is still a kid at heart who secretly admires Doremi. Her fairy is Fafa.</description>
<picture>64454.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="18286" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
