<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1768" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-06-26</startdate>
<enddate>2004-12-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ojamajo Doremi Na-i-sho</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Ojamajo Doremi Naisho</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Bothersome Witch Doremi Se-cr-et</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">DoremiOAV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">DoremiOVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">おジャ魔女どれみ ナ・イ・ショ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1766" type="Parent Story">Motto! Ojamajo Doremi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/doremi_n/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2939" type="Series Composition">Yamada Takashi</name>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
<name id="2208" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umakoshi Yoshihiko</name>
<name id="5654" type="Music">Oku Keiichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Detailing the summer between the http://anidb.net/a1766 [Motto!] and http://anidb.net/a1767 [Dokkaan!] season, looking develop each of the five witches romantically. http://anidb.net/ch14739 [Hana] is back to being a baby... and the mahou shop is a bakery. Each episode centres on a certain character`s "secret", or Na-i-sho.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="124">7.71</permanent>
<temporary count="126">7.45</temporary>
<review count="2">9.24</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2675.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3797</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1376</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3453</identifier>
<identifier>beuijj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/doremi_n/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>408</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>320606</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1662" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-22">
<name>weaponized paper fan</name>
<description>Harisen (ハリセン meaning "slapping fan" in Japanese) is a giant paper fan, usually made in a closed fashion, It is used in Japanese comedy shows as a form of physical comedy (this is what is usually seen in anime when a character smacks another on the head with a paper fan).</description>
<picurl>47539.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2684" parentid="2812" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>New York</name>
<description>The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States. New York City is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2795" parentid="1973" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>baking</name>
<description>The art of making bread, cakes, pastries, pies, tarts, quiches, cookies and similar food in the oven.
Mmmm.... smells nice.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6039" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-18">
<name>piggyback ride</name>
<description>One of the protagonists (usually male) gives another character (usually female) a ride on the back. Can be interpreted as a sign of closeness or endearment in a romance setting.
Reasons: The female character is exhausted from previous running, or has a fit of anaemia, or hurt herself and no longer can walk.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14734" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="22">5.09</rating>
<name>Harukaze Doremi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Doremi is the protagonist. Doremi reflects a typical mahou shoujo: lively to the point of being noisy, a poor student, clumsy and careless but very compassionate, and has shown to be boy-crazy in earlier seasons. Her favorite food is steak (which she is unable to obtain throughout the entire series). She proclaims herself to be "the unluckiest pretty girl in the whole world." Her name is a play on the first 3 notes of the musical scale DoReMi. Her fairy is Dodo, and is very much like Doremi.</description>
<picture>64455.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14735" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="22">6.40</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Hazuki is a friend of Doremi since kindergarten, is a shy, passive and sweet girl. Hazuki cares about her family very much, especially her mother; she did not really like the dresses she got from her mother, but would do everything that she was asked to do. Hazuki has a large fear of ghosts and tries to counter it with thoughts of Majo Rika; this seldom works. In the end, she chose a specially reputated secondary school rather than staying with Doremi. Her fairy is Rere.</description>
<picture>64456.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1940" picture="21213.jpg">Akiya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14736" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="14">5.87</rating>
<name>Senoo Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senoo Aiko is an outgoing tomboy who has split-curled hair. She is a transfer student from (Osaka in Japanese) and speaks in Kansai-ben, a Japanese dialect originating in Osaka. Her parents are divorced, so she lives with her father, a taxi driver, while her mother, a nurse, works in Osaka. She loves both her parents very much and wishes for them to get back together, even going so far as to attempt forbidden magic to do so. She is also one of the most athletic students in the school, but also has a short temper. In the end, she left with her parents back to Osaka and is living happily with them and her grandpa. Her fairy is Mimi.</description>
<picture>64457.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14737" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="30">8.67</rating>
<name>Segawa Onpu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Segawa Onpu is a famous idol who became a witch apprentice of Majo Ruka, rival of Majo Rika. She is adored by many, mostly boys. She is cool and enigmatic at first, but her kind and selfless heart becomes more apparent as she spends more time with Doremi and her friends. She lives with her mother, who used to be a singer herself before an accident occurred (and has now become her daughter`s agent). Her father is constantly away from home as an engineer. Her fairy is Roro.</description>
<picture>64460.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14738" type="main character in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="8">5.55</rating>
<name>Asuka Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka Momoko is a transfer student from New York City and was the apprentice of the late Majo Monroe. Her father is an architect, and her mother is a photographer. She becomes friends with Doremi and the others, who teach her how to speak Japanese. In return, she spends her time teaching them how to bake during Motto! Ojamajo Doremi. Her most prized possession is an earring given to her by Majo Monroe before she passed away. She loved her so much that she even attempted to use forbidden magic to bring her back to life. Momoko returns to America at the end of the series. Her fairy is Nini.</description>
<picture>42443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2360" picture="228063.jpg">Miyahara Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14739" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="5">3.19</rating>
<name>Makihatayama Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makihatayama Hana was a baby born from the Witch Queen Rose, a large blue flower in the Witch Queen Garden that produces a new baby every 100 years as successor to the throne. Hana is given to Doremi to be cared for after she stumbles across her. In Ojamajo Doremi DOKKAAN, she transforms herself into an 11-year-old so she could attend school with her "mothers" and takes on the name of Hana Makihatayama. Of all her "mothers", Doremi`s personality is more apparent in her. Hana returns to the Witch World with Majo Rika and the fairies in the end.</description>
<picture>42444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14740" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="21">7.03</rating>
<name>Harukaze Pop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Pop is Doremi`s younger sister. She attends Sonatine Kindergarten for the first half of the series and then moves on to Misora First Elementary School in the latter half. She loves to annoy Doremi. She acts older than her age, and has more responsibility than her older sister. Deep inside, she is still a kid at heart who secretly admires Doremi. Her fairy is Fafa.</description>
<picture>64458.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39653" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-14">
<name>Tamaki Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1689.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39655" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="58">8.23</rating>
<name>Segawa Onpu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64461.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46463" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Koizumi Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3985.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2204" picture="23065.jpg">Ichimura Oma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46464" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Miyamoto Masaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3999.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2898" picture="228086.jpg">Tsumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46466" type="appears in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Nakata Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4005.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="11020" picture="39571.jpg">Miyashita Michio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46473" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Sagawa Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4094.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3420" picture="228543.jpg">Fujita Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46475" type="appears in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Oota Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4120.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="41926" picture="166716.jpg">Fujita Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46484" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Yada Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4152.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2360" picture="228063.jpg">Miyahara Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46485" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Kotake Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4216.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="650" picture="233419.jpg">Hyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46487" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-30">
<name>Kimura Takao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4234.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2005" picture="188512.jpg">Yamazaki Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46502" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Morikawa Dai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4274.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="19170" picture="50009.jpg">Dounowaki Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46509" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Hasebe Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4329.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="170535.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46514" type="appears in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Satou Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4343.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4665" picture="27220.jpg">Takahashi Naozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46517" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Ijuuin Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4362.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46525" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Iizuka Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4389.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4703" picture="27477.jpg">Tamaki Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46527" type="appears in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Wada Minto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4429.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3875" picture="25549.jpg">Hanioka Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46529" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Harukaze Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33138" picture="90502.jpg">Shino Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46530" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Harukaze Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33139">Mochizuki Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46533" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Ichikawa Koyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8393" picture="224321.jpg">Saitou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46535" type="appears in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Senoo Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3704" picture="76764.jpg">Tsukui Kyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46542" type="appears in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Segawa Tsuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3369" picture="24397.jpg">Yamaga Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46544" type="appears in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Segawa Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4101" picture="26184.jpg">Adachi Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46569" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Seki-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1659" picture="223004.jpg">Katsuragi Nanaho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46575" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Nishizawa Yuuka-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4477.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1912" picture="21099.jpg">Tokumitsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46576" type="appears in" update="2012-07-01">
<name>Kyoutou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32940">Akaida Yoshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46645" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-02">
<rating votes="3">6.08</rating>
<name>Lala</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4479.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="37007" picture="136008.jpg">Takamura Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74963" type="appears in" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Fami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74981" type="appears in" update="2015-05-06">
<name>Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74982" type="appears in" update="2015-05-06">
<name>Yoshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74983" type="appears in" update="2015-05-06">
<name>Genki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74984" type="appears in" update="2015-05-06">
<name>Arima Kenichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3062" picture="170303.jpg">Saeki Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74985" type="appears in" update="2015-05-06">
<name>Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1934" picture="186186.jpg">Aida Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75050" type="appears in" update="2015-05-08">
<name>Waku Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75228" type="appears in" update="2015-05-15">
<name>Ichikawa Koyuki (Shoujo Jidai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173509.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75229" type="appears in" update="2015-05-15">
<name>Atsuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86443" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="7">8.19</rating>
<name>Harukaze Doremi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Doremi is the protagonist. Doremi reflects a typical mahou shoujo: lively to the point of being noisy, a poor student, clumsy and careless but very compassionate, and has shown to be boy-crazy in earlier seasons. Her favorite food is steak (which she is unable to obtain throughout the entire series). She proclaims herself to be "the unluckiest pretty girl in the whole world." Her name is a play on the first 3 notes of the musical scale DoReMi. Her fairy is Dodo, and is very much like Doremi.</description>
<picture>64449.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86444" type="main character in" update="2016-11-29">
<name>Fujiwara Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Hazuki is a friend of Doremi since kindergarten, is a shy, passive and sweet girl. Hazuki cares about her family very much, especially her mother; she did not really like the dresses she got from her mother, but would do everything that she was asked to do. Hazuki has a large fear of ghosts and tries to counter it with thoughts of Majo Rika; this seldom works. In the end, she chose a specially reputated secondary school rather than staying with Doremi. Her fairy is Rere.</description>
<picture>64453.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1940" picture="21213.jpg">Akiya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86445" type="main character in" update="2018-03-18">
<name>Senoo Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senoo Aiko is an outgoing tomboy who has split-curled hair. She is a transfer student from Osaka and speaks in Kansai-ben, a Japanese dialect originating in Osaka. Her parents are divorced, so she lives with http://anidb.net/ch46535 [her father], a taxi driver, while http://anidb.net/ch46538 [her mother], a nurse, works in Osaka. She loves both her parents very much and wishes for them to get back together, even going so far as to attempt forbidden magic to do so. She is also one of the most athletic students in the school, but also has a short temper. In the end, she left with her parents back to Osaka and is living happily with them and her grandpa. Her fairy is http://anidb.net/ch46648 [Mimi].</description>
<picture>64452.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86446" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="8">8.57</rating>
<name>Harukaze Pop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukaze Pop is Doremi`s younger sister. She attends Sonatine Kindergarten for the first half of the series and then moves on to Misora First Elementary School in the latter half. She loves to annoy Doremi. She acts older than her age, and has more responsibility than her older sister. Deep inside, she is still a kid at heart who secretly admires Doremi. Her fairy is Fafa.</description>
<picture>64454.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="19077" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波乱のサイクリング 男の子のないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Screwed Up Bicycle Trip: The Secret of the Boys</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haran no Cycling: Otokonoko no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39783" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">N.YのMAHO堂 ももこのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maho-dou in New York: Momoko`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New York no Mahoudou: Momoko no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39784" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">泳いでナンボ! あいこのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Value of Swimming! Aiko`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyoide Nanbo! Aiko no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39864" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノンスタンダード おんぷのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Non-standard: Onpu`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Non-standard: Onpu no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39907" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙を知るひと ぽっぷとハナのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someone Who Knows the Sorrow: Pop and Hana`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida o Shiru Hito: Pop to Hana no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40874" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">金平糖の思い出 ばあやのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories in Confeito: Baaya`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Confeito no Omoide: Baaya no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41413" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイヤキダイスキ! 親子のないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love Taiyaki! Father and Son`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyaki Daisuki! Oyako no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45722" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リコーダー事件! 優等生のないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Case of the Flute! Secret of the Honor Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Recorder Jiken! Yuutousei no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46800" update="2006-06-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バッチグー野球部 魔女たちのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Excellent Baseball Team: The Witches` Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bacchigoo Yakyuubu: Majo-tachi no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46801" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">結婚の約束 幼なじみのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marriage Promise: An Old Friend`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kekkon no Yakusoku: Osananajimi no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46802" update="2006-05-31">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バレンタイヂィ はづきのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Valentine`s Day: Hadzuki`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valentine`s Day: Hazuki no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50527" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">7人目の魔女見習い のんちゃんのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seventh Witch Apprentice: Non-chan`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shichininme no Majo Minarai: Non-chan no Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50528" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時をかけるお雛さま どれみのないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dolls Through the Ages: Doremi`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Kakeru Ohina-sama: Doremi no Naisho</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
