<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1783" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-11</startdate>
<enddate>2004-12-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Genshiken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ゲンシケン</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">現代視覚文化研究会</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Genshiken TV</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Genshiken - Gesellschaft zum Studium moderner visueller Kultur</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Sociedad para el Estudio de la Cultura Visual Moderna</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Гэнсикэн</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">مجتمع دراسة الثقافة المرئية الحديثة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gendai Shikaku Bunka Kenkyuu Kai</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ґеншікен</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">现视研</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">げんしけん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Genshiken: The Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Genshiken</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Genshiken - Club d`étude de la culture visuelle moderne</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Genshiken</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Genshiken</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4782" type="Sequel">Genshiken (2006)</anime>
<anime id="2163" type="Other">Kujibiki Unbalance</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4121" approval="79" total="141">NHK ni Youkoso!</anime>
<anime id="130" approval="29" total="30">Otaku no Video</anime>
<anime id="116" approval="21" total="23">Comic Party</anime>
<anime id="7525" approval="16" total="37">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai</anime>
<anime id="2835" approval="5" total="21">Hachimitsu to Clover</anime>
<anime id="13114" approval="3" total="11">Anime-Gataris</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="74461">for any type of otaku, casual or not.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="604679">an entertaining primer for the otak-urious.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="724513">This is an unexpectedly great anime. It`s so realistic that I can relate to the characters very well. The jokes sneak up on you and slap you hard. Funny and original.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="324043">Must see by all means.watch it and come back and tell i didnt like it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="361783">Must see for all otaku</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.genshiken.info/</url>
<creators>
<name id="975" type="Animation Work">Palm Studio</name>
<name id="974" type="Original Work">Kio Shimoku</name>
<name id="3624" type="Character Design">Oogawara Haruo</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="1508" type="Series Composition">Mizushima Tsutomu</name>
<name id="739" type="Work">Genco</name>
<name id="3624" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oogawara Haruo</name>
<name id="6623" type="Character Design">Kinoshita Hirotaka</name>
<name id="6623" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kinoshita Hirotaka</name>
<name id="6718" type="Direction">Ikehata Takashi</name>
<name id="5148" type="Music">Takumi Masanori</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the same-named seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr974 [Kio Shimoku], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr31447 [Afternoon].
The college freshman http://anidb.net/ch2519 [Sasahara Kanji] dives face first into the Japanese otaku lifestyle of anime, manga, video games, pornographic doujinshi, and the like. What better place to do so than by joining The Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture club at his college.
Note: Kio Shimoku pokes fun at every element of the otaku world. This is an anime for hardcore fans, with very complicated references that will test your knowledge of all things otaku.
— written by Pokute (edited)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7705">7.63</permanent>
<temporary count="7765">8.12</temporary>
<review count="8">8.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83820.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1442</identifier>
<identifier>qifeae</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.genshiken.info/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Genshiken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>げんしけん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>473</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321216</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7025</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2004/genshiken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2927" parentid="2676" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Akihabara</name>
<description>Akihabara is a common name for the area around Akihabara Station in the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo, Japan. It gained the nickname Akihabara Electric Town shortly after World War II for being a major shopping center for household electronic goods and the post-war black market. Nowadays, Akihabara is considered by many to be an otaku cultural center and a shopping district for video games, anime, manga, and computer goods.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214314.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4207" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>doujin</name>
<description>Doujin is a general Japanese term for a group of people or friends who share an interest, activity, hobbies, or achievement. The word is sometimes translated into English as clique, coterie, society, or circle (e.g., a "sewing circle").
In Japan the term is used to refer to amateur self-published works, including but not limited to manga, novels, fan guides, art collections, music and video games. Some professional artists participate as a way to publish material outside the regular publishing industry.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68439.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4573" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>Comiket</name>
<description>Comiket, also known as the Comic Market, is the world`s largest self-published http://anidb.net/t6989 [comic book fair], held twice a year in Tokyo, Japan.</description>
<picurl>167005.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2519" type="main character in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="89">4.89</rating>
<name>Sasahara Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wishy-washy Sasahara Kanji is a freshman at Suioh University. He joins the Genshiken after a little persuasion from Kousaka Makoto and quickly engulfs himself in the otaku universe</description>
<picture>17825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="610" picture="18093.jpg">Ooyama Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2520" type="main character in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="88">4.38</rating>
<name>Kousaka Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Makoto is an all-out otaku who joined Genshiken at the same time as Sasahara. He is a happy-go-lucky type who is mostly oblivious to the world around him.
Kousaka and his childhood friend Kasukabe both enroll at the university at the same time and become lovers shortly after the start of the story.</description>
<picture>17826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2521" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="165">8.29</rating>
<name>Madarame Harunobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madarame often tries to play the role of a tough, military otaku but never quite manages to pull it off. Kasukabe often pick on him because of this.
When the original president resigns, Madarame takes over and thus become the second president in the history of Genshiken.</description>
<picture>17827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2522" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="58">5.70</rating>
<name>Tanaka Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanaka is a master of cosplay. He can create any outfit in a week, often in less time if necessary but he never cosplays himself. At conventions he uses the alias Fukurou.
Later in the anime he starts going out with Kanaka Oono</description>
<picture>17828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2523" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="57">3.45</rating>
<name>Kugayama Mitsunori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kugayama is a stuttering, taciturn person. Initially he is the only person in Genshiken who can draw reasonably well but he usually never do more than rough sketches.</description>
<picture>17829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6405" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="13">3.72</rating>
<name>Enomoto Chihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very good natured person who is nicknamed "Happy Fortune" by his friend Mugio. His parents died when he was 10 years old, and since that time he has been living with his seemingly irresponsible older sister. Having fended for himself for quite some time, he is very good with cooking and cleaning. His role in the group is that of the secretary.</description>
<picture>23773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6406" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="18">7.41</rating>
<name>Akiyama Tokino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cheerful (though not overly bright) second-year student at Rikkyoin High. She is the group`s "President", and therefore is a candidate to be next year`s Student Council President. Tokino loves mushrooms to the point of obsession. Her knowledge of mushrooms is encyclopaedic; she knows them by sight and has an insatiable appetite for them. She is often seen carrying around a thick book entitled Mushrooms of the World.</description>
<picture>23774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6407" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="33">8.69</rating>
<name>Ritsuko Kubel Kettenkrad</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A half-German girl, Ritsuko is the current President of the Student Council, and a childhood friend of Chihiro. Despite their childhood promise (revealed in the anime as a promise that he will marry her if she stops "being a crybaby") and her obvious feelings for him, she works hard to hide these from him throughout the series. She wears a helmet which seems to be a mark of the office she holds. It seems she used to cry a lot, and has been working hard to stop her tears in an attempt to perhaps live up to a promise she made to Chihiro.</description>
<picture>23775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6408" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="14">4.47</rating>
<name>Kamishakujii Renko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A highly-strung, overachieving girl who considers Tokino her arch-enemy. Renko`s history with Tokino goes back to their days in kindergarten: it is revealed that Tokino once took so long in the bathroom that Renko, unable to wait any longer, wet herself. Ever since that time, Renko has made it her personal mission to somehow embarrass and humiliate Tokino in return. Renko has the unusual ability to read an entire book in under a minute—but unfortunately, she can only remember the information she has read for three minutes afterward.</description>
<picture>23776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6410" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="17">6.23</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Vice-President and possibly Secretary of the current Student Council. Like Izumi, Kasumi comes from a yakuza family, and lost her parents as a child. She always carries a sword. She is cold and reserved, a ferocious fighter, and she seems to have only allowed one person—Ritsuko—to be truly close to her. She also has a habit of speaking her mind, which at time frightens Risa.</description>
<picture>23778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6411" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="11">4.45</rating>
<name>Lisa Humvee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Current Student Council Treasurer. Because Ritsuko counts on her, and treated her with respect when few of the other students in the school would, Lisa has become very faithful and unwaveringly loyal to Ritsuko. She is American.</description>
<picture>23779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6412" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="15">5.95</rating>
<name>Yamada Kaoruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Renko`s team, clearly in awe of and devoted to Renko. Her primary job seems to be trying to keep "Renko-sama" calm, but she does not succeed all that often.</description>
<picture>23780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6413" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="12">5.28</rating>
<name>Enomoto Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chihiro`s elder sister (but her appearance makes her look like his younger sister), and a maths teacher at Rikkyoin. While she can typically be found wearing glasses her personality can change when her glasses are not being worn. She is also very clumsy at times, often falling down sets of stairs and seems to really like sake and just relaxing in her underwear when she doesn`t need to be dressed.</description>
<picture>23781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6414" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="13">5.64</rating>
<name>Asagiri Komaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A quiet and thoughtful girl, in line to be the next Student Council treasurer. She seems to be the sole caretaker for her younger triplet brothers and a frail younger sister called Koyuki. Komaki is very smart, and when at home does all chores to keep the house running smoothly for her and her siblings.</description>
<picture>23782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6415" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="6">4.37</rating>
<name>Rokuhara Mugio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A good friend of Chihiro`s, surprisingly uncompetitive in the face of the Kujibiki. His team lost early on so he never got a chance to face off against Chihiro`s team.</description>
<picture>23784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6416" type="appears in" update="2009-04-22">
<rating votes="11">4.52</rating>
<name>Tachibana Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tough and unsentimental girl, the next possible Student Council Vice-President. It is implied that her family has yakuza connections, and she is often seen playing high-stakes games of Mahjong—a game in which she is extremely skilled. Another self-reliant character, Izumi does her best to make her own living through gambling and shuns offers of outside help.</description>
<picture>23785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7108" type="main character in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="200">6.62</rating>
<name>Oono Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>American high school, joining the Genshiken at the beginning of the Fall term. Normally soft-spoken and easily embarrassed, Ohno is surprisingly upfront when it comes to one of her two main passions: cosplay. With a nice figure and large bosom, Ohno and her cosplaying (using costumes sewn personally by Tanaka, whom she begins dating) quickly become Genshiken`s main attraction at student fairs. Ohno`s other main passion is yaoi involving muscular, middle-aged, exceedingly bald men. One of the reasons Ohno joins Genshiken in the first place is because only they would accept her fetish. She is also close to Saki, as Saki was the first one to find out about Ohno`s preference for older men.</description>
<picture>138881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7109" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="50">8.25</rating>
<name>Gendai Shikaku Bunka Kenkyuukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>29215.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7448" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="144">7.61</rating>
<name>Ogiue Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fifth president of Genshiken and former member of the Manga Society, Ogiue is a girl who seemingly hates otaku, particularly female ones, but is arguably more perverse of a yaoi fan than Ohno. Ogiue`s tastes in yaoi stem from a preference for shounen series, and like Kugayama she is an amateur artist. Despite her harsh attitude, Ogiue is actually easily coerced into doing things to which she initially objects. Ogiue has a tendency to fantasize about and then draw highly sexual homosexual encounters between the men she knows in real life, particularly Sasahara and Madarame. Ogiue has terrible eyesight, normally wears contacts, and speaks a Tohoku dialect when not speaking Japanese formally. Her most distinctive feature is her paintbrush-like hairstyle, and her last resort when losing an argument is to try and jump out of a nearby window.</description>
<picture>26047.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9990" type="main character in" update="2010-06-24">
<rating votes="147">5.84</rating>
<name>Kasukabe Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka`s girlfriend. Fashionable, violent, confident, occasionally smokes, and not at all attracted by the sexual charms of cartoon characters, Saki is not an otaku in any sense of the word. She follows Kousaka into Genshiken, and is eventually blackmailed by the first Genshiken chairman into joining the club. Surprisingly, Saki actually saves Genshiken from being shut down on two separate occasions, though her motives have more to do with revenge and guilt than becoming more of an otaku.
Despite being vehemently against otaku activities such as wearing nekomimi (cat-ears) at the start of the series, Saki eventually becomes comfortable with the other club members to the point that she can be considered their close friend (aside from the possible exception of Kuchiki). Saki has a tendency to use nicknames. She calls Sasahara "Sasayan", Kugayama "Kugapii", and Ogiue "Ogichin" by nicknames, and even though she at first refuses to call Kuchiki by his self-appointed nickname ("Kucchi"), Saki starts using that nickname as well.</description>
<picture>30145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33096" type="appears in" update="2011-06-06">
<rating votes="38">3.02</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>6347.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56484" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="14">4.40</rating>
<name>Sasahara Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60304" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="3">7.18</rating>
<name>Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60305" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Haraguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60306" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Takayanagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60307" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Sawazaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60308" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kitagawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60310" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>MC</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60311" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Alex</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60312" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Takashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60313" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Mizudori Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9606" picture="35844.jpg">Endou Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60314" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Okada</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5011" picture="68997.jpg">Higasayama Tsugumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60315" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Kimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Part of the school council.</description>
<picture>152922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60316" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Ishida</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60317" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<name>Suzuki Kenji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66842" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Iinchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23602" update="2006-09-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="34">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">現代における視覚を中心とした文化の研究</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Study of the Modern Visual Culture</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le club d`études de la culture visuelle moderne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gendai ni Okeru Shikaku o Chuushin to Shita Bunka no Kenkyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25061" update="2004-12-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消費と遊興による現代青少年の比較分類</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comparative Classification of Consumption and Diversion Among Modern Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les jeunes, la consommation et le divertissement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouhi to Yuukyou ni Yoru Gendai Seishounen no Hikaku Bunrui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25247" update="2004-11-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地域文化振興の問題点とその功績</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Issue of Regional Cultural Advancement and Its Merits</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`exposition, son succès et ses problèmes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiiki Bunka Shinkou no Mondaiten to Sono Kouseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25576" update="2004-11-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">扮装と仮装の異化による心理的障壁の昇華作用</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sublimated Process of Mental Blocks Regarding the Dissimilation Between Dress and Costume</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`effet sublimatoire du déguisement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funsou to Kasou no Ika ni Yoru Shinriteki Shouheki no Shouka Sayou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25823" update="2004-11-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自律行動に見る排斥と受容の境界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boundary Between Rejection and Acceptance Seen in Autonomous Behavior</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Acceptation et refus de l`indépendance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiritsu Koudou ni Miru Haiseki to Juyou no Kyoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26052" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サブカルチャーをめぐる他者との関係論</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Subculture and Its Circular Relationship to Others Surrounding It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rapport aux autres à travers la subculture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subculture o Meguru Tasha to no Kankeiron</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26271" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対人関係における行動選択の特徴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Characteristics of Actions and Decision in Personal Relationships</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réaction caractéristique dans les rapports humains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taijin Kankei ni Okeru Koudou Sentaku no Tokuchou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26363" update="2004-12-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">量産型製造過程における比較研究</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comparative Research of the Mass Production Process</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Étude sur la fabrication des maquettes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryousangata Seizou Katei ni Okeru Hikaku Kenkyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26364" update="2006-09-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特殊閉鎖状況下における説明義務の有無について</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Concerning Whether Explanation Is Obligatory Under Special Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comportement en huis clos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokushu Heisa Joukyuuka ni Okeru Setsumei Gimu no Umu ni Tsuite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26365" update="2008-03-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">経済効果から考える余暇消費のフェティシズム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fetishism of Leisure Spending Taking into Account Economic Effect</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fétichisme vu à travers l`économie de loisir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keizai Kouka kara Kangaeru Yoka Shouhi no Fetishism</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26366" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="25">9.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">都市型犯罪における悪意の所在論</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Position of Malice in the Phenomenon of Urban Crimes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La préméditation dans les crimes urbains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshigata Hanzai ni Okeru Akui no Shozairon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26367" update="2008-03-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">組織の再構築時に発生する課題と対策</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Problems and Countermeasures Arise When an Organization Undergoes Reconstruction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tâches pour la reconstruction d`un organisme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshiki no Saikouchikuji ni Hassei Suru Kadai to Taisaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42133" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42134" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71766" update="2007-04-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus DVD2 - Tokyo Character Show 2004</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154000" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154001" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154002" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154003" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154004" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154005" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154006" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154007" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154008" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154009" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154010" update="2013-09-11">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
