<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="179" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2000-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boogiepop wa Warawanai: Boogiepop Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Бугипоп никогда не смеется</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Фантомът Бугипоп никога не се смее</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Бугіпоп-Фантом</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">幻影死神</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="short">Бугипоп</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BP</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Boogiepop</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブギーポップは笑わない Boogiepop Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Boogiepop Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Boogiepop Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Boogiepop Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Boogiepop Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">בוגיפופ</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Boogiepop Phantom</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13899" type="Parent Story">Boogiepop wa Warawanai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="99" approval="84" total="94">Serial Experiments Lain</anime>
<anime id="1265" approval="3" total="6">Mousou Dairinin</anime>
<anime id="3291" approval="1" total="5">Jigoku Shoujo</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="31156">"For fans" only because I think this anime is too sophisticated for the average viewer. You will have to piece together the plot on your own, instead of having it fed to you. The visuals and sounds are both unique, and lend well to the atmosphere portrayed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="534603">Pros:  Episodic format, cool and eerie stories, interesting ideas

Cons:  Can be difficult to follow, a bit grimdark, and the artwork can get sort of dull.

Bottom line:  This series might not be for everyone but I loved it.  If you like philosophical and episodic based shows I highly recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="20064">unconventionnal anime lovers GO !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="386728">This show is really underrated. 

The story can be quite difficult to follow and the outdated animation(looking at it from 2019 point-of-view) will be a turn-off for some but investing the time in watching sure is rewarding. 

Can`t really say the show is outstanding, given how it ended, but there is something that didn`t made me sigh at the very end as it has happened with other shows. On the contrary - it made me want to got through it one more time. The ending tightens all the loose ends throughout the series and justifies it all. All in all, a great show! 

Considering how we have another Boogiepop airing right now this might be the perfect time to give this one a go.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="5807">Unique storytelling.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20070309184239/http://www.vap.co.jp/boogie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="2315" type="Series Composition">Murai Sadayuki</name>
<name id="6575" type="Character Design">Suga Shigeyuki</name>
<name id="8905" type="Original Work">Kadono Kouhei</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Boogiepop light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr8905 [Kadono Kouhei] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr8904 [Ogata Kouji].
A scream in the night, and in that instant the world changed... or at least, it appeared to.
http://anidb.net/ch52883 [Boogiepop], also called Death, hangs out in the city, and whenever you encounter it, she`ll take you with her. http://anidb.net/ch53367 [Kirima Nagi], a high school student, seems to be fighting Boogiepop, or to at least try to. But then there are disappearances everywhere, and strange happenings occur. And nobody sees the link between them. In a mixture of chaos and thrilling horror, Nagi tries to find out what happened, and why it still hasn`t happened to her.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2346">6.09</permanent>
<temporary count="2369">7.15</temporary>
<review count="9">8.10</review>
</ratings>
<picture>231574.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>82</identifier>
<identifier>jlneed</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20070309184239/http://www.vap.co.jp/boogie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Boogiepop_Phantom</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブギーポップは笑わない</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159838</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3460</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/581</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2000/boogiepop</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="17">
<externalentity>
<identifier>boogiepop</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7092</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2214" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-05">
<name>paranoia</name>
<description>Paranoia is a thought process believed to be heavily influenced by anxiety or fear, often to the point of irrationality and delusion. Paranoid thinking typically includes persecutory beliefs, or beliefs of conspiracy concerning a perceived threat towards oneself. Paranoia is distinct from phobias, which also involve irrational fear, but usually no blame. Making false accusations and the general distrust of others also frequently accompany paranoia. For example, an incident most people would view as an accident or coincidence, a paranoid person might believe was intentional.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3328" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>melancholic</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4715" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-07-01">
<name>dementia</name>
<description>Serious emotional and mental deterioration of organic or functional origin, often age-related.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5104" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-11-22">
<name>vignetted picture</name>
<description>In photography and optics, vignetting is a reduction of an image brightness or saturation at the periphery compared to the image center, usually caused by faulty optics.
Although vignetting is normally unintended and undesired, it is sometimes purposely introduced for example in comics, animation or video games as a creative, false camera effect, such as to draw attention to the center of the screen.</description>
<picurl>43292.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="52883" type="main character in" update="2018-03-10">
<rating votes="2">9.64</rating>
<name>Boogiepop</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53356" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-02">
<name>Jounouchi Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36034" picture="172051.jpg">Hodoshima Shizuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53357" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<name>Saotome Masami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53358" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Tonomura Moto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53359" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<name>Suzuki Yasuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="487" picture="61736.jpg">Watanabe Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53360" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<name>Boogiepop Phantom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53361" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Hoken no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17286" picture="46639.jpg">Katou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53362" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5322" picture="29436.jpg">Fukamizu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53363" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Chichioya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4690" picture="49427.jpg">Itou Kazuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53364" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Sasaoka Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53365" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Kisugi Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kisugi Makiko is the doctor treating Jounouchi Hisashi. She gives him the drug that eventually gives him his strange power.</description>
<picture>133067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53366" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Jounouchi (Shougakusei)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133069.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53367" type="main character in" update="2013-03-03">
<rating votes="2">7.04</rating>
<name>Kirima Nagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53368" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Morita Junsa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53382" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Arifuji Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arifuji Misuzu is a student of Hijiridani High School, Class 3-5. Nicknamed "Panuru", she is known for her philosophy of accepting and loving the world as it is, with all its chaos and ugliness.
The reality is that Misuzu has repressed her memories of finding the corpse of her best friend, Touyama Megumi, a victim of the serial killer five years ago. As a coping mechanism, she tries to live Megumi`s life in addition to hers, and soon becomes allies with Manticore Phantom under the pretense of her spreading of Panuru`s worldview, a ruse for Manticore killing humans.</description>
<picture>133100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4710" picture="27532.jpg">Nasu Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53383" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Suema Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133106.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53384" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Suganuma Youji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53385" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Touyama Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Touyama Megumi was Arifuji Misuzu`s best friend. She was the one who actually told Misuzu about "Panuru" and his philosophy of acceptance.
She was killed by the serial killer 5 years ago, and the shock of finding her body in Kitaguchi Park led to Misuzu`s eventual separation from reality.</description>
<picture>133105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5011" picture="68997.jpg">Higasayama Tsugumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53390" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Yamamoto Junsa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Officer Yamamoto is a colleague of http://anidb.net/ch53368 [Officer Morita].</description>
<picture>133102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46547" picture="189704.jpg">Kobayashi Soutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53393" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Kuroda Shinpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19751" picture="86101.jpg">Chikada Wasei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94425" type="main character in" update="2018-03-10">
<rating votes="1">8.81</rating>
<name>Miyashita Touka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94569" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-16">
<name>Poom Poom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5260" picture="29319.jpg">Tochihara Rakuto</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1744" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Poom Poom プーム プーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Poom Poom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Poom Poom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1745" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Interlude 間奏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Interlude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Interlude: Kansou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1746" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MY FAIR LADY けがれなき少女への愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Fair Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Fair Lady: Kegarenaki Shoujo e no Ai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1747" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Life Can Be So Nice 世界を受け入れし者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life Can Be So Nice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Life Can Be So Nice: Sekai o Ukeireshi Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1748" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Light in Darkness 闇の灯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light in Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Light in Darkness: Yami no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1749" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Portraits from Memory 記憶の肖像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Portraits from Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Portraits from Memory: Kioku no Shouzou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1750" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">You`ll never be young twice 過ぎさりし我が時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`ll Never Be Young Twice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">You`ll Never Be Young Twice: Sugisarishi Waga Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1751" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">She`s So Unusual 彼女の生き方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She`s So Unusual</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">She`s So Unusual: Kanojo no Ikikata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1752" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">A Requiem 眠りによって全てが終わる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Requiem: Nemuri ni Yotte Subete ga Owaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1753" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Until Ure In My Arms Again 世にかなわぬ願いなく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until Ure in My Arms Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Until Ure in My Arms Again: Yo ni Kanawanu Negai Naku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1754" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Under The Gravity`s Rainbow 虹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Gravity`s Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Under the Gravity`s Rainbow: Niji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1755" update="2015-12-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Mother`s Day 汝, 母を愛せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother`s Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mother`s Day: Nanji, Haha o Aiseyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5581" update="2007-12-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">9.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">AMV - Happy End</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85730" update="2010-05-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Special (unspecified)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
