<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1807" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>1980-05-08</startdate>
<enddate>1981-01-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Densetsu Kyojin Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Great God Legend Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Legendary Giant God Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Space Runaway Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">伝説巨神イデオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Space Runaway Ideon</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1809" type="Sequel">Densetsu Kyojin Ideon Hatsudou Hen</anime>
<anime id="1808" type="Summary">Densetsu Kyojin Ideon Sesshoku Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=119</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="3484" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="5311" type="Music">Sugiyama Kouichi</name>
<name id="3484" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3485" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kogawa Tomonori</name>
<name id="3485" type="Character Design">Kogawa Tomonori</name>
<name id="1694" type="Series Composition">Takizawa Toshifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Humanity`s pursuit of knowledge leads them to the planet Solo, where they find mysterious remains of a long dead alien civilization, including the 3 part super robot Ideon, and a powerful warship. Using these, the Earthlings sent to investigate the ruins defend themselves in their constant conflicts against powerful aliens called the Buff Clan, who are in pursuit of Ide, the mysterious energy that powers the Ideon.
Source: ANN
Note 1: Ideon was originally to be 43 episodes and was fully planned for such. It unfortunately had the plug pulled after 39.
Note 2: Ideon was the project Tomino Yoshiyuki worked on directly after the cancellation of the original Mobile Suit Gundam.
Note 3: Ideon was the biggest influence for Neon Genesis Evangelion.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="240">5.72</permanent>
<temporary count="241">6.40</temporary>
<review count="2">5.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148785.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1097</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1722</identifier>
<identifier>upedci</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=119</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Space_Runaway_Ideon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>伝説巨神イデオン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1555</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89413</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/214</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1980/ideon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4459" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>undefeatable spaceship</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3792" type="main character in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="4">9.57</rating>
<name>Yuuki Cosmo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cosmo, male lead of Ideon, is a teenager who lived on the planet Solo with his father, who was an archaeologist. When the Buff Clan attacks Solo and his father is killed, Cosmo and several of his friends get into three recently excavated trucks, which convert into the Ideon. Cosmo is the primary pilot of the Sol Conver/Ideo-Delta, as well as the Ideon when in its combined form. He occasionally gets into arguments with Solo Ship captain Bes Jordan, but overall is a respected and dependable crew member.

Cosmo is killed in the final battle against the Buff Clan when the Ideon is destroyed.
</description>
<picture>19671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4117" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">6.31</rating>
<name>Karala Ajiba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karala, female lead of Ideon, is youngest daughter of Supreme Commander Doba Ajiba of the Buff Clan military. Investigating the Ide on the planet Solo, she heads down to the planet against orders and is stranded there with her attendant, Mayaya. She is held captive on the Solo Ship but the crew sees her as a kind hearted individual and she becomes a regular crew member. Initially attempts are made to rescue her, but she is soon seen as a traitor to the Buff Clan, including from her elder sister Harulu. Karala later becomes romantically involved with Solo Ship Captain Bes Jordan.

As the series draws to a close, Karala becomes pregnant with Bes`s baby, whom the crew of the ship nickname "Messiah". Karala is transported by the Ide to her father`s ship, the Bairal Jin however her desire for peace between the races falls on deaf ears. Karala successfully makes it back to the Solo Ship due to the power of the Ide, which saves her when her shuttle is destroyed. Her sister Harulu sneaks aboard the Solo Ship, angry and jealous with her and shoots her three times in the face.
</description>
<picture>20084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1734" picture="38029.jpg">Toda Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4118" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">9.14</rating>
<name>Jordan Bes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A soldier in the Earth Military`s forces who is stationed on Solo, Bes becomes the leader of the refugees on the Solo Ship following the Buff Clan attack. He initially is the pilot of the Sol Vainer/Ideo-Nova, but retires from piloting it and takes on the role of Solo Ship captain. Bes is a well liked and respected member of the Solo Ship crew and begins a romantic relationship with Karala.

Karala eventually becomes pregnant with Bes`s child, whom the Solo Ship crew nickname "Messiah". He continues to lead the Solo Ship into its final battle against the Buff Clan. During the battle he is shot multiple times by Buff Clan soldiers and is killed upon the destruction of the Solo Ship.
</description>
<picture>140980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58489" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">4.70</rating>
<name>Formossa Sheryl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A linguistic scholar stationed on the planet Solo along with her father and younger sister. Following the Buff Clan attack and her father`s death, Sheryl heads aboard the Solo Ship along with the other survivors. She is constantly trying to find out more about the mysterious "Ide" that powers the Ideon and the Solo Ship. She has an adversarial relationship with Karala.

Sheryl forms a romantic relationship with Gije Zaral following his defection to the Solo Ship. She enters a state of despair following the murder of her sister and the death of Gije shortly afterwards. Believing the Ide will provide greater protection for the Solo Ship, she carries the baby Piper Lou onto the deck of the ship while the Ideon is about to fire at an approaching comet with its Wave Leader Gun. As a result of the blast she is blown off the ship to her death.
</description>
<picture>140932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58490" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Abadede Gurimade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The initial commander of the Buff Clan investigation of Logo Dau (Solo) in the initial episodes and the main commander watching over Karala, Mayuyu, Gije and Damido. Has a wife and child who he wishes to return home to.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58491" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Damido Vetch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the officers in charge of the initial expedition that results in the discovery of the Planet Solo. Damido is a colleague of Gije`s and along with him pursues Karala early in the series. Damido is much more aggressive than Gije and appears to be more concerned with wiping out the enemy than rescuing Karala.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2783" picture="23189.jpg">Tanaka Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58492" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Daram Zuba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An officer in the Ome Foundation who was also a former lover of Harulu. Daram assists Harulu after her Dorowa Zan is destroyed in a fight against the Solo Ship. He also leads the pursuit of the Solo Ship on the planet Kyaral, and later to the Earth sphere.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30719">Kihara Shoujirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58493" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Doba Ajiba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Supreme Commander of the Buff Clan military. Doba is the father of both Karala and Harulu. Like Harulu, Doba despises Karala for abandoning the Buff Clan and doesn`t care whether she lives or dies.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58494" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Harulu Ajiba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The elder sister of Karala, and daughter of Doba, Supreme Commander of the Buff Clan military. A high-ranking member of the Buff Clan military, Harulu leads the pursuit of the Solo Ship and Ideon for much of the first half of the series. She views her younger sister as a traitor to the Buff Clan and despises her.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58495" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">9.14</rating>
<name>Gije Zaral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The commander of the initial Buff Clan search expedition that discovered the planet Solo. Gije is a friend and former fiance of Karala`s, and hence is gravely concerned with her safety after she heads to the planet Solo. Initially he leads multiple operations to rescue Karala, and is later sent by Harulu to the Buff Clan homeworld to perform further study of the Ide.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1985" picture="21285.jpg">Hayashi Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58496" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Kicchi Kicchin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4941" picture="222847.jpg">Ukai Rumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58497" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Piper Lou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A baby who is one of the refugees on the Solo Ship. As the youngest member of the Solo Ship crew, Lou is critical to controlling the Ide, which responds with more power to young children like Lou. In fact the Ideon displays greater powers almost every time Lou is brought aboard. The Ide protects Lou and the children for they are of a new generation - representing the general innocence of children.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58498" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Malaca Fuad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the children on the Solo Ship. He is the most timid of the children and is scolded by Moera for not toughening up.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4594" picture="77604.jpg">Takagi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58499" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Novak Ursula</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the young children aboard the Solo Ship. Ursula`s parents were killed in the attack on New Lopia. She is the leader of the kids, and is often seen leading Fuad and Piper Lou in various activities. She doesn`t understand very much the things that happen around her, but is often happy to help with any minor duties on the ship.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33758" picture="194738.jpg">Matsubara Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58500" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">2.54</rating>
<name>Afta Deck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who is a friend of Cosmo`s and Kasha`s on Solo. He`s generally seen with Rapappa, a tame two-tailed squirrel perched on his shoulder. Although just a young kid, Deck desires to become a pilot of the Ideon and when Cosmo sees how dedicated he is to it, he allows Deck to become his co-pilot on the Ideo-Delta. As expected for his age, Deck is immature at times but for the most part gets along with everyone though gradually as the series progresses he begins to prove himself as a pilot, establishing himself as a predominant role in controlling the Ideon.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38331">Matsuda Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58501" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Banda Lotta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teenage girl from the planet Solo who becomes one of the civilian refugees aboard the Solo Ship. Lotta`s primary role aboard the ship is taking care of the young children along with Lin.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1811" picture="222844.jpg">Yamada Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58502" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Formossa Lin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sheryl`s younger sister, who is often seen taking care of the children along with Lotta.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9582" picture="219362.jpg">Yokozawa Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58503" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Fam Rapo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The medic of the Solo Ship whose love interest is Moera. Along with Moera, Rapo acts as a parental figure to the orphaned Fuad.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38332" picture="140981.jpg">Tsuruta Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58504" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Nabeul Hatari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pilot who survives the Buff Clan attack on New Lopia in the second episode and is one of the refugees who boards the Solo ship. Hatari becomes a subordinate and confidante of Bes, even taking control of the Solo ship`s operations when Bes became ill.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32396" picture="151667.jpg">Yokoo Saburou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58505" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Fatom Moera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Solo Ship`s crew, who serves as the main pilot for the Ideo Nova for the majority of the series. He is romantically involved with the ship`s doctor, Rapo. He is also seen chastising Fuad on several occasions for his wimpy behavior, encouraging him to stand up for himself and become a man.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10992">Sasaki Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58506" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Gyabari Techno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The co-pilot for the Ideo-Buster.</description>
<picture>140936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32960">Sakuramoto Masahiro</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="32845" picture="157270.jpg">Onoda Eiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58507" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Mars Vent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The co-pilot for the Ideo-Nova.</description>
<picture>140935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30731" picture="2051.gif">Mitsuhashi Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58508" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Ira Joriba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer of the Solo Ship.</description>
<picture>140934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58509" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">4.70</rating>
<name>Imhof Kasha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teenage girl who was friends with Cosmo on Solo, Kasha quickly becomes involved in the fighting when the Buff Clan launch their attack on Solo. Kasha becomes the main pilot of the Ideo-Buster/Sol-Amber. Although a good pilot, Kasha is quite hot tempered and aggressive which can get her in trouble at times. Like Cosmo, she at times conflicts with the opinions on the adults on the ship.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5637" picture="188452.jpg">Shiraishi Fuyumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58511" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Gond Bow</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140976.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58512" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Zuroo Jikku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140975.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58513" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Gil Bow</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140974.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58514" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Dekka Bow</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140973.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58515" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Kopora</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140972.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58516" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Zanza Lubu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140971.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58517" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Adigo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140970.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58518" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Gido Mack</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140969.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58519" type="appears in" update="2014-05-17">
<name>Abzonor</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140968.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58520" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Garbo Jikku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140967.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58521" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Ganga Lube</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140966.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58522" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Rogg Mack</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140965.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58523" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Jig Mack</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140964.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58524" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Dog Mack</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140963.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58525" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Giran Doe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>140962.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58526" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<name>Solo Ship</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Solo Ship was originally discovered by archeologists on the Planet Solo while preparing that planet for colonization. The Solo Ship was the second of 2 major archeological finds (the first being the Ideon), found at a second archeological site. When the Buff Clan attacked the Planet Solo and quickly annihilated the planet`s capital, New Lopia, the colonists quickly fled to the only place where they could be safe - the Solo Ship. Originally thought to be nothing more than a ruin, the Solo Ship quickly responded to the power of `Ide`, which emerged due to the start of the war. The surviving colonists fled the planet Solo in this ship and remained in it until the series.
Like the Ideon, the Solo Ship has few weapons of its own at first, but is equipped with various cannons and missile launchers by the colonists who occupy it. Its main defense is the Ideon itself, which can stand right on the deck of the ship and surround the both of them with its powerful barrier. What makes the Solo Ship special and more advanced than anything Earthlings had before is its DS Drive, which enables the Solo Ship to enter Null-Space and travel as fast as any Buff Clan craft.
The Solo Ship is destroyed at the end of `The Ideon: Be Invoked` by a blast from the Gando Rowa.</description>
<picture>140961.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58527" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Ideo Busta</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140960.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58528" type="appears in" update="2014-05-17">
<name>Sol Comber</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58529" type="appears in" update="2014-05-17">
<name>Ideo Nova</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140958.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58530" type="appears in" update="2014-05-17">
<name>Sol Bania</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140957.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58531" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Ideo Delta</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140956.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58532" type="appears in" update="2014-05-17">
<name>Sol Amber</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>140955.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58533" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<name>Ideon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Ideon was originally constructed by a long dead alien civilization on the planet Solo (known as the 6th Civilization because it was the 6th alien civilization humanity had discovered). It is comprised of three trucks, the Sol-Amber, Sol-Conver and Sol-Vainer, which transform and combine to form this gigantic humanoid mech. Each of these trucks were individually restored by the scientists on Solo, and it wasn`t until a 7th alien civilization, the `Buff Clan` attacked that the Ideon itself was revealed when the three trucks transformed on their own. The Ideon is carried aboard the Solo Ship throughout the series as they flee through the universe.
The Ideon and its individual parts are powered by the `Ide`, a mysterious yet infinite power source that fluctuates constantly, effecting the Ideon`s performance. If the Ide Gauge (which can be found in the cockpit of each of the Ideon`s 3 parts) does not display the Ide to be at an appropriate level, not only will the Ideon`s attack/defense capabilities be decreased, but it can also separate back into its 3 parts. Ide responds more to a person the younger they are, hence the Ideon`s pilots become younger and younger as the series goes on. Bes, the captain of the Ideon pilots it along with Cosmo, Kasha, Tekuno and Bento in the early episodes, but soon retires from the job, handing it over to the younger Moera. The child Deck becomes a pilot later on, being able to bring more out of the Ideon because of his younger age. The Ideon can even respond to babies, as is the case when the infant Piper Lou sneaks aboard, and occasionally its individual parts can operate without a pilot at all.
The Ideon has a host of weapon bestowing it with incredible offensive strength, making it one of the most powerful mecha in anime history. It contains a multitude of Missile Ports and Glen Cannons(which were put on by the colonists after the Buff Clan attacked) all over its body allowing it to attack in all directions. The Ideon features a barrier that can protect both itself and the Solo Ship from any attack, but its strength relies solely on the level of Ide. If the Ide gauge is low, the barrier can be useless. Halfway through the series while at the planet Ajian, the Ideon`s pilots discovered a tremendous power in the Ideon`s Mini Black Hole cannon. When activated this creates a black hole which sucks in everything around the Ideon. Its power is so great though that it dealt considerable damage to both friend and foe. As powerful as that device is though, its only the third most powerful weapon of the Ideon`s. The second is the Ideon swords, two rays of energy that emit from the Ideon`s wrists and are powerful enough to chop a planet in two (which they eventually do). Most powerful of all is the Ideon Gun, also known as the Wave Leader Gun, which emits waves of energy that can wipe out planets, fleets, whatever gets in the way with no trouble at all. The one caveat is that these weapons use up a tremendous amount of energy, meaning that they must be used sparingly.
The Ideon is destroyed in `The Ideon: Be Invoked` in the final battle against the Ganda Rowa, the Buff Clan`s most powerful weapon.</description>
<picture>140954.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58630" type="appears in" update="2013-08-07">
<name>Mayaya Rau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayaya is Karala`s attendant and accompanies her to Solo when she heads there. She is captured along with Karala and held on the Solo Ship.

Mayaya is shot to death when she makes an attempted escape from the Solo Ship. In the compilation movie "A Contact", she is instead shot by Banda Lotta who had desired revenge against the Buff Clan.
</description>
<picture>141064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33758" picture="194738.jpg">Matsubara Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58655" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<name>Gindoro Jinmu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of the Ome Foundation, a private company of mercenaries that conspires with Doba Ajiba to overthrow the Buff Clan emperor. After his underlings fail to defeat or capture the Ideon, Gindoro teams up with Doba on the Buff Clan flagship Bairal Jin. He was instrumental in the creation of the Gando Rowa, the Buff Clan`s most powerful weapon.

Following the death of Emperor Zuou he remains with Doba, not aware that the Buff Clan homeworld was destroyed as well. As the fighting escalates Gindoro desires to flee causing conflict with Doba, who shoots him. His spirit talks to Doba shortly following his death.
</description>
<picture>141101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5229" picture="156605.jpg">Kanie Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58760" type="appears in" update="2013-08-11">
<name>Doku Jilbal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mecha designer who Harulu permits to head after the Solo Ship and Ideon.

While he is successful in taking multiple members of the Solo Ship hostage, he is tricked in battle by Cosmo and killed by the Ideon.
</description>
<picture>141288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58761" type="appears in" update="2013-08-13">
<name>Guhaba Geba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan Military officer under the command of Harulu Ajiba. He humiliates Karala in front of everyone when she tries to make peace with her sister.
He is defeated and killed against the Ideon while piloting the Zigg Mack.</description>
<picture>141289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58762" type="appears in" update="2013-08-11">
<name>Zuou Habel Gante</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emperor of the Buff Clan. Doba Ajiba conspired with the Ome Foundation to overthrow him.

He is killed when the Buff Clan`s Earth is destroyed by meteors.
</description>
<picture>141290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59045" type="appears in" update="2013-08-19">
<name>Rukuku Kil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan officer sent to capture the Ideon as it approaches Earth. A loyal soldier of the Emperor, she looks down on the Ome Foundation`s Daram Zuba, whom she picks up after his failed attempts to defeat the Ideon.

After Daram`s death Rukuku comes upon a video of him talking about Harulu. Fellow Buff Clan soldier Kulara Kina kills Rukuku to obtain this tape for Harulu, who was angry at Rukuku for her laughing at it.
</description>
<picture>141721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59046" type="appears in" update="2013-08-19">
<name>Kulara Kina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan soldier under the jurisdiction of Harulu, she accompanies Hannibal Gen to Rukuku Kil`s Garowa Zan in order to spy on her.

Kulara assassinates Rukuku under Harulu`s orders in order to get a video with Daram on it, and as revenge for Rukuku laughing at it. Her effort is worthless however as the entire ship is blown up soon after. </description>
<picture>141722.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59107" type="appears in" update="2013-08-22">
<name>Camyulla Lanban</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Officer at the Braziller base who comforts Cosmo following a terrifying battle against the Buff Clan.

When the Buff Clan attacks Braziller, she dies when she is crushed following a car crash.
</description>
<picture>141795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32697" picture="203361.jpg">Kondou Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59108" type="appears in" update="2013-08-22">
<name>Hannibal Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan officer who battles the Solo Ship shortly after it leaves the Earth. He teams up with the Earth Officer Marshall Franklin in order to capture the Ideon and Solo Ship.

Hannibal Gen meets his end at the hands of the Ideon in his Gido Mack mecha. </description>
<picture>141796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59141" type="appears in" update="2013-08-23">
<name>Gyamus Ragu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan officer under the command of Harulu who attacks the Solo Ship on the planet Flag Star.
Gyamuse dies after his Devil Twin soldiers fail to destroy the Solo Ship. </description>
<picture>141851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3643" picture="24947.jpg">Kanemoto Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59142" type="appears in" update="2013-08-23">
<name>Marshall Franklin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Officer in the Earth Military who teams up with the Buff Clan to seize the Solo Ship and Ideon.

When the Solo Ship crew decide to abandon it, Marshall lies to them about his intentions and tries to seize it but is killed when his fleet falls under the attack of the Buff Clan.
</description>
<picture>141853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3246" picture="215972.jpg">Ueda Toshiya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="18391" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗黒からの浮上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surfacing from Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ankoku kara no Fujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18392" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊迫の月基地潜行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltrate the Lunar Base</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinpaku no Tsuki Kichi Senkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18393" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活のイデオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrection of Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu no Ideon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18394" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激震の大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bursting Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekishin no Daichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18395" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決・大砂塵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle in the Sandstorm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu Daisajin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18396" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばソロシップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Solo Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Solo Ship</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18397" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄・囮の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shocking Decoy Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu Otori no Hoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18398" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異星人を撃て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack on the Alien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ihoshi Jin o Ute</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18399" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵戦艦を撃沈せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sink the Enemy`s Battleship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki Senkan o Gekichin seyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18400" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コスモスに君と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Cosmos With You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kosumosu no Kimi to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18401" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃える亜空間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning Null Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeru Akuukan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18402" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入ゲリラを叩け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strike the Infiltrating Guerillas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu Guerillas o Hatake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18403" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の炎のなかで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amidst the Flames of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Honoo no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18404" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">必殺のダミド戦法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Damido`s Lethal Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hissatsu no Damido Senpou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18405" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の逃亡者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Space Runaway</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Toubousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18406" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニューロピア炎上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destruction of New Lopia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New Lopia Enjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18407" recap="true" update="2007-02-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">甦える伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend Lives Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Densetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18408" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソロ星脱出せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from Planet Solo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soroboshi Dasshutsu seyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18409" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">捨て身の狙撃者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperate Sniper</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sutemi no Sogekisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18410" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲のイデオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ideon`s Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu no Ideon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18411" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫撃・双子の悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle the Devil Twins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakugeki Futago no Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18412" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘・ゲルの恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deadly Fight - Fear of Gel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou Gel no Kyoufu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18413" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">撃破・ドク戦法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Doku`s Attack Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekiha Doku Senpou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18414" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">故郷[ふるさと]は燃えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Home Aflame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furusato wa Moete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18415" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イデオン奪回作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plan for Retrieving Ideon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ideon Dakkai Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18416" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白刃の敵中突破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breakthrough the Enemy`s Front</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakujin no Teki Chuu Toppa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18417" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閃光の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparkling Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou no Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18418" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追撃・遺跡の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pursuit to the Ruined Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuigeki Iseki no Hoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18419" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無限力・イデ伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infinite Power: Legendary Id</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugen Ryoku Id Densetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18420" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇襲・バジン作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surpise Bajin Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishuu Bajin Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18421" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波導ガンの怒り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wrath of the Wave Gun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nami Shirubegan no Ikari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18422" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワフト空域の賭け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waft Area Gamble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waft Kuuiki no Kake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18423" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りの白い旗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Flag of Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Shiroi Hata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18424" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">憎しみの植民星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Colony of Hatred</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nikushimi no Shokuminboshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18425" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">流星おちる果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Meteor`s Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuusei Ochiru Hate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18426" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜空間脱走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from Null Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuukan Dassou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18427" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アジアンの裏切り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Betrayal on Ajian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ajian no Uragiri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18428" update="2006-07-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャムス特攻指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gyamose`s Special Command</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyamose Tokkou Shirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18429" update="2006-07-06">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘・猿人の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle on the Ape Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou Saujin no Hoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121739" update="2010-09-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1980-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121740" update="2010-09-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1980-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
