<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1809" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1982-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>1982-07-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Densetsu Kyojin Ideon Hatsudou Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Runaway Ideon: Be Invoked</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Ideon: Be Invoked</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">El Ideon: La Invocación</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">伝説巨神イデオン 発動篇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1807" type="Prequel">Densetsu Kyojin Ideon</anime>
<anime id="1808" type="Prequel">Densetsu Kyojin Ideon Sesshoku Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="354131">An excellent (and brutal) idea of super robot subversion. However, it requires a lot of boring groundwork to be fully enjoyed.

Recommended for very patient mecha/sci-fi fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="534780">As it has been said, watching the entire franchise isn`t an easy task, but this strange, inspiring and spiritual movie makes it worth in the long run. Unfortunately, one has to watch the TV series to fully appreciate the characters.

No wonder this strange mecha movie inspired Hideaki Anno to make Evangelion.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/contents/ideon/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3485" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kogawa Tomonori</name>
<name id="3485" type="Character Design">Kogawa Tomonori</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="3484" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1694" type="Direction">Takizawa Toshifumi</name>
<name id="3484" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* The epic conclusion to the http://anidb.net/a1807 [Ideon] saga, featuring what was meant to be the final five episodes of the TV series.
The Solo Ship and its crew continue their intense battle with the Buff Clan leading to a final battle that will determine the fate of all life in the universe.
Source: ANN
Note: This movie features the last episode of the TV series `Space Runaway Ideon` (39), and four more episodes (40-43) that were meant to air on TV, but never did since the show was cancelled. This movie was the second part of a double feature along with the http://anidb.net/a1808 [Densetsu Kyojin Ideon/Sesshoku Hen] movie.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="203">7.69</permanent>
<temporary count="203">7.07</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>148671.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2726</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2193</identifier>
<identifier>nnkynj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=215</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Space_Runaway_Ideon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>伝説巨神イデオン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>148178</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1721</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1438" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-18">
<name>ruthless</name>
<description>This character will stop at nothing to achieve their goals and will be unbound by any constraints</description>
<picurl>214979.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5807" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2007-08-08">
<name>cosmic reset</name>
<description>All events that occurred up to a certain point are mysteriously undone, as if the Universe pressed a rewind button. This usually means some characters are being given another chance to unknowingly play out events differently, perhaps to prevent certain consequences from the previous time line`s actions. Occasionally they become doomed to repeat portions of their life over and over again until an individual event or series of events are performed correctly in just the right way, as seemingly to gain the Universe`s approval.</description>
<picurl>36685.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3792" type="main character in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="4">9.57</rating>
<name>Yuuki Cosmo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cosmo, male lead of Ideon, is a teenager who lived on the planet Solo with his father, who was an archaeologist. When the Buff Clan attacks Solo and his father is killed, Cosmo and several of his friends get into three recently excavated trucks, which convert into the Ideon. Cosmo is the primary pilot of the Sol Conver/Ideo-Delta, as well as the Ideon when in its combined form. He occasionally gets into arguments with Solo Ship captain Bes Jordan, but overall is a respected and dependable crew member.

Cosmo is killed in the final battle against the Buff Clan when the Ideon is destroyed.
</description>
<picture>19671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4117" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">6.31</rating>
<name>Karala Ajiba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karala, female lead of Ideon, is youngest daughter of Supreme Commander Doba Ajiba of the Buff Clan military. Investigating the Ide on the planet Solo, she heads down to the planet against orders and is stranded there with her attendant, Mayaya. She is held captive on the Solo Ship but the crew sees her as a kind hearted individual and she becomes a regular crew member. Initially attempts are made to rescue her, but she is soon seen as a traitor to the Buff Clan, including from her elder sister Harulu. Karala later becomes romantically involved with Solo Ship Captain Bes Jordan.

As the series draws to a close, Karala becomes pregnant with Bes`s baby, whom the crew of the ship nickname "Messiah". Karala is transported by the Ide to her father`s ship, the Bairal Jin however her desire for peace between the races falls on deaf ears. Karala successfully makes it back to the Solo Ship due to the power of the Ide, which saves her when her shuttle is destroyed. Her sister Harulu sneaks aboard the Solo Ship, angry and jealous with her and shoots her three times in the face.
</description>
<picture>20084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1734" picture="38029.jpg">Toda Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4118" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">9.14</rating>
<name>Jordan Bes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A soldier in the Earth Military`s forces who is stationed on Solo, Bes becomes the leader of the refugees on the Solo Ship following the Buff Clan attack. He initially is the pilot of the Sol Vainer/Ideo-Nova, but retires from piloting it and takes on the role of Solo Ship captain. Bes is a well liked and respected member of the Solo Ship crew and begins a romantic relationship with Karala.

Karala eventually becomes pregnant with Bes`s child, whom the Solo Ship crew nickname "Messiah". He continues to lead the Solo Ship into its final battle against the Buff Clan. During the battle he is shot multiple times by Buff Clan soldiers and is killed upon the destruction of the Solo Ship.
</description>
<picture>140980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58489" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">4.70</rating>
<name>Formossa Sheryl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A linguistic scholar stationed on the planet Solo along with her father and younger sister. Following the Buff Clan attack and her father`s death, Sheryl heads aboard the Solo Ship along with the other survivors. She is constantly trying to find out more about the mysterious "Ide" that powers the Ideon and the Solo Ship. She has an adversarial relationship with Karala.

Sheryl forms a romantic relationship with Gije Zaral following his defection to the Solo Ship. She enters a state of despair following the murder of her sister and the death of Gije shortly afterwards. Believing the Ide will provide greater protection for the Solo Ship, she carries the baby Piper Lou onto the deck of the ship while the Ideon is about to fire at an approaching comet with its Wave Leader Gun. As a result of the blast she is blown off the ship to her death.
</description>
<picture>140932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58491" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Damido Vetch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the officers in charge of the initial expedition that results in the discovery of the Planet Solo. Damido is a colleague of Gije`s and along with him pursues Karala early in the series. Damido is much more aggressive than Gije and appears to be more concerned with wiping out the enemy than rescuing Karala.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2783" picture="23189.jpg">Tanaka Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58492" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Daram Zuba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An officer in the Ome Foundation who was also a former lover of Harulu. Daram assists Harulu after her Dorowa Zan is destroyed in a fight against the Solo Ship. He also leads the pursuit of the Solo Ship on the planet Kyaral, and later to the Earth sphere.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30719">Kihara Shoujirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58493" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Doba Ajiba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Supreme Commander of the Buff Clan military. Doba is the father of both Karala and Harulu. Like Harulu, Doba despises Karala for abandoning the Buff Clan and doesn`t care whether she lives or dies.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58494" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Harulu Ajiba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The elder sister of Karala, and daughter of Doba, Supreme Commander of the Buff Clan military. A high-ranking member of the Buff Clan military, Harulu leads the pursuit of the Solo Ship and Ideon for much of the first half of the series. She views her younger sister as a traitor to the Buff Clan and despises her.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58495" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">9.14</rating>
<name>Gije Zaral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The commander of the initial Buff Clan search expedition that discovered the planet Solo. Gije is a friend and former fiance of Karala`s, and hence is gravely concerned with her safety after she heads to the planet Solo. Initially he leads multiple operations to rescue Karala, and is later sent by Harulu to the Buff Clan homeworld to perform further study of the Ide.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1985" picture="21285.jpg">Hayashi Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58496" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Kicchi Kicchin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4941" picture="222847.jpg">Ukai Rumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58497" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Piper Lou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A baby who is one of the refugees on the Solo Ship. As the youngest member of the Solo Ship crew, Lou is critical to controlling the Ide, which responds with more power to young children like Lou. In fact the Ideon displays greater powers almost every time Lou is brought aboard. The Ide protects Lou and the children for they are of a new generation - representing the general innocence of children.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58498" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Malaca Fuad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the children on the Solo Ship. He is the most timid of the children and is scolded by Moera for not toughening up.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4594" picture="77604.jpg">Takagi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58499" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Novak Ursula</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the young children aboard the Solo Ship. Ursula`s parents were killed in the attack on New Lopia. She is the leader of the kids, and is often seen leading Fuad and Piper Lou in various activities. She doesn`t understand very much the things that happen around her, but is often happy to help with any minor duties on the ship.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33758" picture="194738.jpg">Matsubara Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58500" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">2.54</rating>
<name>Afta Deck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who is a friend of Cosmo`s and Kasha`s on Solo. He`s generally seen with Rapappa, a tame two-tailed squirrel perched on his shoulder. Although just a young kid, Deck desires to become a pilot of the Ideon and when Cosmo sees how dedicated he is to it, he allows Deck to become his co-pilot on the Ideo-Delta. As expected for his age, Deck is immature at times but for the most part gets along with everyone though gradually as the series progresses he begins to prove himself as a pilot, establishing himself as a predominant role in controlling the Ideon.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38331">Matsuda Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58501" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Banda Lotta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teenage girl from the planet Solo who becomes one of the civilian refugees aboard the Solo Ship. Lotta`s primary role aboard the ship is taking care of the young children along with Lin.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1811" picture="222844.jpg">Yamada Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58502" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Formossa Lin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sheryl`s younger sister, who is often seen taking care of the children along with Lotta.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9582" picture="219362.jpg">Yokozawa Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58503" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Fam Rapo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The medic of the Solo Ship whose love interest is Moera. Along with Moera, Rapo acts as a parental figure to the orphaned Fuad.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38332" picture="140981.jpg">Tsuruta Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58504" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Nabeul Hatari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pilot who survives the Buff Clan attack on New Lopia in the second episode and is one of the refugees who boards the Solo ship. Hatari becomes a subordinate and confidante of Bes, even taking control of the Solo ship`s operations when Bes became ill.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58505" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Fatom Moera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Solo Ship`s crew, who serves as the main pilot for the Ideo Nova for the majority of the series. He is romantically involved with the ship`s doctor, Rapo. He is also seen chastising Fuad on several occasions for his wimpy behavior, encouraging him to stand up for himself and become a man.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10992">Sasaki Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58506" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Gyabari Techno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The co-pilot for the Ideo-Buster.</description>
<picture>140936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32960">Sakuramoto Masahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58507" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Mars Vent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The co-pilot for the Ideo-Nova.</description>
<picture>140935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30731" picture="2051.gif">Mitsuhashi Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58508" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Ira Joriba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer of the Solo Ship.</description>
<picture>140934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58509" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="3">4.70</rating>
<name>Imhof Kasha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teenage girl who was friends with Cosmo on Solo, Kasha quickly becomes involved in the fighting when the Buff Clan launch their attack on Solo. Kasha becomes the main pilot of the Ideo-Buster/Sol-Amber. Although a good pilot, Kasha is quite hot tempered and aggressive which can get her in trouble at times. Like Cosmo, she at times conflicts with the opinions on the adults on the ship.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5637" picture="188452.jpg">Shiraishi Fuyumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58630" type="appears in" update="2013-08-07">
<name>Mayaya Rau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayaya is Karala`s attendant and accompanies her to Solo when she heads there. She is captured along with Karala and held on the Solo Ship.

Mayaya is shot to death when she makes an attempted escape from the Solo Ship. In the compilation movie "A Contact", she is instead shot by Banda Lotta who had desired revenge against the Buff Clan.
</description>
<picture>141064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33758" picture="194738.jpg">Matsubara Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58655" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<name>Gindoro Jinmu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of the Ome Foundation, a private company of mercenaries that conspires with Doba Ajiba to overthrow the Buff Clan emperor. After his underlings fail to defeat or capture the Ideon, Gindoro teams up with Doba on the Buff Clan flagship Bairal Jin. He was instrumental in the creation of the Gando Rowa, the Buff Clan`s most powerful weapon.

Following the death of Emperor Zuou he remains with Doba, not aware that the Buff Clan homeworld was destroyed as well. As the fighting escalates Gindoro desires to flee causing conflict with Doba, who shoots him. His spirit talks to Doba shortly following his death.
</description>
<picture>141101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58659" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<name>Torolof</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Harulu`s underlings and co-pilot of the Zanza Lubu.

Torolof is killed when she infiltrates the Solo Ship along with Harulu and Kilarul and is shot with a bazooka by Banda Lotta.
</description>
<picture>141105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30730" picture="77704.jpg">Nashiwa Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58660" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<name>Kilarul</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Harulu`s underlings and co-pilot of the Zanza Lubu.

She is killed along with Harulu when the Bairal Jin is struck by a blast from the Ideon Gun.
</description>
<picture>141106.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58761" type="appears in" update="2013-08-13">
<name>Guhaba Geba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan Military officer under the command of Harulu Ajiba. He humiliates Karala in front of everyone when she tries to make peace with her sister.
He is defeated and killed against the Ideon while piloting the Zigg Mack.</description>
<picture>141289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58762" type="appears in" update="2013-08-11">
<name>Zuou Habel Gante</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emperor of the Buff Clan. Doba Ajiba conspired with the Ome Foundation to overthrow him.

He is killed when the Buff Clan`s Earth is destroyed by meteors.
</description>
<picture>141290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59045" type="appears in" update="2013-08-19">
<name>Rukuku Kil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan officer sent to capture the Ideon as it approaches Earth. A loyal soldier of the Emperor, she looks down on the Ome Foundation`s Daram Zuba, whom she picks up after his failed attempts to defeat the Ideon.

After Daram`s death Rukuku comes upon a video of him talking about Harulu. Fellow Buff Clan soldier Kulara Kina kills Rukuku to obtain this tape for Harulu, who was angry at Rukuku for her laughing at it.
</description>
<picture>141721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59046" type="appears in" update="2013-08-19">
<name>Kulara Kina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Buff Clan soldier under the jurisdiction of Harulu, she accompanies Hannibal Gen to Rukuku Kil`s Garowa Zan in order to spy on her.

Kulara assassinates Rukuku under Harulu`s orders in order to get a video with Daram on it, and as revenge for Rukuku laughing at it. Her effort is worthless however as the entire ship is blown up soon after. </description>
<picture>141722.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="18389" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>1982-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227429" update="2020-03-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Be Invoked - Trailer (3:46)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
