<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1812" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>23</episodecount>
<startdate>1977-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>1978-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Muteki Choujin Zanbot 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Invincible Super Man Zambot 3</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">L`invincibile Zambot 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Zanbot 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Zambot 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">無敵超人ザンボット3</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Zambot 3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1813" type="Other">Muteki Koujin Daitarn 3</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=18</url>
<creators>
<name id="5230" type="Character Design">Yasuhiko Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="3484" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3484" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3637" type="Music">Watanabe Takeo</name>
<name id="6617" type="Music">Matsuyama Yuushi</name>
<name id="25816" type="Original Work">Suzuki Yoshitake</name>
</creators>
<description>There once existed a planet named Beal, until it was wiped out by the mysterious entity known as Gaizok. The few remaining survivors escaped to Earth and split into three families, named Jin, Kamie, and Kamikita respectively. While attempting to start a new life, the collectively known "Jin Family" prepared for the inevitable Gaizok invasion on Earth and its giant mechanical beasts known as "Mecha Boosts". In order to defend their new home, they have built three vehicles which when combined form the mighty Zambot 3. The Jin Family must not only defend against Gaizok attacks, but also harsh criticisms from the very people they protect, who blame the Jin Family for the invasion in the first place.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="114">6.63</permanent>
<temporary count="114">6.63</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>235984.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1178</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2200</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1925</identifier>
<identifier>peurdn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://zambot3.net/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=18</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/international/works/detail.php?cid=18</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Invincible_Super_Man_Zambot_3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>無敵超人ザンボット3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1773</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89484</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1360</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>238</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3818" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-21">
<name>kids in war</name>
<description>When minors participate in armed conflict.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="53855" update="2010-09-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1977-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ザンボ・エース登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zambo-Ace Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Appare Zambot Ace</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53856" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃える死神の花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning Flower of Death</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53857" update="2007-08-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ザンボット3出現!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zambot 3 Awakens!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53858" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結! キング・ビアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unite! King Beal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unite! King Beal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53859" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海が怒りに染まる時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the ocean is filled with Anger</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53860" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">父が帰ってきた日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day My Father Returned</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53861" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば! わが友よ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye! My friend</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53862" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">廃墟に誓う戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Soldier`s Oath at the Ruins</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53863" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うし! キング・ビアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger! King Beal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53864" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンドック現わる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bandok Appears!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53865" update="2007-08-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">決死の爆破作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death-Defying Bomb Operation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53866" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生日の死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birthday Death Match</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53867" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">果てしなき戦いの道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neverending Journey of War</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53868" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スカーフよ永遠なれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scarf Of Eternity</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53869" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海に消えた老将</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Old Admiral Disappears to the Ocean</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53870" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星が輝く時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the Star Twinkles</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53871" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間爆弾の恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror of the Human Bombs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53872" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アキと勝平</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aki and Kappei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53873" update="2008-01-29">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日への脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape for Tomorrow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53874" update="2008-01-29">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Before the Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53875" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 神ファミリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Jin Family</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53876" update="2006-07-29">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブッチャー最後の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Day of Butcher</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53877" update="2010-09-03">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃える宇宙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning Space</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102043" update="2010-09-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1977-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102044" update="2010-09-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1977-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217896" update="2019-06-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">放送開始告知</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01 (17sec): Broadcast start notice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Housou Kaishi Kokuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217897" update="2019-06-08">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">クローバー「ザンボット３ コンビネーションプログラム」CM 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 02 (32sec): Clover "Zanbot Combination Program CM 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Clover "Zanbot Combination Program" CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217898" update="2019-06-08">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">クローバー「ザンボット３ コンビネーションプログラム」CM 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 03 (16sec): Clover "Zanbot Combination Program CM 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Clover "Zanbot Combination Program" CM 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
