<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1815" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>44</episodecount>
<startdate>1978-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>1979-01-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toushou Daimos</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fighting King Daimos</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fighting General Daimos</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Robot Romance Trilogy (Part 3)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Objectif planète Terre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tosho Daimos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Roman Robo Series 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">闘将ダイモス</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Daimos</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Generał Daimos</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1734" type="Other">Chou Denji Machine Voltes V</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<creators>
<name id="3962" type="Music">Kikuchi Shunsuke</name>
<name id="5441" type="Animation Character Design">Kanayama Akihiro</name>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
<name id="990" type="Work">Toei Agency</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="6526" type="Original Work">Yatsude Saburou</name>
<name id="5725" type="Chief Direction">Nagahama Tadao</name>
</creators>
<description>The third of http://anidb.net/cr5725 [Nagahama Tadao]`s Romance Super Robot Trilogy. (#1: http://anidb.net/a1814 [Chou Denji Robo Combattler V], #2: http://anidb.net/a1734 [Chou Denji Machine Voltes V])
After the destruction of their homeworld, the survivors of the planet Barm head towards Earth with the goal of negotiating the purchase of land to emigrate to. Unfortunately, during the negotiations, the Barmian`s leader, Leon, is assassinated by his second in command, Olban, and the delegation from Earth is framed for the murder. In the ensuing chaos, Doctor Isamu Ryuuzaki of the Earth delegation is shot and killed.
Shortly after the disastrous end of the talks, the Barmians (called "Valerians" in Starbirds) begin a campaign of terror against Earth, lead by Leon`s son, Admiral Richter, who deploys a variety of "Mecha Soldiers" against the planet`s defenses. The only thing standing between the Earthlings and annihilation is the transforming, karate-using super robot, Daimos and its pilot, Kazuya Ryuuzaki. But that changes when he meets and falls in love with a mysterious girl named Erika, who turns out to be Richter`s sister. Over the course of their struggles to reunite, Kazuya and Erika each learn that the other`s people are not all evil... and that their own people are not all good.
Note: Episode 24 was also screened at Toei Manga Matsuri on 17.03.1979. The only change made was making it widescreen.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="202">5.54</permanent>
<temporary count="210">7.00</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4114.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1295</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3991</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2816</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1935</identifier>
<identifier>sqnepi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tōshō_Daimos</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>闘将ダイモス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3790</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>146641</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>89450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>905</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>n105</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>248</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="23233" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-15">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Izumi Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21780" picture="73531.jpg">Kuri Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23234" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-15">
<name>Yuuzuki Kyoushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5195.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6662" picture="24334.jpg">Sogabe Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23235" type="main character in" update="2010-10-15">
<name>Ryuuzaki Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23236" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-15">
<rating votes="2">7.23</rating>
<name>Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27067" picture="73530.jpg">Ueda Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23237" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-15">
<name>Richter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3227" picture="24207.jpg">Ichikawa Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="25029" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の出あいは戦火の中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fated Encounter During Wartime</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`invasione della Terra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Deai wa Senka no Naka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27804" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛将バルバス翼たたむとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Short Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moushou Barbas Tsubasa Tatamu Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27805" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイモスパワーアップ作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daimos Power-up Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daimos Power-up Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27806" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">白いつばさの記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory of White Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Tsubasa no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27807" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球を守れ! 戦え一矢!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect the Earth! Fight, Kazuya!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu o Mamore! Tatakae Kazuya!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27808" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかねを狙うキューピット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Appointment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okane o Nerau Cupid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27809" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">とび出せエリカ命をかけて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unintentional Bait</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobi Dase Erika Inochi o Kakete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27810" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">誇り高き別離</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arika`s Double</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokori Takaki Betsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27811" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵バームへ出撃開始!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All To Baam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki Baam e Shutsugeki Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27812" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">母星の誇りを賭けた勇士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Who Staked his Pride in his Home Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bosei no Hokori o Kaketa Yuushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27813" update="2012-01-23">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ド根性カイロの秘密兵器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Photographic Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Do Konjou Cairo no Himitsu Heiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27814" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">極楽島は非情の島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paradise Island is Callous Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuraku Shima wa Hijou no Shima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27815" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の美少女エリカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious and Beautiful Erika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Bishoujo Erika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27816" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">京四郎決死の激突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sad Childhood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoushiro Kesshi no Gekitotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27817" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢! 私の兄は地球の敵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare! My Older Brother is the Earth`s Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu! Watashi no Ani wa Chikyuu no Teki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27818" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うし! 和泉博士の命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Struggle Against The Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayaushi! Izumi Hakase no Inochi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27819" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">誇り高き若獅子リヒテル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Face To Face</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokorinakaki Nyaku Shishi Richter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27820" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘かなる平和への戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Base</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hisoka Naru Heiwa e no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27821" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">小バームの大攻防戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All For All</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shou Baam no Daikoubousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27822" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイモス! 危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daimos! Critial Moment!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daimos! Kikiippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27823" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エリカとダイモス涙の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Terrible Mabose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erika to Daimos Namida no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27824" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しきバランドークの最期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Baranduk!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Baranduk no Saigo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27825" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝く真実は戦う勇気の中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dispersed Astronave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayaku Shinjitsu wa Tatakau Yuuki no Naka ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27826" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">まやかしの平和は要らない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A False Peace is Unnessersary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayakashi no Heiwa wa Iranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27827" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイモビック爆発1秒前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack On Daimovic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daimovic Bakuhatsu Ichi Byou Sen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27828" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と裏切りのバラード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ballad of Love and Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Uragiri no Ballad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27829" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しい罪は涙で消えない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sorrowful Crime Won`t be Erased by Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashii Tsumi wa Namida de Kienai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27830" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">正義の空手を見せてやれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Show me your Karate of Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seigi no Karate o Misete Yare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27831" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイモビックの豆台風!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sabotage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daimovic no Mametaifuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27832" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底城! 大攻撃開始!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack On The Undersea Base</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiteijo! Daikougeki Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27833" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙をふいて立ち上がれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stand Up, With Flowing Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida o Fuite Tachiagare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27834" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">花嫁になるエリカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bride-to-be Erika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanayome ni Naru Erika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27835" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺し屋ゲロイヤーの襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koroshiya Geroiya no Shuugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27836" update="2013-04-30">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1979-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日への驀進</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rush to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita e no Bakushin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27837" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナナは優しい地球の戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nana, Gentle Soldier of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nana wa Yasashii Chikyuu no Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27838" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エリカが三輪に殺される</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Earthly Prisoner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erika ga Miwa ni Korosareru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27839" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙からの使者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission For Peace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Kara no Shisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27840" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エリカ! 死刑台を登る!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards The Salvation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erika! Shikei Dai o Noboru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27841" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ああリヒテル! 絶体絶命!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Impossible Alliance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27842" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる平和への旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Escape From Utopia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Heiwa e no Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27843" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">渡すものか! 俺のダイモス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Supreme Commander</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watasu Mono ka! Ore no Daimos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27844" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">罠にはまった一矢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kasuya In A Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wana ni wa Matta Kazuya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27846" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">一矢を襲うエリカの弾丸!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To The Thresholds Of Baam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazuya o Osou Erika no Dangen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27847" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才科学者アイザムの挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Scientist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai Kagakusha Aizamo no Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62237" update="2006-09-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer from "Polonia 1"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62238" update="2010-10-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62239" update="2010-09-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1978-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67117" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Starbirds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">OAV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
