<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1852" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-12-21</startdate>
<enddate>2004-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nikutai Ten`i</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Nukutai Teni</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Transferencia corporal</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">육체전이</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">肉体転移</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Body Transfer</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Nikutai Teni</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Échanges de corps</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<creators>
<name id="771" type="Work">Arms</name>
<name id="771" type="Animation Work">Arms</name>
<name id="20982" type="Character Design">Jun`you Haruna</name>
<name id="931" type="Original Work">Silky`s</name>
<name id="4372" type="Direction">Fujimoto Yoshitaka</name>
<name id="5636" type="Music">Shura Tooru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the erotic game by http://anidb.net/cr931 [Silky`s].
During the summer break of the high school, a mysterious vessel used for the ritual was sent to the archaeology club. The club members and http://anidb.net/ch52185 [I] lost our conscience when the light from the vessel illuminated us. When I came to, my conscience was transferred into the body of http://anidb.net/ch52178 [Kurahashi Yoshimi] whom I adored like my elder sister. Her body of a girl was very soft, smelled good, and so sensitive to sexual pleasure. It was unfair that the woman was totally different from the man... The other members exposed to the light from the vessel exchanged their minds and bodies, and they were taken into the secret world of the sexual desire. The strange phenomena repeated over and over. Would they be able to return to their world?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="927">4.74</permanent>
<temporary count="943">6.59</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2607.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4654</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1430</identifier>
<identifier>mudztf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5188</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2704" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-15">
<name>cum play</name>
<description>Fetish of sorts where the focus is of the semen that is ejaculated. This can include snowballing, drinking copious amounts of semen, eating it off food, using it to brush one`s teeth, acting as a urinal for semen, gargling it, rinsing one`s mouth with it, or any other act where semen is involved that does not have to do with fertilization of an egg.
This should not be used if one cannot visibly see semen in scenes or if the scene is extremely short.</description>
<picurl>236279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2734" parentid="2695" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-18">
<name>scissoring</name>
<description>Scissoring is a lesbian sex act where the partners interlock their spread legs (like two pairs of scissors) and grind their vulva together to stimulate each other.</description>
<picurl>166100.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4318" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-28">
<name>plot with porn</name>
<description>Any adult-rated work where porn is not the only point to it. As in, it has a plot that is not merely an excuse for having sex on screen. Even better if the sex is actually plausibly worked into said plot or used for characterization.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6218" parentid="2704" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-13">
<name>gokkun</name>
<description>Gokkun is a sexual activity in which a person, not necessarily but usually a female, swallows semen directly from a penis or from a container. The Japanese word "gokkun", whose meaning is close to "gulp" in English, is an onomatopoeia resembling the sound made by swallowing.</description>
<picurl>234875.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="52178" type="main character in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="6">6.53</rating>
<name>Kurahashi Yoshimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33527" picture="86109.jpg">Ayase Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52179" type="main character in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="6">6.78</rating>
<name>Sakajou Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28779" picture="200444.jpg">Moegi Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52180" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="3">7.86</rating>
<name>Ootani Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25726" picture="197088.jpg">Kisaragi Mikoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52181" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="5">7.18</rating>
<name>Ozawa Yukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5521" picture="45037.jpg">Kaneda Mahiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52182" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="3">7.86</rating>
<name>Kamimura Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6818" picture="177897.jpg">Takana Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52183" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="4">7.02</rating>
<name>Akiyama Konomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5593" picture="127833.jpg">Hatono Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52184" type="main character in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="5">7.18</rating>
<name>Akiyama Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2394" picture="51297.jpg">Noda Asumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52185" type="main character in" update="2013-01-18">
<rating votes="2">9.10</rating>
<name>Aoshima Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34983" picture="16806.jpg">Madera Tsukasa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="18808" update="2005-01-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18809" update="2005-01-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
