<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="186" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>48</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>1999-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aa! Megami-sama! Chicchaitte Koto wa Benri Da ne!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ah! My Goddess: Being Small is Convenient</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Моя богиня! Приключения Мини-Богинь</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">오! 나의 여신님 ~작다는 것은 편리해~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">mini goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ams: chikobene</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ああっ女神さまっ 小っちゃいって事は便利だねっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Adventures of Mini-Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Mini-Göttinnen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ah! My Mini Goddess</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="27" type="Parent Story">Aa! Megami-sama!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1092" approval="10" total="10">Binzume Yousei</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="266334">This was a bit better than I thought. But only a bit. It`s still not good, overall. Rather good animation and a few funny moments thanks to Gan isn`t really enough to keep you going. Episode 28 came out of nowhere, being all serious and artsy, and I liked that. Still, this series is absolutely for fans only. Huge fans. There`s nothing really worthwhile here otherwise.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="817" type="Original Work">Fujishima Kousuke</name>
<name id="4245" type="Story Composition">Yonemura Shouji</name>
<name id="5679" type="Chief Direction">Sutou Norihiko</name>
<name id="4572" type="Music">Murayama Tatsuya</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="6043" type="Character Design">Kazui Hiroko</name>
<name id="8384" type="Direction">Matsumura Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>"One ordinary day in may. Three goddesses from heaven appeared at the door of a likable young college student. The goddesses used their many powers to help people find happiness. And sometimes for a lark they would make themselves small." — from intro
Spring, love is in the air and http://anidb.net/ch7534 [Gan] the rat gets a lot more than he bargains for with the help of http://anidb.net/ch2237 [Urd]`s fortune telling.
Urd, http://anidb.net/ch2240 [Skuld] and Gan are sunbathing when another rat falls through the ceiling mumbling about "arms and arms of gold" somewhere in the attic. Skuld assembles three treasure-hunting thingamajiggies and the adventure is on.
Gan, sitting on the temple roof enjoying the sun, wishes he could fly like a bird... Urd is only too happy to grant that wish, or something along those lines. When Skuld offers her assistance via another set of her gadgets only deep space seems to be the limit.
Having gained too much weight, Urd and Skuld are only too happy to help Gan slim down to normal using Skuld`s brand new gadgets and Urd`s latest concoction.
Eating a not so fresh piece of cake, Gan ends up with a stomach ache. The cures that Urd and Skuld think up are worse than the ailment though, turning the poor Gan into Gabira, the Giant Monster.
Thankfully, http://anidb.net/ch2234 [Belldandy] usually stays out of "helping" even more...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1290">4.28</permanent>
<temporary count="1311">6.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3436.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>266</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>303</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9</identifier>
<identifier>tdkray</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Oh_My_Goddess!#The_Adventures_of_Mini-Goddess</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ああっ女神さまっ#.E3.81.82.E3.81.82.E3.81.A3.E5.A5.B3.E7.A5.9E.E3.81.95.E3.81.BE.E3.81.A3_.E5.B0.8F.E3.81.A3.E3.81.A1.E3.82.83.E3.81.84.E3.81.A3.E3.81.A6.E4.BA.8B.E3.81.AF.E4.BE.BF.E5.88.A9.E3.81.A0.E3.81.AD.E3.81.A3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1301</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>125545</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1643</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="509" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-19">
<name>clone</name>
<description>This character is grown from a single somatic cell or cell nucleus and genetically identical to it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1994" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-25">
<name>flying</name>
<description>This character has wings, natural or artificial, which enable the character to take flight. Or is in command of some form of levitation (e.g. a witch using a broom to fly).
Not to be confused with "flying planes" or "flying helicopters".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3108" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-20">
<name>catastrophic gadgets</name>
<description>Comedy element: One of the characters in the anime tends to "invent", "create", or "call into existence" all sorts of wacky gadgets. The intent is to help the other protagonists in some way. Only that this fails every single time, ending in a catastrophe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3826" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-26">
<name>evil laugh</name>
<description>The thing all great evil villains do after saying/doing something evil.
Some notable examples of great evil villains with evil laughs: Dr. Evil, Dr. Horrible, The Joker, Lelouche, Light, and Mickey Mouse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4665" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>propaganda</name>
<description>Propaganda is communication aimed at influencing the attitude of a community toward some cause or position. As opposed to impartially providing information, propaganda in its most basic sense, presents information primarily to influence an audience. Propaganda often presents facts selectively (thus lying by omission) to encourage a particular synthesis, or uses loaded messages to produce an emotional rather than rational response to the information presented. The desired result is a change of the attitude toward the subject in the target audience to further a political agenda.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6090" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Norse mythology</name>
<description>Norse mythology, or Scandinavian mythology, is the body of mythology of the North Germanic people stemming from Norse paganism and continuing after the Christianization of Scandinavia and into the Scandinavian folklore of the modern period. The Norse mythology consists of tales of various deities, beings, and heroes derived from numerous sources from both before and after the pagan period, including medieval manuscripts, archaeological representations, and folk tradition. [...]
Most of the surviving mythology centres on the plights of the gods and their interaction with various other beings, such as humanity and the jötnar, beings who may be friends, lovers, foes and/or family members of the gods. The cosmos in Norse mythology consist of Nine Worlds that flank a central cosmological tree, Yggdrasil. Units of time and elements of the cosmology are personified as deities or beings. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7061" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-27">
<name>the lives of mini-people</name>
<description>The show features the lives of mini-people, characters much shorter than would be natural, and how they interact with a world of things much bigger than themselves. This is not about characters merely being short, but about living in a world of things that, from their perspective, are gigantic.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2215" type="appears in" update="2015-02-19">
<rating votes="233">3.72</rating>
<name>Morisato Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morisato Keiichi is a 21-year-old Engineering student at Nekomi Technical Institute. He has a natural aptitude for anything mechanical, and is brilliant when it comes to engineering. Keiichi is a member of the NIT Motor Club. Keiichi is a good person with a good heart. He is nice to everyone regardless of how they treat him or what they do. He is very forgiving of Skuld and Urd; despite the amount of trouble and grief they cause him.</description>
<picture>168975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2234" type="main character in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="819">8.93</rating>
<name>Belldandy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Belldandy is exceptionally kind-hearted, even for a goddess. She can easily sense other people`s emotions and tries her best to be empathetic to all those around her, displaying a combination of "serene beauty and acceptance". She rarely holds a grudge and is always willing to forgive anyone who does injury to her.</description>
<picture>43148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2237" type="main character in" update="2018-06-01">
<rating votes="573">8.66</rating>
<name>Urd</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urd is Belldandy`s older half sister and is the second Goddess to appear to Keiichi. Unlike her younger sister Belldandy, Urd is very impulsive and headstrong. Belldandy describes Urd as being very passionate about everything she does. Urd is a great believer in the idea that the `End justifies the Means`. Urd`s impulsiveness often makes her act first without fully considering the consequences.</description>
<picture>168963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2240" type="main character in" update="2015-02-19">
<rating votes="349">4.94</rating>
<name>Skuld</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skuld is the younger sister of Belldandy and is the third Goddess to appear to Keiichi Morisato. Skuld is an engineering genius, capable of building just about anything out of the most mundane parts under most limited resources. Skuld regularly clashes with her sister Urd, particularly when it comes to Belldandy`s relationship with Keiichi. However, the two sisters do love each other and will work together to solve a problem or stave off a mutual threat.</description>
<picture>168962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2246" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="50">5.15</rating>
<name>Marller</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marller or Mara in the English anime was once the childhood friend of the goddesses who are the main characters, though now she`s a demon. Urd and Mara used to be very good friends, but got separated when Urd chose to be a goddess. Her actual duty is to increase the market share of the demons on earth, though she decides that removing the goddesses will make it one hundred percent.</description>
<picture>1985.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7534" type="main character in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<name>Gan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gan, also known as gan-chan, is the much-abused temple rat from the Adventures of Mini-Goddess series. Generally nice and friendly, Gan is somewhat emotional and very excitable, but highly prone to gluttony. Due to his nice and trusting nature, he`s often led off on some wild adventure by Skuld and Urd, with the end result of Gan getting physically abused in some way.</description>
<picture>26245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4768" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">占いしようよっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Tell Your Fortune</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Partnersuche mit Hindernissen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lisons donc ton avenir !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uranai Shiyou yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4769" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空を飛ぼうよっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Fly in the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der König der Lüfte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Allez, parcourons le ciel !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora o Tobou yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4770" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">屋根裏の秘宝 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Treasure in the Attic, Part II</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf in den Kampf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor dans le grenier (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaneura no Hihou: Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4771" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">屋根裏の秘宝 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Treasure in the Attic, Part I</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf Schatzsuche</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor dans le grenier (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaneura no Hihou: Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5919" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙を翔ぼうよっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Fly Into Space</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Ratte im Weltraum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Traversons l`espace !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu o Tobou yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5920" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スリムでGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Slimming Down! Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Traumfigur</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En piste pour le régime !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Slim de Go!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5921" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大怪獣ガビラ 誕生篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gabira, the Giant Monster: The Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Angriff der Schimmelpilze</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Moizilla, le monstre géant (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikaijuu Gabira: Tanjou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5922" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大怪獣ガビラ 決戦篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gabira, the Giant Monster: The Final Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Monster Schimmella</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Moizilla, le monstre géant (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikaijuu Gabira: Kessen Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5923" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~誰が為に鐘は鳴る~ 缶詰の謎...?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Whom the Bell Tolls: The Mysterious Can of Food</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die mysteriöse Dose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère de la boîte de conserve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ta ga Tame ni Kane wa Naru: Kanzume no Nazo...?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5924" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~誰が為に鐘は鳴る~ ダイヤの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Whom the Bell Tolls: The Secret of the Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Fluch des Diamanten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret du diamant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ta ga Tame ni Kane wa Naru: Dia no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5925" update="2005-01-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰が為に鐘は鳴る 大怪獣ガビラ 逆襲篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gabira, the Gant Monster: The Strike Back</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schimmellas Rache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Moizilla, Le monstre géant (3)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ta ga Tame ni Kane wa Naru: Daikaijuu Gabira - Gyakushuu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5926" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野球やろうぜっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Play Baseball!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Baseball-Profis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jouons au base-ball !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakyuu Yarouze!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5927" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウルドの子守日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Urd`s Babysitting Journal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Alles-Hört-Auf-Mein-Kommando-Pille</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal d`Urd, baby-sitter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urd no Komori Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5928" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロポーズ大作戦ですだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Proposal Scheme</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Operation Große Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est le stratagème de demande en mariage, da !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Propose Daisakusen Desu Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5929" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新婚さんいらっしゃい!! ですだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome, Newlyweds!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Urds Verwandlung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue les jeunes mariés, da !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkon-san Irasshai!! Desu Da</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5930" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デンワしてダーリンっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phone Me, Darling!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ruf mich an, Liebling!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ah! my goddess ! appelle-moi, darling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denwa Shite Darling!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5931" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大雪原SOS 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SOS in the Big Snowfield, Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein gefährliches Unterfangen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">SOS dans la neige (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisetsugen SOS: Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5932" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大雪原SOS 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SOS in the Big Snowfield, Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf ums Überleben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">SOS dans la neige (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisetsugen SOS: Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5933" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キッチンファイター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kitchen Fighters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rattenkämpfe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat de boxe dans la cuisine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitchen Fighter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5934" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">岩ちゃんの華麗なる日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gan-chan`s Magnificent Days</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Rattenleben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fabuleux destin de Gan-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gan-chan no Kareinaru Hibi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5935" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ああっ仏さまっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ah, My Buddah!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verliebt in einen Buddha</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ah! my bouddha !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa! Butsu-sama!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5936" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">岩ちゃんの骨まで愛して</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story of Gan-chan: Love Me to the Bone</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Fressmaschine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amour dévorant de Gan-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gan-chan no Hone made Aishite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5937" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンドやろうぜ A面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Form a Band! Side A</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aller Anfang ist schwer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vive le rock`n roll ! - Face A</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Band Yarou ze: A-men</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5938" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンドやろうぜ B面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Form a Band! Side B</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine schwierige Entscheidung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vive le rock`n roll ! - Face B</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Band Yarou ze: B-men</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5939" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チュウ・ハード 岩ちゃん絶体絶命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chu Hard: Gan-chan`s Desperate Situation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Antidiebstahlmaschine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rat fatal - Gan-chan menacé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuu Hard: Gan-chan Zettai Zetsumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5940" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チュウ・ハード2 魔王降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chu Hard 2: Descent of the Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vorsicht: Käse!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rat fatal 2 - L`arrivée du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuu Hard 2: Maou Kourin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5941" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウルドでPON!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pop! Goes the Urd</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fanpost von Gan-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avec Urd, pon !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urd de Pon!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5942" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rainy Day</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rainy Day</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Tag im Regen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jour de pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rainy Day</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5943" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢で逢いましょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Meet in Our Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verräterische Träume</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontrons-nous en rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume de Aimashou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5944" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女名探偵スクルドの事件簿1 盗まれた三つの秘宝の謎 湯煙に隠された危険な罠!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Female Detective Skuld`s First Case... Mystery of the Three Stolen Treasures: The Dangerous Trap Hidden in the Steamy Smoke!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Detektiv Skuld</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le célèbre détective Skuld, dossier numéro 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Meitantei Skuld no Jikenbo 1: Nusumareta Mittsu no Hihou no Nazo - Yukemuri ni Kakusareta Kiken na Wana!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5977" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女神 愛の劇場 女神の剣 GODDESS BLADE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goddess Love Theater: Goddess Blade</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf dem Bösen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée de la Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Megami Ai no Gekijou: Megami no Tsurugi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5978" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こちら他力本願寺内 すぐやる課</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quick Fix Division of the Tariki Hongan Temple</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Muckikraftamin-Pillen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Temple tous risques - section d`intervention rapide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kochira Tarikihonganjinai Suguyaruka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5979" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">釣りバス日誌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fishing Journal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Petri Heil!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Carnet de pêche perchée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuri Bass Nisshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5980" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我に僕(しもべ)を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Give Me Some Servants</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Verräter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À moi, des serviteurs !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ware ni Shimobe o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5981" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1998-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍びのオキテ 上の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rules of the Ninja: Volume I</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mr. Kontrolletti</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La loi des ninjas (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobi no Okite: Jou no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5982" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍びのオキテ 下の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rules of the Ninja: Volume II</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Kampf geht weiter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La loi des ninjas (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobi no Okite: Ge no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6375" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウルドVSウルド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Urd vs. Urd</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das zweite Ich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Urd contre Urd</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urd vs Urd</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6376" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">岩ちゃん選挙に立つ 立志編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gan-chan Runs For Election "Being Self-Made" Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bestechung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gan-chan candidat aux élections (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gan-chan Senkyo ni Tatsu: Risshi Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6377" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">岩ちゃん選挙に立つ 風雲編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gan-chan Runs For Election "Time of Change" Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lügen haben kurze Beine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gan-chan candidat aux élections (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gan-chan Senkyo ni Tatsu: Fuuun Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6378" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウルド究極ダイエット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Urd`s Ultimate Diet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Schlankheitswahn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le furieux régime d`Urd</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urd Kyuukyoku Diet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6379" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハッピーバースデイ岩ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy Birthday, Gan-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Drei Wünsche</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Joyeux anniversaire Gan-chan !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happy Birthday Gan-chan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6380" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ああっ平凡な大学生っ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ah! My Average College Student</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schön ist das Studentenleben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ah! mon banal étudiant !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa! Heibon na Daigakusei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6381" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こんな事もあるんだねっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Happens Once in a While</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Raumschiff Lavamat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce genre de chose arrive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konna Koto mo Arunda ne!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6382" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機関車岩ちゃん No.0044</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gan-chan the Locomotive</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Volle Kraft voraus!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gan-chan la locomotive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikansha Gan-chan No.0044</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6383" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">味噌の壷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miso Jar</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefangen im Misotopf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pot de miso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miso no Tsubo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6384" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DX人生すごろく★衛星版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deluxe Game of Life: Satellite Version</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bis zum bitteren Ende</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeu de la vie - Édition prestige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">DX Jinsei Sugoroku: Eiseiban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6385" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めきめきメモリアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mekimeki High School Memorial</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Frühlingsgefühle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Crac-Crac Memorial</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mekimeki Memorial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6386" update="2009-02-24">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1999-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これからどうなるのっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What`ll Happen Next?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gan-chan geht auf Reisen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Que se passera-t-il ensuite ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore kara Dou Naru no!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48836" update="2009-12-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48837" update="2011-09-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96133" update="2011-09-03">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109738" update="2011-09-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
