<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1864" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>19</episodecount>
<startdate>1986-05-03</startdate>
<enddate>1986-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hikari no Densetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Legend of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Story of Hikari</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Hikari - Die kleinen Superstars</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Легенда о Хикари</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Legenda Światła</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">光の伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die kleinen Superstars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Cynthia ou le rythme de la vie</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Hilary</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Piruetas</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="478" approval="1" total="5">Glass no Kamen</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/hikari_no_densetsu.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="830" type="Unknown Relation">Tatsunoko Production</name>
<name id="7871" type="Character Design">Hashimoto Toyoko</name>
<name id="5273" type="Series Composition">Sonoda Hideki</name>
<name id="500" type="Chief Direction">Mochizuki Tomomi</name>
<name id="5946" type="Music">Kawamura Eiji</name>
<name id="10046" type="Original Work">Asou Izumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Schoolgirl Hikari has two loves: rhythmic gymnastics and Ohishi, a schoolmate who is one of the best gymnasts in his league. But Hikari isn`t the best gymnast in her school and Hatsuki, the best gymnast, loves Ohishi as well. Natsukawa, Hikari`s childhood friend, plays in a band called Mr.D. Over the years, he has come to love Hikari very deeply. Will Hikari gain Ohishi`s love? Or will Natsukawa win her over? When a champion in women`s gymnastics visits, Hikari yearns to enter a world youth championship for gymnastics. Where will her dream lead her?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="114">5.81</permanent>
<temporary count="116">6.52</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>13160.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2224</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>632</identifier>
<identifier>xzrruk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.at-x.com/program/detail/1060</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/hikari_no_densetsu.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hikari_no_Densetsu#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>光の伝説#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1104</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="658" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>gymnastics</name>
<description>A competitive sport in which this character performs optional and prescribed acrobatic feats mostly on special apparatus in order to demonstrate strength, balance, and body control.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4785" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>rock music</name>
<description>Rock music is a genre of popular music that originated as "rock and roll" in the United States in the 1950s, and developed into a range of different styles in the 1960s and later, particularly in the United Kingdom and the United States. Musically, rock has centered on the electric guitar, usually as part of a rock group with electric bass guitar and drums. Typically, rock is song-based music usually with a 4/4 time signature using a verse-chorus form, but the genre has become extremely diverse. Like pop music, lyrics often stress romantic love but also address a wide variety of other themes that are frequently social or political in emphasis. The dominance of rock by white, male musicians has been seen as one of the key factors shaping the themes explored in rock music. Rock places a higher degree of emphasis on musicianship, live performance, and an ideology of authenticity than pop music.</description>
<picurl>10250.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97854" type="main character in" update="2018-09-04">
<name>Kamijou Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9656" picture="36040.jpg">Itou Tsukasa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="26413" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">置き忘れた夢を取り戻せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Retrieve the dream that has been forgotten.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Reingelegt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le premier concert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26414" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追いかけてみたい... 私の新体操</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I want to chase My rythmic gymnastics!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fahrkarte zur Meisterschaft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cynthia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26415" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">好きになってもいいですか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is it alright to like you?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der erste Sieg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Willy je t`aime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26416" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日へと続く夏色の道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The continuing summer road to tomorrow.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wieder zu Hause</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tournoi de corbeille</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26417" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">昨日の笑顔はもうほしくない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I no longer yearn for yesterday`s smile.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Plattenvertrag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde est une jungle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26418" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お風呂でドッキリ!? 胸さわぎの修学旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart-pumping moment at the baths!? The school trip which creates a stir in the heart.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Klassenreise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`excursion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26419" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">全中大会開幕! 私をささえていてほしい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening ceremony! I want your support.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blinde Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les premiers championnats de Cynthia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26420" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もっと遠くを見つめたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I want to see it further.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unter falschem Namen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aller toujours plus loin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26421" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえれ女王! ターゲットはひとり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrection of the Queen! There is only one target.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Finale</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La victoire de Déborah</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26422" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリア登場! 誰かをいつも追いかけて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maria appears! Who is the one who is chasing?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Dianas Abschied</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une championne bulgare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26423" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">渡せない! 栄光へのパスポート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unable to transcend! The passport to glory.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Sprungbrett</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En route vers la victoire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26424" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">切れないでリボン! 恋に... とどけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do not cut the ribbon! Communicate...the love.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nervenkrieg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le ruban du destin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26425" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">片想いの季節・ラブソングが歌いたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Season of affections, I want to sing a love song.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Trainingslager</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La maladie d`amour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26426" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あこがれに向かって飛べたら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If you fly towards your goal.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Es wird ernst</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cynthia n`en fait qu`à sa tête</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26427" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆれる想いを受けとめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overcome the shaking desire.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Aussprache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confessions</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26428" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢みる力をわたしにください</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please give me the strength to witness my dream.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Triumph</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ne jamais abandonner son rêve</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26429" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時間よとまれ・この一瞬にかける!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please stop time, overcome this moment!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sieg oder Niederlage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`important c`est de participer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26430" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつかわかりあえる時まで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Till we understand.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefährlicher Sport</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une mère anxieuse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26431" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見る夢も同じ・二人はライバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The same dream, the two rivals.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Liebesgeständnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le face à face</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97361" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1986-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97362" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1986-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120270" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120271" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
