<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1865" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-08-05</startdate>
<enddate>1990-01-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gosenzosama Banbanzai!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gosenzo-sama Banbanzai!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">御先祖様万々歳!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1866" type="Summary">Maroko</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="24973">Way underrated. Full of brilliantly written dialog and laugh out funny.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/title/gosenzo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6745" type="Character Design">Utsunomiya Satoru</name>
<name id="131" type="Original Work">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="131" type="Direction">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
</creators>
<description>The Yomota family is small and typical: father Kinekuni (42), mother Tamiko (38), and son Inumaru (17). One day, a beautiful girl appears at their front door, calling herself Maroko Yomota, granddaughter of Inumaru who travels back in time with a time machine to visit her ancestors. Even with Tamiko`s strong objection, Kinekuni and Inumaru welcome her to stay with them, and the structure of a happy family has begun to collapse.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="207">7.33</permanent>
<temporary count="210">7.20</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>1003.gif</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5344</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2674</identifier>
<identifier>ykaadv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/title/gosenzo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>御先祖様万々歳!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88660</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2330</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="27632" update="2009-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪婦破家 (あくふいえをやぶる)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Evil Woman breaks into the Household</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Teuflische Frau taucht im Haushalt auf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akufu Ie o Yaburu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27633" update="2006-08-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">酒池肉林 (しゅちにくりん)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gorgeous Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Grenzenloses Festmahl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuchinikurin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27634" update="2006-08-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虎視眈眈 (こしたんたん)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Ambush</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Hinterhalt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koshitantan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27635" update="2006-08-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">捲土重来 (けんどちょうらい)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Calm before the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Ruhe vor dem Sturm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kendochourai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27636" update="2006-08-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一蓮托生 (いちれんたくしょう)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One For All, All For One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichirentakushou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27637" update="2006-08-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">胡蝶之夢 (こちょうのゆめ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Papillon Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kochou no Yume</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
