<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1868" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2005-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gankutsuou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">King of the Cave</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Count of Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Count of Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Count of Monte Cristo: Gankutsuou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lord of the Cave</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cavern King</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Le comte de Monte-Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">El Conde de Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Граф Монте-Кристо</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Hrabia Monte Christo</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Gankutsuou: Hrabia Monte Christo</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="synonym">Greven af Monte-Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="synonym">Greven af Monte Christo</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Grafas Montekristas</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Monte Kristo Kontu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gankutsu Ou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gankutsuou De Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">The Count</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Ganku-Ou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gankut-Ou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gank-Ou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gank</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">巌窟王</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gankutsuou: The Count of Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gankutsuou - Le comte de Monte-Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il conte di Montecristo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Gankutsuou</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">암굴왕</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Zemsta hrabiego Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مونت كريستو</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">O Conde de Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">MonteCristo</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Hrabě Monte Christo</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Monte Cristo grófja</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Contele de Monte Cristo</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">کونت مونت کریستو</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4396" approval="5" total="11">Le Chevalier D`Eon</anime>
<anime id="5113" approval="4" total="16">Mononoke</anime>
<anime id="4832" approval="3" total="9">Romeo x Juliet</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="29">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="485629">I was initially turned off by the animation and artistic direction, but hung on because I was familiar with the Count of Monte Cristo (and familiar with the fact that almost every interpretation has a different climax / ending).  If you can get past the outlandish setting and unconventional style you will love it (this is definitely for fans of the source material).  It also goes against all conventions for anime series (the protagonist &amp; company have a friend that ends up sleeping around with some of their mothers).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="211653">From what I`ve read in other comments, if you haven`t read the actual story, you won`t be too disappointed with this series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It take a while to establish everything and is slow to begin with but once they start the action, this series gets pretty good, not to mention pretty dark at times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other thing I will mention here is the very unique artwork/animation style. I have NEVER seen anything like this style before (Although I`m not a HUGE ANIME NUT like some). I thought it was very colourful and vibrant but at the same time, it created a wonderful sinister ambience. To me, the animation alone, is something to be admired and appreciated.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298777">This wasn`t one of my favorites but was very intriguing. I couldn`t wait to see what would happen next.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="353881">The best adaptation of Dumas` novel, and with creation too. Tbh, I prefer this ending rather than the novel`s. In Gankutsuou`s specific setting it fits in and more suitable than kee[ing the original.
Art work first seems to be an eyesore but somehow the more I watch the more I feel it`s so captivating, e.g. the scene the count 1st appeared, the scene where Haidee walked in the opera house.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="452392">Fantastic anime! Visuals are gorgeous and story-telling is fantastic!  Do NOT miss this!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="315968">Great story, although it does waver in the last third. Worth seeing though just for The Count, who is one of the most exciting characters to appear in anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="186509">By no means better then the original The Count of Monte Cristo but a interesting version of it nonetheless. Highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="538961">You already know if this is something you want to see, knowing of the source material and its straying from anime convention. Needless to say, definitely not for everyone. 

I would say it`s let down a little in one aspect. If I were to show this to someone not familiar with anime, at the over the top reactions  - even considering the intentional melodrama - the person would no doubt roll their eyes or even laugh. Why couldn`t the characters respond more naturally? I really cant understand what goes through Japanese minds, its infuriating at times. It especially stands out here in this series because of the unusual high standard of everything else. It`s such a pity, I feel this could have gone a long way in gaining recognition for the medium outside the usual circles.

On and also (this not being a fault of the show itself) if you are familiar with the story, some episodes can be a bit slow, so keep that in mind.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="311540">Absolutely stunning masterpiece based on a classic novel by Alexandre Dumas who I honestly believe would have been pleased with the adaptation.  The anime stays true to that which is most important within the novel and creates the same level of intrigue, suspense and twists that made the novel such a delight to read.  Did I mention the stunning animation to match the plot?  The use of flash sequences to create movement in characters, seriously, watch it, it`s just amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="459074">I enjoyed the unusual artwork for this anime even if it took me some time to get used to it. I really think this anime is great for everyone and should be given a shot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="795721">The best adaptation of Monte Cristo, imo.
I rarely like a naive character, but I do like Albert. His character development is my favorite and makes the couple last episodes feels more powerful. The Count and Haydee looks really charismatic. Valentine and Victoria design is my favorite. Every characters design is unique. Even the background characters.
The animation is OK. Episode six is probably the best.
It has been years, but I`m still singing the calm (before the storm) opening song. The ending song is cool too.
The plot? Great!

Some problem though. The art-style is to harsh for my eyes (still love it). I watched it back when Animax airing at 3 PM (?). Gave me a big headache. Some CGI scene also gave me a motion sickness. Probably why I always watch it on night. But the anime is just so damn good. This anime feels like a drug.

Tl;dr, one of the best slow-paced revenge anime. Watch it. Your eyes can`t handle it? Watch it slowly, it helps for me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="224005">If you liked Count of Monte Christo you`ll LOVE this and even if you didn`t this is a spectacular anime of it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="75679">Masterpiece!!
Watch it know. 
Unique.
It`s the perfect exemple of what you can do in an anime that you can`t in a manga, a novel or a movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="411071">the art , the sound , the imageniation u definitely must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="425337">I have seen many anime`s over my life, so many in fact that some seem to blur together. It has gotten to the point that i can predict outcomes due to my formalities. As For Gankutsuou its something new , even though it was based off of previous works, The art style of the whole animation is food for my artistic soul and which the story equally holds the same value this anime is a must see! You will thank me after you watch it, happy Viewing!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="261686">A work of art, within a work of art.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="339943">The Count of Monte Cristo as you`ve never seen it before-- and yet, probably the book`s most faithful adaptation to date, science fiction elements aside.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="193384">It`s good. You have to watch it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20111219084923/http://www.gankutsuou.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="1464" type="Series Composition">Kouyama Shuuichi</name>
<name id="1462" type="Direction">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="1463" type="Original Work">Alexandre Dumas</name>
<name id="1466" type="Character Design">Matsubara Hidenori</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="1462" type="Original Plan">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="1474" type="Music">Jean-Jacques Burnel</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based loosely on the book written by http://anidb.net/cr1463 [Alexandre Dumas] titled Comte de Monte-Cristo (The Count of Monte Cristo), this story is set in a far future time against an intergalactic backdrop.
http://anidb.net/ch954 [Albert] was a boy who had been born to a noble family in Paris. He made a journey to the moon with http://anidb.net/ch963 [Franz] to escape from their tedious lives. On the moon, he met a millionaire calling himself http://anidb.net/ch958 [the Count of Monte Cristo].
The Count lived a life of splendour in a rich hotel, with beautiful women waiting on him and strong men guarding him. Albert was fascinated by this Count who seemed to know everything, and the two became friends. Albert eventually invited the Count to visit him in Paris.
The Count`s past slowly resurfaces, to the greatest displeasure of everybody involved.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4647">8.11</permanent>
<temporary count="4702">8.23</temporary>
<review count="13">7.84</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221586.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4194</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1465</identifier>
<identifier>eaehir</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/gankutsuou/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20111219084923/http://www.gankutsuou.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gankutsuou:_The_Count_of_Monte_Cristo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>巌窟王_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>478</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321241</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7013</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1291" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-01">
<name>aristocrat</name>
<description>An aristocrat or noble is a member of the aristocracy or nobility, an upper class in feudal societies. Nobles may or may not hold any specific nobility title. For simplicity`s sake, royalty should also be considered nobility.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2740" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>mother-son incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between a mother and her son.</description>
<picurl>210876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3088" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-31">
<name>manipulation</name>
<description>When someone else is pulling the strings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3433" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>power corrupts</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3826" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-26">
<name>evil laugh</name>
<description>The thing all great evil villains do after saying/doing something evil.
Some notable examples of great evil villains with evil laughs: Dr. Evil, Dr. Horrible, The Joker, Lelouche, Light, and Mickey Mouse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3958" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>coup d`etat</name>
<description>A coup d`état (/ˌkuːdeɪˈtɑː/; French: blow of state; plural: coups d`état), also known as a coup, a putsch, or an overthrow, is the sudden and illegal seizure of a government, usually instigated by a small group of the existing state establishment to depose the established government and replace it with a new ruling body. A coup d`état is considered successful when the usurpers establish their dominance. If a coup fails, a civil war may ensue.</description>
<picurl>10266.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4575" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-20">
<name>ukiyo-e</name>
<description>A genre of Japanese woodblock printing and painting, featuring motifs of landscapes, tales from history, the theatre, and pleasure quarters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5679" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>machiavellian intrigues</name>
<description>Named after Niccolò di Bernardo dei Machiavelli (3 May 1469 - 21 June 1527). Machiavelli is considered one of the founders of modern political science, and was a philosopher and diplomat.
He is famous for his political treatise `The Prince`, which is essentially a manual about the acquisition and maintenance of power, including the need for deceit and the application of armed force.
It is the use of deceit from which the term `Machievellian` derives. This term generally applies to a person who uses deceit to manipulate others for their own amoral (and usually power hungry) ends.
This anime contains at least one character whose intrigues drive the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="43" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="14">6.28</rating>
<name>Eugenie de Danglars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s fiancée. The only daughter of the Danglars family, whose father is a prominent banker in Paris. Growing up as Albert`s childhood friend, she is always talking back to him. She is cheerful and social, and is good at playing the piano. She has a strong desire to become a pianist in the future.</description>
<picture>23475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="954" type="main character in" update="2012-01-31">
<rating votes="25">3.72</rating>
<name>Albert de Morcerf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert de Morcerf was born between General Fernand, who is setting his sights on becoming the next president, and Mercedes, also known as the flower of high society, he was raised in comfort. He meets The Count of Monte Cristo in a city called Luna, which is situated on the surface of the moon. He ends up being attracted to The Count`s elegant outlaw behaviours and becomes captivated by him.</description>
<picture>23474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="956" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="23">7.46</rating>
<name>Haydee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious, beautiful girl who works for The Count. Due to her exotic looks and classy appearance, she becomes the talk of high society in Paris. When there is a visitor at The Count`s mansion, one can catch a glimpse of her. However, she rarely appears in public.</description>
<picture>23473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="958" type="main character in" update="2012-02-02">
<rating votes="76">9.19</rating>
<name>Monte-Cristo Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An enormously wealthy and enigmatic man who returned triumphantly from the depth of space. With Albert`s introduction, he makes his debut in the high society of Paris. With his attractive looks and witty conversation skills, he instantly becomes a favourite within that world.
However, his true identity is that of a cool-headed, vengeful demon, who vows to seek revenge against his former friends who have betrayed him in the past.</description>
<picture>23472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="960" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-14">
<rating votes="19">7.76</rating>
<name>Peppo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A beautiful boy dressed as a girl who Albert meets during his trip. Due to unexpected circumstances, (s)he ends up falling in love with him at first sight. (S)he has a personality like a little devil, and is always toying with Albert`s heart.</description>
<picture>23471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="961" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Mercedes de Morcerf</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s mother. With her beauty and her cultured background, she is known as the flower of high society. At home, she supports the family as a good wife and mother.</description>
<picture>23470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="962" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-02">
<rating votes="8">2.69</rating>
<name>Fernand de Morcerf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s father. General of the space military. Widely regarded as a hero around space, his popularity has prompted him to consider running in the next presidential election. He is keeping busy preparing for the next presidential campaign.</description>
<picture>23469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="963" type="main character in" update="2012-02-01">
<rating votes="31">7.73</rating>
<name>Franz d`Epinay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s best friend. An intelligent, smart boy who always looks after Albert, in spite of being dragged around by Albert`s spontaneous ideas and whims. He gets concerned about Albert, who is progressively being captivated by The Count, and warns him repeatedly to be careful.</description>
<picture>23468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3459" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="8">4.81</rating>
<name>Valentine de Villefort</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only daughter of Attorney General Villefort. She is a quiet girl, who cares for her wheelchair-bound grandfather, Noirtier more than anybody else in her family. She is engaged to Franz.</description>
<picture>23467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31934" picture="85797.jpg">Miura Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3460" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="6">4.74</rating>
<name>Maximilien Morrel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s friend. A military captain who was raised as a commoner. Due to his nature of being too serious and honest, he ends up proposing to Valentine, who already has a fiancée. His family operates a trading business in Marseilles.</description>
<picture>23466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3461" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.12</rating>
<name>Lucien Debray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s friend. Works as the Interior Ministry`s first secretary. He is a womaniser and at first glance, may seems shallow, but is a good adviser to Albert and Franz.</description>
<picture>23465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2047" picture="68288.jpg">Domon Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3462" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Beauchamp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s friend. Raised as a commoner, he is a reporter who works for a tabloid newspaper. Being overzealous about his work as a reporter, he is always trying to gather up stories without taking into consideration that he may be bothering others by doing so.</description>
<picture>23464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3463" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">3.52</rating>
<name>Raoul de Chateau-Renaud</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albert`s friend. The oldest child of a noble family. Born in a distinguished family in Paris of old aristocratic lineage, he is a popular individual who is liked by everyone. An unequalled lover of classic cars, he works hard on his collection day and night.</description>
<picture>23463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12276" picture="10557.gif">Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3464" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="9">3.01</rating>
<name>Andrea Cavalcanti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Andrea Cavalcanti is the son of an aristocrat who came from the eastern part of space. He possesses immense wealth that has been passed over many generations. With handsome looks and noble manners, he has instantly become a young nobleman of high society in Paris.</description>
<picture>23462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3465" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="7">2.21</rating>
<name>Danglars Danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The president of Danglars Bank, the largest bank in Paris. Father of Eugénie. He is a mogul who dominates the economy in Paris, and is extraordinarily obsessed with money.</description>
<picture>23461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3466" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">2.30</rating>
<name>Victoria de Danglars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Eugenie. Taking advantage of her husband`s indifference, she enjoys having affairs with younger men. She loves her fine horse named Eclipse, which she acquired at a high price.</description>
<picture>23460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3467" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="6">1.88</rating>
<name>Gerard de Villefort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief Judge of the High Court. Father of Valentine. He holds the highest decision-making authority within the administration of justice in Paris. His judgements are purely cold-hearted. Given his ambitious professional career goals and strong desire to attain power, he frequently neglects his family.</description>
<picture>23459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3468" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">2.55</rating>
<name>Heloise de Villefort</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valentine`s stepmother. She is excessively protective over her only child Edouard, the son she had with Villefort, and spoils him rotten. Her hobby of toxicology has gradually intensified, leading her to conducts experiments in her personal greenhouse.</description>
<picture>23458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3469" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">6.62</rating>
<name>Giovanni Bertuccio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Count of Monte Cristo`s servant. A quiet, calm and dependable individual, who serves as The Count`s right hand man. His special skills are martial arts and cooking.</description>
<picture>23457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3470" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="6">5.52</rating>
<name>Baptistin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Count of Monte Cristo`s loyal servant. He is talkative, frivolous and deeply adores ducktails. His special skill is throwing knives.</description>
<picture>23456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3471" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="2">3.53</rating>
<name>Ali</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Count of Monte Cristo`s servant. He shows no expression and does not say anything, but he has a unique power that allows him to tame animals using telepathy.</description>
<picture>23455.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3472" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="5">1.47</rating>
<name>Edouard de Villefort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Villefort and Heloise. He grew up pampered and spoiled.</description>
<picture>23454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3095" picture="23998.jpg">Kitou Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3473" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">7.80</rating>
<name>Noirtier de Villefort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former chief of the Interior Ministry`s secret service agency. Villefort`s father. He is now partially paralysed and uses a wheelchair to get around. He dotes on his granddaughter, Valentine, who is always around to take care of him.</description>
<picture>19233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32668" picture="87959.jpg">Nagata Hirotake</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3474" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="5">2.04</rating>
<name>Caderousse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An enigmatic elderly man who arrives in Paris after receiving an invitation to a funeral from Edmond Dantes. He seems to have some connections to Fernand and Danglars` pasts, but...?</description>
<picture>23453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21163" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23913" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅の終わりに僕らは出会う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At Journey`s End, We Meet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous nous rencontrons à la fin du voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi no Owari ni Bokura wa Deau</title>
<summary>Young aristocrat Albert visits the city of Luna on the surface of the moon. He quickly falls under the spell of an enigmatic gentleman - the Count of Monte Cristo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505960</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24550" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24813" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24876" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月に朝日が昇るまで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until the Sun Rises over the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jusqu`à ce que le soleil se lève sur la Lune</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Prima che sorga il sole sulla luna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki ni Asahi ga Noboru made</title>
<summary>Albert is kidnapped! Franz`s frantic attempt to collect the ransom money comes up short, so he warily seeks the assistance of the Count of Monte Cristo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505972</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25073" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">5/22, 嵐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">5/22, Stormy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">22 mai, tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="it">22 maggio. Tempesta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">5/22, Arashi</title>
<summary>Back in Paris, Albert`s sheltered friends grow suspicious upon the arrival of the mysterious Count of Monte Cristo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505974</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25249" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mother`s Secrets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de ma mère</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il segreto di mia madre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha no Himitsu</title>
<summary>The questions surrounding the Count multiply when Albert visits the man`s lavish mansion in Champs Elysees, which is filled with complicated tricks and gold ornaments.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505976</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25816" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたは婚約者を愛してますか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Love Your Fiancee?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aimez-vous votre fiancée ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata wa Kon`yakusha o Aishitemasu ka</title>
<summary>During a pleasure cruise arranged by the Count, a disagreement leads to a duel between Albert and Maximilien. Albert`s raw emotions allow his host to grasp even more sway over his destiny.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505978</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25879" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の憂鬱, 僕の憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Melancholy, My Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sa mélancolie, ma mélancolie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Yuuutsu, Boku no Yuuutsu</title>
<summary>The Count of Monte Cristo positions himself deeper into the lives of those around Albert after meeting a banker and his frustrated wife.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505980</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25880" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘蜜の花園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Flower Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jardin secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu no Hanazono</title>
<summary>The lives of Albert`s aristocratic friends are full of secrets - and the Count is among those prone to whispering in the ears of ladies known to be spoken for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505982</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25881" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブローニュの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night in Boulogne</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un soir à Boulogne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boulogne no Yoru</title>
<summary>At a party thrown by the Count, the guests play a game. They search for a secret room in the villa where a curse is sealed away. Albert has already discovered one secret kept between the Count and Heloise.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505984</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25882" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇色の夢を見た</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Dreamed a Dark Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`ai fait un sombre rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamiiro no Yume o Mita</title>
<summary>The charms of the Count are fading for some, as mysteries and suspicions multiply. The controversy surrounding the mysterious man can only grow when a hidden poisoner begins to ply their trade.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505986</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25883" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エドモンからの手紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Letter from Edmond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une lettre d`Edmond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Edmond kara no Tegami</title>
<summary>Villefort, Danglars, and Morcerf are invited to a funeral. Albert suspects something is wrong and follows them to an old church, where the lid of the casket is about to be opened.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505940</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25884" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">婚約, 破談</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Engagement Broken</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rupture des fiançailles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kon`yaku, Hadan</title>
<summary>Three aristocratic households are growing aware that they are caught in a conspiracy. Franz immediately suspects the Count, but Albert won`t hear of it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505942</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25885" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンコール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encore</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rappel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Encore</title>
<summary>Albert`s engagement is in jeopardy; Baron Dangler prefers his daughter to marry into wealth. Albert rushes to the opera house to find Eugenie - but the curtain may have already closed on his love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505944</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25886" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エデ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haidee</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Haydée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haidee</title>
<summary>Attorney General Villefort demands the arrest of the Count of Monte Cristo, but Heloise takes steps to prevent it from happening.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505946</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25887" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さまよう心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un cœur errant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samayou Kokoro</title>
<summary>After the announcement of Eugenie and Andrea`s engagement leaves Albert feeling betrayed, the Count appears and invites him on a journey deep into the universe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505948</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25888" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せの終わり, 真実の始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of Happiness, the Beginning of Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fin du bonheur, début de la vérité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Owari, Shinjitsu no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Aboard his spaceship, the Count of Monte Cristo tells Albert about an old friend who was betrayed and imprisoned. Back home, Franz is close to learning an important secret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505950</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25889" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スキャンダル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scandal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Scandale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scandal</title>
<summary>Closing in on the secret of the Gankutsuou, Franz learns of a sailor named Edmond Dantes who had strange connections to many of the families in Parisian high society.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505952</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25890" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révélations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku</title>
<summary>After the Count reveals a shocking truth, Albert is left shattered when Franz explains a horrible and twisted story of revenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505954</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25891" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou</title>
<summary>Mercedes enters the misty woods to meet the Count - but only a scene of violence is waiting for her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505956</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25892" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たとえ, 僕が僕でなくなったとしても</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even If I Should Stop Being Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Même si je n`étais plus moi-même</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatoe, Boku ga Boku de Nakunatta Toshitemo</title>
<summary>The Count escalates his plan for revenge, launching a bitter blow at his next target, the Danglars Bank. The impact will be felt by many - including Albert.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505958</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25893" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら, ユージェニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Eugenie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, Eugénie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara, Eugenie</title>
<summary>Being rescued from danger by Chateau-Renaud, Albert learns about Eugenie`s marriage and rushes over to the Danglars` home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505962</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25894" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴公子の正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Boy`s True Identity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`identité du Marquis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikoushi no Shoutai</title>
<summary>An abominable memory, consigned to the darkness of the past, has been resurrected by the hands of the Count and his plan of revenge enters its final stage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505964</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25895" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Riposte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu</title>
<summary>The final target of the Count`s rage returns to Earth and the bombardment of Paris begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505966</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25896" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エドモン・ダンテス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Edmond Dantes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Edmond Dantès</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Edmond Dantes</title>
<summary>Albert and Mercedes are seriously wounded as Fernand prepares for his final showdown with the Count of Monte Cristo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505968</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25897" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渚にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Shore</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sur le rivage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagisa nite</title>
<summary>Five years later, Albert returns to Paris to visit the relics of his former life and the grave of a dear friend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>505970</identifier>
<identifier>gankutsuou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="57232" update="2007-09-04">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Museum: メカニック関連設定資料</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Museum 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Museum: Mechanic Kanren Settei Shiryou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57233" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Museum: 美術背景設定資料</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Museum 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Museum: Bijutsu Haikei Settei Shiryou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57234" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Storyboard</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57235" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Video Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57236" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57237" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136753" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136754" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Short Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136755" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV and DVD Promo Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136756" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Footage of Various Events</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136757" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">福山潤・平川大輔・中村千絵・中原麻衣 座談会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Round-Table Discussion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukuyama Jun, Hirakawa Daisuke, Nakamura Chie, Nakahara Mai: Zadan Kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136758" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">福山潤・中田譲治 対談 Newtype企画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Conversation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukuyama Jun, Nakata George: Newtype Kikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136762" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">前田真宏監督インタビュー 「最終幕に向けて」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director Interview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maeda Masahiro kantoku Interview "Saishuu Maku ni Mukete"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136763" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">DVD発売告知キャストコメント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment on DVD Release</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">DVD Hatsubai Kokuchi Cast Comment</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136764" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">東京国際アニメフェア2005 東京アニメアワード 授賞式の模様 &amp; スタッフ受賞コメント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Anime Fair 2005 Anime Award Ceremony and Staff Comment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo Kokusai Anime Fair 2005, Tokyo Anime Award, Jushoushiki no Moyou &amp; Staff Jushou Comment</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136849" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136850" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136851" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136852" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136853" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136854" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136855" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136856" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136857" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136858" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136859" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136860" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見所コメント 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiyuu Comment 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midokoro Comment 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
