<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="187" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-07-05</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Magical Nyan Nyan Taruto</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Магическая Девочка-Кошка Таруто</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mahou Shoujo Neko Taruto</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">MMMT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MNNT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Taruto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法少女猫[まじかる にゃん にゃん]たると</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Magical Meow Meow Taruto</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="221410">Predy ezt meg köll nézned^^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20050205165526/http://www.b-ch.com/contents/taruto/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1924" type="Direction">Sunaga Tsukasa</name>
<name id="6043" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kazui Hiroko</name>
<name id="6517" type="Original Work">Kaishaku</name>
<name id="794" type="Animation Work">TNK</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="6043" type="Character Design">Kazui Hiroko</name>
<name id="7133" type="Series Composition">Ueda Kouji</name>
<name id="10659" type="Series Composition">Takadera Akihiko</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
</creators>
<description>The lore of cats speak of the Nekomata family, the members of which possessed extremely powerful magical powers. Long ago, the Nekomata family line ceased to exist, but cats everywhere have come to know the exploits of the Nekomata as fairy tales. Taruto is a girl cat that firmly believes she is a long lost member of the Nekomata. She endeavours to practice the magical cat arts, but everything she does turns into magical disaster! Luckily she has a really nice keeper and very understanding friends.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="288">4.20</permanent>
<temporary count="289">6.34</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>5024.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>415</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>952</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>258</identifier>
<identifier>frcyse</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20050205165526/http://www.b-ch.com/contents/taruto/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法少女猫たると</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234396</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4737</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2079" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-05">
<name>magatama</name>
<description>Magatama are curved beads which first appeared in Japan during the Joumon period. They are often found inhumed in mounded tumulus graves as offerings to deities. They continued to be popular with the ruling elites throughout the Kofun Period of Japan, and are often romanticised as indicative of the Yamato Dynasty of Japan. They are mainly made of jade, agate, quartz, talc, and jasper. Some consider them to be an Imperial symbol, although in fact ownership was widespread throughout all the chieftainships of Kofun Period Japan. It is believed that magatama were popularly worn as jewels for decoration, in addition to their religious meanings. In this latter regard they were later largely replaced by Buddhist prayer beads in the Nara period. In modern Japan, the magatama`s shape of a sphere with a flowing tail is a common visual representation of the human spirit.
The most important magatama is the Yasakani no Magatama, which is part of the Imperial Regalia of Japan, added some time around the Heian period. The Yasakani no Magatama stands for benevolence, and is one of the three items used in the ceremony of imperial ascension. In Japanese mythology, the jewels, along with the mirror, were hung on the tree outside of Amaterasu`s cave to lure her out. It is believed to be a necklace composed of jade magatama stones instead of a solitary gem as depicted in popular culture. It is believed to be enshrined in Kokyo, the Japanese Imperial Palace.
The consensus among Japanese archaeologists is that magatama originated in Joumon Japan before spreading to the Asian continent through the Korean peninsula. It is claimed that the earliest Korean prehistoric magatama date to the Early Mumun (post-850 BC) and are generally found in the southern part of peninsula in proximity to Japan. Charles Keally, an archaeologist who has conducted research on magatama, states: The magatama`s origins are more controversial. These curved jewels of jadeite are common in Kofun Period burials, and they are common also in Korean sites of the same age. But magatama are found in Yayoi sites, too, and unquestionable true magatama are reported also in Jomon sites in Tohoku as early as about 1000 B.C., long before true magatama appeared in Korea. The magatama is found also on early Korean royal gold crowns and has long been considered a sign of royalty in Korea as well as being a connection with Shamanistic elements.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>62069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="104417" type="main character in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Taruto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104422" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104423" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="86" picture="222842.jpg">Yamamoto Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104424" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Monaka Iori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104425" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Monaka Kinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236392.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2051" picture="224288.jpg">Tsuruno Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104426" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Doumyouji Anzuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104427" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Okaki Geppei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104428" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Gallette</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104429" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Chiffon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104430" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Rakugan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104431" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Nachos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104432" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Torte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236305.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104433" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Kabekawa Mousse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104434" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Saburet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104435" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Nougat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236309.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104436" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Potechi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104437" type="appears in" update="2019-07-14">
<name>Cookie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104438" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Candy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104495" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Rinjin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104497" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Golden Shop Lady</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48559" picture="197380.jpg">Saitou Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104498" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23531" picture="222835.jpg">Yukiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104499" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Blanc Mange</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104500" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Andou Natsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104501" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Custer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104503" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Chikuro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9599" picture="222797.jpg">Aoyama Touko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104504" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Dop</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104505" type="appears in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Jelly Beans</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3505">Shimizu Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104506" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-17">
<name>Uirou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104510" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-18">
<name>Mouhitori no Taruto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2077" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はらはら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uneasiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harahara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2078" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぺらぺら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">labbing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Perapera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2079" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のこったのこった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perserverance Perserverance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokotta Nokotta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2080" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">むかしむかし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Time Ago</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukashi Mukashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2081" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さいたさいた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blooming and Blooming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saita Saita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2082" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじまりはじまり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Ye, Come All!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2083" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">てくてく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walked to Walk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tekuteku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2084" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ないしょないしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naisho Naisho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2085" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めでたしめでたし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy Ending</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Medetashi Medetashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2086" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちりんちりん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ting Ting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chirinchirin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2087" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どきどき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pit-a-pat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2088" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちかちかきらきら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glittering, Twinkling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikachika Kirakira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84588" update="2007-10-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
