<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1889" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-03-18</startdate>
<enddate>1989-03-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saint Seiya: Saishuu Seisen no Senshi-tachi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Les chevaliers du zodiaque - Le dieu des enfers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Saint Seiya: Movie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖闘士星矢 最終聖戦の戦士たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Saint Seiya: Warriors of the Final Holy Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Les chevaliers du zodiaque - Lucifer : les guerriers de la dernière guerre sainte</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">I Cavalieri dello Zodiaco - L`ultima battaglia</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Los caballeros del zodiaco: El guerrero de armageddon</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Os Guerreiros do Armagedon: A Batalha Final</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="826" type="Parent Story">Saint Seiya</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="123101">This, like most of the other films, is short compared to what we watch nowadays in movie theatres or at home but it ends being good enough to call it worth the time spent to watch.

Some clichés are once again used (like Ikki saving Shun in every single movie) but if you ignore that, the rest is solid. Even the Lucifer short story is great and gives you a bit of Hades feeling which to many is a great story.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="4116" type="Character Design">Araki Shingo</name>
<name id="4248" type="Character Design">Himeno Michi</name>
<name id="4398" type="Direction">Akehi Masayuki</name>
<name id="4295" type="Music">Yokoyama Seiji</name>
<name id="5870" type="Character Design">Naoi Masahiro</name>
<name id="867" type="Original Work">Kurumada Masami</name>
</creators>
<description>Earth is treatened by Lucifer and his fallen angels. Saori and her bronze saints races against time to stop Lucifer from destroying the world.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="419">3.82</permanent>
<temporary count="425">6.17</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>31842.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3332</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1260</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2442</identifier>
<identifier>eprqbx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2430</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>150724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2293</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="29" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-18">
<name>Western zodiac</name>
<picurl>161118.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10544" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="29">7.93</rating>
<name>Aries no Muu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Under the tutelage of Shion, the Pope of the Sanctuary, Muu was able to become the Gold Saint of Aries at a young age. While all gold saints have a base of psychic powers to some degree, Muu has been stated to possess the strongest raw psychic talent among all living gold saints. This allows him to manipulate his gift to various degrees: psychokinesis, telepathy, teleportation, and various other powers are at his command.
Muu is very soft spoken, with a scholarly-like personality; his demeanor is very tranquil and logical, almost as if he is a professor of the Sanctuary. He is good friends with Taurus Aldebaran, and is very respectful to the 243 year old master Libra Douko.</description>
<picture>31552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10553" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<name>Taurus no Aldebaran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aldebaran is one of the 12 Guardians of Sanctuary, with the Taurus as his destined constellation. He was the physically strongest of the Gold Saints of modern era. He is Brazilian in origin.
Unlike most of the characters, Aldebaran is often depicted as a friendly guy, laughing and being less serious in times of peace. He was a good friend of Aries Mu, and with Pegasus Seiya (as this last is said in the anime adaptation of the Hades Saga, when Aldebaran sacrificed himself with the other eleven Gold Saints to destroy the Wailing Wall).</description>
<picture>31560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30885" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="73">6.82</rating>
<name>Pegasus no Seiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33220" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="93">7.05</rating>
<name>Andromeda Seiza no Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4932" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33221" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="54">6.26</rating>
<name>Cygnus no Hyouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3277" picture="192234.jpg">Hashimoto Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33222" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="82">8.27</rating>
<name>Dragon no Shiryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33223" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="74">8.27</rating>
<name>Phoenix no Ikki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33224" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="93">7.58</rating>
<name>Kido Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33225" type="appears in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="4">7.36</rating>
<name>Eris</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eris tempted Eri with a golden apple to possess and use her as a tool to bring chaos into this world. After capturing Saori Kido (Athena), Eris placed a golden apple in front of Saori`s chest to drain her power and life force to the point she would no longer need Eri`s body, and proceeds with her plan to take over the world. It had been foretold that, if Athena were to die, all of the dead Saints with grief in their hearts would be revived to finish Earth`s destruction.</description>
<picture>73097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3250" picture="24693.jpg">Fujita Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33448" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Lucifer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2080" picture="43095.jpg">Tsukayama Masane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33449" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Chitenshi no Ashtaroth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33450" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Gitenshi no Moa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33451" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Rikitenshi no Eligor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3370" picture="74440.jpg">Yamaguchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33452" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Shitenshi no Beelzebub</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1816" picture="20691.jpg">Mori Katsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33453" type="appears in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Abel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5208" picture="67245.jpg">Hirokawa Taichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33475" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="23">8.46</rating>
<name>Bronze Saints</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>73618.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43866" type="appears in" update="2012-04-26">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Natasha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3642" picture="25837.jpg">Tsuboi Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43913" type="appears in" update="2012-04-27">
<name>Julian Solo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="19148" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1989-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139023" update="2012-04-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139024" update="2012-04-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">ED</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139025" update="2012-04-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OP</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
