<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1942" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-03-02</startdate>
<enddate>2002-07-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Trava: Fist Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Трава: Межпланетный кулак</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">Trava - Pěstní planeta</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Trava - Tarpplanetinis Kumštis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Trava</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">TRAVA FIST PLANET</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6529" type="Side Story">Redline</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1170" approval="52" total="52">Dead Leaves</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="9746">The more I watch it, the more I love it. Different in art and animation style. Interesting story and a funny non-human main characters duo.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="340757">fun &amp; wacky anime, would love to see them do more.  The should do a series about the Speedmaster battle competition that they were saving up for</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="5160" type="Direction">Koike Takeshi</name>
<name id="5160" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koike Takeshi</name>
<name id="5160" type="Character Design">Koike Takeshi</name>
<name id="699" type="Original Work">Ishii Katsuhito</name>
<name id="699" type="Direction">Ishii Katsuhito</name>
</creators>
<description>From the Japanese short film anthology series "Grasshoppa!" A far, far future story in which two aliens (the future of mankind?) are sent to the planet Fable to mark Area 78. The fee they will receive for fulfilling their contract is extremely lucrative, so why is it they have a bad feeling about a simple job? If that weren`t bad enough, they pick up a young lady, Mikuru, whom they find in the vicinity of the planet, in cryosleep. It`s a wacky and slick SF adventure of hot girls, hot mecha and hotter gags.
Source: http://www.jmate.com/reviews/article_139.html</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1003">5.35</permanent>
<temporary count="1016">6.75</temporary>
<review count="2">7.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10467.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1980</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3600</identifier>
<identifier>skazhq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.grasshoppa.jp/lineup/lineup_06.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Trava:_Fist_Planet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10210" type="main character in" update="2009-07-06">
<rating votes="21">6.70</rating>
<name>Trava</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5595" picture="29757.jpg">Tsuda Kanji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10216" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-06">
<rating votes="14">5.50</rating>
<name>Shinkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6025" picture="47319.jpg">Morishita Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10218" type="appears in" update="2009-07-06">
<rating votes="5">6.58</rating>
<name>Mikiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6026" picture="30746.jpg">Kohinata Shie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10220" type="appears in" update="2009-07-06">
<rating votes="4">4.20</rating>
<name>Reiter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30657.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10224" type="appears in" update="2009-07-06">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Suezaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30663.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="19283" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2002-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19284" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2003-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Planet 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30644" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2002-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31433" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2002-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31434" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2002-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
