<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="195" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-12-03</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Seisou Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin - Reflection</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin: Time Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin OVA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin: Seisouhen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin: Seisou Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Kenshin Reflection</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RuroKen OVA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Seisouhen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kenshin ova 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">るろうに剣心 -明治剣客浪漫譚- 星霜編</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Samurai X: Reflection</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Kenshin - The Chapter of Atonement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kenshin le vagabond - Le chapitre de l`expiation</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Kenshin, El Guerrero Samurai: Final</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="90" type="Prequel">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="400127">This OVA is great for Kenshin fans. Remommend it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260880">the end of a great story.It will definitely broke your heart..If you have seen the prequel,don`t miss it .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="406082">A bittersweet bookend to an excellent series.  While not as good as the prequel OVA it is still well worth the watch and will most likely leave you in tears.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422302">it`s a great OVA! Like it much!
it`s also a small review of the tv series and the end of it!
must watch!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Movie/TV/Kenshin/seisou/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1410" type="Direction">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="1418" type="Character Design">Matsushima Akira</name>
<name id="1414" type="Music">Iwasaki Taku</name>
<name id="509" type="Original Work">Watsuki Nobuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch443 [Himura Kenshin] still searches for atonement...
...and http://anidb.net/ch6619 [Kamiya Kaoru] waits patiently for his return, together with their son, http://anidb.net/ch6623 [Kenji].
It is a battle of love and endurance, as much as it is of justice and inner peace.
Witness the closing of a timeless tale, the ending of a legend, as continued from that of the manga.
Note: Seisou Hen was later collected into a feature-length motion picture with 7 minutes of new animated sequences.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4684">7.53</permanent>
<temporary count="4745">8.10</temporary>
<review count="7">6.30</review>
</ratings>
<picture>135450.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>310</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>401</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>689</identifier>
<identifier>pvglff</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Movie/TV/Kenshin/seisou/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rurouni_Kenshin:_Reflection</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>るろうに剣心_-明治剣客浪漫譚-_(アニメ)#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2581</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236282</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5086</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="435" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-29">
<rating votes="209">8.77</rating>
<name>Hiko Seijuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiko Seijuurou XIII is Himura Kenshin`s master in the anime/manga series Rurouni Kenshin.
Hiko is shown to be sarcastic, misanthropic and a punishing taskmaster, often referring to Kenshin as "My stupid/idiot apprentice," and bringing up Kenshin`s past to provoke him into training harder. Kenshin describes his personality as "crude, cruel, and hateful." Despite this rough exterior, he has a deep sense of responsibility to Kenshin and those he protects, in the rare cases when he does get involved in a situation (usually at his own will). He has also been shown to be highly respectful and polite towards those he considers to be a true warrior, while at the same time condescending on those he considers to be weak. He loves sake, himself, and teasing Kenshin, although this is a testament to his excellent skill and powerful body. Master and student frequently have bouts of slapstick conflict between them. He dislikes socialising, and in order to avoid having to work with people, he makes his living as a pottery artist.</description>
<picture>14731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="443" type="main character in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="1034">9.06</rating>
<name>Himura Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Set in a fictional version of Japan, during the pre-Meiji period, Kenshin is a former legendary assassin known as "Hitokiri Battousai". At the end of the Bakumatsu, he becomes a wandering samurai, now wielding a sakabatou ("reverse-blade sword"), a katana that has the cutting edge on the inwardly curved side of the sword, thus being nearly incapable of killing. Kenshin wanders the countryside of Japan offering protection and aid to those in need, as atonement for the murders he once committed as an assassin. In Tokyo, he meets a young woman named Kamiya Kaoru, who invites him to live in her dojo despite learning about Kenshin`s past. Throughout the series, Kenshin begins to establish lifelong relationships with many people, including ex-enemies, while dealing with his fair share of enemies, new and old. Through these encounters and relationships, Kenshin begins to find true atonement for his past enabling him to fully conquer his "Battousai" nature.</description>
<picture>84396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3011" picture="55684.jpg">Suzukaze Mayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="446" type="cameo appearance in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="91">7.98</rating>
<name>Yukishiro Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukishiro Tomoe was the eldest daughter of a samurai, a low-level bureaucrat who served the Tokugawa Shogunate in Edo. Her only sibling was her younger brother Enishi, who viewed her as a surrogate parent because of their mother`s death shortly after his birth; he threw a tantrum on hearing of her engagement to Kiyosato Akira, the second son of another similarly-ranked family. Her skills included the Edo-mae style of cooking (distinct from Kyoto cuisine), the flower-arrangement art of Ikebana, and beautiful calligraphic handwriting; her signature perfume was the scent of white ume blossoms (hakubaiko). As required by the Shogunate, she practiced Buddhism. Early on, Tomoe`s closeness with the young Battousai was compared to an iris flower, which blooms best in the rain, `even in a rain of blood`.</description>
<picture>14742.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6132" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="201">8.89</rating>
<name>Saitou Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saitou Hajime, based on the real-life personage of the same name, was the leader of the 3rd Squad of the Shinsengumi during the Revolution. He has a long-standing rivalry with Kenshin and firmly believes in "Swift Death to Evil".</description>
<picture>23318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6138" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-04">
<rating votes="2">7.35</rating>
<name>Kiyosato Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23326.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6168" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-15">
<rating votes="6">5.31</rating>
<name>Yukishiro Enishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23391.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6584" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-04-14">
<rating votes="95">7.47</rating>
<name>Shishio Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6618" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="64">4.48</rating>
<name>Myoujin Yahiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Myoujin Yahiko is a young boy, the son of a samurai. When he was younger, both of his parents died, and he was taken in by the Yakuza, who forced him to live as a pickpocket. Once he meets up with Kenshin and Kaoru, he decides to stand up to the Yakuza, and escapes with Kenshin`s help. He joins Kaoru`s dojo to become a stronger swordsman, becoming the first graduate of http://anidb.net/ch21040 [Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu]. Over the course of the series, he becomes a strong warrior. He hates being treated like a child.</description>
<picture>24367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6619" type="main character in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="190">6.62</rating>
<name>Kamiya Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamiya Kaoru is a seventeen-year old dojo instructor and the first main character Kenshin meets. Kaoru is a teacher of the Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu style, a swords style used to protect people, and not harm others. Since her father was killed in the war, responsibility for running the family dojo fell to young Kaoru. After defending Kaoru from the fake Battousai and his allies, Kenshin is invited to live at the dojo. Kaoru quickly develops a crush on Kenshin, soon falling in love with him, although she tends to violently deny it. She recognizes that Kenshin, despite his violent past, is a gentle soul who only wants peace by atoning for the lives he stole during the revolution. Although, personality-wise, she is very different than Yukishiro Tomoe, Kenshin`s first love, (i.e. Kaoru is loud, brash, insecure, and cannot cook anything tasty), Kenshin sees that she is also selfless, compassionate, and caring of others almost to a fault. Her understanding of his nature and wanting to help him find the peace he so desires also draws him to her. In the manga, he is able to find atonement (and Tomoe`s smile) by protecting Kaoru`s happiness as well as his new friends. At the end of the series, she and Kenshin marry and have a son together.</description>
<picture>84399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9823" picture="36572.jpg">Fujitani Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6620" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="123">7.47</rating>
<name>Sagara Sanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagara Sanosuke is a street fighter who befriends Kenshin early in the series. As a youth, Sanosuke ran away from home to join the Sekiho Army, a group of farmers and merchants who fought for the Ishin Shishi during the Meiji Revolution. When the Sekiho were betrayed and executed by the other revolutionaries, Sanosuke escaped and began to pick fights to vent his anger. He challenges Kenshin, a former Ishin Shishi, but when Sanosuke is defeated he becomes one of Kenshin`s closest friends and strongest allies. Sanosuke enjoys fighting, gambling, and mooching off of other people.</description>
<picture>24369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6621" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="26">6.07</rating>
<name>Takani Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takani Megumi, 22 years old, originally forced to make opium for an industrialist, with Kenshin`s support and encouragement, she becomes a doctor to atone for her past misdeeds. Having an attraction for Kenshin herself but knowing that his heart belongs to Kaoru, she takes many opportunities to make Kaoru jealous by asserting herself onto Kenshin (much to Kenshin`s chagrin). Because she is a little older and wiser and can be quite cunning, she is nicknamed "fox lady" by Sanosuke. When it comes down to it, she is loyal and concerned over friends and is always there to patch them up (especially Sanosuke). She also tries to "help" Kaoru to come to terms with her feelings toward Kenshin so that Kenshin could lead a long, happy life. She is from the Aizu region, now Fukushima Prefecture.</description>
<picture>24372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6622" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="10">5.31</rating>
<name>Sanjou Tsubame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanjou Tsubame, a waitress at Tae`s restaurant, becomes Myoujin Yahiko`s sweetheart. She was saved by him from the ronin her family worked for as Yahiko stopped them from robbing the Akabeko. She is very shy and soft spoken. When Himura Kenshin enters a deep depression after the supposed death of Kamiya Kaoru at the hands of Yukishiro Enishi, Tsubame pleads for Kenshin to help Yahiko fight back against one of Enishi`s abandoned allies and brings Kenshin back into the world of the living. Tsubame and Yahiko become a couple in the manga storyline. Watsuki has mentioned in his notes Tsubame and Yahiko`s son Myoujin Shin`ya, who he considered using in a story idea. In Samurai X: Reflection (Rurouni Kenshin: Seisouhen), Tsubame and Yahiko had become a couple.
Watsuki said that he did not use a specific model for Tsubame`s personality. When the author thought of the concept "a young girl being a young man`s motivation to act" he used her as the heroine of the Yahiko storyline printed in Volume 5. The author used Tsubame as a "testament" of "wrong thinking of a previous age" and gave her a manner that contrasts with Yahiko`s "acts-before-he-thinks" manner. According to Watsuki the model originated from a popular "planet-themed" anime series. As Tsubame is "an average girl" the author decided that her hair should either be in a bowl cut or in pigtails. After watching the "planet-themed" series he decided to use a bowl cut. In the final chapter and Yahiko no Sakabatou Watsuki designed Tsubame to look "as cute as possible" since he wanted a story where she was the heroine." Originally he intended for the new waitress outfit, which looks similar to a maid outfit, to be exclusively for Yahiko no Sakabatou since the maid style was in fashion at the time. Watsuki feared that the fashion could be outdated by the time he wrote Yahiko no Sakabatou, so he used the new waitress outfit in the final chapter of Rurouni Kenshin. Tsubame`s name originates from places where Watsuki lived in Niigata.</description>
<picture>24373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6623" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-10">
<rating votes="4">6.40</rating>
<name>Himura Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of http://anidb.net/ch6619 [Kamiya Kaoru] and http://anidb.net/ch443 [Himura Kenshin].</description>
<picture>24374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6624" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-28">
<rating votes="6">8.02</rating>
<name>Yamagata Aritomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamagata Aritomo was one of Kenshin`s comrades. Yagamata grew a mustache since taking position of power in the Meiji government. Yamagata tries to convince Kenshin to stop carrying a sword, but Yamagata realizes that Kenshin`s openly-displayed sword and his actions as a rurouni ensure safety for others. In the anime, he appears again as the assassination target of a corrupt politician, Hashizume, but thanks to Kenshin, he was saved and Hashizume was arrested. Watsuki said that he could not get his version of Yamagata to resemble surviving photographs of the real Yamagata.</description>
<picture>24375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3829" picture="25535.jpg">Kaneko Holly</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6625" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-03">
<name>Ujiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6626" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-03">
<name>Kamiya Koshijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6627" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="8">7.73</rating>
<name>Udou Jin`e</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurogasa, otherwise known as Udou Jin`e, was a hitokiri during the Revolution, and there is evidence he continued killing people well after the end of the Revolution. A master of the Nikaidou Heihou technique (the forced character "Hei" is formed with the kanji for one, two, and eight), attacked high-ranking Imperialist officials of the Meiji government (leading some to believe he fought for the Tokugawa shogunate during the war, since he did state that he was a member of the Shinsengumi, though his thirst for blood led him to killing members of his own squad), killing anyone who stood in his way. He appears as a man dressed in a long scarf, straw hat, and long kimono, and has a unique isukumi (paralyzing terror) technique to project chi toward people, hypnotizing them with his eyes (known as the Shin no Ippou or "One Side of the Soul"). It can also be used to strengthen himself. Kurogasa is obsessed with defeating the famous Hitokiri Battousai (Himura Kenshin) when he meets him during Kurogasa`s attempted assassination of Tani Juusanrou, a government official. He leaves, stating that if Kenshin cannot fight him to his fullest potential, he does not want to fight him at all. Kurogasa kidnaps Kamiya Kaoru the next day, in an effort to force Kenshin to once again become a hitokiri. Kenshin follows Kurogasa`s trail to the forest, where the two duel once again. Despite Kaoru`s life being in danger, Kenshin still does not fight with the intent to kill, and Kurogasa overwhelms him. Not wanting to settle for Kenshin holding back Kurogasa paralyzes Kaoru`s lungs using his Shin no Ippou, therefore making her unable to breathe. The two resume the battle, and Kenshin becomes angry enough to turn into Hitokiri Battousai as Kurogasa looks on gleefully. Kenshin hits Kurogasa`s right arm with the sheath of his sword, crushing Kurogasa`s elbow and severing Kurogasa`s ligaments; therefore Kurogasa can no longer wield a sword with his right arm. Kenshin is about to kill Kurogasa when Kaoru breaks Kurogasa`s spell with her will; she yells "No!," releasing Kenshin from the Battousai spell. Kenshin then frees Kaoru, while Kurogasa picks up his wakizashi with his left hand, and stabs himself in the heart. Jin`e mortally wounded himself so the police would not discover the fact that Shibumi employed him.</description>
<picture>24379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6628" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="36">8.34</rating>
<name>Seta Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seta Soujirou is a teenage boy who is Shishio`s right-hand man. He is noted in the series for always smiling, and apparently displaying no emotions in battle.</description>
<picture>24381.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6629" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="27">4.02</rating>
<name>Komagata Yumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komagata Yumi is an oiran, a courtesan in Yoshiwara, formerly an akasen. Because of that, she is beautiful, intelligent, dignified, well-cultured, and was brought up in a comfortable life. She was always interested in social issues and occurrences in Japan, and became reviled at the Japanese government`s stance regarding prostitutes. She came to love Shishio Makoto with an utmost passion, which he returned. Thus, she joined Shishio`s conspiracy to bring down the Meiji government. She is constantly concerned about Shishio`s medical state.
Yumi dies trying to protect Shishio when his body becomes overheated in his fight with Kenshin. After she hurls herself in between Kenshin and Shishio and convinces the former to spare the latter, Shishio runs her through with his sword, mortally injuring her in the process and wounding Kenshin as well. Knowing that she has finally been of use to Shishio in his most important battle, she dies happy and released of her former frustration for not being able to fight next to him. She appears with Shishio and Houji in hell.
Watsuki originally designed Yumi to be a "sexy" accessory for Shishio, as the Rurouni Kenshin author figured that a villain should have a "temptress" around him; Watsuki had not intended to develop Yumi into a character motivated by love. Watsuki had no particular personality model for Yumi. Yumi is a version of Ogin, a character played by the actress Kaoru Yumi in Mitokoumon Gaiden: Kagerou Ninpou-Chou, a spinoff series of Mitokoumon. Watsuki had no specific design model; he designed Yumi "on the spot" with the intention of her to "be sexy." Halfway through the development of Yumi throughout the story, Watsuki became a fan of Morrigan Aensland from Darkstalkers (Vampire Hunter) and as a result Watsuki began to expose more of Yumi`s cleavage and shoulders, "eventually increasing the sexiness by about 120%."
In the end Watsuki intended for Yumi to find happiness in following Shishio everywhere; Yumi`s motivation for sacrificing herself is not receiving death, but being with Shishio. Watsuki said that the concept of Yumi going with Shishio to hell "struck" him. Watsuki reported that he received response letters for Yumi`s sacrifice, including some praising the development and others criticizing it. Watsuki stated that some people who tried to cosplay as Yumi found difficulty in "keeping the top up."
Watsuki stated that drawing Yumi taught him that he could have fun with drawing female characters not just by making them appear "cute," but also making them "seductive, or even evil." Watsuki added that, since Yumi had a "sexed-up body," botching "even one line" could make the character appear "downright indecent." Watsuki stated that Yumi taught him the importance of "skillful sketching."</description>
<picture>24382.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6630" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="5">6.64</rating>
<name>Sadojima Houji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sadojima Houji is Shishio`s second in command. He used to be an official in the Meiji government but lost faith in it when he saw no one in the government worthy of controlling the country. He abandoned his position in the government and eventually met Shishio. Houji, too, envisions Japan as a mighty power led by Shishio, ruling with the principles of basic animal survival. Houji is indeed unique; although he is not proficient in any fighting style, he is a cunning organizer and possesses frightening leadership qualities. His skills as a staff officer figure are quite amazing; he even manages to purchase Rengoku—the gigantic ship—on the black market. Houji`s plan with the Rengoku fails when Kenshin, Sanosuke, and Saitou arrive at the dock and Tsukioka Tsunan`s bombs, which Sanosuke carries, blow a hole into the ship, causing it to sink; since Houji did not have any members of the Ten Swords accompany the ship, Kenshin and his allies were able to destroy the ship. Houji was `baptized` by Shishio`s intense body heat to kindle in him a belief in hell.
Houji strongly believes in Shishio`s strength as he throws away a gun he had hidden after learning of Shishio`s fifteen minute limit. He is in utter disbelief when Shishio is finally defeated by Kenshin and then attempts to destroy the complex in which the fight took place so that if Kenshin died, there would be no victor; thus Shishio would never have been beaten. As the complex collapses, Houji was saved by Anji and Soujirou. Anji convinces Houji to surrender himself to the police, and Houji agreed with the intent of using the criminal courts to project Shishio`s ideals and plans. At the end of the Shishio arc, it was revealed that Houji committed suicide in prison after government officials decided that his voice was too dangerous and refused to grant him a trial. After slitting his throat, he wrote a message on the wall with his own blood: "This world is dead to me now. I go to follow my master to hell." The message was directed at the Meiji government to convey Houji`s disgust with the regime and his loyalty to Shishio. He is last shown in Hell with Shishio and Yumi, vowing to follow Shishio when he declares that he will conquer Hell.
Watsuki stated that much of the overall concept for Houji originates from a character from X-Men whose name sounds similar to Houji`s name; Watsuki said that the X-Men character gave him a "hint" for the story and that Houji`s personality does "not so much" originate from the X-Men character. The X-Men character did not directly fight but instead invents machines to help his team members, so Watsuki wanted a character who held a support role in the Ten Swords. At first Houji was an individual who was often surprised, but Watsuki decided that was would "get awfully dull." Watsuki that when he decided to make Houji Shishio`s second in command, then the character concept "struck chords in my heart." Watsuki stated that Houji`s character design is "100% original" to him and that the design is one which Watsuki is the most confident in; Watsuki reported that several people believed that the design originated from Giant Robo. Watsuki added that the one aspect he did not like about Houji is the costume; Watsuki wanted to make it more "European style authentic" to the time period, but he could not find sufficient resources to make the costume in this manner. Watsuki said that Houji becomes "a pretty cool guy" at the end of the Shishio arc.</description>
<picture>24383.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6631" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="74">8.21</rating>
<name>Shinomori Aoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinomori Aoshi, the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch20161 [Oniwabanshuu], is a skilled swordsman who is highly respected by his comrades. His goal for much of the series is to claim the title of "the strongest" for the pride of the Oniwabanshuu.</description>
<picture>84397.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6632" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Raikouji Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3420" picture="228543.jpg">Fujita Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20109" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-07-28">
<rating votes="13">6.35</rating>
<name>Oguni Gensai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oguni Gensai is the doctor who takes Megumi as his apprentice. In the anime he has two grandchildren, Ayame and Suzume.</description>
<picture>52090.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20113" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">6.24</rating>
<name>Sekihara Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sekihara Tae is the 20-something manager of the beef hot pot (gyuunabe, or sukiyaki) restaurant, the Akabeko. She has a twin sister named Sae managing in a similar restaurant called the Shirobeko in Kyoto. Sagara Sanosuke also owes her a seemingly large sum of money in which interest is accounted for. In the anime, and a bit in the manga, she has also tried to push the relationship between Himura Kenshin and Kamiya Kaoru since it seemed it to her that it was not working.
Watsuki originally created Tae as a plot convience in the Zanza story arc and he intended for Kaoru to patronize a restaurant operated by "a good friend"; the author said he used "no thought" while creating Tae, including a lack of planning in her character design. Tae`s personality originates from Kamiya Megumi in Watsuki`s first "Rurouni" story. As the story progressed Watsuki found himself adding additional details about Tae, such as her family name, her status as the daughter of the owner of Akabeko, and her collecting of Nishiki paintings. Watsuki said that Tae was his first character to evolve in the manner that she did. Watsuki did not give Tae lipstick so she would be easily distinguished against Megumi. Her character design originates from a rejected model for Kenshin with a prototype Kenshin hairstyle colored black and a "softer, female" face. Watsuki originally intended for Tae to have a Kansai dialect and had an assistant from the Kansai region to vet the dialog, but Watsuki ultimately rejected the idea after he felt the concept was becoming too strange.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>52168.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20118" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">6.35</rating>
<name>Keisatsu Shochou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A local police chief, Chief Muraki is a good friend of Kenshin`s and often informs him of local disturbances. During the Jinchuu arc, Uramura`s residence is attacked along with the Maekawa dojo and the Akabeko as part of Yukishiro Enishi`s plan to strike at the places in Tokyo most important to Kenshin; fortunately Uramura and his family are saved by Kenshin. As a favour to Kenshin, he deliberately points the police in the wrong direction when they attempt to arrest Sanosuke toward the end of the manga. He was not given a name until the Jinchuu arc in the manga.</description>
<picture>52196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3253" picture="24232.jpg">Kameyama Sukekiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20484" type="appears in" update="2010-08-07">
<name>Akabeko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A beef hot pot restaurant</description>
<picture>52867.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20701" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<name>Kawaji Toshiyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawaji Toshiyoshi is a government official who assists Ookubo.</description>
<picture>53233.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20702" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="2">6.28</rating>
<name>Ookubo Toshimichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In history, Ookubo Toshimichi (大久保 利通) (1830-1878) was one of the five Ishin Shishi - Men of Spirit and the last of the three to have the highest honors in the government. He outlived Katsura Kogorou and Saigou Takamori. He was a leader of the Satsuma clan, who supported the restoration of imperial power. He was responsible for the suppression of the Satsuma rebellion in 1877, led by Ookubo`s university friend, Saigou Takamori. In Rurouni Kenshin, Ookubo appears to Kenshin for help in the Shishio Makoto crisis. In real life, Ookubo was murdered by six discontented clansmen on his way to Tokyo on May 14, 1878. In the Rurouni Kenshin series, Seta Soujirou murders him and the clansmen take responsibility.
Watsuki feels that many Japanese people have bias towards Saigou and that Ookubo was "sly" and "cunning." Watsuki expressed disappointment in this and instead stated that while Ookubo was a strategist during the Bakumatsu, Ookubo was ethical during the Meiji era and did not try to enrich himself while other politicians conspired with the wealthy to make money. To support his point, after Ookubo died he had few assets and many debts; many of his debts were due to his covering government shortfalls. Watsuki felt that Ookubo, who had been demonized during his time period, needed more appreciation from the population. In the design Watsuki tried to use portrait photographs, but he could not find any. He tried using a statue as a model, but Watsuki believes that the final character does not look at all similar to the statue. In retrospect he believed that the character resembles President of the United States Abraham Lincoln, another historical figure that Watsuki had respect for. He commented "that must have found its way in there, somehow..."</description>
<picture>53239.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20774" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-08-14">
<name>Arai Shakku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arai Shakkuu was the swordsmith who made Kenshin`s sword, since Kenshin hopes to get a replacement for his broken sakabatou.</description>
<picture>53370.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2310" update="2012-04-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2001-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">るろうに剣心 - 星霜編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After So Many Years Have Passed - Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rurouni Kenshin - Seisouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2311" update="2005-01-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2001-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">るろうに剣心 - 星霜編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After So Many Years Have Passed - Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rurouni Kenshin - Seisouhen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
