<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1950" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2005-01-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nanami-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">نانامي - شان</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Nanami-chan 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ななみちゃん</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3319" type="Sequel">Nanami-chan 2nd Series</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/nanami/anime/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1050" type="Unknown Relation">NHK</name>
<name id="1263" type="Work">Robot</name>
<name id="6814" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oohashi Sachiko</name>
<name id="9100" type="Music">Kuricorder Quartet</name>
<name id="15407" type="Character Design">Inaba Takuya</name>
<name id="19735" type="Direction">Nomura Tatsutoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>A girl, Michi, and her family move to live in a very particular tree house called Happiness House. Even though her mother is less than enthusiastic, Michi loves their new cottage, peacefully resting on a huge tree branch, next to many other unusual houses. High up in the tree, Michi, discovers her room in the attic, where a curious, acorn-shaped creature named Nanami greets her. And so Michi`s life on this wondrous tree begins...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="133">3.53</permanent>
<temporary count="134">5.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>168263.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4132</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3845</identifier>
<identifier>wszrjx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/nanami/anime/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nanami-chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ななみちゃん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7196</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2419" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-17">
<name>glutton</name>
<description>A character (who quite often is anything but fat) eats enough for an entire football team, usually devastating the whole table — and perhaps entire restaurants — with their insatiable hunger. Often combined with a speed-eating technique that makes food seem to vanish spontaneously from the plate.</description>
<picurl>239821.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5763" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>rock-paper-scissors</name>
<description>Whenever a decision has to be made in anime, the Japanese protagonists seem to be awfully fond of playing rock-paper-scissors (or jan-ken-pon) to determine the outcome.</description>
<picurl>62869.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5840" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>birthday</name>
<description>All about the birthday celebration of at least one of the protagonists in this anime.
This includes a birthday party with a birthday cake and other food and presents — lots of them.</description>
<picurl>161031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="19434" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議な木の実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mysterious Acorn</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Tajemniczy żołądź</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19804" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">しあわせ荘の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret of the Happiness House</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Tajemnica Szczęśliwego Domu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase-sou no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20161" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ななみの家出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ucieczka Nanami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20509" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハロー, エッフェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hello Eiffel</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Cześć, Eiffel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21305" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プールの女王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pool Queen</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Królowa basenu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21306" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ママのサボテン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mom`s Cactus</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kaktus mamy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22310" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shoot!</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Strzał!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22448" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rainy Day</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Deszczowy dzień</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22449" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">となりの宇宙人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Alien Next Door</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Obcy z sąsiedztwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22814" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕焼け音楽会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunset Music Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Festiwal o zachodzie słońca</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22815" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2004-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の空き部屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Vacant Room</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Tajemniczy pusty pokój</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22816" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2005-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知の誕生日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Michi`s Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Urodziny Michi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
