<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="202" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-07-19</startdate>
<enddate>1997-07-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shinseiki Evangelion Gekijouban: Air / Magokoro o, Kimi ni</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Neon Genesis Evangelion: End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Конец Евангелиона</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Evangelion`un Sonu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Кінець Євангеліона</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Evangelion movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">EoE</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">End of Eva</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新世紀エヴァンゲリオン劇場版 Air / まごころを, 君に</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion - The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion - The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">신세기 에반게리온 - 엔드 오브 에바</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Evangelion: The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อีวาเกเลี่ยน: ปัจฉิมภาค</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">The End of Evangelion</title>
<title xml:lang="gl" type="official">O final de Evangelion</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="22" type="Prequel">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="326" type="Prequel">Shinseiki Evangelion Gekijouban: Shi to Shinsei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12986" approval="9" total="17">Devilman: Crybaby</anime>
<anime id="8778" approval="2" total="17">Gekijouban Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
<anime id="431" approval="1" total="4">Koroshiya-1 The Animation Episode 0</anime>
<anime id="256" approval="1" total="4">Shoujo Kakumei Utena: Adolescence Mokushiroku</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="19">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="67016">ถึงดูแล้วไม่เข้าใจก็เถอะ</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="241883">Highly recommended not for the conclusion but for the art too!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="252455">Amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="305286">You can`t not see this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="323986">no matter what they say, i love this ending!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="386693">This is totaly must see - the most mind fucking epic EPICNESS!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="57320">Great End of the Great Saga. Dead end or new beginning? Decease of all hopes or birth of the new one? In any case, this anime is really finished. No open endings, no unfinished storylines. Just eternal redness of sea waters, shining with white sand and starry sky, crossed with bloody strake, retiring below the horizon...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="150612">Evangelion itself is a masterpiece and a must-see. Putting that aside, EoE marks the true, explosive conclusion that the series deserved. It is emotionally engaging from start to finish, and the animation is beautiful. The soundtrack is also unforgettable, with hauntingly beautiful songs like "Komm, süßer Tod" echoing in my mind years after first hearing it. This film should be considered essential viewing to truly complete the Evangelion plotline.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="57" type="Chief Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="718" type="Original Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="57" type="Chief Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="58" type="Direction">Tsurumaki Kazuya</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="57" type="Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="1389" type="Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="57" type="Original Work">Anno Hideaki</name>
</creators>
<description>Having prevented the Third Impact and thus saving the planet, http://anidb.net/ch5009 [NERV] unexpectedly finds itself under attack. Conscious of http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Gendou]`s betrayal, http://anidb.net/ch7187 [SEELE] launches a massive attack on Tokyo-3 in order to conclude the Human Instrumentality Project at any cost. NERV must now fight its most fearsome opponent: mankind itself.
Source: ANN
Note: The end of the http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] left many questions as to the fate of NERV, the Children, the Angels, and many other plot factors unanswered, unexplained, or otherwise hanging. To answer a legion of now befuddled Evangelion fans, Gainax remade the ending into a two-part movie known as http://anidb.net/a202 [Death and Rebirth] which was to supersede episodes 25 and 26 of the television series. Ultimately, Rebirth became only the first half of the first episode of The End of Evangelion, with some minor differences. The End of Evangelion picks up where Rebirth left off.
Revival of Evangelion is considered the final form of the Evangelion movies, which had been released in several forms prior to Revival. The Revival release includes Death(True)2 and The End of Evangelion.
Note: The 2003 Renewal of Evangelion is the final remastered version. It includes:

* http://anidb.net/a22 [The original TV series], episodes 1-20
* The Director`s Cut of episodes 21-24 of the original TV series
* http://anidb.net/a326 [Death(True)^2], released on the ninth disc with the label of Revival of Evangelion
* http://anidb.net/a202 [The End of Evangelion], released on the tenth disc, with the label Evangelion – The Feature Film
</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9497">7.83</permanent>
<temporary count="9578">8.12</temporary>
<review count="12">6.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133474.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>419</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1055</identifier>
<identifier>jqwqwc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_End_of_Evangelion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新世紀エヴァンゲリオン劇場版_Air/まごころを、君に</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>472</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>153289</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新世紀福音戰士劇場版</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4555" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>man the hell up!</name>
<description>There is a male character in this anime that is overall not very manly. Most of the time he starts off as your typical high school student. In time there are, through major changes in his life, several more characteristics added to his personality. Usually these add up to be extremely pathetic and the character becomes quite annoying. This goes along with the viewers wish for him to get over it and do something about it. Hence, he should "Man the hell up!".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5872" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>bad luck</name>
<description>You are living a blessed life far from any troubles. Your sister is a famous reporter, you have a good looking girlfriend and you excel in your studies aiming to be a scientist. Your future is looking bright. But reality is, fate hates you. Your sister is killed, your girlfriend breaks up with you after being crippled in a terrorist attack and finally you end up as a pizza delivery boy.
And just when you thought it can`t get worse, it does. Your former girlfriend turns into a Darth Vader knock-off, tries to impose her world view on others by force and is out there to kill you. Yes, your life does truly suck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5996" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>tragic ending</name>
<description>Up to the very end of the anime the viewer will hope that the story will end well and that the characters will in some way be able to solve the problems.
Not so. The sense of foreboding doom could not be averted. The social or personal calamity strikes mercilessly.
Examples: The catastrophic meteor strike does hit Earth after all. The long sick loved one cannot be saved. After overcoming all obstacles a random cruel event ends the life of the protagonist. A almost forgotten tragedy in the past has repercussions in the present.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6849" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-19">
<name>organism cloning</name>
<description>Organism cloning, also called reproductive cloning, is the creation of an organism that is genetically identical to another. While this is a natural phenomenon in many species, this tag is specifically about artificial organism cloning, as in Dolly the sheep. Cloning of multicellular organisms, and especially of human beings, remains both a scientific frontier and a highly controversial subject, especially in regards to its ethics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="39" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="1229">7.84</rating>
<name>Souryuu Asuka Langley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka is only one quarter Japanese, which accounts for her Japanese name but European appearance. Asuka is a native of Germany, having been raised there, though her nationality is technically American. Asuka`s native language is German, and in both the series and the manga she tends to curse in German. She is a child prodigy and has earned a university degree in an unspecified field as a teenager; she also speaks fluent Japanese, but has trouble reading and writing kanji. She is characterized by her fiery red hair and equally fiery temper. Asuka is very proud of being an Eva pilot, and near-constantly wears her A10 nerve clips in her hair, because she wants everyone around her to know that she is a pilot.</description>
<picture>14311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="309" type="main character in" update="2018-02-15">
<rating votes="1351">4.12</rating>
<name>Ikari Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikari Shinji is the "Third Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6997 [EVA-01]. He is the son of http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou] and the late http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui]. Abandoned by his father when he was a toddler, Shinji has grown up to be reclusive and withdrawn, often choosing to run away from difficult situations. He is reunited with his father when he is summoned to pilot EVA-01, and because of this meets his future caretaker http://anidb.net/ch5007 [Katsuragi Misato] and the mysterious pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00], http://anidb.net/ch310 [Ayanami Rei].
Over time and with encouragement from Misato, Rei and his classmates http://anidb.net/ch7981 [Suzuhara Touji] and http://anidb.net/ch8643 [Aida Kensuke], he learns to be more confident and appreciative of others. Shinji is put to task fighting the invading Angels, and later meets a foreign pilot whom he often comes in conflict with, http://anidb.net/ch39 [Souryuu Asuka Langley].</description>
<picture>128273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="310" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="1632">8.13</rating>
<name>Ayanami Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayanami Rei is the "First Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00]. Shrouded in mystery, she is socially withdrawn and rarely shows emotion. Seemingly completely devoted to her duty as an EVA pilot, her only apparent human relationship being with http://anidb.net/ch5009 [Nerv] commander http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou].
Rei comes to know http://anidb.net/ch309 [Ikari Shinji], and after some initial mistrust they come to better understand each other, revealing more of Rei`s emotional side and helping Shinji trust others again.
Rei`s body was created at Nerv in an attempt to bring back Gendou`s wife http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui], who was stuck inside http://anidb.net/ch8704 [EVA-01]. Soulless clones of her are kept hidden in the deepest levels of NERV, to be used both as replacement bodies for Rei should she die and as "cores" of the Dummy Plugs. Gendou, plans to make Rei help him control Instrumentality to reunite him with his wife.</description>
<picture>59479.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5000" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-14">
<rating votes="399">5.36</rating>
<name>Ikari Gendou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At Nerv, Gendo is responsible for the research done on the Evas and the Human Instrumentality Project. He is the father of the Third Child, Shinji Ikari. At the start of the series, he is the only person having an effective connection to Rei Ayanami.
Gendo is a brilliant scientist and politician (the master of puppets in the series) who works diligently for his organization; however, he is an extremely cold and distant father towards his son, and has no qualms about using and discarding people to achieve his goals.</description>
<picture>21249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5007" type="main character in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="790">7.53</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The operations director at Nerv. Her duties at Nerv include acting as a field commander for the Eva pilots, issuing orders and relaying battle strategies as well as processing input from Akagi Ritsuko and the technicians monitoring the Evas. She also handles many bureaucratic aspects of Nerv`s operations.
At the beginning of the series, Misato first brings Shinji Ikari to Nerv and is able to convince him to pilot the Eva Unit 01. She then chooses to have Shinji move in with her rather than live alone, and later takes in Sohryu Asuka Langley. As the series progresses, through her former lover Kaji Ryouji she learns the truth behind the Human Instrumentality Project and the depths of deception that Nerv and Seele have gone to keep the Project secret, even from her.
While on the job, Misato is very professional and capable, in stark contrast to her life at home. Until Shinji`s arrival, her living space was a complete mess. She cannot cook for herself and relies solely on instant food (she is often considered gross by Shinji and Ritsuko for combining food like ramen and curry). She also drinks copious quantities of beer, and drinks one first thing in the morning to get her day started (later in the series she apparently switches to canned coffee as a supplement). She also smokes, though only occasionally and only during chaotic events.</description>
<picture>21277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5008" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="176">4.61</rating>
<name>Akagi Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nerv`s head scientist and heavily involved in the repairs and maintenance of Tokyo-3`s defences against the Angels, particularly the Evas.
She is the daughter of Akagi Naoko, the developer of the MAGI supercomputer system which controls Nerv. In many ways, Ritsuko is living in the shadow of her mother, whom she both admires and despises. Naoko was the head scientist working on the Evangelion project before her death, and Ritsuko is continuing the work her mother began with the Evas, as well as continuing the development of the Magi supercomputer system. Flashbacks to a teenaged Ritsuko reveal that she is a natural brunette, just like her mother.
Ritsuko is extremely intelligent, with a strong dedication to her work and a stoic, detached attitude which is frequently contrasted against Katsuragi Misato`s hot-headness, especially during Eva combat. Her occasional jibes at Misato are a source of comic relief in the series. She has a great affinity for cats, and Misato chides her at one point for substituting her cats for human affection. She also is a heavy smoker, as evidenced by an ashtray on her desk filled with cigarette butts stained by her lipstick.</description>
<picture>21278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5009" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="35">8.13</rating>
<name>Nerv</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organisation led by Ikari Gendou and tasked with defending Earth against the Angels through use of the Evangelion units. It was formerly known as Gehirn, a UN Research Agency. It was reorganised into Nerv once Nerv HQ and Tokyo-3 became fully operational. There are several global branches of Nerv besides the main headquarters under Tokyo-3 itself.
The Nerv Logo is half a fig leaf covering its name, with the motto "God`s In His Heaven... All`s Right With The World" forming the quarter circle on the bottom. The motto comes from Robert Browning`s poem "Pippa Passes."
In Genesis 3:7, Adam and Eve cover their "nakedness" with fig leaves. The fig leaf has covered nakedness in art and sculpture for hundreds of years, symbolically representing the guilt of original sin.</description>
<picture>21279.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6995" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="107">4.08</rating>
<name>Ibuki Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A First Lieutenant at Nerv and a computer technician who works primarily with Akagi Ritsuko. Her main role during the battles against the Angels is to constantly monitor the Eva pilots` synchronization ratios and send various emergency commands to the Evas as ordered by Misato or Gendou. In spite of her profession, Maya despises violence of any sort, and is frequently shown becoming nauseated and averting her eyes during battles with the Angels.</description>
<picture>25248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6998" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="26">7.39</rating>
<name>EVA-02</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Evangelion Unit 02, built by Nerv Germany, is the first Production Model Eva. It is piloted by Souryuu Asuka Langley and is the first Evangelion built specifically for combat. The Eva`s armour is primarily red with yellow and white on the arms and head. The head armour has two movable sections, one covering both the jaw and lower eyes and the other above the upper pair of eyes. These plates are hinged and can shift, displaying the Eva`s eyes underneath. This is first seen underwater during the fight with Gaghiel. As a result of being constructed by Nerv Germany, and also as an accommodation for its three-quarters-German pilot, its default language setting is German. Unit 02 features a different progressive knife from earlier Eva units as well as an internal weapon rack in the right shoulder binder which fires dartlike weapons.
Unlike Unit 01, it only goes truly "berserk" once, just before its destruction. It has achieved an unusually high sync ratio with its pilot(s), on two other occasions: once in combat against the 6th angel Gaghiel, and once under the influence of the 17th Angel. It is known to contain the maternal part of the soul of Asuka`s mother.
Unit 02 has blue blood, which is first seen when the fourteenth Angel, Zeruel, cuts off its arms. It has brown skin and four orange eyes, first seen when the MP Evas tear it apart.</description>
<picture>30415.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7000" type="appears in" update="2009-07-07">
<rating votes="14">7.24</rating>
<name>Lilith</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second Angel is Lilith (Though technically also the first human, due to the GeoFront in which Lilith resides is supposed to be the birthplace of all humans, and the GeoFront where Adam was located is the birthplace all Angels.). Lilith initially appears as a white, legless giant, whose face is covered with a mask displaying the logo of Seele. Numerous human-like legs protrude from its legless stumps. The Angel is crucified on a giant cross-like restraint in Terminal Dogma, the deepest level of Nerv headquarters. Lilith`s torso constantly leaks LCL from an unseen wound, forming a lake of LCL at the base of its restraint which is tapped to fill the Evas` entry plugs.
In First Impact, Lilith usurped Adam as the progenitor of life on Earth. All life on Earth is supposedly descended from this Angel, although it is never specified if this is in a biological sense or a metaphysical sense. Lilith`s descendants possess the "Fruit of Wisdom," the source of human science and technology. The "Deleted Scenes" from episode 23 also reveal that Unit 01 is artificially derived from Lilith.
Lilith was discovered in the Black Moon, underneath Japan. The Black Moon was converted into the GeoFront, and the site of Lilith`s body became Terminal Dogma. It is never stated whether Lilith was already crucified when it was found, or whether it was later crucified. At some point after Ikari Yui`s contact experiment with Unit 01, Lilith`s soul was placed into Ayanami Rei. Later, once it was retrieved, the Lance of Longinus was used to impale the Angel. When Kaji revealed Lilith to Katsuragi Misato, both assumed it was Adam. Tabris later properly identified it as Lilith. The series does not explicitly reveal Lilith`s exact role in the plans for Instrumentality.
In The End of Evangelion, Ikari Gendou tried to initiate his version of Instrumentality by pushing his right hand (to which had been grafted the embryonic body of the Angel Adam) into Rei`s body. Rei, however, absorbed Adam (along with most of Gendou`s arm) into herself, rejected Gendou`s control of her, and merged with Lilith on her own. Though Rei merged with Lilith, she took Lilith into the form of Rei for most of The End of Evangelion. The merged Rei/Lilith freed itself from its bonds and transformed into a colossal winged version of Rei. It then generated an anti-AT field which covered the entire planet, nullifying the AT fields of every human and reverting humanity back into the primordial soup. Rei/Lilith died when Shinji rejected Instrumentality.</description>
<picture>28066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7187" type="appears in" update="2009-07-07">
<rating votes="21">5.06</rating>
<name>Seele</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Nerv and Gehirn`s secret backers, who wish to implement the Human Instrumentality Project, and arguably the "true villains" of the series. It consists of at least twelve prominent people; five of them form the Instrumentality Committee, which directly oversees Nerv`s progress, officially in the name of the UN. Its members are referred to as the "Old Men."
Seele is a secret organisation, the real puppetmasters behind the United Nations. Its origins are shrouded in mystery; they would claim to have existed since ancient times, functioning as an Illuminati-like power cabal over most of the world`s governments. This cannot be verified, but they have been operating since at least soon after World War II, when they acquired the secret sections of the Dead Sea Scrolls. The secret Dead Sea Scrolls predicted the arrival of the Angels and of Third Impact, and Seele began striving to develop means to defeat the Angels so that a human-centred Instrumentality process would proceed. Having decided that humanity as a whole had reached an evolutionary dead end, Seele seeks to bring about Instrumentality and unite all humans into one hyper-being, the next stage of existence.
In German "Seele" means "soul".</description>
<picture>1122.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7960" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="317">6.59</rating>
<name>Nagisa Kaworu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tabris, the seventeenth and final Angel, holds the form of a human, Kaworu Nagisa. Like the other Angels, he is "born of Adam", although it is implied that he was created by Seele. He contains the soul of Adam, similar to how Rei contains the soul of Lilith. Tabris` AT field is the most powerful ever detected, strong enough to block out "light, magnetism, sub-atomic particles, everything". He may control any Evangelion unit he wishes, even from outside the entry plug, so long as the soul inhabiting the Eva is dormant. Within the entry plug, he can set his synchronization ratio at any level he wishes. The nature or even the very existence of his core is not revealed.
Tabris, as Kaworu, infiltrated Nerv under the pretense of being sent to replace Asuka as Unit 02`s pilot. During his stay in Tokyo-3, he formed an extremely close relationship with Shinji. Kaworu later revealed himself as an Angel, seizing control of Unit 02 and descending with it towards Terminal Dogma. Shinji, in Unit 01, was sent to stop him, but was forced to battle Unit 02 while Tabris proceeded to Terminal Dogma. Tabris` AT field manifested during the battle, effectively cutting both of them off from all contact with anyone outside. After he reached Terminal Dogma, Tabris was surprised to discover that the Angel held there was not Adam, but Lilith. Shinji incapacitated Unit 02 and proceeded to try to stop the Angel. Tabris, gripped in Unit 01`s hand, stated his unwillingness to destroy mankind by causing Third Impact, and asked Shinji to kill him. Shinji, after a long period of hesitation, crushed the Angel in his Eva`s hand.</description>
<picture>128274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8642" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-12">
<rating votes="129">3.33</rating>
<name>Fuyutsuki Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nerv`s Deputy Commander and Ikari Gendou`s right hand man. He does not especially like Gendou, but he is the closest thing to a confidant that Gendou has in the series.
Once a professor of meta-biology at Kyoto University, Fuyutsuki became interested in the research and theories undertaken by Ikari Yui, and became her sponsor and mentor. Shortly thereafter, he was directed by his superiors to initiate a similar arrangement with Rokobungi Gendou.
Later, after the Second Impact, Fuyutsuki travelled with Gendou to the ruins of Antarctica, and began to suspect that Gendou and his associates in Seele were more powerful and dangerous than he originally realized. In 2003, Fuyutsuki discovered for himself the true nature of the events leading up to Second Impact and Seele`s involvement in initiating that catastrophe. Gendou led him into the GeoFront and Central Dogma, and asked Fuyutsuki to join him in "creating a new future for mankind."</description>
<picture>75303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8665" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="100">4.23</rating>
<name>Horaki Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Class representative of the class that Shinji and the other Eva pilots attend. She has a by-the-book demeanour and takes her responsibilities as "class rep" seriously. Although she frequently bickers with Touji, she reveals to Asuka that she has an enormous crush on Touji but is unable to openly express her feelings to him. She also appears to be Asuka`s only friend. Hikari is an accomplished cook who appears to take care of her two sisters.</description>
<picture>27961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8666" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="53">4.61</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A First Lieutenant at Nerv and one of the three main computer technicians directly serving under Commanders Ikari and Fuyutsuki in the command post of Central Dogma, the others being Aoba and Ibuki. Hyuga at first gives the impression of being something of a nerd, reading manga while on his break time, but is a highly skilled technician. His quick thinking and bravery help save Nerv headquarters from the attack by Matariel, and he acts as a spy for Misato, helping her obtain information regarding Nerv`s machinations.
The true extent of his feelings for Misato is shown in The End of Evangelion as Rei/Lilith takes the form of Misato during Instrumentality and passionately kisses him; his body reverts to LCL.</description>
<picture>75305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1925" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8667" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="58">4.05</rating>
<name>Aoba Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoba Shigeru is a First Lieutenant at Nerv and a computer technician. At times a stereotypical metalhead, he is a cynical nihilist and plays guitar (he can also sometimes be seen playing air guitar). Of the three technicians seen regularly in Central Dogma, his character is explored the least in the series.
In The End of Evangelion, during Instrumentality, Rei/Lillith appears to him not as any loved one but rather as a bombardment of Reis which forces their way through his AT Field while he cowers and screams in horror under his desk.</description>
<picture>75304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2394" update="2016-06-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>1997-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="33">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16184" update="2016-06-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1997-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="24">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16185" update="2014-04-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1997-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="23">2.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35812" update="2014-01-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版 #26実写パート (特別ラッシュ編集版)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijouban #26 documentational part (special raw material version)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijouban #26 Jissha Part (Tokubetsu Rush Henshuu Ban)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
