<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2041" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1982-03-03</startdate>
<enddate>1983-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kikou Kantai Dairugger XV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Voltron (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Vehicle Voltron</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Vehicle Force Voltron</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Armored Squadron Dairugger XV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機甲艦隊ダイラガーXV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Armored Fleet Dairugger XV</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Voltron (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Voltron</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="117027">Maybe I`m talking in favor of this series because is the one I watched as kid. But this one has a good enough story for a mecha series in space with a massive mecha with lots of vehicles that join together to form it. The story is deeper than in GoLion because it isn`t limited to a battle between two planets and for the sake of one kingdom but about survival of races and where as expected in anime the bad guys aren`t so bad, things that were lacking in GoLion the one is often compáred to because the Voltron franchise.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="5528" type="Character Design">Kiyoyama Shigetaka</name>
<name id="4537" type="Series Composition">Fujikawa Keisuke</name>
<name id="4404" type="Chief Direction">Morishita Kouzou</name>
<name id="4339" type="Chief Designer">Mukuo Takamura</name>
<name id="4283" type="Chief Designer">Kubota Tadao</name>
<name id="990" type="Work">Toei Agency</name>
<name id="1009" type="Work">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
<name id="6526" type="Original Work">Yatsude Saburou</name>
<name id="4295" type="Music">Yokoyama Seiji</name>
</creators>
<description>Dairugger XV is an exploration robot, as well as an intended peace-keeping force. The Earth is in a time of prosperity. The president of the Terran League launches a mission to explore beyond the galaxy. After commencing its mission of exploration, the starship Rugger-Guard is attacked by a ship of the Galbeston Empire. Dairugger, the super robot, is deployed in order to defend the Earth. It is somewhat by fate that they must help the people of Galbeston find a new planet before it explodes, and liberate it from its despotic Emperor.
Note: Part of the United States series, Voltron: Defender of the Universe.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="104">4.82</permanent>
<temporary count="105">6.21</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>128049.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1123</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3609</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2001</identifier>
<identifier>ifsfmj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Armored_Fleet_Dairugger_XV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機甲艦隊ダイラガーXV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89350</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1982/dairager</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5638" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-25">
<name>military is useless</name>
<description>The regular military force per se or certain units thereof are way out of their league when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes (e.g. powerful aliens). Thus the regular military is completely useless. 
Often, only children (of all people) with special abilities and/or powered suits can defend Earth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="20314" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陸奥よ立ち直れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letters From Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mutsu yo Tachinaore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20315" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙要塞攻略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save the Space Station</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Yousai Kouryaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20316" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばアキレウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Building a New World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Achilles</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20317" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第10番惑星突破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Running Out</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 10-ban Wakusei Toppa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20318" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">二連星の亡霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Fleet From Another Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nirensei no Bourei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20319" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">必死の海中合体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Peace - A Fish Story!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hisshi no Kaichuu Gattai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20320" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">危機迫る可住惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whose World Is It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiki Semaru Kajuu Wakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20321" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">前線基地撃破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man-Made Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zensen Kichi Gekiha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20322" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女隊長エンマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This World`s for the Birds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Taichou Emma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20323" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河の夜明け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of Hazar`s World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga no Yoake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20324" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独な守備隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Day on a New World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku na Shubitai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20325" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">テレス司令失脚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nerok Scores Big</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teles Shirei Shikkyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20326" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄への救助命令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, New World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku e no Kyuujo Meirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20327" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">光芒惑星の苦闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just Like Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koubou Wakusei no Kutou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20328" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑星Kの死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defend the New World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakusei K no Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20329" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新大陸惑星発見</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Solar System</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shintairiku Wakusei Hakken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20330" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対防衛圏進入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zero Hour Approaches</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Boueiken Shinnyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20331" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙砦の反乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolt of the Slaves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Toride no Hanran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20332" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガルベストン攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Drules` World Cracks Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Galveston Koubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20333" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">実験惑星の攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Try This World for Size</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikken Wakusei no Koubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20334" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エルドラの悲願</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet of the Amazons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eldora no Higan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20335" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新連合艦隊来援</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captain Newley Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Rengoukantai Raien</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20336" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デノン少年と大鹿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Moon Rises Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denon Shounen to Oojika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20337" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第3惑星を守れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coconuts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 3 Wakusei o Mamore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20338" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃える空洞惑星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hazar Bucks the Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeru Kuudou Wakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20339" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">安芸チーム捕まる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frozen Assets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aki Team Tsukamaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20340" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">救援艦隊全滅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Help Not Wanted</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuuen Kantai Zenmetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20341" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">一触即発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What`s on First</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isshokusokuhatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20342" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い月が昇る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Great Stone Space Faces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Tsuki ga Noboru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20343" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">姿なき超兵器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Color Me Invisible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugatanaki Chouheiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20344" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突する銀河</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Search of New Worlds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu Suru Ginga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20345" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑星K奪還作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hazar on the Carpet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakusei K Dakkan Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20346" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">心のなかの敵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet Stop For Repairs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Naka no Teki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20347" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">立て, 銀河警備軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meanwhile Back at Galaxy Garrison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tate, Ginga Keibigun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20348" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラガーマンの涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s the Old Ball Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ruggerman no Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20349" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">栄光の決死隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Very Short Vacation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikou no Kesshitai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20350" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴動·ガルベストン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hazar Is Demoted</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boudou Galveston</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20351" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二つの反逆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s on First</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Hangyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20352" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球非常事態</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raid on Galaxy Garrison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Hijoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20353" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">テレスとアシモフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Anybody`s World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teles to Asimov</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20354" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄惑星の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Planet Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku Wakusei no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20355" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">反撃·地球艦隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Curious Comet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangeki Chikyuu Kantai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20356" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙会談決裂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Enemy Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Kaidan Ketsuretsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20357" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵司令部を探せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smashing the Meteor Barrier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki Shireibu o Sagase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20358" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の樹海伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolo`s Lost World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Jukai Densetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20359" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">探査基地陥落</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Could Be a Long War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tansa Kichi Kanraku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20360" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">つかの間の休戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Temporary Truce</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukanoma no Kyuusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20361" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙要塞奇襲さる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet of the Bats</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Yousai Kishuu Saru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20362" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">流星雨に散れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Storm of Meteors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuseiu ni Chire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20363" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたクウ·ラガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Moon People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Kuu Rugger</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20364" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下都市大激戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Drules Surrender</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Toshi Daigekisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20365" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アシモフ帰還命令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No, Who`s on Second</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asimov Kikan Meirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52232" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fleet of Doom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122492" update="2010-09-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1982-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122493" update="2010-09-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1982-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
