<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2047" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1976-03-20</startdate>
<enddate>1976-03-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">UFO Robo Grendizer Tai Great Mazinger</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">UFO Robo Grendizer vs. Great Mazinger</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">UFO Robo Grandizer vs. Great Mazinger</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">UFOロボ グレンダイザー対グレートマジンガー</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Goldorak contre Great Mazinger</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Mazinga contro Goldrake</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="956" type="Character">Great Mazinger</anime>
<anime id="962" type="Parent Story">UFO Robo Grendizer</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373531">Even if you just have a small amount of interest in retro animes or the many genres that Ufo Robo Grendizer really belong to, according to this fan. Legendary anime that is full packed with sci-fi adventure, action, aliens, mecha, mysterious heroes etc.

A classic must see anime example if you want to check out anime classics, when you still made everything by your own hands and no computers where available . Those clumsy and destructive device that never ever can come close to the masters that created genuine feelings through their own amazing minds, feelings of the heart and soul + draw directly onto the canvas</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="3962" type="Music">Kikuchi Shunsuke</name>
<name id="984" type="Original Work">Dynamic Planning</name>
<name id="5209" type="Music">Watanabe Chuumei</name>
</creators>
<description>This is the first movie where Grendizer appears on the big screen! And what a title to attract the audience. Who would`ve ever thought of seeing Grendizer fighting Great Mazinger. Well guess what? That title is misleading, because it wasn`t really a fight, otherwise Grendizer would rip Great Mazinger apart.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="116">4.23</permanent>
<temporary count="118">5.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>144471.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3609</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2395</identifier>
<identifier>kxxcqj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>UFO_Robot_Grendizer_tai_Great_Mazinger</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>UFOロボ_グレンダイザー対グレートマジンガー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2727</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>145423</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m067</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5122" type="main character in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="26">7.02</rating>
<name>Kabuto Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29444" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-02">
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<name>Makiba Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66960.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="20377" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63156" update="2006-09-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
