<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2064" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-06-30</startdate>
<enddate>2004-09-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tsuki wa Higashi ni Hi wa Nishi ni: Operation Sanctuary</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Moon is East, The Sun is West: Operation Sanctuary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hani Hani: Operation Sanctuary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hani hani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Hanihani</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">月は東に日は西に Operation Sanctuary</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">달은 동쪽으로 해는 서쪽으로 ~OperationSanctuary~</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2188" approval="4" total="4">W Wish</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.hanihani.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1741" type="Character Design">Nakano Norikatsu</name>
<name id="1298" type="Original Work">August</name>
<name id="1741" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakano Norikatsu</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
<name id="777" type="Animation Work">Radix</name>
<name id="6279" type="Series Composition">Tougou Mitsuhiro</name>
<name id="31058" type="Direction">Jinno Shousei</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a game by http://anidb.net/cr1298 [August Soft].
Since my parents were both killed by an accident, I, Kusumi Naoki, have living with my uncle in his house.
"Nano-kun, you`d better wake up, or you`ll be late for school"
The new school year starts today. My childhood friend, Honami, still comes by to wake me up, although I often complain that I`m too old for that...
Today, we`ll become sophomores of Hasumidai Gakuen High School. When we walk to school, my cousin Matsuri, who this year starts to go to the same school, passes me by: "Nakoki, I`ll be going first".
I think this normal life will continue forever...
However, when I try to take a nap on the roof, a girl falls on me. "...Yusuke?", she asks. This girl, a transfer student who becomes my classmate, seems to take me for another person.
Gradually, as time goes by, the normal days supposed to pass routinely begin to change.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="753">3.25</permanent>
<temporary count="759">6.24</temporary>
<review count="1">7.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>12218.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12881</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>648</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1409</identifier>
<identifier>omojho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hanihani.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tsuki_wa_Higashi_ni_Hi_wa_Nishi_ni:_Operation_Sanctuary#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>月は東に日は西に_〜Operation_Sanctuary〜#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>403</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321026</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>80</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11424" type="main character in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="3">6.93</rating>
<name>Fujieda Honami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoki`s childhood friend. A Family-oriented, reliable, sensitive and considerate type. She can also be unexpectedly stubborn. Member of the cooking club and enjoys making pastries (esp. candy). Her favourite food is white chocolate. Opinions from those around her: No.1 person to be married to.</description>
<picture>3081.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2253" picture="172548.jpg">Kanda Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11425" type="main character in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="3">6.93</rating>
<name>Amagasaki Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who has fallen from the sky. She`s optimistic, strong, and doesn`t easily get discouraged type. She also tends to jump into conclusions. Member of the Astronomy Club. Mikoto is from the future, 100 years later. Opinion from others: Lovely person.</description>
<picture>3080.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2008" picture="45124.jpg">Kusayanagi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11431" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-20">
<rating votes="3">6.93</rating>
<name>Shibugaki Matsuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoki`s cousin. She`s energetic, lucid, efficient and hates to lose type. She often jumps to conclusion. Her hobby is reading shoujo manga and her favourite food is Okonomiyaki (Hiroshima style). She`s part of the Canteen Management Committee (Cafeteria). Opinion from others: Cafeteria Idol</description>
<picture>3082.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2009" picture="45037.jpg">Kajita Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47325" type="main character in" update="2012-07-28">
<name>Kuzumi Naoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47326" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-28">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Nishina Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1623" picture="171605.jpg">Iwai Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47327" type="appears in" update="2012-07-28">
<name>Hirose Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47328" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-28">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Tachibana Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="461" picture="188441.jpg">Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47343" type="appears in" update="2012-07-28">
<name>Shibugaki Genzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47344" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-28">
<rating votes="2">6.33</rating>
<name>Akiyama Fumio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5816" picture="210569.jpg">Hatamiya Kanoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47345" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-28">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Nonohara Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1886" picture="21014.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47346" type="appears in" update="2012-07-28">
<name>Fukano Junichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47347" type="appears in" update="2012-07-28">
<name>Usami Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8524" picture="32957.jpg">Honma Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47348" type="appears in" update="2015-04-25">
<name>Amagasaki Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="20518" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空から舞い降りた少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl Who Flew Down from the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora Kara Maiorita Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21583" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽しい学園生活の予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensing a Fun School Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanoshii Gakuen Katsu no Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21963" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキ身体検査</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Exciting Physical</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki Karada Kensa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22431" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ, まるぴん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Marupin!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire, Marupin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22510" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハッピーバースデー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happy Birthday</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22652" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のバイシクル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Bicycle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Bicycle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22746" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラザー&amp; シスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother and Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Brother &amp; Sister</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22898" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night for each one of them</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23125" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Matsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23164" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一人の自分</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Myself</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Hitotsu no Jibun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23211" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時空を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Traveling through Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikuu o Koete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23212" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月は東に日は西に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon to the East Sun to the West</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki wa Higashi ni Hi wa Nishi ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23213" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東奔西走スクールライフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bustling Busy School Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhonseisou School Life</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136642" update="2012-01-26">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Operation Sanctuary</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12`: Operation Sanctuary</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136643" update="2012-01-26">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11`: Memories</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136644" update="2012-01-26">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢と現実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10`: Dreams &amp; Reality</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136645" update="2012-01-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロンリネス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9`: Loneliness</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136673" update="2012-01-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136674" update="2012-01-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136675" update="2012-01-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
