<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2091" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>43</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-12-02</startdate>
<enddate>1991-04-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Quest</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Dragon Quest 勇者アベル伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Dragon Quest: Yuusha Abel Densetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">DQ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DRAGON QUEST</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Warrior</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1105" type="Same Setting">Dragon Quest: Dai no Daibouken</anime>
<anime id="2095" type="Same Setting">Dragon Quest Retsuden: Roto no Monshou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4391" approval="2" total="3">Super Mario Brothers: Peach-hime Kyuushutsu Daisakusen!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.super-vision.co.jp/dvd/draque/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4557" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kanazawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="28055" type="Original Work">Bird Studio</name>
<name id="4557" type="Animation Character Design">Kanazawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2939" type="Series Composition">Yamada Takashi</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="1190" type="Original Work">Enix</name>
<name id="1962" type="Chief Direction">Yamada Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="148" type="Chief Direction">Rintarou</name>
<name id="7362" type="Music">Mickie Yoshino</name>
<name id="5311" type="Music">Sugiyama Kouichi</name>
<name id="5972" type="Original Work">Chunsoft</name>
<name id="48705" type="Original Plan">Horii Yuuji</name>
<name id="5313" type="Music">Kazz Toyama</name>
<name id="5084" type="Direction">Kanda Takeyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Dragon Quest is loosely based on Dragon Quest III. The names and some of the characters are familar, but the world map is smaller and a very different shape. The two main characters are Abel and Tialah. Tialah receives the legendary Red Stone from the Aliahan Village sage Master Yogi. Soon after, Tialah is kidnapped by the evil Baramos who wants to use the Red Stone to resurrect The Great Dragon and be granted eternal life. Abel swore to rescue Tialah and he is given the Blue Stone, which can only seal the Dragon once it has been released.
Source: http://www.dqshrine.com/ma/dq/</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="79">5.53</permanent>
<temporary count="83">6.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>197585.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2118</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>624</identifier>
<identifier>rorhly</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.super-vision.co.jp/dvd/draque/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Warrior:_Legend_of_the_Hero_Abel</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンクエスト_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89094</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>89183</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>960</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1536</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1989/dragonquest</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="39639" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリアハンの村 別離</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ariahan Village: Parting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ariahan no Mura: Betsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39640" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アベルを救え! 風の山の死闘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 27</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abel o Sukue! Kaze no Yama no Shitou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39641" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レーべの村 地図を探せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Liebe Village: Search for the Map</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Liebe no Mura: Chizu o Sagase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39642" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔王バラモスの弱点!!月食の夜の怪奇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lunar Eclipse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou Baramos no Jakuten!! Gesshoku no Yoru no Kaiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39643" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アベルよ急げ!! ティアラがすぐそこに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abel yo Isoge!! Tiala ga Sugu Soko ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39644" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜の鍵を奪え! 激突ナジミの塔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Najimi Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu no Kagi o Ubae! Gekitotsu Najimi no Tou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39645" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇のバザール 勇者の武器を探せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Bazaar: Yuusha no Buki o Sagase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39646" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルイーダの村 ガラムに突撃せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Luida no Mura: Garam ni Totsugeki Seyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39647" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざめよティアラ! 赤き珠の聖女として</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame yo Tiala! Akakitama no Seijo to Shite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39648" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大勇者アベルに栄光あれ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glory to the Great Hero Abel!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiyuusha Abel ni Eikou Are!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39649" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄!! 闇の帝王ゾーマの出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu! Yami no Teiou Zoma no Shutsugen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39650" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリアハンの城 旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ariahan Castle: Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ariahan no Shiro: Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39651" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠の果て 廃墟の街ドムドーラの怪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku no Hate: Haikyo no Machi Domdora no Kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39652" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1989-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女戦士 デイジィ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Female Warrior Daisy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Senshi: Daisy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39653" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜伝説を追って再び故郷アリアハンへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 30</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu Densetsu o Otte Futatabi Kokyou Ariahan e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39654" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正か邪か? いま甦る伝説の竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei ka Ja ka? Ima Yomigaeru Densetsu no Ryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39655" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる旅立ち 伝説の勇者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of Heroes: A New Start</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Tabidachi: Densetsu no Yuusha-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39656" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アベルよ竜に立ち向かえ!封印せよ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abel yo Ryuu ni Tachimukae! Fuuin Seyo!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39657" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海峡の門 恐るべき竜伝説の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaikyou no Mon: Osorubeki Ryuu Densetsu no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39658" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘!! アベル対オルテガ意外な真実!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 31</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou!! Abel Tai Ortega Igai na Shinjitsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39659" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイシンの一撃! アークデーモンの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaishin no Ichigeki! Archdemon no Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39660" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪いを解け! 悲しきルドルフ将軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Break the Curse! The Sad General Rudolph</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroi o Toke! Kanashiki Rudolph Shougun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39661" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪いの兜 謎の戦士オルテガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 29</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroi no Kabuto: Nazo no Senshi Ortega</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39662" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吹雪の剣を探せ!! ネザーの町 試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fubuki no Ken o Sagase!! Nether no Machi: Shiren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39663" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜伝説 マイラの港へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of the Dragon. To the Port of Mairae</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu Densetsu: Myla no Minato e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39664" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水上都市ヴェルギンへ修行!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suijou Toshi Vergin e Shugyou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39665" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アベル復活 うなれ! いなずまの剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 28</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abel Fukkatsu: Unare! Inazuma no Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39666" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブレスストーン 希望の灯をともせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stone Breath. Light the Fire of Hope!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Breathstone: Kibou no Akari o Tomose</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39667" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生か死か!? 竜海峡脱出!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life or Death? Flee the Dragon`s Strait!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei ka Shi ka!? Ryuu Kaikyou Dasshutsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39668" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔の海の亡霊の島へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ma no Umi no Bourei no Shima e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39669" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再びドラン城へ ジキドの陰謀!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi Doran-jou e: Jikido no Inbou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39670" update="2011-05-27">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラン城の怪奇モンスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Creature from Castle Doran</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doran Jou no Kaiki Monster</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45982" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者たちの新たなる決意!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Determination for the Heroes!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha-tachi no Arata Naru Ketsui!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45983" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵か味方か!? 謎の美剣士アドニス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Enemy or an Ally!? The Handsome Swordsman Adonis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki ka Mikata ka!? Nazo no Bikenshi Adonis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45984" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甦れ!! 不死鳥ラーミア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revive! Phoenix Lamia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaere! Fushichou Lamia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45985" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出現!! 天空の浮遊島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Appears!! The Floating Island in the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugen!! Tenkuu no Fuyuu Shima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45986" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青き神殿 アベルよ聖剣を抜け!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blue Shrine - Abel, Pull Out the Holy Sword!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoki Shinden Abel yo Seiken o Nuke!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45987" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃! エスターク城の決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault! Decisive Battle at Estark Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki! Estark Shiro no Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45988" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の竜はアリアハンに!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Dragon is in Ariahan!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Ryuu wa Ariahan ni!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45989" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜神湖に秘められた謎!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hidden Riddle at Dragon God Lake!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuujin Mizuumi ni Himerareta Nazo!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45990" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒れる竜VSスーパーバラモス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angered Dragon VS Super Baramos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okoreru Ryuu VS Super Baramos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45991" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大勇者誕生!! 青と赤の珠の奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of the Greatest Hero!! The Miracle of the Blue and Red Ball</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyuusha Tanjou!! Ao to Aka no Tama no Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45992" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終決戦!! アベルVSバラモス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Decisive Battle!! Abel VS Baramos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuu Kessen!! Abel VS Baramos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46559" update="2010-09-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1991-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122620" update="2010-09-22">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1991-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122621" update="2010-09-22">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1990-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122622" update="2010-09-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227131" recap="true" update="2020-02-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>1990-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者アベルよ! いま旅立ちの時は来た!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hero Abel! The Time of Departure Has Come!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Abel yo! Ima Tabidachi no Toki wa Kita!!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
