<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2092" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-07-20</startdate>
<enddate>1991-07-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Quest: Dai no Daibouken (1991)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドラゴンクエスト ダイの大冒険 (1991)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Quest: Adventure of Dai (1991)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DRAGON QUEST ダイの大冒険 (1991)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2093" type="Sequel">Dragon Quest: Dai no Daibouken - Tachiagare!! Avan no Shito</anime>
<anime id="2095" type="Same Setting">Dragon Quest Retsuden: Roto no Monshou</anime>
<anime id="1105" type="Alternative Setting">Dragon Quest: Dai no Daibouken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="6049" type="Direction">Takenouchi Kazuhisa</name>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="7661" type="Original Work">Inada Kouji</name>
<name id="5311" type="Music">Sugiyama Kouichi</name>
<name id="5334" type="Original Work">Sanjou Riku</name>
</creators>
<description>It starts with a kid named Dai remembering a story told to him by his grandfather, the monster magician Brass, about the defeat of the Demon Lord Hadlar by the hands of a hero who, as the story progresses, is known to be Avan.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="26">5.19</permanent>
<temporary count="26">6.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>14151.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7435</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2447</identifier>
<identifier>nqtgvu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Quest:_Dai_no_Daibōken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンクエスト_ダイの大冒険_(1991年の映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>151447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2687</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="66528" type="main character in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Dai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61722.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3250" picture="24693.jpg">Fujita Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="20656" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136814" update="2012-02-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OP</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
