<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2120" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2006-08-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Top o Nerae 2! Diebuster</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">top2</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Дотянись до неба 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">톱을 노려라! 다이버스터</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Zirveyi Hedefle 2! NihaiAvcı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Diebuster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Top o Nerae! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Top wo Nerae! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Aim for the Top! Gunbuster 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">トップをねらえ2! DIEBUSTER</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gunbuster 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gunbuster 2</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Punta al top 2! Diebuster</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Дайбастер: дотянись до неба - 2!</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">กันบัสเตอร์ 2: ไดบัสเตอร์</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14383" type="Sequel">Top o Nerae 3</anime>
<anime id="185" type="Prequel">Top o Nerae! Gunbuster</anime>
<anime id="4527" type="Summary">Top o Nerae 2! Gekijouban</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4575" approval="117" total="124">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
<anime id="117" approval="57" total="97">Furi Kuri</anime>
<anime id="9875" approval="7" total="13">Kill la Kill</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210645">Sci-fi superpower spectacular.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="251545">Not as good as the first "season", but it`s great enough to witness the resolve of unclear details of Gunbuster`s ending. To understand this anime you HAVE TO watch the prequel!
And: It`s most likely the prototype of TTGL.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="417064">Really good anime with high quality animation.
You can see without looking at the previous series, there is only a small link at the end of the final episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="468351">Definately one of my favourite animes, it was funny, well voiced, well drawn, had a story that was decent, and mechs! we all love mechs.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.top2.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="750" type="Unknown Relation">Bandai Visual</name>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="1389" type="Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="718" type="Original Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="58" type="Original Plan">Tsurumaki Kazuya</name>
<name id="58" type="Direction">Tsurumaki Kazuya</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
</creators>
<description>While Gunbuster`s final mission destroyed the Space Monsters` star system, the intergalactic war still continues. Earth`s only hope lies in the hands of TOPLESS, an elite mecha group of children possessing supernatural powers and new Buster machines. Among their ranks is a rookie named http://anidb.net/ch9221 [Nono] and the ace pilot http://anidb.net/ch9225 [Lal`C] — whom Nono looks at as a "big sister". Together with their teammates http://anidb.net/ch9228 [Nicola] and http://anidb.net/ch9235 [Casio], they must do their very best to protect all of mankind from the wrath of the Space Monsters.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2774">7.31</permanent>
<temporary count="2802">7.71</temporary>
<review count="2">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>74504.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3920</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20547</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1002</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1418</identifier>
<identifier>nilpyb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.top2.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Diebuster</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トップをねらえ2!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>511</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>320202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7261</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3459" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-20">
<name>space monsters</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5907" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-26">
<name>origami</name>
<description>Origami (折り紙, from ori meaning "folding", and kami meaning "paper"; kami changes to gami due to rendaku) is the traditional Japanese art of paper folding, which started in the 17th century AD at the latest and was popularized outside of Japan in the mid-1900s. It has since then evolved into a modern art form. The goal of this art is to transform a flat sheet of material into a finished sculpture through folding and sculpting techniques, and as such the use of cuts or glue are not considered to be origami. Paper cutting and gluing is usually considered kirigami.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9221" type="main character in" update="2015-06-02">
<rating votes="111">8.78</rating>
<name>Nono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hailing from a rural community in the Martian countryside, Nono is a simple and clumsy girl with a big dream: she wants to be a space pilot. And not just any space pilot, but one to rival "Nonoriri". Of course, dreaming of being a pilot and actually becoming one are two entirely different things, as she soon finds out upon reaching the city. Even after landing a somewhat dead-end job as a waitress in one of the city`s bars, Nono stubbornly holds on to her ideals, despite the chiding of her boss and the bar`s regular patrons. Her persistence pays off, however, when she encounters a real space pilot in the person of Lal`C Melk Mark, member of the elite Fraternity and current pilot of Buster Machine Dix-Neuf. It is through Lal`C (whom she impulsively dubs her onee-sama, or big sister) that Nono finally finds the means to make her dreams a reality.
Possessing a bubbly personality and a near-endless supply of optimism, Nono seems to be a normal, if clumsy, country girl. However, Nono is anything but normal; in fact, she isn`t even human, but an android, who can`t quite remember the reason why she was built (though much of her past is revealed later in the series). She idolizes Lal`C, despite the fact that the latter seems to regard her with mild annoyance, and will do anything to please her.
Nono has trace recorded history of http://anidb.net/ch1836 [Takaya Noriko] and http://anidb.net/ch1837 [Amano Kazumi] (The pilots of Buster Machines 1 and 2) in her memory. The very person she Idolizes and wants to become is Takaya Noriko. Due to her damaged memory, Nono cannot remember Noriko`s actual name and thus pronounces it Nonoriri.</description>
<picture>2277.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9222" type="main character in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="46">8.88</rating>
<name>Buster Machine 7 Gou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Though alluded to throughout the series, it is revealed that Nono is in fact a buster machine.
Nono herself is formidable, with the ability to warp almost instantaneously using the singularity built into her. Using three special lenses on the back of her hands and her chest, she can absorb energy blasts. Upon her legs are six banks of lasers similar to the ones used on the old Exelion, as well as additional thrusters. Finally, she can fire off a Buster Beam, or her rendition of a slicing maneuver, where she has the power to cut a moon in half. Not to mention the ability to create multitudes of micro-black holes. However, her greatest ability is to control what is referred to in this series as "Space Monsters", which are actually the Buster Corps support unit built to protect the solar system from the true Space Monsters. The greatest show of this is when the entirety of the collective Buster Corps patrolling and encircling the Solar System is assembled, creating the largest Buster Machine combination to date, "Diebuster". It`s a gigantic red-colored rendition of Nono, though the outfit bears a close resemblance to the legacy Top Squadron uniforms from Gunbuster. Assembled, it is comparable in size to Earth. In this form, Nono resides in the large crest upon the machine`s forehead, which resembles the insignia of the space fleet from Gunbuster.</description>
<picture>28733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9225" type="main character in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="36">7.51</rating>
<name>Lal`C Mellk Mal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The current holder of the top kill score among Topless pilots, Lal`C, along with fellow pilots Nicola and Tycho, is part of the so-called "Idol" group (pilots with exceptionally high kill rates). She is also the current pilot of Buster Machine Dix-Neuf, the oldest buster machine still in operation. Nicknamed "princess" ("hime") by her teammates, Lal`C is outwardly cool and self-confident - traits that draw Nono`s admiration for her, much to her initial annoyance. It is Lal`C who helps induct Nono (with some indirect assistance from Nicola) into the Fraternity as an "auxiliary member", despite the fact that Nono manifests none of the traits associated with being a Topless.
While initially bothered by Nono`s hero-worship of her, Lal`C gradually gets used to her company, to the point where she can talk about things she wouldn`t normally tell anyone. She senses some potential in Nono, and admires the girl`s never-give-up attitude a little (though she might act otherwise), but doubts if guts and perseverance alone can make the girl`s dreams come true.</description>
<picture>2278.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9226" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Dix-Neuf</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The oldest Buster Machine still in active service, its name literally means "nineteen" in French. Its appearance resembles a stereotypical Japanese bike gangster (bosozoku; sporting a long dark trenchcoat covering its muscular-looking body with baggy matching "pants". It has a huge red scar running through its chest and abdomen, and an artificial metal left arm. Dix-Neuf has a cruise mode wherein it resembles a huge space rocket. Its wide array of weaponry includes finger-mounted machineguns, the Buster Gator (a hand-held chainsaw/knuckle weapon augmented by the right forearm rockets), Buster Beam, Buster Might (missiles located in its left forearm), and Burning Wall (micro-missiles stored in the inner layer of its coat) to name a few. When its coat is removed, a huge bronze oni (Japanese demon) face with red eyes and flaming horns is revealed on its back which is capable of offense using eyebeams. When detached, its coat can also transform into a large laser cannon. It also has the ability to teleport to where Lal`C summons it to be when the Topless seal on her forehead is removed.
While capable of battling opponents without a pilot (due to its accumulative AI), Dix-Neuf`s true potential is unleashed when a Topless pilots it: its mobility increases exponentially, its otherwise rigid trench coat is able to flex and move almost as if it weighed little more than a piece of clothing, and it can use weaponry powered by its Topless pilot`s Exotic Maneuvers.
Dix-Neuf had its Degeneracy generator removed and replaced with a cockpit in the chest. This may have been done to bury the technology to keep humans in the solar system, or simply because of the horn going through its right eye, blocking access to the original cockpit located in its head. In its true form, after Lal`C and Dix-Neuf violently installed a Degeneracy generator from one of the fallen Buster Corps "space monster" into itself, the entire machine turns red, with the heavy overcoat turned into pure energy. The large mouthpiece is removed, exposing a human face.
Dix-Neuf saves Lal`C one last time when Nono warps the black hole away from earth, its presumably sealed off with the other buster machines as there are no more threats from Space Monsters.</description>
<picture>2279.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="9228" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="6">3.88</rating>
<name>Nicola Vacheron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only male Topless on the "Idol" team, Nicola is the pilot of Buster Machine Vingt-Sept and, before Lal`C`s inclusion into the ranks of the Topless, was considered one of the most powerful Topless of his generation. He is Lal`C`s inspiration (in as much as Lal`C is Nono`s inspiration), and seems to have a relationship with her, though it is debatable whether it is of a romantic nature or not. He is interested in Nono and sees potential in her to be a Buster Machine pilot, despite the fact that Nono has never manifested any kind of Topless reaction (something that, according to their minder Casio, may not be possible in artificial beings), and secretly helps Nono join the Fraternity under the premise of being an "auxiliary" member.
Considered "old" among the current Topless (as he is nearing late adolescence), Nicola is already having a hard time manifesting the Exotic Maneuvers needed to power his machine. As such, he seems to secretly be seeking a way to extend his "tenure" as a Topless, to the point of joining the Serpentine Twin`s inner circle and acting as their watcher over Nono`s activities.
He ultimately loses his ability to pilot the Buster machine and becomes a lieutenant in the empire.</description>
<picture>2280.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9230" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Vingt-Sept</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Vingt-Sept is a somewhat gangly-looking machine sporting outstretched wings which can be used as a secondary pair of arms at its shoulders that house a multitude of speaker-like openings on its surface, which likely help magnify the range and effect of the reality-bending Exotic Maneuvers Nicola uses. It has the ability to create reality distortions which it can use to manipulate objects around it and use them as offensive weapons, other than that it has two swords for slicing through the enemy. Designed primarily for quick movement and melee combat, Vingt-Sept is light on ranged attacks, relying instead on remote-detonated "mines", as evidenced in the battle against the Jupiter Express. Its name means "twenty-seven" in French.</description>
<picture>2281.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="9232" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Buster Machine 90 Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Tycho`s final Buster Machine, Quatre-Vingt-Dix is the newest model to be rolled out of the factories in more than a decade. Slim and feminine in appearance (even sporting a pink and white paint job), Quatre-Vingt-Dix seems to be designed as a long-ranged support unit, as most of the attacks it displays in the series seemed to be ranged (as well as affecting wide areas) in nature. It is famous for its Buster Smash, a tennis-inspired wide-area attack capable of freezing large numbers of opponents instantaneously. Its name means "ninety" in French.</description>
<picture>2282.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="9233" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="17">4.10</rating>
<name>Tycho Science</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The final member of the "Idol" team, Tycho is brash, impulsive, and utterly determined (at least in the beginning) to best Lal`C`s longstanding kill record, seeing it as a chance to wipe the normally smug look off the face of the teacher`s pet (another of Lal`C`s nicknames among the members of the Fraternity). She has a low opinion of Topless in general (despite the fact that she`s a Topless herself) due to an event in her childhood where - in spite of her powers - she was unable to cure the illness of a close friend, and is annoyed by Nono`s constant attempts to prove herself worthy to become a Buster Machine pilot. Ironically, it is Nono who later helps her change her way of thinking for the better. While it isn`t outwardly implied, the two become friends, though not on the same level as Nono and Lal`C.</description>
<picture>2283.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9234" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Soixante-Six</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>2284.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="9235" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-10">
<rating votes="4">3.12</rating>
<name>Casio Takashirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only adult member of the "Idol" team, Casio is their guardian, technician, and confidant rolled into one. A former Topless himself (he was a pilot of Dix-Neuf before Lal`C joined the Fraternity), Casio possesses an intimate understanding of the workings of the Buster Machines, as well as the people forced to pilot them. That is part of why he was one of the first to express his doubts on Nicola`s assertion that Nono had the potential to become a pilot. Despite his initial misgivings, however, he joins Lal`C in welcoming Nono into their "team".
Despite being a lech and a joker, Casio can be surprisingly serious when the situation merits it. He secretly yearns to pilot a Buster Machine again, but is resigned to the fact that he can only be near them, due to his advanced age. He is aware of the shady activities of the Serpentine Twins, but not the exact details of their little "project". Casio`s fate at the end of the series is unknown, but presumably remains an engineer in the empire.</description>
<picture>2285.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60455" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Roy Anyan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60456" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Katoferu Patata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20580" picture="53996.jpg">Sonobe Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60457" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Gouya Reishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60458" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Nyan Nuoku Cham</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60459" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Citron Limone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60460" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Pashika Pesuka Perushikumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60461" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Guruka Kukushisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4628" picture="224317.jpg">Kobayashi Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60462" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Ruu Sun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60463" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Hatori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60464" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Serpentine Shimai (Imouto)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60465" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Serpentine Shimai (Ane)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60472" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Quarante-Deux</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This designation seems to refer to the two separate Buster Machines of the Serpentine Sisters. These Machines combine together into something resembling a gargoyle`s head. Their offensive capabilities, if any, are not known.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144320.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60473" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Vingt-Deux</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144321.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60474" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Trente-Six</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144322.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60475" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Cinquante</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144323.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60476" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Cinquante-Cinq</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144324.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60477" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Soixante</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144325.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60478" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Soixante et Un</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144326.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60479" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Quatre-Vingt-Neuf</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144328.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60480" type="appears in" update="2013-10-16">
<name>Quatre-Vingt-Sept</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>144327.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75523" type="appears in" update="2015-06-01">
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="24162" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お姉さまと呼ばせて下さい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please, Let Me Call You Onee-sama!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onee-sama to Yobasete Kudasai!</title>
<summary>Nono, a young girl from the country, moves to the big city in order to achieve her dream: becoming a space pilot! However, in order to do that, she`ll not only have to reach for the top, she`ll have to go Topless--and her chance comes a lot sooner than expected!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685575</identifier>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24532" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25069" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お姉さまなんかになりたくない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Want to Be an Onee-sama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onee-sama Nanka ni Naritakunai</title>
<summary>Mars` Space Force isn`t happy about space monsters showing up on their doorstep, and they blame the Fraternity. Lal`c is questioned about the role of Topless in the attack, and Nono proves whether she`s got heart.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685577</identifier>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38183" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トップレスなんて大嫌い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hate the Topless</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Topless Nante Daikirai</title>
<summary>Tycho wrecks her Buster Machine, ruining her chance to reach top. Not to worry--there`s another Buster Machine in the works. But will it awaken for someone whose only concern is her score?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685579</identifier>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40716" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活!! 伝説のバスターマシン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrection!! The Legendary Buster Machine!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu!! Densetsu no Buster Machine!</title>
<summary>Nono`s despair grows as her certainty that she`ll get a Buster Machine fades. She`s sent to Pluto to recover an old Buster Machine, but there`s more going on than a salvage operation... and to Nono`s heart!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685581</identifier>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="45863" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星を動かすもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mover of Planets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi o Ugokasu Mono</title>
<summary>After the Titan incident, the world has changed. Topless are a disease, and humanity`s last hope for salvation is the least likely person in the Sol System.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685583</identifier>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="50665" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたの人生の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story of Your Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata no Jinsei no Monogatari</title>
<summary>With the survival of humanity itself at stake, one desperate plan remains: the sacrifice of the Earth, to strike at the beast! But where is Buster Machine #7?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685585</identifier>
<identifier>gunbuster-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="77933" update="2007-06-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="77934" update="2007-06-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141207" update="2012-07-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141208" update="2012-07-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141209" update="2012-07-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course 01</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
