<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2149" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>8</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>1997-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Seiki GPX Cyber Formula Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Century GPX Cyber Formula Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新世紀GPXサイバーフォーミュラSAGA</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2438" type="Sequel">Shin Seiki GPX Cyber Formula Sin</anime>
<anime id="2462" type="Prequel">Shin Seiki GPX Cyber Formula Zero</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=129</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="706" type="Character Design">Hisayuki Hirokazu</name>
<name id="706" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hisayuki Hirokazu</name>
<name id="621" type="Chief Direction">Fukuda Mitsuo</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>After his disappointing loss in the last round of the 14th Cyber Formula World Grand Prix, which causes him the championship, Hayato Kazami decides that he needs a change and switches over to the Sugo Garland SF-03 for the 15th Cyber Formula World Grand Prix while he waits for the newest Asurada design. However, his hope to make up for the past year`s letdown was made difficult when Aoi ZIP Formula had a major restructuring and brought in Kyoshiro Nagumo as the new president of the team. The new car that he brought to the team, drove by newcomer Phil Fritz, is seemingly unbeatable...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="98">6.45</permanent>
<temporary count="99">7.38</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3124.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4231</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1394</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743</identifier>
<identifier>vkdspu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=129</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新世紀GPXサイバーフォーミュラSAGA#.E6.96.B0.E4.B8.96.E7.B4.80GPX.E3.82.B5.E3.82.A4.E3.83.90.E3.83.BC.E3.83.95.E3.82.A9.E3.83.BC.E3.83.9F.E3.83.A5.E3.83.A9SAGA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4054</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1180</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2767" parentid="2759" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-12-12">
<name>formula racing</name>
<description>Formula racing is any of several forms of open-wheeled single-seater motorsport. The origin of the term lies in the nomenclature that was adopted by the FIA for all of its post-World War II single-seater regulations, or formulæ. The best known of these formulæ are Formula One, Formula Two, and Formula Three.</description>
<picurl>147039.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11350" type="main character in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Kazami Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hayato was introduced to the world of Cyber Formula when by accident he became the registered driver of the Cyber Formula car Asurada, designed by his father while he recovered it from the hands of mercenaries. The Cyber System registers a unique user for the vehicle at the time of activation and the it would take a week to reformat the vehicle for another driver. This was not an option as the race was to be held much sooner. This forces the Sugo Grand Prix team to go with Hayato as the driver for the license race over the team`s driver at the time, Akira Hiyoshi. After earning his licence to compete in the Cyber Grand Prix, Hayato becomes the youngest driver to ever compete in the Grand Prix, at the time.
(Taken from Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>33816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9195" picture="33999.jpg">Kanemaru Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11353" type="main character in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="29">8.07</rating>
<name>Sugou Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2586.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11355" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Kaga Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bleed Kaga was a former `Crash Racer` racing on the fringes of recognized professional racing. These racing often dangerous and resulting in death gave him a plethora of skills he passed on to then rookie driver Hayato Kazami when they met on the highways of Japan. They quickly became friends which was complicated when Bleed, always chasing the big money made the jump to the new Aoi ZIP Formula team formed when Aoi began to lose confidence in their rising star Naoki Shinjyo. Bleed and Hayato would first be friends then rivals as their goals in racing began to clash.
(Taken from Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>33822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11356" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Sugou Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11357" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-11">
<rating votes="6">9.26</rating>
<name>Shinjou Naoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoki Shinjyo is a highly successful two-time European F3 Champion before making the switch the Cyber Formula racing after being scouted by Aoi Formula boss, Kyoko Aoi. After passing the Japanese qualifying rounds he makes his debut in America during the 2015 season with high hopes for both him and his team.
(Taken from Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>129310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11358" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Karl Richter von Randoll</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karl Richter von Randoll is the eldest child of one of the most prominent families in his native Austria. From an incredibly wealthy background he excelled at all sports and endeavors until he took the challenge of Cyber Formula while chasing Asuka Sugo. Nicknamed the `Amadeus of the Circuit` or simply `Genius` he wins his debut race humiliating Naoki Shinjyo in the process and establishes himself as a contender for the 2015 title. An early rival to Hayato Kazami and a spoiled brat, he finds a purpose in his life through Cyber Formula and forms real lasting friendships.</description>
<picture>33826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11398" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-29">
<name>Jackie Gudelian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11399" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-29">
<name>Franz Heinel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11400" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-12">
<name>Edehi Bootsvorz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33594" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-20">
<rating votes="12">5.54</rating>
<name>Aoi Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="22730" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">NO TITLE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Title</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Title</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22731" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">NEVER</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Never</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22732" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">FIRED!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fired!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fired!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22740" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">CRITICAL DAYS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Critical Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Critical Days</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22741" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BURNING!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Burning!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22742" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">EVENING CALM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evening Calm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Evening Calm</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22743" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">LOSE HIS WAY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lose His Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lose His Way</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22744" update="2011-05-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">LIFTING TURN</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lifting Turn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lifting Turn</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147659" update="2013-02-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
