<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2151" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-12-04</startdate>
<enddate>1994-12-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S: Kaguya-hime no Koibito</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">美少女戦士セーラームーンS かぐや姫の恋人</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sailor Moon S Movie: Hearts in Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Sailor Moon S Der Spielfilm: Schneeprinzessin Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Czarodziejka z Księżyca: Sailor Moon S - the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Sailor Moon S: Corações de Gelo</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เซเลอร์มูน S "แผนยึดครองโลกของเจ้าหญิงหิมะ"</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2538" type="Parent Story">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://sailormoon.channel.or.jp/index_pc.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1740" type="Direction">Shibata Hiroki</name>
<name id="3636" type="Original Work">Takeuchi Naoko</name>
<name id="3166" type="Music">Arisawa Takanori</name>
</creators>
<description>A fierce snowstorm hits Tokyo when http://anidb.net/ch7320 [Usagi] and her friends enjoy winter vacation. It is the doing of an old enemy, once repelled by the power of the legendary Silver Crystal of Love and Friendship, who returns to retake Earth and add it to her collection of frozen planets. Crucial to http://anidb.net/ch55445 [Snow Queen Kaguya]`s — as she was called by genius astronomer http://anidb.net/ch55412 [Kakeru Oozora] — plan is a magical crystal from outer space approaching Earth disguised as a comet. Once Snow Queen Kaguya gets hold of the crystal, she will have the power to freeze all life and cover the Earth in ice.
Will Kakeru`s warnings be heeded? Will http://anidb.net/ch7321 [Sailor Moon] find the crystal before the enemy? And will her powers be enough to save the Earth? All hope lies with the legendary power of the Silver Crystal of Love and Friendship once again!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="917">5.71</permanent>
<temporary count="934">7.05</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>169011.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1399</identifier>
<identifier>smcfkj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sailormoon.channel.or.jp/index_pc.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sailor_Moon_S:_The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版美少女戦士セーラームーンS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1127</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>극장판_미소녀전사_세일러문_S</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版美少女戰士S</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4928</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2343" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>ojou-sama laugh</name>
<description>A type of haughty laughter typical of rich young girls, as well as older rich women. Generally sounds like a high-pitched "OHOHOHOHOHOHO".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3771" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>recycled animation -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag overlaps recaps, http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks], and http://anidb.net/t3671 [footage reuse]. For that reason, it is set to be split. If you can, please apply the correct tag to the anime that have it, and remove this one from them; guidance on how to use each of those tags can be found in their description. If what the anime contains is a mere recap, please don`t apply any tag at all, and remove this tag from it instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5871" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-19">
<name>breathing in space</name>
<description>Find yourself in space without an oxygen tank? Not a problem! Breathing in the vacuum of space is just as easy as breathing on Earth, especially if you are a superhero or somehow able to leave the atmosphere under your own power.</description>
<picurl>166122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6352" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>Kaguya-hime</name>
<description>The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter (Taketori Monogatari, 竹取物語), also known as Princess Kaguya (かぐや姫 Kaguya-hime, 赫映姫 or 輝夜姫), is a 10th-century Japanese folktale. It primarily details the life of a mysterious girl called Kaguya-hime, who was discovered as a baby inside the stalk of a glowing bamboo plant by a bamboo cutter, alongside riches in gold. The thumb-sized girl grew into a beautiful woman, and this was known all over the lands. Eventually 5 princes made their way to her to ask her foster father for her hand. Each of them got tasked with something seemingly impossible to fullfil to marry her. After all of them failed, the emporer came to see her, and fell for her beauty. His proposal was denied as well, telling him that she wasn`t of this country and thus couldn`t marry him. In the summer Kaguya-hime started to cry upon seeing the full moon. Her foster parents inquired on the matter and after a while she gave in, telling them that she was actually coming from the moon, and that she needs to return there. When the day came to return, the emperor sent many guards to her home to protect her from the moon people. They came and took her with them anyway, leaving the parents in sadness and tears. The heartbroken emperor wanted to send her a message, and went on to ask where he could find the closest place to heaven. This being the Great Mountain of Suruga Provice. The tale goes on saying that the name of the mountain, which we know today as Mount Fuji, came from the word immortality (fushi, or fuji), and the Kanji from the emperor`s army ascending its slopes, meaning literally "Mountain Abounding with Warriours" (富士山).
The anime or episode either takes on the whole tale of Kaguya-hime or just parts of it.</description>
<picurl>169473.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7320" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="341">7.40</rating>
<name>Tsukino Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukino Usagi is a carefree schoolgirl who can transform into the de facto leader of the series` primary heroines, the Sailor Senshi.</description>
<picture>154978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7321" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="358">7.40</rating>
<name>Sailor Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7326" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="302">7.57</rating>
<name>Mizuno Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7335" type="main character in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="240">8.06</rating>
<name>Hino Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hino Rei is the real identity of http://anidb.net/ch7337 [Sailor Mars]. She works as a miko at the Hikawa Shrine, and is shown to have an affinity with two crows who live there, named Phobos and Deimos (the same as Mars` two moons).
Rei is fiery, boy-crazy, practical and ambitious, longing to one day become a singer, model, and voice actress envisioning herself as ultimately getting married.
Rei and Usagi have a very tempestuous relationship and argue frequently. Though these arguments are usually petty, early in the series Rei tries to take Usagi`s role as Senshi Leader. Her loyalty to Usagi becomes much stronger later in the series, and affection replaces the earlier resentment.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>154972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7341" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="197">7.65</rating>
<name>Kino Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7344" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="212">6.99</rating>
<name>Aino Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7374" type="main character in" update="2013-05-28">
<rating votes="114">5.76</rating>
<name>Chiba Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiba Mamoru is an university student who live in the same town as Usagi. They hate each other initially but later become lovers.
Chiba Mamoru is the reincarnation of http://anidb.net/ch9313 [Prince Endymion] and the civilian identity of http://anidb.net/ch7375 [Tuxedo Kamen]. In the 30th century, he will be known as http://anidb.net/ch7487 [King Endymion].</description>
<picture>137248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7463" type="main character in" update="2020-03-26">
<rating votes="132">3.54</rating>
<name>Chibiusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7481" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="162">6.89</rating>
<name>Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7490" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="75">7.13</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55412" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-01">
<rating votes="2">4.65</rating>
<name>Oozora Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kakeru Oozora is a genius astronomer who dreams of meeting a princess who lives on the Moon and who he calls Kaguya. He saw her once, but nobody believed him, even his best friend with whom he is secretly in love - http://anidb.net/ch55530 [Himeko Nayotake]. For his romanticized opinions and fantasies, he was laughed at by his colleagues from scientific society: "In modern world, where science rules, there is no place for such unscientific fantasies and dreams." Even Himeko can not understand his unscientific attitude.
One night, he discovered a new comet near the Moon. Its beauty reminded him of Kaguya, so he entitled it "http://anidb.net/ch55445 [Princess Snow Kaguya]". Shortly after, he saw a meteorite crashing nearby. He immediately got in his car and took this fallen piece home for further analysis. Unfortunately for him, this comet he saw is a platform of an evil Ice Witch that wants to freeze the whole Earth, and the meteorite he took home - a crystal of some kind - is her ultimate weapon to achieve this goal. Not only the Ice Queen is looking for this crystal, the crystal itself starts to drain Kakeru`s vital energy.
After saving http://anidb.net/ch7481 [Luna] from car accident and being almost hit by the car instead of her, he took her home and tended to her until she got better.
Later on, after the Ice Queen is defeated, http://anidb.net/ch7321 [Sailor Moon] wish upon the Silver Crystal to grant Luna her wish to become human as she is in love with Kakeru. Luna wants to show him his dreamed Princess Kaguya to encourage his will to fight against the darkness put into his heart by the crystal - Luna itself will become his Princess.
At the end, he finds enough courage, thanks to Luna, to confess his true feelings to Himeko.</description>
<picture>135915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55445" type="main character in" update="2013-04-28">
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<name>Princess Snow Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main villain in http://anidb.net/a2151 [Sailor Moon S Movie]. The name "Princess Snow Kaguya" is given to her by http://anidb.net/ch55412 [ Oozora Kakeru], the astronomer who first discovered the comet she is living at. Therefore, it is not her real name, which is not revealed or mentioned at all.
Once repelled from taking over the Earth by bright light in past, the Ice Queen - Princess Snow Kaguya - returns to add the Earth to her collection of frozen worlds. Sending a fragment of her comet to the Earth, she slowly starts to freeze the planet with all the livings. The fragment (a crystal of some sort) is the key for an immediate freezing of the planet, but she loses it out of her sight as it is grabbed by Kakeru who thinks of it as of an interesting meteorite and wants to analyze it. Therefore, she sends her minions - Snow Dancers - to find it.
Even though she manages to find the crystal before http://anidb.net/ch7321 [Sailor Moon] and to freeze the Earth, she is defeated and destroyed by Sailor Soldiers at the end.
Note: Princess Kaguya is a character from Japanese folklore since she is the main character of an old Japanese legend - The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter. For further information, see e.g. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Tale_of_the_Bamboo_Cutter.</description>
<picture>135989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4735" picture="29144.jpg">Masuyama Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55530" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-01">
<rating votes="2">3.84</rating>
<name>Nayotake Himeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Himeko Nayotake is a famous Japanese astronaut who was chosen to participate in the Luna Frontier Project, a space project funded by the United States, making her the youngest active astronaut in history. By this, her dream about going into outer space finally comes true. She is a close friend of http://anidb.net/ch55412 [Kakeru Oozora] with whom she is in love.
Kakeru and Himeko often argue since Himeko can not understand Kakeru`s unscientific fantasies and his belief in silly fairy-tales about princess he calls Kaguya living on the Moon. She even tells him that he could have been an excellent astronaut, if only he could stop thinking about his fantasies. This results in a quarrel during which Kakeru reject the possibility to stay by her side since their opinions differ a lot. Understanding his words as rejection of her feelings, Himeko leaves Kakeru`s apartment sobbing.
At the end, when she returns from her mission, Kakeru greets her at the airport with roses and they make up while confessing their true feelings towards each other - even though Kakeru is aware of her feelings towards him.</description>
<picture>136108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109158" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Luna (human)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245773.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21501" update="2004-09-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1994-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38643" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1994-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38644" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116989" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercials 1-2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116990" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116991" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116993" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">English Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116994" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116995" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154857" update="2013-10-08">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Luna Transformation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154858" update="2013-10-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Transformations and Special Attacks</title>
</episode>
<episode id="220983" update="2019-09-07">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>11</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Chris Hackney</title>
</episode>
<episode id="220984" update="2019-09-07">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>12</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Michelle Ruff</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
