<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2153" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-12-23</startdate>
<enddate>1995-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Super S: Sailor 9 Senshi Shuuketsu! Black Dream Hole no Kiseki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">美少女戦士 セーラームーン SuperS セーラー9戦士集結! ブラック・ドリーム・ホールの奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sailor Moon Super S: The Fabulous 9 Get Together! Miracle in the Black Dream Hole</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Sailor Moon Super S: Reise ins Land der Träume</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Sailor Moon Super S: O Buraco Negro dos Sonhos</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เซเลอร์มูน SuperS "รวมพลังอัศวินเซเลอร์ทั้ง 9! ปาฏิหาริย์แห่งแบล็กดรีมโฮล"</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2540" type="Parent Story">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Super S</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://sailormoon.channel.or.jp/index_pc.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3166" type="Music">Arisawa Takanori</name>
<name id="3636" type="Original Work">Takeuchi Naoko</name>
<name id="1740" type="Direction">Shibata Hiroki</name>
</creators>
<description>Night after night, all around the world children are being kidnapped. What evil is hiding behind such a thing? In Tokyo, a strange melody is making children run from their homes to the world of sweet dreams, and the Sailor Soldiers are investigating the matter. What is worse, http://anidb.net/ch7463 [Chibi-Usa] is enchanted by the melody as well.
For what purpose does someone kidnap and gather all these children? Does it present a threat to the Earth? Will the Sailor Soldiers be able to stop this evil-doing and save the world and the children? Will http://anidb.net/ch7320 [Usagi] save Chibi-Usa from the clutches of evil?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="774">5.18</permanent>
<temporary count="787">6.81</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>151064.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3561</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>813</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1240</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1278</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361</identifier>
<identifier>xyfpik</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sailormoon.channel.or.jp/index_pc.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sailor_Moon_SuperS:_The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>美少女戦士セーラームーンSuperS_セーラー9戦士集結!ブラック・ドリーム・ホールの奇跡</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1758</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1760</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152737</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>159562</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4376</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1129</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>미소녀전사_세일러문_SuperS_세일러_9전사_집결!_블랙_드림_홀의_기적</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版美少女戰士SuperS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5370</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7320" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="341">7.40</rating>
<name>Tsukino Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukino Usagi is a carefree schoolgirl who can transform into the de facto leader of the series` primary heroines, the Sailor Senshi.</description>
<picture>154978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7321" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="358">7.40</rating>
<name>Sailor Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7326" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="302">7.57</rating>
<name>Mizuno Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7330" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="177">7.56</rating>
<name>Sailor Mercury</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7335" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="240">8.06</rating>
<name>Hino Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hino Rei is the real identity of http://anidb.net/ch7337 [Sailor Mars]. She works as a miko at the Hikawa Shrine, and is shown to have an affinity with two crows who live there, named Phobos and Deimos (the same as Mars` two moons).
Rei is fiery, boy-crazy, practical and ambitious, longing to one day become a singer, model, and voice actress envisioning herself as ultimately getting married.
Rei and Usagi have a very tempestuous relationship and argue frequently. Though these arguments are usually petty, early in the series Rei tries to take Usagi`s role as Senshi Leader. Her loyalty to Usagi becomes much stronger later in the series, and affection replaces the earlier resentment.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>154972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7337" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="137">7.53</rating>
<name>Sailor Mars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7341" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="197">7.65</rating>
<name>Kino Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7342" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="171">7.36</rating>
<name>Sailor Jupiter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7344" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="212">6.99</rating>
<name>Aino Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7345" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="178">7.58</rating>
<name>Sailor Venus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7463" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-26">
<rating votes="132">3.54</rating>
<name>Chibiusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7464" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-26">
<rating votes="47">5.07</rating>
<name>Sailor Chibi Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7481" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="162">6.89</rating>
<name>Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7490" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="75">7.13</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7497" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="64">8.21</rating>
<name>Sailor Uranus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruka is a stubborn, protective individual, but is also strong-willed, capable, charming, lesbian, and occasionally even doting. She is formally introduced in the third story arc, although she appears in silhouette alongside Sailor Neptune in the final episode of Sailor Moon R. She is the second tallest of the Sailor Senshi at 5`9", just behind Sailor Pluto at 5`10".
Haruka is a racecar driver, even though she is barely sixteen years old when she appears. However, the timing of her birthday to the Japanese school year means she is one grade ahead of the Guardian Senshi.</description>
<picture>2653.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7502" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="58">6.87</rating>
<name>Sailor Neptune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7524" type="appears in" update="2015-03-14">
<rating votes="70">6.27</rating>
<name>Sailor Pluto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4105" picture="39793.jpg">Kawashima Chiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8481" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="20">4.50</rating>
<name>Diana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9852" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<name>Peruru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9867" type="appears in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Jouou Badiane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5058" picture="43359.jpg">Yoshida Rihoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21503" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1995-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40905" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami-chan`s First Love (Production Crew`s Interview)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40906" update="2014-05-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美ちゃんの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami-chan`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami-chan no Hatsukoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40907" update="2005-09-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami-chan`s First Love Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40908" update="2005-09-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami-chan`s First Love Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116996" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami-chan no Hatsukoi Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116997" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercials 1-3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116998" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116999" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117000" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">English Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117001" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117002" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154855" update="2013-10-08">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Transformations and Special Attacks</title>
</episode>
<episode id="220985" update="2019-09-07">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Kate Higgins</title>
</episode>
<episode id="220986" update="2019-09-07">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Sandy Fox</title>
</episode>
<episode id="220987" update="2019-09-07">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Tara Sands</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
