<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2160" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-08-19</startdate>
<enddate>2006-01-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ajisai no Uta</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あじさいの唄</title>
</titles>
<url>http://ajisai.sod.co.jp/top.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
<name id="11244" type="Direction">Toyama Sou</name>
<name id="5527" type="Music">Sawada Kan</name>
<name id="7638" type="Chief Animation Direction">Baba Toshiko</name>
<name id="39699" type="Original Work">Mori Kurimaru</name>
</creators>
<description>This is a heartwarming story about a family during the Edo era. The main character, http://anidb.net/ch66121 [Kuritarou], lives with his father and a stray dog. Despite his mother`s death, he continues to live a cheerful life.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9">5.30</permanent>
<temporary count="10">5.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>152415.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4188</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1472</identifier>
<identifier>nklyoy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ajisai.sod.co.jp/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あじさいの唄</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>320514</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2690" parentid="2641" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Tokugawa period</name>
<description>The anime takes place during a period of Japanese history running from 1603 to 1868.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="66120" type="main character in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Kurinosuke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66121" type="main character in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Kuritarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39693" picture="152416.jpg">Miyatani Keita</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66122" type="main character in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Hahaue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39694" picture="152417.jpg">Wakui Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66123" type="main character in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Chichiue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39695" picture="152418.jpg">Kanie Keizou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21560" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2004-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うすあさぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usu Asagi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35730" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2004-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">びゃくろく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byakuroku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35731" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2004-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">からくれない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kara Kurenai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189022" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2006-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋唄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Uta</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
