<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2181" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-29</startdate>
<enddate>2005-04-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Munto: Toki no Kabe o Koete</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Мунто 2: За Стенами Времени</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Munto 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Munto: Toki no Kabe wo Koete</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">munto2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">MUNTO 時の壁を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Munto 2: Beyond the Walls of Time</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6427" type="Sequel">Tenjoubito to Akutobito Saigo no Tatakai</anime>
<anime id="738" type="Prequel">Munto</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.munto.com/data/munto2/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="526" type="Character Design">Aratani Tomoe</name>
<name id="1672" type="Direction">Kigami Yoshiji</name>
<name id="736" type="Series Composition">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="49217" type="Music">Ikeda Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>At one time, the future of the world depended on a certain girl:
"Please wait for me Munto, I will get there at any cost."
The two worlds were saved by the power called Akuto, which http://anidb.net/ch3717 [Yumemi] and http://anidb.net/ch3718 [Munto] released.
However, the kings of the heavenly world, who regained the power of Gods, started to deny the wisdom of the Heads and seceded from the Union, one after another. Their ambitions made them fight each other, and the order of the heavenly world has been lost. The war of the Gods shakes the heavens and the lower realms. Its influence transcends space and time, and finally, reaches the human world. The kings are about to attack Munto`s magic realm, and even though this is a serious assault, Munto hesitates to contact Yumemi.
At the same time, http://anidb.net/ch3771 [Guntarl] plans to capture Yumemi and use her for his own ends. And http://anidb.net/ch3770 [Gasu] has abandoned the mission as an Outsider, but a cursed unusual event forces him to get involved.
Yumemi`s decision to act is beyond http://anidb.net/ch3719 [Ichiko] and http://anidb.net/ch3764 [Suzume]`s understanding. But the two girls decide to stick with their precious friend. Can Yumemi overcome the seemingly insurmountable wall of space and time to reach the land where Munto is waiting? The destruction of the two worlds is at hand, and only this unassuming girl can save them, yet again.
Source: official site</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="667">5.84</permanent>
<temporary count="676">7.05</temporary>
<review count="1">9.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11983.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1135</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2043</identifier>
<identifier>cvykwl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.munto.com/data/munto2/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Munto</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>MUNTOシリーズ#.E6.99.82.E3.81.AE.E5.A3.81.E3.82.92.E8.B6.8A.E3.81.88.E3.81.A6</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>643</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8332</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1662" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-22">
<name>weaponized paper fan</name>
<description>Harisen (ハリセン meaning "slapping fan" in Japanese) is a giant paper fan, usually made in a closed fashion, It is used in Japanese comedy shows as a form of physical comedy (this is what is usually seen in anime when a character smacks another on the head with a paper fan).</description>
<picurl>47539.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2837" parentid="2628" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>floating island</name>
<description>A floating island is an island either floating in the sky, or actually floating in the ocean (mobile). The island`s flotation can be powered either by magic or science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4517" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>inter-dimensional schoolgirl</name>
<description>One, or more, schoolgirls cross through time, space or some dimension using a space-warp-magic-portal-wormhole-singularity-thing to save one, or more, worlds, or planets.
A major twist could be that the schoolgirl might originate from that very magic-futuristic world, bearing one great secret legendary power to defeat one big bad legendary foe. The return back home is the leitmotiv of the whole series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3717" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="16">2.77</rating>
<name>Hidaka Yumemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yumemi is the main character of the story, and the only person who can see the "floating islands in the sky." She is afraid of her ability because it makes her different from others, and has learned the hard way that most people don`t believe what she sees. Because of this, she keeps her gift to herself, carrying a pink umbrella to block out the view of the sky.</description>
<picture>26487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4211" picture="26400.jpg">Mima Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3718" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="13">6.39</rating>
<name>Munto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruler of the Magical Kingdom (one of several kingdoms in the sky). He deliberately falls to the dangerous Lower World in a desperate bid to contact Yumemi and save his people and the heavenly world. He is proud and stubborn to a fault, but also strong, courageous and caring.</description>
<picture>26489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4215">Higo Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3719" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="15">2.15</rating>
<name>Ono Ichiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yumemi`s classmate and childhood friend. Ichiko is a very positive and energetic person. She always encourages Yumemi whenever she feels gloomy and is very protective of her. However, she also seems to have co-dependent tendencies and can be overly controlling due to her own insecurities. She had always wanted to see the islands in the sky Yumemi spoke of, and quietly wished for the day that she would see them.</description>
<picture>26490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3764" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="15">7.05</rating>
<name>Imamura Suzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yumemi`s classmate and childhood friend. She is a very optimistic and cheerful girl who lives at her own pace. She has a rather immature and childish personality, but is always smiling. Though she is a girl with a very soft-spoken nature and childish at that, she often surprises others by her wise words and "outsider-looking-in" view.</description>
<picture>26491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3766" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="2">1.17</rating>
<name>Tobe Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of http://anidb.net/ch3717 [Yumemi], http://anidb.net/ch3719 [Ichiko] and http://anidb.net/ch3764 [Suzume]. He is a very bright student with a realistic, dependable, but "fence-sitter" personality. Because he often listens to http://anidb.net/ch3719 [Ichiko] and is shown to admire her on many levels, it is implied that he has a crush on her, but http://anidb.net/ch3719 [Ichiko] herself shows no signs of noticing this.</description>
<picture>26495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3767" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<name>Hidaka Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father of http://anidb.net/ch3717 [Yumemi] and http://anidb.net/ch3769 [Chikara].</description>
<picture>26501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3768" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="3">2.85</rating>
<name>Hidaka Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of http://anidb.net/ch3717 [Yumemi] and http://anidb.net/ch3769 [Chikara].</description>
<picture>26499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3131" picture="234931.jpg">Tanii Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3770" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="4">5.20</rating>
<name>Gasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The enigmatic guardian of Time, Gasu is described as an "Outsider," which may explain his and http://anidb.net/ch3775 [Iryita]`s Arabic-themed clothing. Despite the dangers of overstepping his role, he allows http://anidb.net/ch3718 [Munto] to slip through a hole in time to find http://anidb.net/ch3717 [Yumemi].</description>
<picture>26521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3771" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="4">2.29</rating>
<name>Guntarl</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Guntarl" is a corruption of the German name "Gunther,". He answers to the Elders of the Heavens, and is in command of the united armies. He is a cunning and dangerous person who hungers for power. He is the one who directs the attacks against http://anidb.net/ch3718 [Munto]`s Magical Kingdom in an attempt to seize control.</description>
<picture>26525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3772" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="4">1.35</rating>
<name>Gulidori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>King of http://anidb.net/ch7663 [Horuguuzu] country.</description>
<picture>19640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3773" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="7">5.28</rating>
<name>Ryueri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A prophetess under Munto`s supervision who has the gift of foresight. She sacrifices her own vision to help Munto find the way to restore Akuto and monitors his journey from the Heavens. Calm and collected, she is a motherly figure, especially to the young Toche.</description>
<picture>26505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3774" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="3">2.29</rating>
<name>Tochye</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Apprentice of http://anidb.net/ch3773 [Ryueri].</description>
<picture>26513.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3775" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="6">4.78</rating>
<name>Iryita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A small, imp-like girl who is constantly seen with http://anidb.net/ch3770 [Gasu]. She is shown to care for him deeply and treats him with the utmost respect and trust, crying out in fear when he is hurt. http://anidb.net/ch3770 [Gasu] also seems to care for Iryita, diving into space to catch her when she is falling. Her personality is mischievous and spunky.</description>
<picture>26534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3776" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="10">5.84</rating>
<name>Raika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A general of Enda (one of the Heavenly World`s countries). A strong warrior and determined at what she does, Raika is also shown to be a fair leader in battle, her subordinates respecting her orders and carrying them out.</description>
<picture>26520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4217" picture="151698.jpg">Yanagisawa Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3777" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="2">5.42</rating>
<name>Rui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7656" type="appears in" update="2009-06-30">
<name>Madou Kuni</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>30338.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7659" type="appears in" update="2009-06-30">
<name>Rengougan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Military alliance of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
<picture>30339.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7661" type="appears in" update="2009-06-30">
<name>Enda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
<picture>30346.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7663" type="appears in" update="2009-06-30">
<name>Horuguuzu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
<picture>30345.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7664" type="appears in" update="2009-06-30">
<name>Ondo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
<picture>30344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7665" type="appears in" update="2009-06-30">
<name>Shainan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
<picture>30340.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7666" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<name>Shozeto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
</character>
<character id="7667" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<name>Ryannei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
</character>
<character id="7668" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<name>Ruhkon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of Heavenly World`s countries.</description>
</character>
<character id="7743" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<name>Ichiko no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch3719 [Ichiko]`s father.</description>
<picture>26686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7769" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<name>Raruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Queen of Enda.</description>
<picture>26724.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7770" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<name>Izuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26725.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7771" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<name>Ramuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26726.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7773" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<name>Gurai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26728.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7775" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<name>June</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26732.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="34024" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38537" update="2006-03-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2005-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
