<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2186" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-09</startdate>
<enddate>2005-10-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Мобильный воин ГАНДАМ: Судьба поколения</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">جندام سيد دستني</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Мобилен Костюм Гъндам Сийд: Съдба</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gundam Seed 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gundam Seed Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">種死</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gs2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SEED2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GSD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダムSEED DESTINY</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">机动战士高达SEED Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam Seed Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">기동전사 건담 씨드 데스티니</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โมบิลสูท กันดั้มซี้ด เดสทินี่</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4170" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny Final Plus: Erabareta Mirai</anime>
<anime id="252" type="Prequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED</anime>
<anime id="4366" type="Side Story">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED C.E. 73 Stargazer</anime>
<anime id="4905" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny: Jiyuu no Daishou</anime>
<anime id="4457" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny: Kudakareta Sekai</anime>
<anime id="4466" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny: Sorezore no Tsurugi</anime>
<anime id="4758" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny: Sadame no Gouka</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10846" approval="9" total="11">Aldnoah.Zero (2015)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="261686">Fans will love it.&lt;br /&gt;Everyone else will hate it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="37821">If you like Gundam Seed, you would like its sequel, Gundam Seed Destiny</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gundam-seed-d.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="621" type="Direction">Fukuda Mitsuo</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="620" type="Character Design">Hirai Hisashi</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="7988" type="Series Composition">Morosawa Chiaki</name>
<name id="10769" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takase Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="13968" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ikeda Tamotsu</name>
<name id="5404" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishii Masanori</name>
<name id="1766" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kabashima Yousuke</name>
<name id="10840" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakuma Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="15952" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsuda Hiroshi</name>
<name id="8004" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kamata Yuusuke</name>
<name id="9136" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shigeta Satoshi</name>
<name id="3738" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshida Tooru</name>
<name id="10849" type="Chief Animation Direction">Arisawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1650" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>Cosmic Era (C.E.) 70, the "Bloody Valentine" tragedy escalated into a war between the Earth Alliance and ZAFT. It became severe. Making many sacrifices, they achieved a truce after the second battle at Yakin Due. However, this truce didn`t subdue the conflicts between Naturals and Coordinators completely.
During the war, Shinn Asuka was involved in Earth Alliance`s intrusion into Orb. While he was escaping from the fire, he lost his parents and little sister before his very eyes. When he was deep in sorrow gripping his sister`s cellular phone, which is his only memento of her, a gundam, which was the principal cause of the war, was flying over his head. Being disappointed, he left Orb and went to PLANT.
In C.E. 73., he became a ZAFT soldier.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4304">6.05</permanent>
<temporary count="4427">7.68</temporary>
<review count="26">7.11</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83885.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2669</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>94</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1479</identifier>
<identifier>ftpchb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam-seed-d.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mobile_Suit_Gundam_SEED_Destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士ガンダムSEED_DESTINY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>477</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321250</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6927</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/96</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1286" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-28">
<name>megalomaniac</name>
<description>Megalomania is a psychopathological condition characterized by delusional fantasies of power, relevance, and omnipotence, and by inflated self-esteem.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>70559.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2835" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Africa</name>
<description>The world`s second-largest continent and the birthplace of the human species, Africa is a place of a huge diversity, with deserts and savannas, with famine and precious stones, with cultural and economical riches of all kinds. Throughout history, Africa has been the cradle of empires and has been ruled by foreign powers, and as of the early 21st century sees swift changes and economic boom going side by side with inhuman levels of poverty.</description>
<picurl>126530.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2836" parentid="7082" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Australia</name>
<description>Australia, officially the Commonwealth of Australia, is a sovereign country comprising the mainland of the Australian continent, the island of Tasmania and numerous smaller islands. It is the largest country in Oceania and the world`s sixth-largest country by total area. The neighbouring countries are Papua New Guinea, Indonesia and East Timor to the north; the Solomon Islands and Vanuatu to the north-east; and New Zealand to the south-east. Australia`s capital is Canberra, and its largest city is Sydney.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192049.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3432" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>pacifism</name>
<description>The belief and following of principles stating all and any conflict has a peaceful solution without use of violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-12-04">
<name>world government</name>
<description>When a whole planet (e.g. Earth or a fictional planet) has one single government.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3671" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>footage reuse</name>
<description>Footage reuse is the employment of a sequence of frames many times, generally as a side effect of a constrained anime production budget. This can happen by using the same footage once at a time, but many times over the course of the show, or by directly looping it. Types of scenes that tend to get reused include: transformations, such as those typical of superheroes or magical girls, characters that change into powered-up versions of themselves, or robots changing shape; attacks, especially when involving a series of steps that must be followed before the attack can be launched; and any kind of action that involves repeating the same movement.
This tag does not apply if the footage changes significantly between iterations. An example of that is the infamous Endless Eight arc of http://anidb.net/a6367 [the 2009 iteration of Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu]; even as the plot repeated itself, each episode of the arc showed it in different ways.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3779" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-06">
<name>fight for peace</name>
<description>Don`t they all... 
The protagonists are trying to ensure long-lasting peace by fighting a vicious enemy, hoping to defeat the threat permanently.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5708" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-27">
<name>going berserk</name>
<description>At least one of the characters in this anime gets really ticked off, so much so, that he/she wants to smash and destroy everything on his/her path.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7082" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-07">
<name>Oceania</name>
<description>Oceania is a geographic region comprising Melanesia, Micronesia, Polynesia and Australasia. Situated in the southeast of the Asia Pacific region, Oceania is the smallest continental grouping in land area and the second smallest in population after Antarctica.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214397.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="726">7.13</rating>
<name>Kira Yamato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The young civilian who becomes the pilot of the prototype http://anidb.net/ch1577 [Strike Gundam]. Kira is a first-generation Coordinator whose parents are Naturals, and his family has taken refuge in the neutral territory of the resource satellite Heliopolis to avoid the war. However, Kira finds himself drawn into the conflict when Heliopolis is attacked by http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces, and he remains aboard the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] warship http://anidb.net/ch1507 [Archangel] in order to protect his friends and loved ones. As a Coordinator, Kira has remarkable mental and physical abilities, and his computer programming talents enable him to rewrite the http://anidb.net/ch1577 [Strike Gundam`s] operating system in mid-battle to adapt to new combat conditions.</description>
<picture>52595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="300" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="400">6.55</rating>
<name>Athrun Zala</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Athrun Zala is a member of the elite Le Creuset team which attacks Heliopolis, Athrun subsequently becomes the pilot of the captured Aegis Gundam. As a child, Athrun attended a preparatory school on the moon, where he became good friends with Kira Yamato. Now, with his father leading the most warlike faction of the PLANT Supreme Council and his mother among the casualties of the "Bloody Valentine" tragedy, Athrun is determined to defeat the treacherous Earth Alliance - and shocked to discover that Kira is fighting on the side of the enemy. Athrun has a talent for mechanical tinkering, and has created numerous robot pets for his friends and acquaintances.</description>
<picture>52590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="302" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-27">
<rating votes="758">7.93</rating>
<name>Lacus Clyne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of PLANT Supreme Council chairman Siegel Clyne, whose career as a pop star has made her the idol of the Coordinators. Dispatched to join a memorial service on the anniversary of the "Bloody Valentine" tragedy, Lacus is left drifting in space when her ship is attacked by Earth Alliance forces, and her lifepod is subsequently retrieved by the Alliance warship Archangel. Lacus treats friend and foe alike with kindness and respect, and even her fiancé Athrun Zala is sometimes perplexed by her apparent naïveté.</description>
<picture>161846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="304" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="304">5.58</rating>
<name>Cagalli Yula Athha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This tomboy princess is the daughter of Lord Uzumi, one of the leaders of the neutral Orb Union. Despite her aristocratic upbringing, Cagalli is tough and headstrong, and her impulsive nature often leads her to take bold risks. Learning that her nation is secretly aiding the Earth Alliance, she travels to the resource satellite Heliopolis to see the evidence for herself, and after escaping the satellite`s collapse she makes her way to Earth to join the Desert Dawn resistance group in northern Africa. By the time she returns to Orb aboard the warship Archangel, Cagalli has formed strong bonds with both Strike Gundam pilot Kira Yamato and his estranged friend Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>52589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1484" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="52">7.56</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X20A Strike Freedom Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>During the First Earth/ZAFT War in C.E. 71, ZAFT`s http://anidb.net/ch1489 [ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam] comes to be known as one of the most powerful mobile suits ever created. In the last stages of the war, ZAFT creates a successor unit, the ZGMF-X20A Strike Freedom Gundam. However, the Strike Freedom is stolen before its completion by Terminal, a secret organization associated with followers of Lacus Clyne. Although ZAFT`s original plan was to produce multiple units with overwhelming firepower, the stolen unit is instead refined for use by the Freedom Gundam`s former pilot, Kira Yamato. The Strike Freedom is a major improvement over the original Freedom Gundam in various respects. The wings feature new high output thrusters developed from the "Voiture Lumiere" propulsion system used by the GSX-401FW Stargazer. A similar propulsion system is used by ZAFT`s ZGMF-X42S Destiny Gundam. The Strike Freedom is powered by the hyper deuterion nuclear reactor technology developed by ZAFT. This new design stores power in deuterion form, providing a continuous deuterion charge and, in theory, an endless power supply. However, it is possible for the suit`s power to be expended before the reactor can replenish it. The Strike Freedom retains a set of hip-mounted rail cannons, although the cannons can swivel behind the main body and swap places with a pair of hip-mounted, combinable beam rifles (similar to the old GAT-X103 Buster Gundam). The Strike Freedom is also armed with a chest beam cannon, head-mounted vulcan guns and a pair of beam sabers. The biggest change in armaments, however, is in the Strike Freedom`s wings. Where the original Freedom Gundam carried a pair of plasma beam cannons, the Strike Freedom features eight DRAGOON (Disconnected Rapid Armament Group Overlook Operation Network) units. The DRAGOON units housed in the wings utilize an improved quantum communications system, allowing normal pilots without expanded spatial awareness to use them. Also, like the original Freedom Gundam, the Strike Freedom is capable of docking with the METEOR mobile weapons platform.
In early C.E. 74, the original http://anidb.net/ch1489 [Freedom Gundam] is destroyed in a battle with Shinn Asuka`s ZGMF-X56S Impulse Gundam. The Strike Freedom first enters combat when Kira flies into Earth orbit in the MBF-02 Strike Rouge to assist the Eternal, under attack by ZAFT forces. Afterwards, Kira, accompanied by Lacus Clyne in the ZGMF-X19A ∞ Justice Gundam, returns to Earth and rendezvous with the Archangel. With ZAFT`s attack on the Orb Union (codenamed Operation Fury) in full swing, Kira joins in the defense of Orb and engages Shinn`s new Destiny Gundam. When the Three Ships Alliance heads to space to counter ZAFT`s forces, Kira participates in the final battle over the Moon. During the battle, he causes heavy damage to Rey Za Burrel`s ZGMF-X666S Legend Gundam. Using the METEOR, Kira also heavily damages ZAFT`s mobile space fortress Messiah. Soon after, the death of PLANT Supreme Council Chairman Gilbert Durandal and the destruction of Messiah mark the end of the war.</description>
<picture>77824.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1489" type="appears in" update="2011-11-30">
<rating votes="41">8.99</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam is one of the new Gundam designs built by ZAFT. The Freedom Gundam is equipped with a wide variety of powerful weapons for use in its HiMAT (High Mobility Aerial Tactics) mode. One of these weapons is the twin "Balaena" plasma beam cannons, which are stored in the wings and mounted over the shoulders during use. The Freedom Gundam`s other main armament consists of twin hip-mounted "Xiphias" rail cannons. Other standard armaments include head vulcans, twin beam sabers and a beam rifle. The Freedom Gundam is also capable of using something far more powerful: the METEOR support system. This mobile weapons platform is designed specifically for use by the Freedom Gundam and ZGMF-X09A Justice Gundam and is stored aboard the support ship Eternal. By using the METEOR, the Freedom Gundam can deliver a blitzkrieg attack utilizing various cannons, missile launchers and two long beam swords.
The Freedom Gundam is first used in May C.E. 71 when Kira Yamato steals it with the help of Lacus Clyne. Kira uses his new suit to travel to Earth and join the battle between ZAFT and the Alliance at Alaska. Following the battle, Kira rejoins his comrades on the Archangel and travels to Orb after Murrue Ramius decides to defect from the Alliance. There, Kira fights to protect Orb from the Alliance and is later joined by his old friend and former enemy Athrun Zala piloting his new ZGMF-X09A Justice Gundam. Following the defeat of Orb, Kira returns to space and is joined by Lacus Clyne and her stolen support ship Eternal, which provides Kira with his METEOR support system. Along with Athrun, Kira uses his METEOR to save the PLANTs from destruction by nuclear missiles. At the war`s end on September 27, the Freedom Gundam is heavily damaged in a battle against Rau Le Creuset`s ZGMF-X13A Providence Gundam. After the war, the Freedom Gundam is secretly repaired and hidden in Orb. In late C.E. 73, the Freedom Gundam is reactivated by Kira to fight off a squad of UMF/SS0-3 ASH mobile suits used by a group of special ops Coordinators sent to assassinate Lacus. In early C.E. 74, PLANT Supreme Council Chairman Gilbert Durandal orders the destruction of the Archangel and Freedom Gundam after their interference in several battles between the Alliance and ZAFT. Soon after, ZAFT then initiates "Operation Angel Down," and during that battle the Freedom Gundam is destroyed by Shinn Asuka`s ZGMF-X56S Impulse Gundam.</description>
<picture>77823.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1501" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="30">8.60</rating>
<name>Orb Union</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An island nation in the southern Pacific Ocean, which possesses considerable industrial and military power despite its small size and lack of natural resources. Its assets include high technology, an abundant supply of geothermal energy thanks to its numerous active volcanoes, and a policy of nondiscrimination against Coordinators which has enriched Orb`s talent pool. The Orb Union also has its own mass driver and controls its own space colony, the resource satellite Heliopolis.
In Orb`s complex political system, power is shared between an elected assembly and representatives of the five noble families who originally ruled over the islands.</description>
<picture>16027.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1507" type="appears in" update="2009-04-16">
<rating votes="110">5.81</rating>
<name>LCAM-01XA Archangel</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>While the Earth Alliance plays a game of catch up with ZAFT on mobile suit development, it also designs a new type of battleship to complement their mobile suits. Developed in conjunction with Orb`s Morgenroete company, the design of the Archangel class is based on that of Orb`s Izumo class. In addition to carrying mobile suits, the Archangel features many new technologies not seen in other Alliance vessels. The Archangel is capable of atmospheric entry, thanks to an ablative gel that can be spread across the hull. The Archangel also features laminated armor, making it very difficult to seriously damage in battle. In terms of weaponry, the Archangel is a mobile fortress. Its main weapon is the dual "Lohengrin" positron blaster cannon housed in the `legs` at the forward end of the ship. The Archangel`s armament includes an array of other weapons, such as "Gottfried" beam cannons, "Valient" linear cannons, "Igelstellung" vulcan guns as well as missile launchers.</description>
<picture>16039.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1508" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-08">
<rating votes="223">6.84</rating>
<name>Murrue Ramius</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1509" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="48">6.01</rating>
<name>ZAFT</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The military forces of the PLANTs. ZAFT is a militia made up of civilian volunteers, and the organization has no formal rank structure, so its members are instead addressed by descriptive titles like "commander" and "captain." The ZAFT forces are organized into independent teams named after their commanders, and much like the modern-day U.S. Marines these teams can operate equally well on land, at sea, in air, or in outer space. Since ZAFT`s membership is made up of genetically enhanced Coordinators, its forces are more than a match for the numerically superior Earth Alliance.
ZAFT was originally a political organization called the Zodiac Alliance, which was founded in C.E. 50 by Siegel Clyne and Patrick Zala. The Zodiac Alliance took on its present name in C.E. 65, and three years later it was reorganized to become an explicitly military organization equipped with the revolutionary new weapons known as mobile suits. The ZAFT forces are currently subject to the authority of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council], and report directly to the chairman of the National Defense Committee.</description>
<picture>16042.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1542" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="24">1.64</rating>
<name>Earth Alliance</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An international coalition formed by the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANT] sponsor nations and their terrestrial allies to battle the forces of http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT]. The Earth Alliance is not a single political entity, but rather a collaboration between several individual nations, which regard each other as potential adversaries even though they are currently united against a common foe. The dominant powers within the Earth Alliance are the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation], the http://anidb.net/ch1595 [Eurasian Federation], and the http://anidb.net/ch1598 [Republic of East Asia], all three of which invested heavily in the construction of the PLANTs. The South African Union and the United States of South America are junior partners in the Alliance, with the latter having been forcibly annexed by the Atlantic Federation at the start of the war.
The Earth Alliance was formally established on February 7, C.E. 70, two days after final negotiations between the PLANTs and the sponsor nations were disrupted by a terror bombing at the lunar city of Copernicus. The Alliance was created as a successor to the former United Nations, whose leadership was wiped out in the Copernicus attack, and like its predecessor it`s nominally an international organization headed by a moderate secretary-general. However, in practice it`s little more than a military alliance dominated by the Atlantic Federation and its fellow PLANT sponsor nations.
The Earth Alliance is headed by a moderate Secretary-General, but the real leaders of the Earth Alliance are http://anidb.net/ch1579 [Blue Cosmos] and its http://anidb.net/ch1578 [Logos] benefactors.
At the beginning of C.E. 71, the Alliance is headquartered at the JOSH-A Base in Alaska. At the beginning of C.E. 71 its other major strongholds include the Kaohsiung spaceport in Taiwan, the Panama spaceport in Central America, the Victoria spaceport in eastern Africa, and the Ptolemaeus Lunar Base. After the destruction of JOSH-A and the Ptolemaeus Base in the first war, their functions are transferred to Heavens Base in Iceland and the Arzachel Lunar Base.</description>
<picture>1777.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="1547" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">5.99</rating>
<name>O.M.N.I. Enforcer</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The formal name of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance`s] military forces, which are more commonly referred to as the Earth Alliance Forces, or simply Earth Forces.</description>
<picture>16082.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1554" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="22">3.23</rating>
<name>PLANT Supreme Council</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The executive committee which governs the PLANTs and controls the ZAFT forces. The dozen members of this supreme council serve as elected representatives of the twelve sectors, or "cities," into which the PLANTs are grouped. The council itself meets at Aprilius One, the administrative capital of the PLANTs.
Each member of the council is assigned to one of its five specialized committees - Administrative, Diplomatic, Judicial, Legislative, or National Defense. Each of these committees has its own chairman, and the overall council is chaired by a Supreme Council chairman. The council is also divided along political lines, with a roughly even split between radicals who seek to escalate the war, and moderates who hope to end the conflict through negotiation.</description>
<picture>16231.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1571" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="24">4.99</rating>
<name>PLANT</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A new type of space settlement, created chiefly by Coordinators. Roughly 120 of these constructs are gathered at Lagrange point 5, a gravitationally stable area in Earth orbit, and these settlements have become a new homeland for Coordinators fleeing the persecution they experienced on Earth. As their name suggests, the PLANTs were created to serve as research and manufacturing sites, but their unique design also enables them to recreate a lush natural environment, with abundant vegetation and open water.
These hourglass-style structures consist of two disc-shaped living areas, each ten kilometers in diameter, which rotate around a central hub to produce artificial gravity. Each living area is anchored to the hub by a 30-kilometer central shaft and a network of high-tension strings, and a high-speed elevator runs up the central shaft to provide access to the hub. A set of external mirrors, attached to the central hub, are used to reflect sunlight into the inner surfaces of the living areas.
The PLANTs are grouped into twelve sectors, or "cities," each with its own scientific or industrial speciality. These cities are named after the months of the Roman calendar, and each is made up of roughly ten individual PLANT settlements, which are referred to as Januarius One, Januarius Two, and so forth.
The construction of the PLANTs began in C.E. 38, with funding supplied by the Atlantic Federation, the Eurasian Federation, and the Republic of East Asia. The PLANT settlements were initially managed by a directorate controlled by these sponsor nations, but in C.E. 53 their inhabitants formed a http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] to represent them in their dealings with the directorate. With the start of open hostilities between the PLANTs and the Earth Alliance in C.E. 70, the PLANTs effectively became an independent nation, governed solely by the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [Supreme Council].
After the first war between Earth and the PLANTs, the citizens of the PLANTs adopt a new name for their space settlements to reflect their independent status, and this acronym is redefined to mean People Liberation Acting Nation of Technology.</description>
<picture>1778.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="1576" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Morgenroete Incorporated</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A semi-nationalized munitions company based in the http://anidb.net/ch1501 [Orb Union], which also maintains facilities at the resource satellite Heliopolis. Although its primary clients are the armed forces of the neutral nation Orb, Morgenroete has been secretly collaborating with the Atlantic Federation on its Gundam development project and on the construction of the warship Archangel. On January 20, C.E. 71, five prototype Gundam mobile suits are rolled out at the company`s Heliopolis factory, and five days later the facility is attacked by http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] commandos, drawing http://anidb.net/ch1 [Kira Yamato] and his friends into the conflict.
Beam weapons, second-generation mobile suit operating systems, the Lohengrin positron blaster cannon (later adapted by ZAFT as the Tannhäuser installed in the bow of the assault ship Minerva), Variable Phase Shift Armor and the Mirage Colloid cloaking device were all developed at Morgenroete either entirely or in part during the war or immediately after, partly under the aegis of chief designer Erica Simmons. More esoteric technologies were also developed at Morgenroete under the aegis of the Sahaku twins, including energy-draining weaponry.</description>
</character>
<character id="1578" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="7">1.03</rating>
<name>Logos</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The secret society that controls Blue Cosmos. Logos is made up of a handful of powerful industrialists and defense contractors who see war as a business, and manipulate world events to profit from the misery it creates. Using agents such as Blue Cosmos and Phantom Pain, Logos works from behind the scenes to create conflict and fan the flames of war. Lord Djibril, the current leader of Blue Cosmos, is among the members of this organization.</description>
</character>
<character id="1579" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="22">1.25</rating>
<name>Blue Cosmos</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The most radical of the anti-Coordinator activist groups formed by resentful Naturals. According to the Blue Cosmos ideology, genetic modification is a violation of the natural order, and all Coordinators must be exterminated "for the preservation of our blue and pure world."
Blue Cosmos was originally an environmental pressure group, but after the revelation of George Glenn`s secret in C.E. 15, the organization launched a campaign of terror and assassination against Coordinators and the medical professionals who were working to create them. It is believed that the group is supported by the Azrael Conglomerate, a powerful industrial concern which is one of the Atlantic Federation`s major military contractors.
After the first war between Earth and the PLANTs, Lord Djibril becomes the new leader of Blue Cosmos, and the organization continues to create conflict between Naturals and Coordinators.</description>
</character>
<character id="1581" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">1.03</rating>
<name>Phantom Pain</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The nickname of the Earth Alliance`s 81st Autonomous Mobile Group, which carries out the attack on Armory One. Although this elite special forces organization is made up of http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] personnel and equipment, it is actually an irregular unit under the direct control of the http://anidb.net/ch1578 [Logos] secret society. Phantom Pain has the authority to borrow resources from the regular http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] forces as it sees fit, and it employs forbidden technology such as Mirage Colloid stealth systems despite the restrictions of the Junius Treaty.</description>
</character>
<character id="1594" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Atlantic Federation</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>This nation is the dominant power in the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance], and the creator of the http://anidb.net/ch1507 [Archangel] and the prototype Gundams. Before the war, the Atlantic Federation was the most influential of the sponsor nations which funded the construction of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and then forced their Coordinator inhabitants into economic bondage. When the leadership of the United Nations was wiped out by a terror attack at the lunar city of Copernicus, the Atlantic Federation took the lead in organizing the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] and issuing a declaration of war against the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs].
The Atlantic Federation was originally formed from the nations of Britain and North America. At the beginning of the first war it expanded its territory by annexing the http://anidb.net/ch1601 [United States of South America], but this conquest is eventually undone when the Junius Treaty restores South America`s independence.
During the first war the Atlantic Federation`s major military base, the JOSH-A facility in Alaska, doubles as the headquarters of the Earth Alliance forces. After the destruction of JOSH-A, its functions are transferred to Heavens Base in Iceland.</description>
</character>
<character id="1595" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Eurasian Federation</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of the leading powers within the Earth Alliance, this nation is a longtime rival, and now uneasy ally, of the Atlantic Federation. Originally formed from the nations of Europe and northern Asia, the Eurasian Federation is governed by a federal council dominated by the nations of the European region. Among its strategic assets is the space fortress Artemis, located at Lagrange point 3.
When a new war breaks out between Earth and the PLANTs, the Eurasian Federation once again sides with the Atlantic Federation. Meanwhile, its citizens become increasingly vocal in their demands for independence. As the war continues, ZAFT forces begin to intervene on behalf of these independence movements, liberating their homes and cities from Eurasian Federation control.</description>
</character>
<character id="1598" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Republic of East Asia</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The third major power within the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. Along with the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation] and http://anidb.net/ch1595 [Eurasian Federation], the Republic of East Asia was one of the primary sponsors of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANT] construction project. Though its political influence is no match for that of the Alliance`s leading powers, its large population gives it a high industrial production capacity. Originally made up of the modern-day nations of China, Japan, and Korea, the Republic of East Asia encompasses much of the Asian region.</description>
</character>
<character id="1600" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>South African Union</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The fourth member of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] is a collective formed by the nations of southern Africa. Unlike the Alliance`s other member nations, the South African Union was not a sponsor of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANT] construction project, and thus has no economic stake in the conflict. Instead, its participation in the war appears to have been motivated by its antagonism towards the PLANT-aligned African Community. However, the South African Union has fared badly in the fighting, and is now in the process of dropping out.</description>
</character>
<character id="1601" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>United States of South America</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A nation which formerly controlled much of Central and South America, and collaborated with the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation] in the construction of the Porta Panama mass driver. Before the outbreak of war, the United States of South America had aligned itself with the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and made arrangements to covertly exchange shipments of food and manufactured goods, and it refused to join the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance] once open hostilities began. On February 19, C.E. 70, Alliance forces launched an armed invasion of this nation, and its territory was annexed by the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation]. However, its independence is restored with the conclusion of the Junius Treaty on March 10, C.E. 72.</description>
</character>
<character id="1603" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>African Community</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An economic and military cooperative formed by the nations of the northern half of the African continent. Friendly to the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and hostile to the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance], the African Community is now effectively http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] territory. Nonetheless, a handful of local resistance groups, like the Desert Dawn group based in the Libyan desert, continue to fight a guerilla war against the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] occupation.</description>
</character>
<character id="1605" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">3.43</rating>
<name>Oceania Union</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A union whose territory encompasses the Australian continent and its neighboring nations. Since it wasn`t one of the sponsor nations that profited from the economic exploitation of the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs], the Oceania Union was quick to ally itself with them as tensions increased between the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] and their terrestrial sponsors. In C.E. 68 the Oceania Union agreed to covertly exchange shipments of food and manufactured goods with the PLANTs, and on February 20, C.E. 70, it formally declared its support for the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] in their struggle against the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. The Oceania Union went on to host the Carpentaria Base, http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT`s] first terrestrial stronghold.</description>
</character>
<character id="1649" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="19">1.32</rating>
<name>Muruta Azrael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fanatical leader of the secret society http://anidb.net/ch1579 [Blue Cosmos], which seeks to exterminate all Coordinators. Azrael is also the president of a major weapons manufacturing conglomerate and a director of the Defense Industry Association, and as a result he has great influence over the leadership of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. After he convinces the Alliance to attack the neutral http://anidb.net/ch1501 [Orb Union], Azrael then accompanies the invasion force to supervise the operation and observe his newest weapons in action.</description>
<picture>16191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1659" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-24">
<rating votes="19">1.29</rating>
<name>Lord Djibril</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The new leader of http://anidb.net/ch1579 [Blue Cosmos], and a member of the secret society of military industrialists known as http://anidb.net/ch1578 [Logos]. Djibril and his fellow Logos members manipulate world affairs from behind the scenes using the nations of the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance], and in particular the http://anidb.net/ch1594 [Atlantic Federation], as their puppets. After the fall of Junius Seven, Djibril seizes on this disaster as a pretext for war against the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs], but his burning hatred for Coordinators drives him to escalate the conflict faster than even his fellow Logos members are comfortable with.</description>
<picture>52586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1673" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="5">1.03</rating>
<name>Bruno Azrael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of http://anidb.net/ch1578 [Logos] and a possible relative of http://anidb.net/ch1649 [Muruta Azrael].</description>
</character>
<character id="1679" type="appears in" update="2014-09-28">
<rating votes="6">3.43</rating>
<name>FAITH</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>FAITH is a http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] special forces organization whose members report directly to the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council]. The members of this elite organization operate outside the regular ZAFT command structure, and have the authority to plan operations and give orders on the battlefield as they see fit. FAITH membership is awarded only to individuals with distinguished combat records and excellent personal qualities.</description>
<picture>16221.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1680" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="11">5.25</rating>
<name>Clyne Faction</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>After the theft of the http://anidb.net/ch1489 [Freedom Gundam], former http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] chairman Siegel Clyne is branded a traitor. Clyne and his followers become fugitives, waging an underground campaign of resistance to the radical leadership of Patrick Zala. The Clyne Faction carries on the fight even after Siegel himself is gunned down, working within the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs] to thwart Patrick Zala`s plans.
http://anidb.net/ch302 [Lacus Clyne] takes over the command of Clyne Faction after the death of her father.</description>
</character>
<character id="1686" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="11">6.05</rating>
<name>Siegel Clyne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chairman of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] that governs the Coordinator homeland. Although Clyne once worked side by side with Patrick Zala to create http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] and win independence for the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs], over the years the two have become political rivals, and Clyne now leads a moderate faction of the Supreme Council which seeks to end the war through peaceful negotiation. Clyne represents the PLANTs of Aprilius City, which specialize in space sciences, and is the father of pop star http://anidb.net/ch302 [Lacus Clyne].</description>
<picture>16230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1692" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">1.54</rating>
<name>Patrick Zala</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council] who serves as chairman of its National Defense Committee, and is thus the commander in chief of the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces. Having lost his wife Lenore in the Bloody Valentine tragedy, Zala is intent on revenge against the Naturals, and he is the leader of a radical faction of the Supreme Council which seeks to escalate the war against the http://anidb.net/ch1542 [Earth Alliance]. Zala represents the PLANTs of December City, where the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces are headquartered, and is the father of http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] soldier http://anidb.net/ch300 [Athrun Zala].</description>
<picture>16242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1693" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="32">2.23</rating>
<name>Gilbert Durandal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The latest chairman of the http://anidb.net/ch1554 [PLANT Supreme Council]. Durandal is a leading member of the moderate faction of the PLANT leadership, and he hopes to carry on the legacy of the late http://anidb.net/ch1686 [Siegel Clyne] and achieve reconciliation with the Naturals. But even as he seeks peace through diplomacy and negotiation, Durandal continues to develop and manufacture new weapons, and as the new conflict escalates he resorts to deceptive means to manipulate public opinion in the http://anidb.net/ch1571 [PLANTs].</description>
<picture>52574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1699" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="10">5.25</rating>
<name>Ake no Sabaku</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A resistance group based in northern Africa, in modern-day Libya, which fights against the http://anidb.net/ch1509 [ZAFT] forces who have effectively taken control of the http://anidb.net/ch1603 [African Community]. The group is led by the grizzled guerilla fighter http://anidb.net/ch1700 [Sahib Ashman], and its members are recruited from local towns like Tassil and Moula, as well as the city of Banadiya.</description>
</character>
<character id="8625" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="25">2.86</rating>
<name>Rey Za Burrel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rey is a quiet, calm, and polite soldier who keeps himself out of other people`s way, he gladly follows his orders no matter what they might be. He is also extremely loyal to the Chairman of the PLANTs Gilbert Durandal, Rey is also shown to have a past with the mysterious Rau Le Creuset.
- Wikipedia -</description>
<picture>52569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8626" type="main character in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="54">1.29</rating>
<name>Shinn Asuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An emotionally troubled member of the ZAFT who moved to the Plants from the neutral nation of Orb after he lost his family in an Earth Alliance attack.
- Wikipedia -</description>
<picture>52564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8627" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="19">3.44</rating>
<name>Meer Campbell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8628" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="42">6.08</rating>
<name>Lunamaria Hawke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lunamaria Hawke is a mobile suit pilot for the ZAFT military forces.</description>
<picture>52570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8630" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="22">6.72</rating>
<name>Meyrin Hawke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lunamaria`s younger sister and CIC officer for the Minerva. Deeper into GSD, she later jumps ship to the Lacus Faction and becomes CIC for the Eternal.
Towards the end of GSD and during Final Plus, she acts as a love interest towards Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>52576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8631" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="27">3.68</rating>
<name>Stellar Loussier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is one of the Earth Forces Extendeds (enhanced through drugs and surgery) and has two personalities: an innocent and angry side. Her memories have been erased in order to fight battles without any emotion. Because of her modifications without being genetically altered, she quickly changes from being calm and happy, to fuming and violent. Her worst fear is dying and has an emotional breakdown whenever someone mentions death near her.</description>
<picture>52583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9127" type="appears in" update="2018-10-04">
<rating votes="170">4.75</rating>
<name>Haro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haro is the mechanical mascot of the Gundam science fiction anime metaseries, and is the only character that appears in more than one timeline.
The original Haro is a little robot companion built by the main character Amuro Ray. It is a cute testament to Amuro`s exceptional talent for machines. Haro`s features include a limited range of speech, and the ability to hover (in environments with atmosphere and low gravity) by flapping its ear-like appendage coverings. Haro can usually be found rolling behind Amuro`s next door neighbor Frau Bow. The ability to detect brain waves is also one of Haro`s functions; in one of the episodes, Haro actually claimed that the brain wave of Amuro was lowered/different.
In Zeta Gundam, a mass-produced Mk-II version of Haro ends up in the hands of that series` main protagonist Kamille Bidan, who initially suspects it to be the original. He repairs the robot, only to have it constantly address him as Amuro.
During the events of Char`s Counterattack, Amuro gives a "third-generation" Haro to Hathaway, the son of his captain Bright Noa.
Haro continues to permeate the Gundam franchise, having appeared in Gundam SEED as Lacus Clyne`s multi-colored horde of simple-speech robot pets, built for her by Athrun Zala. These Haros are roughly 1/4 the size of their Universal Century counterparts and are similar in function, however a few possess certain abilities such as unlocking doors. Lacus`s favorite Haro is a pink machine that she refers to as "Pink-Chan" (often translated as "Mr. Pink" or "Pinky"). Another notable Haro in Lacus`s collection is "Navy-Chan", a navy blue robot on which she paints a mustache bearing a distinct resemblance the facial ornament of the ∀ Gundam of the CC (正歴 Seireki) calendar system. The rest of Lacus` Haros have been seen in yellow, orange, blue, green, and black. The parody comic Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Club Yonkoma states that Athrun has built a total of 35 Haros for Lacus.
In Mobile Suit Gundam 00, Celestial Being had produced unknown numbers of Haros as an assistant of daily maintenance works. Currently at least 6 unique Haros have appeared in the animation production. The Haros in the series took much more maintenance and combat role than any other series` counterpart, usually seeing them operating with various machines, including mobile weapons.</description>
<picture>28615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12914" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="110">8.35</rating>
<name>Mu La Flaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A famous ace pilot of the Earth Alliance, who brings his Moebius Zero mobile armor aboard the Archangel after his original mothership is destroyed. Mu earned the nickname "Hawk of Endymion" by singlehandedly shooting down five ZAFT mobile suits in one of the war`s early battles. Aside from his piloting skills, tactical abilities, and extensive combat experience, Mu`s greatest contribution to the Archangel is probably the morale boost provided by his relaxed and lighthearted personality.</description>
<picture>2799.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14305" type="appears in" update="2012-07-28">
<rating votes="33">7.77</rating>
<name>Rau Le Creuset</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rau Le Creuset is the Commander as well as a natural who constantly has to take drugs in order to help with the defects in his DNA that casues him to age rapily. He seems to be an extremely intelligent leader, but also believes that because ZAFT and Earth Alliance want to fight, they should be able to do so. In addition, Rau Le Creuset is also clone of his father, Al Da Flaga.He never appears in public without his distinctive face mask, and his actual appearance - like the nature of his apparent rapport with Earth Alliance ace Mu La Flaga - thus far remains a secret.
Created illegally as a Coordinator by Al Da Flaga while also carrying the NewType gene from his father, he is the son of Al Da Flaga, who had named him as his son over Mu La Flaga. Due to unfortunate circumstances, their house burned down and Rau Le Creuset became enlisted in the ZAFT military because of his relations to Patrick Zala. Rau Le Creuset has a bit of an aging problem that causes him to grow up and develop at a faster rate than everyone else, which is why he must take blue and white pills in order to slow down his aging process. In the ZAFT military, Rau Le Creuset becomes the commander of one of the most greatest teams of ZAFT, the Le Creuset Team, which is sometimes envied by others for their skill as they have ZAFT`s topguns in their ranks .He is a ruthless and enigmatic commander of the elite ZAFT team that attacks Heliopolis and then relentlessly pursues the Archangel. Raw Le Creuset also plays a key role in the ZAFT Military as he reports directly to Patrick Zala since Partrick`s son Athrun Zala is in his team.
While he has a somewhat a good personality on the outside, it acts like more of a veil that covers up his true intentions, which are somewhat psychotic. He desires world peace and realizes the situation between the Earth Alliance and ZAFT as they both want to destroy each other. Thus, what he believes, is that he should help them achieve that by any means necessary similar to the modern age and nuclear missiles. Once again, despite his craziness, he is very refined and reasonable on the outside in making orders.
He is extremely skilled at piloting any mobile suit or Gundam of any type and a very good strategist. He makes long term plans for his peacemaking operation throughout a large span of time, and manages to pull them off.</description>
<picture>41814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17721" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="22">6.84</rating>
<name>Yzak Joule</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Le Creuset team which raids Heliopolis, who becomes the pilot of the captured Duel Gundam. A second-generation Coordinator whose mother sits on the PLANT Supreme Council, Yzak is fiercely proud of his elite status, and regards his teammate Athrun Zala as his chief rival. After clashing with the Strike Gundam, Yzak becomes even more intent on defeating the Archangel and its resident mobile suit, and the injuries he sustains in battle serve to further fuel his hatred.
In Gundam SEED Destiny:
The former Duel Gundam pilot now leads the Joule Team and wears the white uniform of a ZAFT commander. As the new conflict escalates, Yzak participates in the Junius Seven demolition operation and helps defend the PLANT homeland from the vengeful Earth Alliance.</description>
<picture>3266.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19525" type="appears in" update="2010-07-12">
<rating votes="10">5.39</rating>
<name>Shiho Hahnenfuss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Coordinator; wears the red uniform of the ZAFT ace pilots; she researches the beam weapon systems on the new CGUE Deep Arms because there are many problems and with help from Yzak she is able to complete the mobile suit; nicknamed the "Housenka" (Balsam) by Yzak Joule because of her combat skills (since beams are shooting out in all directions like a blossoming flower), and she wears the balsam as her personal mark; pilots the ZGMF-515 CGUE and YFX-200 CGUE DEEP Arms. Assigned to the Joule Squadron before the end of the Bloody Valentine War, she participates in the Second Battle of Jachin Due and has fought against Earth Alliance force`s female ace pilot "Sakura Burst" Rena Imelia. After the war when Yzak became the youngest member of the Supreme Council,[citation needed] Shiho leaves the Joule squad briefly to fight in the independence war of the U.S.S.A.; after Yzak returns to the frontline Shiho rejoins the Joule squad and pilots a custom ZGMF-1000/M Blaze ZAKU Warrior. She seems to have romantic feelings towards Yzak, but he does not notice them.
Shiho appears in a crowd or background shots in Gundam SEED and Gundam SEED Destiny, but has no dialogue; however, she is voiced by http://anidb.net/cr3969 [Oomoto Makiko] in related video games.</description>
<picture>51092.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20055" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="7">5.51</rating>
<name>Heine Westenfluss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heine Westenfluss is a Coordinator ZAFT pilot, who piloted a ZGMF-1001 Blaze ZAKU Phantom before becoming the pilot of the ZGMF-X2000 GOUF Ignited. His last name, Westenfluss, is German for west river.
Heine joined ZAFT on February 21, CE 68 and was considered an ace pilot. In addition to wearing a red uniform, given to pilots who had graduated at the top of their class, he also wore FAITH insignia, indicating his membership in that unit; as a result, he reported directly to Chairman Gilbert Durandal. Prior to the events of Gundam SEED Destiny, Heine fought in the Bloody Valentine War (in particular the Second Battle of Jachin Due) as a pilot for the Hawkins team, piloting the YFX-600R GuAIZ Experimental Firearms Type and battling against Earth Alliance ace Morgan Chevalier.</description>
<picture>52045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4926" picture="25983.jpg">Nishikawa Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20346" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<name>Todaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A veteran officer of the Orb naval forces. When the Earth Alliance invaded Orb during the previous war, Todaka rescued the orphaned Shinn and helped him emigrate to the PLANTs. Although he disapproves of his nation`s current policies, Todaka is resigned to carrying out his orders no matter what.</description>
<picture>52563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20347" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Yolant Kent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20348" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Vino Dupre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5029" picture="186201.jpg">Oda Hisafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20349" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Madd Aves</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20350" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="5">6.30</rating>
<name>Talia Gladys</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the newly constructed ZAFT warship Minerva. Talia has superb tactical judgement and the ability to adapt quickly to unexpected battle situations, and her leadership skills enable her to get the most out of her young and inexperienced crew. Although she has a romantic history with Chairman Durandal, Talia`s keen insight sometimes leads her to question his current decisions.</description>
<picture>52571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20351" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="3">2.90</rating>
<name>Arthur Trine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The deputy captain of the Minerva, who serves as Talia`s aide. Arthur lacks his captain`s experience and tactical ability, and he is often bewildered by her seemingly reckless decisions. Nonetheless, he is friendly and reliable, and has a good rapport with Shinn and the other pilots.</description>
<picture>52572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20352" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Chen Jian Yi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="84" picture="16692.jpg">Tai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20353" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Malik Yardbirds</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20354" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Burt Heim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20355" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-30">
<rating votes="21">5.43</rating>
<name>Dearka Elsman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dearka Elsman is an arrogant pilot of ZAFT`s Rau Le Creuset team who looks down on Naturals. He was part of the crew that invaded Heliopolis to steal mobile suits and piloted the GAT-X103 Buster. During the course of the series, Dearka is captured by the Archangel where he meets Kira`s friends which prompt him to change his opinions about Naturals. Seeing how both the Earth Alliance and ZAFT had become controlled by genocidal individuals such as Muruta Azrael and Patrick Zala, Dearka retakes his Buster and fights alongside the Archangel. During the SEED series, Dearka begins a relationship with Miriallia Haw which ends shortly after. In Gundam SEED Destiny, Dearka is shown in a regular ZAFT soldier uniform. His seiyu is Akira Sasanuma and his English voice actor is Brad Swaile.</description>
<picture>52581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2889" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="2936" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20356" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="4">6.34</rating>
<name>Neo Roanoke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20357" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="4">3.67</rating>
<name>Sting Oakley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sting, along with Auel Neider and Stella Loussier, are the three Extended pilots of the Earth Alliance`s special forces team, called Phantom Pain. Together with his comrades he sneaks into the PLANT colony Armory One, where he steals one of the three new Gundam-type mobile suits, the ZGMF-X24S Chaos.</description>
<picture>52584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20358" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="6">1.65</rating>
<name>Auel Neider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Auel, along with Sting Oakley and Stella Loussier, are the three Extended pilots of the Earth Alliance`s special forces team Phantom Pain. He is the most impulsive and brutal of the three, killing his enemies mercilessly and even laughing crazily when he kills people. Together with his comrades, he sneaks into the PLANT colony Armory One, where he steals one of the three new Gundam-type mobile suits, the ZGMF-X31S Abyss. He uses the heavily armed suit to wreak havoc inside the colony, killing many ZAFT soldiers.</description>
<picture>52585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20359" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="1">1.03</rating>
<name>Ian Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the newly constructed Earth Alliance warship Girty Lue, which serves as Phantom Pain`s mothership during the attack on Armory One. Ian is a capable officer who can be relied upon to carry out his duties.</description>
<picture>52587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20360" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>Joseph Copeland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20361" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<name>Yuna Roma Seiran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Orb`s prime minister Unato, and the heir to the powerful Seiran family. The devious Yuna shares his father`s political agenda, and he hopes to marry Cagalli in order to consolidate his family`s control over the Orb Union.</description>
<picture>52591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20363" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="1">1.03</rating>
<name>Unato Ema Seiran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The prime minister of the Orb Union, and the father of Yuna. Thanks to his political skills and the high status of the Seiran family, Unato has little difficulty outmaneuvering his nation`s nominal leader, the idealistic but inexperienced Cagalli. As the new conflict begins, Unato uses his considerable influence to ensure that Orb aligns itself with the Earth Alliance.</description>
<picture>52593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20364" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-07">
<rating votes="35">8.43</rating>
<name>Andrew Waltfeld</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Andrew "Andy" Waltfeld was the commander of the ZAFT forces in the PLANT-pledged African Community, headquartered at Banadiya. He lives with his lover Aisha who assists him in his military operations and eventually serves as the co-pilot of his TMF/A-803 LaGOWE. Unlike other ZAFT and Earth Alliance officers, he is surprisingly human and well aware of the repercussions of war. After forcing Kira Yamato to battle him in their gundams, Andrew and Aisha are seemingly killed in the explosion. Andrew is later seen alive having been saved by Aisha and losing his left eye, left arm and right leg in the process. He assists the Archangel`s goal in ending the war. His character draws heavily from http://anidb.net/ch77678 [Erwin Johannes Eugen Rommel], a WWII German field marshal known as the Desert Fox.</description>
<picture>52599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20365" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="20">4.69</rating>
<name>Miriallia Haw</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She lives in Heliopolis, a space colony in Orb where she is enrolled in the technical college with Kira, Sai, Flay, Tolle and Kuzzey. She is inseparable with her boyfriend Tolle, almost attached at the hip, but they do not show their affection in public. Her personality is mature and well rounded.</description>
<picture>52600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20366" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Joachim Radol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20367" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="4">3.99</rating>
<name>Conille Almeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young resistance fighter who hopes to liberate the Gulnahan region from the control of the Earth Alliance. Coniel meets with the Minerva to deliver vital data that will enable the ZAFT forces to destroy the enemy`s Lohengrin Gate.</description>
<picture>52602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="137" picture="214428.jpg">Sasamoto Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20368" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="3">3.77</rating>
<name>Amagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20369" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="7">4.13</rating>
<name>Kojiro Murdoch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chief mechanic of the Earth Alliance warship Archangel, whose small cadre of talented engineers keep the ship and its fighting vehicles in fine working order. Murdoch is gruff and informal, with a fatherly concern for the pilots who depend on his skills, and he always keeps an eye out for the young and inexperienced Kira.</description>
<picture>52604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20370" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="8">3.21</rating>
<name>Arnold Neumann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ranking non-commissioned officer of the Earth Alliance warship Archangel, and one of the few survivors of the ship`s original crew. After the attack on Heliopolis, Neumann takes over as the ship`s pilot. Quiet and professional, he`s usually overshadowed by his charismatic superiors, but when the Archangel is locked down at the space fortress Artemis he takes charge and breaks the ship free.</description>
<picture>52605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20371" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="7">3.87</rating>
<name>Dalida Lolaha Chandra II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10626" picture="38527.jpg">Toriumi Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20373" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<name>Malchio Shi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although he`s a Natural, this blind monk is trusted by both the Earth Alliance and the PLANTs, and thus serves as an envoy for their occasional attempts at peace negotiations. Malchio also maintains a home for war orphans in the Marshall Islands, where Kira Yamato finds shelter after his fateful battle with Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>52609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20374" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="4">4.78</rating>
<name>Abbey Windsor</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20375" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="8">4.26</rating>
<name>Ledonir Kisaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An officer of the 21st Airborne Unit of the Orb Union`s ground forces. Kisaka was born in the town of Tassil in northern Africa, and when Cagalli travels to northern Africa to fight alongside the Desert Dawn resistance group, Kisaka accompanies her as a bodyguard. Well aware that it`s pointless trying to keep Cagalli out of trouble, he calmly tags along wherever she goes, in the process making sure that she doesn`t inadvertently reveal her true identity.</description>
<picture>52611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20376" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="6">3.77</rating>
<name>Martin Dacosta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2936" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="2889" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20377" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="3">3.77</rating>
<name>Hilda Harken</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20378" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Herbert von Reinhardt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20379" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Mars Simeon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21323" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<name>Miguel Aiman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miguel Aiman is a ZAFT Mobile Suit pilot who was part of a three man unit. Miguel, Ollar and Matthew served as mentors to the Le Creuset team.</description>
<picture>55981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4926" picture="25983.jpg">Nishikawa Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22114" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="5">2.87</rating>
<name>Crot Buer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clotho Buer is a talkative and quarrelsome person who is constantly arguing with his teammates. While he fights in his GAT-X370 Raider, he enjoys shouting out video game-inspired battle cries. Between missions he spends his time playing on a portable game system called the "Great Wonder Swan XXX (unknown number)".</description>
<picture>55974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22116" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="71">1.86</rating>
<name>Flay Allster</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flay, the daughter of Atlantic Federation Vice Foreign Minister George Allster, is a pretty, popular, and to some extent spoiled, Heliopolis technical college student. Her fiancé is Sai Argyle, as arranged for by their parents. She has received a love letter from Sai, which was mentioned in episode 1 of Gundam SEED. The only one of his friends she seems familiar with is Miriallia Haw, with whom she shares idle gossip shortly before ZAFT attacks Heliopolis. She only knows Kira Yamato as "Sai`s friend". She escapes the destruction of Heliopolis in a lifeboat and winds up on the Archangel when Kira retrieves it while piloting the GAT-X105 Strike.</description>
<picture>55978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22117" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="25">7.64</rating>
<name>Natarle Badgiruel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natarle Badgiruel is the executive officer of the Archangel, and supervises the ship`s Combat Information Center. Natarle is stern and operates by the book, though she is willing to do almost anything to reach a certain end, even when it conflicts with Captain Ramius. Nevertheless, Natarle is a superb tactical analyst with keen judgment and a knack for swift decision-making, which made her a valuable asset to the Archangel. After Natarle leaves the Archangel on a transfer order while in Alaska, she is recruited by the Earth Alliance and made captain of the Dominion which forced her to battle against the Archangel. After witnessing the actions of Muruta Azrael of Blue Cosmos, Natarle chooses to defy the Earth Alliance which results in her and Azrael`s death</description>
<picture>55980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22118" type="appears in" update="2010-10-06">
<rating votes="17">6.26</rating>
<name>Nicol Amalfi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicol Amalfi is the youngest member of the Le Creuset team; he pilots the GAT-X207 Blitz, which he steals during the raid on Heliopolis. He is mostly calm and good-natured, and becomes friends with Athrun Zala. His thoughts of the war are moderate, and he says in one episode that he joined ZAFT after hearing what happened to Junius Seven, but never really wanted to fight. A gifted musician, his favorite instrument was the piano. While trying to protect Athrun in battle near the Orb Union, Nicol is accidentally killed by Kira Yamato. His seiyu are Mami Matsui for the series and Romi Park in all future appearances.</description>
<picture>55982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32416" picture="77711.jpg">Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22119" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">3.61</rating>
<name>Orga Sabnak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orga Sabnak is effectively the leader of the three biological CPUs. He uses tactics that are reckless and aggressive, causing him to often nearly hit his teammates while piloting his mobile suit, the GAT-X131 Calamity. He usually spends his time between missions reading paperback novels.[4] He is also the only member of the team to seem to care about the welfare of the other two; when Shani is killed, he screams out his teammate`s name, and tries to attack Yzak, his killer.
Unlike Clotho and Shani, who were killed by Yzak Joule, Orga was killed during the Second Battle of Jachin Due by Three Ships Alliance pilot Athrun Zala in the ZGMF-X09A Justice equipped with the METEOR. Athrun slices Orga in half from behind as he is dodging a beam from Kira.
From flashback sequences in Gundam SEED Destiny, Shinn Asuka`s family is killed by an explosion resulting from a crossfire between Orga`s GAT-X131 Calamity, and the ZGMF-X10A Freedom. It is never made clear which mobile suit, if not both of them, is the direct cause of their deaths.</description>
<picture>55983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30372" picture="79530.jpg">Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22122" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="8">4.52</rating>
<name>Tolle Koenig</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tolle is another one of Kira Yamato`s friends who also lives on the neutral colony Heliopolis and the boyfriend of Miriallia Haw. Tolle was the first one to defend Kira, when Kira`s Coordinator heritage causes the Archangel`s soldiers to point their rifles at Kira. He serves as a co-pilot and operator of the Archangel. Later, he volunteers to pilot the second FX-550 Skygrasper, formerly piloted by Cagalli Yula Athha. He is ultimately killed in action by Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>55987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6890">Inoue Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22136" type="appears in" update="2010-10-07">
<rating votes="5">4.81</rating>
<name>Kuzzey Buskirk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22138" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="6">5.13</rating>
<name>Sai Argyle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sai is another friend of Kira Yamato from Heliopolis. When the colony is raided by ZAFT, he ends up with his friends on the Archangel. Sai is put in charge of enemy detection and electronic warfare identification on the CIC of the Archangel. Initially, Sai was in a relationship with Flay Allster but she breaks it off in favor of Kira, which enrages Sai to the point where he tries to move the Strike. Despite his humiliation, Sai does not try to win back Flay and comes to accept that she is with Kira, who is later reported MIA. With Kira gone, Flay attempts to restart her relationship with Sai, denying she ever felt any emotions for Kira but Sai refuses to believe her. Later, Flay is transferred from the Archangel before Operation Spit Break while Sai and the rest of the crew defect to Orb after they are saved by Kira in the stolen ZGMF-X10A Freedom. Sai makes peace with Kira, and the two of them remain on good terms for the remainder of their enlistment together. Sai continues to serve at his post on the Archangel throughout the rest of the war. During that time, he realizes Flay still cares for him in some respects when she calls his name specifically while trying to communicate with the Archangel, and he is deeply saddened when Flay dies at the hands of Rau Le Creuset. A short OVA set after the series shows him going back to a civilian life, one that apparently involves computers. He still keeps pictures of himself with Flay, despite their tumultuous history, and seems content with this new life.</description>
<picture>56032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22139" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">7.09</rating>
<name>Uzumi Nara Athha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uzumi Nara Athha, is the leader of the United Emirates of Orb and the adoptive father of Cagalli Yula Athha. He is known to be dedicated to the well-being of his nation and uncompromising on his own ideals and the ideals of Orb. When the Earth Alliance invades Orb to acquire their mass driver, Uzumi reveals to Cagalli that Kira Yamato is her brother and forces her to leave Orb before he self detonates it to prevent the Earth Alliance from using their equipment for war.</description>
<picture>56033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22145" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>FX-550 Skygrasper</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>A specialized fighter aircraft created to support the Strike Gundam. The Skygrasper is designed to carry Striker packs out into the battlefield so that the Strike can replace its equipment in mid-battle, and the fighter itself can also use the Striker packs` weapons in combat. The Skygrasper`s built-in weaponry includes a powerful beam cannon and a pair of heavy machine guns, as well as weapons bays for storing bombs and missiles. Two Skygraspers are transferred to the Archangel when it joins with the Earth Alliance`s 8th Fleet, and after the ship descends to Earth, Mu La Flaga begins using one of these atmospheric fighters in place of his Moebius Zero mobile armour.</description>
<picture>56039.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22150" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="4">4.06</rating>
<name>Agamemnon-kyuu Uchuu Bokan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>This 300-meter warship is designed primarily as a carrier, and it can rapidly deploy large numbers of mobile armors using its two linear catapults. Warships of the Agamemnon class, like Admiral Halberton`s Menelaos, often serve as flagships for the Earth Alliance`s space fleets.</description>
<picture>56044.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22156" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<name>METEOR</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Mobile suit Embedded Tactical EnfORcer, or METEOR, is an armed module designed to support the Freedom Gundam and Justice Gundam. These METEOR units serve as gun turrets while attached to the hull of the warship Eternal, and when detached they can dock with a Gundam and draw energy from its nuclear engine. The METEOR is equipped with powerful thrusters for high-speed flight, and its beam cannons, missile launchers, and beam swords give it the firepower of a space warship. Since the Freedom and Justice have the ability to lock onto multiple targets, they can use the METEOR`s battery of long-range weapons to intercept dozens of enemies simultaneously.</description>
<picture>56050.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22184" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.05</rating>
<name>ZGMF-1017 GINN</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The first combat mobile suit developed by ZAFT, and the backbone of its military forces. The fighting strength of the GINN is equivalent to that of five Earth Alliance mobile armours, and can singlehandedly destroy an Alliance escort ship. Although the GINN is classified as a Zero Gravity Maneuver Fighter, it can operate on Earth as well, and this versatile machine can be adapted to a wide range of mission roles and combat environments. Its standard armament consists of a machine gun and a blade for slicing apart enemy mobile armours, but the GINN can also be outfitted with a variety of heavy weapons and guided missiles.</description>
<picture>56137.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22191" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">6.99</rating>
<name>TMF/A-802 BuCUE</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This four-legged mobile suit is the main weapon of ZAFT`s ground forces. Its quadrupedal design makes the BuCUE very stable even in difficult terrain like deserts and snowfields, and its legs are equipped with caterpillar tracks for high-speed movement in these environments. The turret hardpoint on its back can carry either powerful railguns or a large missile pod, and after the Earth Alliance`s prototype Gundams fall into ZAFT`s hands, many BuCUE units are fitted with head-mounted beam sabers based on the technology of these captured Gundams.</description>
<picture>56144.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22193" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">6.23</rating>
<name>FFMH-Y101 Eternal</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>A new ZAFT warship, created to support the nuclear-powered Freedom and Justice Gundams, which is equipped with special facilities for maintaining these unique mobile suits. In addition to a pair of METEOR units, which function as gun turrets while docked with the ship, the Eternal is armed with a single cannon turret and countless batteries of missile launchers. After it is stolen by Lacus Clyne and her followers, this ship joins forces with the Archangel and the Kusanagi to form the independent Three Ships Alliance.</description>
<picture>56146.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22194" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">2.55</rating>
<name>Nazca</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Nazca-class high-speed destroyer which serves as the flagship of the Le Creuset team. This is ZAFT`s newest model of warship, armed with powerful beam cannons and faster than even the Earth Alliance`s Archangel. Its central deck can house six mobile suits, and is equipped with a linear catapult for high-speed take-offs.</description>
<picture>56147.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22239" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.05</rating>
<name>MBF-02 Strike Rouge</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>After the Strike Gundam is destroyed in battle, it is salvaged and rebuilt by the engineers of Morgenroete, who later use the spare parts created during this repair process to construct a duplicate of the original mobile suit. The Strike Rouge is equipped with a power extender to increase its operating time, and as a result its colours are red-shifted when its Phase Shift Armor is activated. It also has an AI (Artificial Intelligence) support system to assist inexperienced pilots. The parts for the Strike Rouge are carried into space aboard the warship Kusanagi, and when the mobile suit is assembled it becomes Cagalli Yula Athha`s personal machine.</description>
<picture>56214.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22240" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">5.99</rating>
<name>MBF-M1 Astray</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The final production version of the Astray series, designed for use by the Orb Union`s national defence forces. The M1 Astray was developed by Morgenroete, using technology that the company obtained from its work on the Earth Alliance`s GAT-X series. Based on the prototype Gundam Astray, this machine has been redesigned for mass production, and is equipped with a backpack flight unit inspired by the Strike Gundam`s Aile Striker pack. The M1 is more than a match for the mass-produced mobile suits of ZAFT and the Earth Alliance, but its production and deployment have been delayed until its operating system can be adapted for use by Natural pilots.</description>
<picture>56215.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22241" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.06</rating>
<name>Orb Kaigun Aegis Kan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Aegis ships which guard the territorial waters of the Orb Union use a trimaran construction, in which the ship`s hull is divided into three sections. Armed with batteries of anti-air and anti-ship weapons, as well as three aircraft decks which can be used to deploy combat helicopters, these ships are capable of driving off even ZAFT mobile suits.</description>
<picture>56222.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22244" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X56S Impulse Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Impulse Gundam is a prototype mobile suit created by ZAFT as part of its Second Stage series. The Second Stage machines use a number of new technologies to deal with the restrictions of the Junius Treaty that ended the previous war, such as a deuterion beam transmission system that allows them to receive an instant energy recharge from their mothership. Because the treaty places strict limits on the number of mobile suits each side can maintain, the Impulse is designed to adapt to a wide range of combat situations by exchanging Silhouette packs, and the mobile suit itself is made up of three separate modules that can be launched and replaced individually. The young ZAFT pilot Shinn Asuka uses the tactical flexibility of this unique machine to tremendous effect.</description>
<picture>56227.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22245" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="4">7.08</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X23S Saviour Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Saviour Gundam is a prototype mobile suit created by ZAFT as part of its Second Stage series. This transformable machine is designed for aerial combat, and it can change into a mobile armor form to carry out high-speed hit-and-run attacks using its powerful beam cannons. Because its development has fallen behind that of the other Second Stage machines, the Saviour escapes capture at Armory One, and Chairman Durandal subsequently offers it to the former Justice Gundam pilot Athrun Zala.</description>
<picture>56228.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22246" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>ZGMF-1000 ZAKU Warrior</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The ZAKU Warrior, whose name stands for ZAFT Armed Keeper of Unity, is part of a new series of mass production mobile suits developed by ZAFT after the end of the previous war. The ZAKU was originally intended to use a nuclear engine, but after the conclusion of the Junius Treaty it was redesigned with a conventional battery system instead. Its overall performance is nonetheless very high, and it can adapt to a variety of combat situations using specialized Wizard backpacks. In the hands of an expert pilot, the ZAKU is a match even for the newest Gundam mobile suits.</description>
<picture>56231.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22247" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>ZGMF-601R GuAIZ R</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A minor update to the GuAIZ introduced in the last stages of the previous war. Its R designation stands for Reinforced. Instead of the extensional arrestors of the original version, the GuAIZ R is armed with a pair of railguns for greater medium-range firepower, and the dual beam claw in its shield has been replaced by a single beam saber. This upgraded machine served as the main mobile suit of the ZAFT forces until the introduction of the ZAKU series.</description>
<picture>56232.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22248" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<name>TFA-4DE GAZuOOT</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>An upgraded version of the ZuOOT used during the previous war. Although the GAZuOOT remains unsuitable for combat against enemy mobile suits, its increased firepower and improved fire control systems enable it to provide more effective fire support than the original version. Because the previous shoulder cannons have been replaced with beam cannons, its model number includes the designation DE for Directional Emission. The GAZuOOT also carries a set of large missiles, and its arms end in cannons instead of general-purpose manipulator hands.</description>
<picture>56234.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22249" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>UMF/SSO-3 ASH</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A new model of amphibious mobile suit used by ZAFT special forces, whose SSO designation stands for Support/Special Operations. The ASH is designed for covert operations rather than regular combat, and its arms are equipped with lethal close-combat weapons instead of normal manipulators. It can also change into a compact mobile armor form for underwater cruising.</description>
<picture>56235.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22250" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>AMA-953 BABI</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A new model of transformable mobile suit designed for aerial combat and classified as an Aerial Maneuver Attacker. Currently being deployed as a successor to the DINN, the BABI has far greater firepower than its predecessor. In mobile armor form, its high speed and the anti-air weapons installed in its wings make the BABI an effective interceptor, and in mobile suit form it can use the Ardor beam cannon in its chest to attack and destroy large ground targets.</description>
<picture>56236.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22271" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>ZGMF-2000 GOUF Ignited</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The GOUF Ignited, whose name stands for Guardian Of Unity Forerunner, was developed by ZAFT as a candidate for its next-generation mass production mobile suit. Although the ZAKU series was selected instead, the development of the GOUF continued due to its high performance, and a handful of prototype machines have been assigned to ace pilots such as Heine Westenfluss. The GOUF carries an arsenal of powerful close combat weapons, including a double-edged beam sword and retractable whips that inflict damage via high-frequency vibration, and the flight unit attached to its back gives it superb mobility and the ability to fly in Earth`s atmosphere.
The mass production model is coloured blue, some ace pilots have their suits in different colour schemes.</description>
<picture>56315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22272" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="1">8.95</rating>
<name>LHM-BB01 Minerva</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Minerva is the first new ZAFT warship constructed since the previous war. Designed for use with Second Stage series mobile suits, it is equipped with a deuterion beam transmitter that can instantly recharge these machines, as well as a complex system of hangars and catapults for launching the components of the Impulse Gundam. The Minerva is also a formidable warship in its own right thanks to its powerful weapons, high speed, and ability to enter the atmosphere and operate on Earth. Due to an attack on Armory One the day before its scheduled launching ceremony, the Minerva and its inexperienced crew soon find themselves on the front lines of a new conflict.</description>
<picture>56290.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22273" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="2">5.00</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X24S Chaos Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Chaos Gundam is a prototype mobile suit developed by ZAFT as part of its new Second Stage series. This transformable assault machine can change into a mobile armor form specialized for high-speed space combat, and armed with powerful beam cannons and beam claws. The Chaos is also equipped with a pair of mobile weapon pods similar to the DRAGOON system used in the previous war, and its improved control system allows these weapons to be used even by ordinary pilots. After the Chaos Gundam is captured during the attack on Armory One, it is assigned to Sting Oakley of the Phantom Pain special forces unit.</description>
<picture>56292.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22274" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="2">5.00</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X88S Gaia Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gaia Gundam is a prototype mobile suit developed by ZAFT as part of its new Second Stage series. Designed for close combat on land, it can change into a four-legged mobile armor form that resembles the BuCUE used during the previous war, and in this form it can use the beam blades installed in its attitude control wings to slice through enemy mobile suits. After the Gaia Gundam is captured during the attack on Armory One, it is assigned to Stella Loussier of the Phantom Pain special forces unit.</description>
<picture>56293.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22275" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<rating votes="3">3.53</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X31S Abyss Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Abyss Gundam is a prototype mobile suit developed by ZAFT as part of its new Second Stage series. Its mobile suit form has tremendous firepower thanks to its arsenal of beam weapons and shell-firing cannons, and it carries a lance equipped with both a beam blade and a physical blade, enabling this weapon to be used even underwater. It can also change into a mobile armor form for underwater combat, although in this form it relies mainly on its guided torpedo launchers. After the Abyss Gundam is captured during the attack on Armory One, it is assigned to Auel Neider of the Phantom Pain special forces unit.</description>
<picture>56295.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23163" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>GAT-02L2 Dagger L</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The standard mass production mobile suit of the Earth Alliance forces. The Dagger L is an improved version of the Dagger series introduced during the previous war, and it inherits the Strike Gundam`s ability to adapt to various combat situations using interchangeable Striker packs. On Earth, these machines are typically equipped with Jet Striker packs that render them capable of atmospheric flight. A black version known as the Dark Dagger L is also employed by special forces such as Phantom Pain.</description>
<picture>56497.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23164" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>GAT-04 Windam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A new model of mass production mobile suit created as a successor to the Dagger series. Like the Dagger L, the Windam can be adapted to various combat situations using interchangeable Striker packs, allowing the Earth Alliance to maintain its numerical advantage by using the same versatile machine in every battlefield. This machine uses the same beam sabers and Stiletto weapons as its predecessor, but carries a larger beam rifle and a new type of shield. After the Phantom Pain special forces unit is transferred to Earth, its commander Neo Roanoke enters combat using a Windam painted in his distinctive personal colors.</description>
<picture>56498.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23165" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<name>YMAF-X6BD Zamza-Zah</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Zamza-Zah is part of a new series of mobile armors developed for the Earth Alliance by Adukurf Mechano-Industries. This huge machine is operated by a three-person crew made up of a commander, a pilot, and a gunner. Armed with powerful guns and a set of claws that inflict damage via high-frequency vibration, the Zamza-Zah can perform attacks in any direction and at all ranges, and the positron reflector on its upper surface generates a protective barrier that can deflect even the Minerva`s Tannhauser cannon. The Earth Alliance deploys one of these machines to attack the Minerva during its escape from the Orb Union.</description>
<picture>56499.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23166" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>YMAG-X7F Gells-Ghe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gells-Ghe is part of a series of huge mobile armors developed for the Earth Alliance by Adukurf Mechano-Industries. Like the Zamza-Zah, it is equipped with a positron reflector capable of deflecting any enemy attack, and since this system is mounted on the front of its body the Gells-Ghe is ideal for defending fixed positions such as Gulnahan`s Lohengrin Gate. This unusual machine is also distinguished by its six insect-like legs and by the mobile suit torso, derived from the old Strike Dagger, that serves as its upper body. The Gells-Ghe is controlled by a three-person crew in the same fashion as the Zamza-Zah.</description>
<picture>56500.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23167" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>GFAS-X1 Destroy Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Destroy Gundam is less of a mobile suit than a mobile gun platform. What this hulking behemoth lacks in mobility, it makes up for with a massive arsenal designed for indiscriminate destruction. The Destroy is also equipped with the same positron reflector shield featured on the Zamza-zah and Gells-ghe, rendering most incoming enemy fire ineffective.
To punish Europe for sympathizing with ZAFT, LOGOS sends the first Destroy unit to Berlin, where it swats aside the ZAFT forces and lays waste to the city and its populace. By the time the Freedom is able to stop the Destroy`s rampage, this weapon of mass destruction has singlehandedly razed most of the city to the ground...</description>
<picture>56501.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23168" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>TS-MA4F Exus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The personal mobile armor of Phantom Pain commander Neo Roanoke. In addition to its linear guns and missile launchers, the Exus also carries a set of Gunbarrels based on the remote weapons used by the Moebius Zero. Its fighting strength is thus remarkably high, and it can battle several ZAFT mobile suits simultaneously. However, this mobile armor is designed exclusively for space combat and can`t be used in Earth`s atmosphere.</description>
<picture>56502.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23169" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="3">6.06</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X19A Infinite Justice Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>56503.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23170" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X666S Legend Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>56504.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23175" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Girty Lue</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The mysterious vessel that serves as Phantom Pain`s mothership during the attack on Armory One. The Girty Lue is equipped with a Mirage Colloid system that enables it to turn invisible, a technology which was supposedly outlawed by the Junius Treaty that ended the previous war, and although its design and armament resemble those of Earth Alliance warships this vessel appears to operate outside the bounds of the regular military. In addition to its Mirage Colloid capabilities, the Girty Lue can also be equipped with a stealth system that propels the ship with jets of gas in order to avoid detection by thermal sensors.</description>
<picture>56506.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23176" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Nelson class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An updated version of the 250-meter warship that serves as the main force of the Earth Alliance`s space fleets. The Nelson class is now capable of carrying mobile suits, and has been equipped with a pair of linear catapults to launch them into battle. Together with its high firepower and defensive strength, the ability to carry mobile suits makes the Nelson class an exceptionally well-balanced warship.</description>
<picture>56507.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23177" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Drake class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An updated version of the Earth Alliance`s 130-meter escort ship. Although it now has linear catapults for launching mobile suits, the carrying capacity of the Drake class is very limited, and it is used mainly to supplement the larger ships or to carry out reconnaissance missions.</description>
<picture>56508.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23178" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>MVF-M11C Murasame</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A next-generation mass production mobile suit used by the Orb Defense Forces. While the previous M1 Astray was designed mainly for land warfare, the Murasame can change into a fighter form for aerial combat and interception, and it boasts high performance in space as well. This all-purpose machine is more than a match for the latest ZAFT and Earth Alliance mobile suits, and serves as a testimonial to Orb`s advanced military technology. The veteran pilot Andrew Waltfeld has his own Murasame painted in distinctive personal colors.</description>
<picture>56509.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23179" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Takemikazuchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>This large aircraft carrier, commanded by the capable Captain Todaka, is the flagship of the Orb expeditionary fleet. The Takemikazuchi uses the same trimaran construction as Orb`s distinctive Aegis ships, and it can carry large numbers of mobile suits on its two-level deck. Its six catapults are used for launching Murasame mobile suits in fighter form, while its complement of M1 Astray Shrikes simply use their hovering capabilities to take off from the upper deck.</description>
<picture>56510.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23180" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<name>ORB-01 Akatsuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>56511.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34697" type="appears in" update="2011-07-16">
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<name>Erica Simmons</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9654" picture="49080.jpg">Yanagisawa Michiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41470" type="appears in" update="2012-02-19">
<rating votes="4">2.67</rating>
<name>Ulen Hibiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47095" type="appears in" update="2012-07-21">
<name>Satou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52463" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Ally</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52464" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Ikeya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2503" picture="186211.jpg">Mochizuki Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52465" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Willard</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52467" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Orson White</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52468" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<rating votes="4">3.95</rating>
<name>Karida Yamato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52469" type="appears in" update="2013-10-08">
<name>King Takeda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>King Takeda is a guest appearance of producer http://anidb.net/cr1516 [Takeda Seiji] in some minor http://anidb.net/a2186 [Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED Destiny] roles.</description>
<seiyuu id="1516" picture="19380.jpg">Takeda Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52470" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Christa Oberuku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52471" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>William Sutherland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52472" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Sarah</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52473" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Soga</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52474" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Takao Schreiber</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="6937" picture="171392.jpg">Imamura Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52475" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Tatsuki Mashima</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3157" picture="24155.jpg">Nishimatsu Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52476" type="appears in" update="2018-03-02">
<name>Toryi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52477" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Nishizawa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2871" picture="23214.jpg">Takahashi Yuugo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52478" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Noi Kazeefusuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52479" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Parnel Jesek</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2503" picture="186211.jpg">Mochizuki Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52480" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Hullburton</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52481" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Homura Athha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3315" picture="196861.jpg">Mizuuchi Kiyomitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52482" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Myrna</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52483" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Mayu Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52484" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Yop Von Arafas</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="16702" picture="45683.jpg">Yoshida Hisanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52485" type="appears in" update="2013-01-30">
<name>Ricardo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52486" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Rey Za Burrel (boyhood)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53294" type="appears in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="4">6.33</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X42S Destiny Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>132927.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53429" type="appears in" update="2013-03-04">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X56S/Beta Sword Impulse Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133161.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53430" type="appears in" update="2013-03-04">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X56S/Gamma Blast Impulse Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133162.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53431" type="appears in" update="2013-03-04">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X56S/Alpha Force Impulse Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133164.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89937" type="appears in" update="2017-06-12">
<name>ZGMF-XX09T DOM Trooper</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>203827.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="22609" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gundam Seed Destiny Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22928" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Zero Attack Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23162" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="26">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒れる瞳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angry Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un regard en colère</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikareru Hitomi</title>
<summary>In year 72 of the Cosmic Era, the Junius Treaty brought the hostilities between ZAFT and the Earth Alliance to a formal conclusion. The treaty banned all military use of nuclear weapons and nuclear power, and placed strict limits on the size of the ZAFT and Earth Alliance forces. However, there are still tensions between the genetically enhanced Coordinators and the unmodified Naturals, and the peace between them remains fragile.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731595</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="23745" update="2006-04-30">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">First Attack Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24917" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いを呼ぶもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Call for War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les racines de la guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai o Yobu Mono</title>
<summary>With Armory One under attack, Athrun commandeers a ZAFT mobile suit to get Cagalli to safety. The three captured Gundams engage Athrun`s ZAKU in combat, but he is rescued by the sudden appearance of the young ZAFT pilot Shinn Asuka and his Impulse Gundam.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731597</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24933" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予兆の砲火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warning Shots</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le feu de la prémonition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yochou no Houka</title>
<summary>Shinn and Rey struggle against the enemy commander Neo Roanoke. In order to help her pilots, ZAFT Captain Talia Gladys orders the newly constructed warship Minerva to launch from Armory One and join the battle. The enemy forces withdraw, and the Minerva gives chase.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731599</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24934" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星屑の戦場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stardust Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille parmi les poussières d`étoiles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshikuzu no Senjou</title>
<summary>The Minerva follows the Girty Lue into the debris belt that surrounds Earth, and sends Shinn and his comrade Lunamaria Hawke in pursuit of the enemy mothership. However, Neo has tricked the ZAFT pilots into following a decoy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731601</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="24935" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">癒えぬ傷痕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scars that Won`t Heal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Blessures inguérissables</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ienu Kizuato</title>
<summary>Aboard the Minerva, Chairman Durandal receives shocking news. The ruins of Junius Seven, the PLANT that was destroyed in the infamous Bloody Valentine incident and where the armistice treaty was later signed, have left their stable orbit and begun falling towards Earth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731603</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26191" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の終わる時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand viendra la fin du monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Owaru Toki</title>
<summary>The Minerva launches its mobile suits to support Yzak and his demolition crew. Shinn, Rey, Lunamaria, and Athrun join the battle against the mysterious group who have sent Junius Seven falling towards Earth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731605</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26192" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">混迷の大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Confusion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terre de confusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konmei no Daichi</title>
<summary>Despite the heroic efforts of its crew, the Minerva has been unable to avert disaster, and the fragments of Junius Seven inflict terrible damage as they fall across Earth`s surface. The Minerva retrieves Shinn and Athrun as they descend to Earth, then sets course for Orb in order to return Cagalli and repair the damage it has suffered in its space battles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731607</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26193" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャンクション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Junction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jonction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junction</title>
<summary>Once the Minerva arrives in Orb, Cagalli resumes her duties as Chief Representative. Her prime minister, Unato Ema Seiran, tells her of the damage caused by the fall of Junius Seven and urges her to approve an alliance with the Atlantic Federation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731609</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26323" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">驕れる牙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bared Fangs</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les griffes de l`arrogance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ogoreru Kiba</title>
<summary>The Atlantic Federation and its allies declare war on the PLANTs in response to the fall of Junius Seven. Although Chairman Durandal still hopes for a diplomatic solution, the ZAFT forces are mobilized to defend the PLANTs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731611</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26324" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血に染まる海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood in the Water</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mer de sang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi ni Somaru Umi</title>
<summary>The Minerva crew find an Earth Forces fleet waiting for them outside Orb`s territorial waters, leaving them no choice but to somehow break through the enemy lines. While Rey and Lunamaria guard the ship, Shinn fights an aerial battle against the Earth Forces mobile suits, but the tide turns against them as the enemy deploys a huge mobile armor whose positron deflector shield can withstand even the Minerva`s Tannhauser cannon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731617</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26325" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選びし道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chosen Path</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choix de son destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erabishi Michi</title>
<summary>The conflict continues to escalate as Earth Forces fleets encircle the ZAFT bases at Gibraltar and Carpentaria, and the PLANT Supreme Council decides to strike back in the name of self-defense. Despite her best intentions, Cagalli yields to her ministers` demands that Orb ally itself with the Atlantic Federation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731615</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26326" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父の呪縛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Father`s Spell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La malédiction du père</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi no Jubaku</title>
<summary>Chairman Durandal tells the horrified Athrun the details of the Earth Forces` latest attack on the PLANTs. Giving up his Alex Dino alias, Athrun admits his true identity and begs Durandal not to let this conflict escalate into another war.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731613</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26585" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえる翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrected Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ailes de la résurrection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Tsubasa</title>
<summary>Thanks to Shinn`s fighting prowess, the Minerva has overcome the Earth Forces fleet. As the ship continues on to Carpentaria, the Orb government concludes its alliance with the Atlantic Federation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731619</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26586" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日への出航[たびだち]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flight to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Départ pour l’avenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asu e no Tabidachi</title>
<summary>In the wake of the assassination attempt on Lacus, Kira and his friends realize that they have been targeted by the government of the PLANTs. Kira then receives a letter from his sister Cagalli, in which she tells him of her intention to marry Yuna and asks him to return Athrun`s ring on her behalf.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731621</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="26587" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦場への帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to the Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour sur champ de bataille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou e no Kikan</title>
<summary>Aboard the Archangel, Cagalli berates the crew for abducting her in the middle of her wedding ceremony. Kira gives Athrun`s ring back to her, and gently asks Cagalli to join them in seeking a better answer to the world`s problems.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731623</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="27420" update="2007-07-02">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<rating votes="1">9.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 01!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27421" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 02!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27422" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 04!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27423" update="2007-07-02">
<epno type="5">P5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 05!) Thalia`s Ass Fanclub</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27424" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 06!) The World`s First One and a Half Hours</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27425" update="2007-07-02">
<epno type="5">P7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 07!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27426" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 08!) Conjunction Junction</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27704" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="5">P13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2005-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 13!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27848" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">インド洋の死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Struggle in the Indian Ocean</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel dans l’océan Indien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Indo You no Shitou</title>
<summary>As the Minerva makes its way through the Indian Ocean, it draws the attention of an old enemy, Neo Roanoke of the elite Phantom Pain taskforce. Neo calls in support from the nearby Earth Forces and launches an aerial assault on the Minerva.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731625</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="28202" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士の条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Soldier`s Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La marque du soldat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi no Jouken</title>
<summary>The fugitive Archangel is now hiding underwater in the neutral Kingdom of Scandinavia. Aboard the ship, Kira and his friends ponder their future plans.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731627</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="28203" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ローエングリンを討て!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack the Lohengrin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Détruisez le Lohengrin !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lohengrin o Ute!</title>
<summary>As the Minerva approaches the Lohengrin Gate, Athrun explains the battle plan to the other pilots. While the Minerva and the soldiers of the Mahamul base draw the attention of the Earth Forces, one pilot will attack the positron cannon via a hidden tunnel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731629</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="28204" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見えない真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hidden Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une vérité dissimulée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mienai Shinjitsu</title>
<summary>The Minerva continues on to the shore of the Black Sea and docks at the city of Diocuia. Recently liberated from the control of the Earth Forces, Diocuia is now the latest stop on Meer Campbell`s morale-building concert tour.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731631</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="28851" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">EDITED</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29059" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="16">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PAST</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Récapitulatif</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Past</title>
<summary>This episode recounts Shinn`s personal history. During the previous war, Shinn and his family lived peacefully in the neutral nation of Orb, but eventually even Orb was drawn into the conflict.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731633</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29060" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さまよう眸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wandering Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Regards errants</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samayou Hitomi</title>
<summary>After their meeting with Chairman Durandal, the Minerva pilots are treated to a day of vacation and given rooms in one of Diocuia`s hotels, and Athrun receives an unexpected guest. The pilots also make the acquaintance of Heine Westenfluss, a FAITH member who has been assigned to the Minerva as an additional pilot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731635</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29061" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼天の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword of the Blue Skies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée céleste</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souten no Tsurugi</title>
<summary>Yielding to pressure from the Earth Forces, the government of Orb has agreed to join the fight against ZAFT. An Orb expeditionary fleet commanded by Yuna Roma Seiran is dispatched to back up Neo Roanoke`s Phantom Pain taskforce.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731637</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="30449" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦火の蔭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shadows of War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ombre de la guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senka no Kage</title>
<summary>The battle between the Minerva and the Orb fleet has been disrupted by the sudden appearance of the Archangel and Kira`s Freedom Gundam. Cagalli enters the battlefield and orders the Orb forces to cease fighting, but Neo pressures Yuna into continuing the battle, and the Orb fleet renews its attack on the damaged Minerva.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731639</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="31209" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違う視線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Differing Views</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Regards fugitifs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigau Shisen</title>
<summary>The battered Minerva retreats to a port on the Sea of Marmara to repair the damage it sustained in the Dardanelles battle. Troubled by the chaos his former comrades created during the fighting, Athrun decides to leave the Minerva and go in search of the Archangel so that he can talk to Kira and the others in person.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731641</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="31210" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪の在処</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Place of Sin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`antre du péché</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi no Arika</title>
<summary>Athrun has arranged a meeting with Kira and Cagalli, but the old friends no longer see eye to eye. Even after hearing of the assassination attempt on Lacus, Athrun still believes in Chairman Durandal`s good intentions, and he returns to the Minerva after urging his friends to keep Orb from participating in the war.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731643</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="33692" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Promesses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku</title>
<summary>After running off alone to the Lodonia laboratory, the Extended soldier Stella Loussier has been captured by the Minerva`s pilots. Shinn brings the injured Stella aboard the Minerva, but the ship`s doctors are unable to treat her due to her abnormal physiology.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731645</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="33693" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unfulfilled Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sentiments inexprimés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi</title>
<summary>Even as Neo prepares for another attack on the Minerva, the ZAFT forces are on the trail of the Archangel and its crew. While Chairman Durandal supervises the pursuit of the fugitive Lacus, Captain Talia of the Minerva receives a report on Athrun`s secret meeting with Kira and Cagalli.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731647</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34126" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残る命散る命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Survivors and Sacrifices</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Survivre et mourir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokoru Inochi Chiru Inochi</title>
<summary>As the Minerva struggles against the combined Orb and Earth Forces fleets, the Freedom Gundam and the Archangel appear on the battlefield once more. Cagalli pleads with the Orb forces to cease fighting, but Yuna orders them to continue their assault on the Minerva.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731649</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35319" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">30-second promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35729" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FATES</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fates</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Destins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fates</title>
<summary>Lacus returns to space and joins her allies aboard the warship Eternal, which is now hidden inside a cluster of asteroids. Chairman Durandal orders his forces to continue searching for Lacus, insisting that she is merely an impostor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731651</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36164" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">刹那の夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fleeting Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un rêve éphémère</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsuna no Yume</title>
<summary>In the aftermath of the battle at Crete, the Archangel retrieves survivors from the Orb fleet, who ask to join Cagalli in her fight to restore Orb`s ideals. Meanwhile, the Minerva is undergoing another round of repairs before continuing on to Gibraltar.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731653</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36165" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明けない夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Endless Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nuit interminable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akenai Yoru</title>
<summary>Shinn and Rey have returned Stella to her allies in order to save her life. As punishment for defying military regulations, the two pilots are placed in detention while the ZAFT leadership determines their fate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731655</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36166" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ステラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stella</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Stella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stellar</title>
<summary>The Destroy Gundam advances towards Berlin, crushing one city after another. The Archangel arrives to confront the Destroy, but even Kira`s Freedom Gundam is no match for its overwhelming power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731657</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36512" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">示される世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World Revealed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand le monde se dévoile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimesareru Sekai</title>
<summary>After laying Stella`s body to rest, Shinn returns to the Minerva with a new determination. When Athrun visits Shinn`s room, he finds Shinn and Rey running combat simulations to prepare for a confrontation with the Freedom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731659</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36659" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cauchemar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu</title>
<summary>Chairman Durandal has revealed the existence of Logos to the public, throwing the world into a state of confusion. Kira and Cagalli fear that their homeland is now in danger, and the Archangel begins making its way back to Orb.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731661</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37146" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">混沌の先に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eve of Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Par-delà le chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konton no Saki ni</title>
<summary>Although the Archangel has escaped the Minerva`s attack, the Freedom has been destroyed, and the ship itself badly damaged. After retrieving Kira, the Archangel continues on to Orb, while Shinn returns to the Minerva and receives a hero`s welcome.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731663</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37147" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アスラン脱走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Athrun on the Run</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Asran déserte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Athrun Dassou</title>
<summary>Chairman Durandal, accompanied by Meer Campbell, presents Shinn and Athrun with a pair of powerful new Gundams. Shinn is delighted with this gift, but Athrun is still upset that they were ordered to attack the Archangel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731665</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37695" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷鳴の闇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunder in the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nuit de tonnerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raimei no Yami</title>
<summary>As Athrun and Meyrin escape from Gibraltar in a stolen mobile suit, Shinn and Rey pursue them in the new Destiny and Legend Gundams. Claiming that the fugitives have stolen classified information, Chairman Durandal orders Shinn and Rey to shoot them down.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731667</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37696" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しき旗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Flag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nouvelle bannière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashiki Hata</title>
<summary>The ZAFT forces gather around Heaven`s Base as they wait for the Earth Forces to respond to Chairman Durandal`s ultimatum. Aboard the Minerva, Lunamaria channels her grief into anger at Logos, while Shinn does his best to comfort her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731669</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38209" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空のキラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kira of the Skies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kira tout puissant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkuu no Kira</title>
<summary>ZAFT has captured Heaven`s Base only to find that Lord Djibril has fled to parts unknown, and Chairman Durandal orders his forces to track the fugitive down. Aboard the Archangel, Kira laments his own powerlessness and wonders what will happen next.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731671</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38210" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄金の意志</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legacy of Gold</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une détermination en or</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougon no Ishi</title>
<summary>Shinn and Rey receive medals for their exploits at Heaven`s Base, and Chairman Durandal awards them their own FAITH insignia. But a new crisis is already beginning, as ZAFT has discovered that Lord Djibril has taken refuge in Orb.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731673</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38554" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自由と正義と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Freedom and Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Liberté et justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiyuu to Seigi to</title>
<summary>Cagalli and her golden mobile suit Akatsuki have turned the tide of battle in Orb`s favor, but she now finds herself facing enemy reinforcements, in the form of the Minerva and Shinn`s Destiny Gundam. Even as the Archangel rushes to Cagalli`s aid, Kira and Lacus return from space with a pair of new Gundams.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731677</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38621" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">反撃の声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Call for Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Contre-attaque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangeki no Koe</title>
<summary>The ZAFT forces renew their attack on Orb. Shinn and Rey enter the battlefield in the Destiny and Legend, and Athrun comes to Kira`s rescue with his new Infinite Justice Gundam. While the four Gundams clash, the battle situation abruptly changes, and Talia orders the ZAFT forces to withdraw.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731679</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39076" recap="true" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リフレイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Refrain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Refrain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Refrain</title>
<summary>Aboard the Archangel, the injured Athrun thinks back upon the path he has followed to this point. Even though he saw the pointlessness of war during the previous conflict, he rejoined ZAFT and fought alongside the Minerva crew in order to bring the new war to an end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731675</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39198" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人のラクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lacus Times Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux Lacus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Lacus</title>
<summary>The real Lacus Clyne has reappeared on the world stage, and the impostor has been exposed. While Chairman Durandal sends Meer Campbell into hiding, the ZAFT forces and their allies grapple with this new revelation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731681</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39414" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変革の序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude to Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`aube du changement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henkaku no Jokyoku</title>
<summary>Although the Requiem cannon has missed the PLANT capital of Aprilius, it has wreaked vast destruction on the surrounding PLANTs. In response, ZAFT sends its lunar orbital fleet to attack Requiem`s first relay station, while the Minerva rushes to the Daedalus base to capture the cannon itself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731683</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39555" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 40!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39603" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chanson de la vérité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjitsu no Uta</title>
<summary>With the Daedalus base captured, Lord Djibril eliminated, and the Requiem relay stations safely under ZAFT control, Chairman Durandal`s victory now appears complete. As the world awaits Durandal`s next move, the Archangel heads for the free lunar city of Copernicus to monitor the situation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731685</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40493" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミーア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Meer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meer</title>
<summary>Lacus and her companions return to the Archangel, carrying with them the body of Meer Campbell. Now that Meer has given her life to save Lacus, Athrun is ashamed to realize how little he knew about her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731687</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40494" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新世界へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To A New World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers un nouveau monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Sekai e</title>
<summary>The fragile peace is shattered, as the world is once again thrown into turmoil by the announcement of Chairman Durandal`s Destiny Plan. To eliminate conflict and secure eternal peace and happiness, Durandal intends to use DNA analysis to assign every human being to his or her proper role in life, creating a regulated society without free will or desire.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731689</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40495" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rey</title>
<summary>By using the Requiem cannon against the Earth Forces` Arzachel base, Chairman Durandal has shown that he will destroy anyone who stands in the way of his Destiny Plan, and it is clear to all that Orb is his next target. The Orb space fleet and its allies scramble to attack the Daedalus base before Requiem can fire again, while the Archangel and Eternal attempt to destroy the cannon`s first relay station.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731691</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40662" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="17">2.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Power</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pouvoir ultime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Chikara</title>
<summary>Having eliminated Requiem`s first relay station, the Archangel and Eternal rush to the moon to join the attack on the Daedalus base, only to find their way barred by the mobile fortress Messiah. Kira tells Athrun and the Archangel to continue on and destroy the Requiem cannon, while he and the Eternal stay behind to deal with Messiah.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>731693</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-seed-destiny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="42200" update="2005-10-12">
<epno type="5">P17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 17!)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47719" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47720" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47721" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47722" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4 - Wings of Words -Cagalli version-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47723" update="2007-01-27">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5 - Wings of Words -Neo version-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47724" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47725" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47726" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47727" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47728" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Making Of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66040" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Music featuring Gundam SEED</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75877" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - Character Songs Remix</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75878" update="2019-10-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - Tanekyara Gekijo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75880" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - World Wide Seed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75881" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - MS Trico Stage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75882" update="2019-10-12">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - Tanekyara Gekijo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75884" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - SEED The Live Tour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75886" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova er - Nicol`s Piano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84169" update="2007-10-10">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova ist - Tanekyara Gekijo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84171" update="2007-10-10">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Seed Supernova ist - Tanekyara Gekijo 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151638" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151639" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151640" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">HD Remastered Blu-ray Box 1 CM2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151641" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">HD Remastered Blu-ray Box 1 CM1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151642" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">HD Remastered PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151644" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「Fields of hope」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Fields of hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Fields of hope</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155050" update="2013-10-14">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「Quiet Night C.E.73」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Quiet Night C.E.73</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Quiet Night C.E.73</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155051" update="2013-10-14">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「Life Goes On」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Life Goes On</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Life Goes On</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157099" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「tears」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: tears</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157100" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「深海の孤独」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Shinkai no Kodoku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Shinkai no Kodoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160310" update="2014-05-29">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 6b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160311" update="2014-05-29">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 6a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160312" update="2014-05-29">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160313" update="2014-07-14">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「君は僕に似ている」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Kimi wa Boku ni Niteiru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Kimi wa Boku ni Niteiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160314" update="2014-07-14">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「焔の扉」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Honoo no Tobira</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: Honoo no Tobira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160315" update="2014-07-14">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept- 「EMOTION」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: EMOTION</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ANIME MUSIC CLIP -Director`s Concept-: EMOTION</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
