<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2189" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-08-20</startdate>
<enddate>2005-08-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban xxxHOLiC: Manatsu no Yo no Yume</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">xxxHolic - A Midsummer Night`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">xxxHolic, ein Sommernachtstraum</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Триплексоголик - Сон в летнюю ночь</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">хххХолик: Сън в лятната нощ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gekijouban xxxHOLiC - Manatsu no Yoru no Yume</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">xxxГолік - Сон у літню ніч</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">xxxHolic - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">XXX Holic</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 XXX HOLiC 真夏ノ夜ノ夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">xxxHolic: The Movie - A Midsummer Night`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">xxxHolic: Der Film</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">XXX Holic, songe d`une nuit d`été</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">XXX HOLIC - 한 여름밤의 꿈</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">xxxHolic the Movie</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4032" type="Parent Story">xxxHOLiC</anime>
<anime id="3317" type="Other">Gekijouban Tsubasa Chronicle: Tori Kago no Kuni no Himegimi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="481642">Besides the plot: The sound track is most beautiful.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="238012">Always recommended xxxholic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284037">This movie is better than I expected. After watching the series, I didn`t expect much from the movie. But my expectation was wrong. This anime rocks. Even if you never watched xxxholic series, this movie is highly recommended. To me, this movie is definitely under-reted.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="1757" type="Character Design">Kise Kazuchika</name>
<name id="1508" type="Direction">Mizushima Tsutomu</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="4364" type="Music">Saitou Tsuneyoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>Yuuko receives a letter from an unknown sender. It is an invitation to an auction. Seven avid collectors were invited to an old mansion. They all admit that they accepted the invitation to complete their collections. They waited for the host, but he does not make an appearance. And one by one the collectors disappear. The strange host and a mysterious girl. A night where odd things happen one after another. What is being auctioned? Who is the host? The cunning and foolish people who are obsessed with "possessions" and the host`s "timeless" passion. What is waiting at the end of this enigmatic series of riddles? And what is the conclusion of the sad love story behind them? Mystery leads to mystery, and reaches the unexpected!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2937">7.06</permanent>
<temporary count="2957">7.77</temporary>
<review count="2">7.24</review>
</ratings>
<picture>36793.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4212</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1719</identifier>
<identifier>fuqtbc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/xxxholic-movie-manatsu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>XxxHolic:_A_Midsummer_Night's_Dream</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>XXXHOLiC</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322483</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7575</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2419" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-17">
<name>glutton</name>
<description>A character (who quite often is anything but fat) eats enough for an entire football team, usually devastating the whole table — and perhaps entire restaurants — with their insatiable hunger. Often combined with a speed-eating technique that makes food seem to vanish spontaneously from the plate.</description>
<picurl>239821.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4477" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>communication with the dead</name>
<description>This character is able of some manner of communication with the dead, or at least with one dead person. This includes talking to the dead, seeing the dead, outright mediumship, or any form of unidirectional or bidirectional form of communication that ordinary characters are not generally able to achieve.
This does not apply in environments where characters are expected to be dead, or where nobody is alive to begin with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="859" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="1667">8.91</rating>
<name>Ichihara Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Being one extremely experienced in her industry, Yuuko is not foolish enough to give away her real name like Watanuki. That aside, Yuuko has served as a major catalyst for Watanuki`s transformation, acting somewhat as his mentor. She loves to drink and eat Watanuki`s wonderful cooking and dragging Watanuki on crazy outings at the drop of a hat.</description>
<picture>130737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="860" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="513">6.44</rating>
<name>Watanuki Kimihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An orphaned boy cursed with the ability to see spirits, Watanuki entered into an agreement with Yuuko to work for her in exchange for the fulfilment of his wish - to never see spirits again. However, despite the fact that he hates his ability, Watanuki often goes out of his way to help people that he comes into contact with because of his power, even when he is not required to do so by his job. He is also very independent, because he has had to live alone for most of his life, and is an excellent cook and housekeeper.</description>
<picture>130738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="861" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="182">6.96</rating>
<name>Doumeki Shizuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doumeki is Watanuki`s classmate and one-sided rival. He is part of the school`s archery club and often participates (and tops) school competitions. He lives by a shrine owned by his late grandfather.</description>
<picture>130744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="862" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="81">5.58</rating>
<name>Ame-warashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Ame-warashi is also known as a rain sprite or rain maker. She is a proud, high ranking spirit/sprite who has a very hostile attitude toward humans due to the fact that "humans have no care or regard whatsoever with living nature". She comes to Yuuko to ask for the service of Watanuki to save someone at a park containing hydrangeas. In the anime, she is portrayed as a good, protective friend of the Zashiki-warashi.</description>
<picture>130745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="863" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="182">8.52</rating>
<name>Zashiki-warashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A vestal sprite who has a crush on Watanuki. In the manga, the Zashiki-warashi first appears at Valentine`s Day determined to give the perfect chocolate to Watanuki, which nearly results in the death of Doumeki. She next appears when Watanuki is sent by Yuuko to a place of pure chi to return the Pipe Fox to its normal small size.</description>
<picture>130742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="865" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="67">6.66</rating>
<name>Moro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maru and Moro are the two girls that led Watanuki into Yuuko`s shop. It isn`t stated whether they were created by Yuuko, Clow Reed, the both of them, or someone else entirely, but since they have no souls and cannot leave the shop, it can be assumed that they were created there.</description>
<picture>130741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="866" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="67">6.66</rating>
<name>Maru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maru and Moro are the two girls that led Watanuki into Yuuko`s shop. It isn`t stated whether they were created by Yuuko, Clow Reed, the both of them, or someone else entirely, but since they have no souls and cannot leave the shop, it can be assumed that they were created there.</description>
<picture>130740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="428">Kojima Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="868" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="216">7.90</rating>
<name>Larg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While the white Mokona left to travel the worlds with the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group, the black Mokona stayed behind to act as a liaison between the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group and Yuuko. Mokona likes to be around Yuuko, drink with her and eat the meals that Watanuki has made, and mostly chirps in with Maru and Moro. Yuuko has mentioned that the Mokonas were created a very long time ago by herself and Clow Reed, in preparation for a future event - the arrival and subsequent journey of the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group - as well as to stop Fei Wong Reed`s plans and save "two futures".</description>
<picture>15187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="426" picture="44708.jpg">Kikuchi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7161" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="64">8.77</rating>
<name>Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The princess of a feudal country called Nihon who sends the ninja Kurogane on the quest that causes him to join the dimension travelers. Tomoyo is the Tsukuyomi, a powerful miko sorceress responsible for maintaining the wards of Nihon that protect the country from demons. She is also a dreamseer with the ability to see into other people`s, to enter another`s dreams, can send trans-dimensional messages through dreams and is able to see the future in her dreams. However, she gave up her dreamseer power to Yuuko as the price for bringing Kurogane, Fay, Shaoran and Mokona to Nihon. Another incarnation of her appears In Piffle World, where she retains much of her nature from Daidouji Tomoyo in Cardcaptor Sakura.</description>
<picture>60819.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="39494" update="2006-03-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2005-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39499" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39582" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63267" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2005-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63268" update="2007-06-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2005-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168019" update="2015-04-19">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Background Art Slideshow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168020" update="2015-04-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character Design Slideshow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168021" update="2015-04-19">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Voice Actor Introduction</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168022" update="2015-04-19">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Event</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168023" update="2015-04-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Commentary</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
