<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="219" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-09-01</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cowboy Bebop: Tengoku no Tobira</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cowboy Bebop - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">CB Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Cowboy Bebop: llamando a las puertas del cielo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Cowboy Bebop: la película</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ковбой Бибоп: Достучаться до небес</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Kowboj Bebop: Pukając do nieba bram</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Kowboj Bebop the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Kowboj Bepop</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Kowboj Bebop</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Kovboy Bebop: Film</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Марсиански Каубой: Врата към Рая</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ковбой Бібоп: Фільм</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bebop movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CB Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Бібоп фільм</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カウボーイビバップ天国の扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cowboy Bebop: Knockin` on Heaven`s Door</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - Der Film</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - Le film</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - Il Film</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Ковбой Бибоп</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">카우보이 비밥 - 천국의 문</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Cowboy Bebop: Pukając do nieba bram</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - O Filme</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - O Filme</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Kovboj Bebop: Lovec odměn</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - palkkionmetsästäjät</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">קאובוי ביבופ: הסרט</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Cowboy Bebop - A film</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Kaubojus Bibopas: Filmas</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Kauboipeitus</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">星際牛仔: 天國之門</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Cowboy Bebop: La Película</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="23" type="Parent Story">Cowboy Bebop</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7208" approval="38" total="46">Trigun: Badlands Rumble</anime>
<anime id="78" approval="2" total="8">Metropolis</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="291451">amazing</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="497780">THE anime action movie. big-budget, absolutely gorgeous, breath taking action and bebop style all over the place. nothin` much in terms of drama or philosophy, but expecting that out of this would be totally missing the point.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="99944">Best animated movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="497940">Great movie, great side story to the original series... Only regret is that it makes me wish that the series hadn`t ended.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/works/list/detail.php?cid=42</url>
<creators>
<name id="129" type="Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="662" type="Character Design">Kawamoto Toshihiro</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
</creators>
<description>Mars is under siege! Just before Halloween 2071, a terrorist bomb destroys a tanker truck on Highway One, close to the densely-populated crater city. There are casualties up to half a mile from the blast — 500 killed or injured by what appears to be a biochemical weapon. The reward for the bomber`s capture is a massive 300,000,000 woolongs... and there are four humans and a dog who really need the money. Down on their luck as usual, the crew of the Bebop get on the case.
Note: The movie takes place between (in the time period of) the http://anidb.net/a23 [Cowboy Bebop] episodes 22 and 23.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8929">8.16</permanent>
<temporary count="8986">8.32</temporary>
<review count="8">8.60</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228413.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>353</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712</identifier>
<identifier>nzheyj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/works/list/detail.php?cid=42</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/cowboy-bebop-movie</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/international/works/detail.php?cid=42</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cowboy_Bebop:_The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>COWBOY_BEBOP</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>310</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234303</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4900</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/199</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>카우보이_비밥_천국의_문</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7614</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2765" parentid="2660" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Mars</name>
<description>Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System after Mercury. In English, Mars carries a name of the Roman god of war, and is often referred to as the "Red Planet" because the reddish iron oxide prevalent on its surface gives it a reddish appearance that is distinctive among the astronomical bodies visible to the naked eye. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, having surface features reminiscent both of the impact craters of the Moon and the valleys, deserts, and polar ice caps of Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214389.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2962" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>neo-noir</name>
<description>Neo-noir is a style that prominently utilizes elements of the now declined film noir, but with updated themes, content, style, visual elements, or media that were absent in films noirs of the 1940s and 1950s.
Films noirs were typically crime dramas or psychological thrillers featuring a pessimistic worldview and starring conflicted antiheroes trapped in difficult situations and making choices out of desperation or nihilistic moral systems, with crime, especially murder, being featured on the majority of them. Some of the most obvious visual elements included low-key lighting, striking use of light and shadow, black-and-white filming, and unusual camera placement such as low-angle, wide-angle, and Dutch angle shots.
Film noir is often associated with urban settings, private detectives, femmes fatales, and bleak endings, but they are not necessary to the genre; a large number of these films, including some of the genre classics, take place in small towns, suburbia, rural areas, or on the open road, feature neither character type, and have clearly happy endings.
Film noir and the early neo-noir would come to influence the formation of tech noir, a crossover of neo-noir and science fiction, in the late 1970s; some the most influencial tech noir works are the American movies Alien (1979), Blade Runner (1982), and The Terminator (1984). Tech noir itself would also help form http://anidb.net/t2861 [cyberpunk] in the early 1980s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3464" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-07">
<name>space western</name>
<description>Space Western is a subgenre of science fiction that transposes themes of American Western books and film to a backdrop of futuristic space frontiers; it is the complement of the science fiction Western, which transposes science fiction themes onto an American Western setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5649" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>jazz</name>
<description>A style of music originating in the Southern USA in the early 20th century, emerging from Blues and Ragtime. Jazz is often associated with the city of New Orleans.
Jazz music is typified by improvisation and syncopation.
Instruments often associated with Jazz are the trumpet, trombone, piano and clarinet.
The anime features a vast amount of jazz, or the theme revolves around it.</description>
<picurl>10253.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5996" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>tragic ending</name>
<description>Up to the very end of the anime the viewer will hope that the story will end well and that the characters will in some way be able to solve the problems.
Not so. The sense of foreboding doom could not be averted. The social or personal calamity strikes mercilessly.
Examples: The catastrophic meteor strike does hit Earth after all. The long sick loved one cannot be saved. After overcoming all obstacles a random cruel event ends the life of the protagonist. A almost forgotten tragedy in the past has repercussions in the present.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="270" type="main character in" update="2015-04-14">
<rating votes="751">9.31</rating>
<name>Spike Spiegel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former member of the Red Dragons mafia group, Spike left his past behind 3 years ago and now lives the life of a wanderer, sailing the cosmos alongside his trusted partner, Jet Black, in their ship, the Bebop. Always after a new prize to restock their dwindling money supply and put food on the table, Spike and Jet will get into all sorts of scrapes to hunt criminals down. Spike`s skills at martial arts and with his gun help make him someone you definitely do not want to mess with.</description>
<picture>14555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="400" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="378">8.13</rating>
<name>Faye Valentine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Faye Valentine is one of the members of the bounty hunting crew in the anime series Cowboy Bebop. She is often seen with a cigarette and in a revealing outfit complete with bright yellow hot pants and a matching, revealing top (and, on occasion, a bikini). She sports violet hair, green eyes, and a voluptuous body. Although appearing to be no more than 23 years old, Faye is actually around 77 years old, having been put into cryogenic freeze after a space shuttle accident, wherein she spent fifty-four years in suspended animation. During the course of the series (set in 2071), Faye manages to cross paths with Spike and Jet twice before she finally makes herself at home aboard their ship the second time around, much to the consternation and disapproval of the two men, both of whom have their own reservations about women in general.
Faye herself is brash, egotistical, and quite lazy, despite taking plenty of time to pamper and care for her own appearance. Faye has been arrested several times in the series, and has spent time in handcuffs on the ship. She, at times, expects the boys to take care of bounties for her, while she sits by idly to reap the benefits and eat all their food, which is another source of conflict.
Seemingly little more than a thorn in her partner`s sides, Faye is actually a well-rounded member of the team. She can handle herself exceptionally well for a woman of her slight appearance, displaying at least once in the series (in "http://anidb.net/e880 [Cowboy Funk]") that she has a powerful punch. Adept at flying, Faye has stood her ground just as well as Spike has in an aerial dogfight in her ship Red Tail, and at times even against Spike in an aerial dogfight (though Spike eventually proved the better pilot). She also excels with guns, and is first seen in the series completely disabling a shop with a Heckler &amp; Koch MP5K, though she is immediately apprehended afterward. In the movie, she is seen with the same gun, in addition to her normal companion: a Glock 30. Faye has an almost unstoppable attitude, and even her sometimes innocent smile can be seen as dangerous. She has many bad habits, such as drinking, habitual gambling, smoking cigarettes and occasionally cigars, becoming unnecessarily violent, and turning on partners when the profits seem too skimpy. Sarcastic and presumptuous, she rarely appears weak or in need of support. She brags and takes care of herself, never trusting others, cheating and lying her way from one day to the next.
She is a woman who is skilled at getting what she wants; her indomitable exterior hides a more delicate interior. Upon awakening from her 54-year cryogenic sleep, not only was she saddled with a massive amount of debt that she had no means to pay, but she was also diagnosed with total amnesia, a stranger in a mysterious world that she was not a part of and did not understand, surrounded by people who claimed to be helping her but were only there to take advantage of her naiveté. The surname "Valentine" was merely a name given to her by the doctor who woke her; the circumstances of her accident, her previous life, and even her real name all remain a mystery, and are only gradually revealed as the series progresses. It has been hinted that she came from Singapore on Earth, and was the daughter of a very wealthy family, as the city`s famous Merlion Statue features prominently in scenes of her childhood, and that memories and a film from her childhood showed her living in a large mansion. Faye is supposedly her real name, as a high school classmate (by now an old disabled woman) recognizes her and calls her by that name. In her debut episode, she claims to be descended from Roma people, but it later becomes apparent that was likely a lie. Utterly betrayed by someone she thought she could trust after waking, Faye found herself burdened with even more money to pay, and the situation resulted in the hardening of her personality to an extreme degree. She even says in Session 11: "we deceive or we are deceived", and that "nothing good ever happened to me when I trusted others."
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>14672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="401" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-14">
<rating votes="229">7.69</rating>
<name>Jet Black</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known on his home satellite as the "Black Dog" for his tenacity, Jet Black is a 36-year-old former cop from Ganymede (a Jovian satellite) and acts as Spike`s foil during the series. Physically, Jet is very tall with a muscular build. He wears a beard with no mustache, and is completely bald save for the back of his head. Spike acts lazy and uninterested, whereas Jet is hard working and a jack-of-all-trades. Jet was once an investigator in the Intra Solar System Police (ISSP) for many years until he lost his arm in an investigation that went awry when his corrupt partner (and friend at the time) betrayed him. His arm was replaced with a cybernetic limb—an operation later revealed to be by choice. As biological replacements were possible, he wanted the fake arm as a reminder of the consequences of his actions. His loss of limb coupled with the general corruption of the police force prompted Jet to quit the ISSP in disgust and become a freelance bounty hunter. Jet also considers himself something of a renaissance man: he cultivates bonsai trees, cooks, enjoys jazz/blues music (he named his ship the Bebop, referring to a type of jazz), especially Charlie Parker, and even has interest in Goethe. As a character, Jet is the quintessential oyaji or "dad" even though he often wishes people would view him as a more brotherly figure (so as not to seem old). Of the crew he shows the most obvious affection when dealing with Edward, most obviously shown when he tells her a story in Session 18; he is also shown attempting to (perhaps falsely) reassure himself after she and Faye leave the crew of the Bebop, hinting that his sometimes-stoic nature may be born of necessity rather than any real lack of emotion.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>14673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="402" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-14">
<rating votes="273">7.67</rating>
<name>Edward Wong Hau Pepelu Tivrusky IV</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Edward Wong Hau Pepelu Tivruski IV is the self-invented personal name of an elite hacker prodigy from Earth. Her birth name is Françoise Appledehli. "Radical Edward" is a very strange, somewhat androgynous, teenage girl claiming to be around 13 years of age. Her mannerisms include walking around in her bare feet, performing strange postures, and her gangling walk. Ed could be considered a "free spirit;" she is fond of silly exclamations and childish rhymes, is easily distracted, has the habit of "drifting off" from reality... sometimes in mid-sentence, and is the show`s primary source of physical humor. Ed`s generally carefree attitude and energy act as a counterpoint to the more solemn and dark aspects of the show. Ed remains a part of the Bebop crew until the 24th episode, when she, along with Ein, leaves the crew to reunite with her father.
Over the course of the show, she rarely walks anywhere, preferring to run, crawl, flip, roll, walk on her hands, ride piggy-back, or, at the very least, saunter. Ed wears a very loose sleeveless shirt and tight, black bicycle shorts, and a pair of large green goggles around her neck or on her head that act as a virtual reality accessory for computers when connected. She is always barefoot and uses her feet for tasks which one would usually use hands, such as scratching her nose, clapping, and typing, and it seems she has followed this habit throughout her life. This also works the other way around, where she walks on her hands instead of her feet. In the episode Mushroom Samba she considers putting on socks and shoes but quickly removes them, as even wearing socks hampers her, and she falls over seconds after putting them on.
She almost always refers to herself in the third person. Not much is known about her origins, only that she spent some of her earlier childhood in an orphanage after being left there by her father, a cartographer (a questionable occupation on a planet which undergoes changes to its landscape daily due to asteroid impacts) named Appledelhi Siniz Hesap Lütfen (which means "excuse me, check please" in Turkish). Ed`s primary use to the Bebop crew is as a hacker; she is widely known to be a whiz kid behind the computer. Ed`s computer of choice is a carry-along Tomato desktop, and when traveling by foot she will balance it on her head. Her goggles can interact with it to give her a virtual reality environment in which she can browse an entire network at once.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>14676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="405" picture="186916.jpg">Tada Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="403" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-14">
<rating votes="146">8.30</rating>
<name>Ein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>14678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10212" type="appears in" update="2009-07-06">
<rating votes="40">8.65</rating>
<name>Bebop Gou Crew</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The crew of the spaceship Bebop are a partnership of bounty hunters, called "cowboys". Originally consisted of Jet Black and Spike Spiegel, later Faye Valentine, Ed (Edward Wong Hau Pepelu Tivrusky IV) and Ein have joined.</description>
<picture>30643.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10219" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="21">7.71</rating>
<name>Bebop</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>A former fishing trawler spaceship owned by Jet Black and refitted to serve as a mobile base for bounty hunting. Contains enough living space to house at least 4 people and one dog. Bebop isn`t equipped with any kind of defensive or offensive weaponry but internal hangars may uphold at least 3 fighter class ships. It is also capable of interplanetary jumpgate travel and planet water landing.</description>
<picture>30652.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13845" type="main character in" update="2010-01-01">
<rating votes="13">6.11</rating>
<name>Vincent Volaju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="560" picture="41051.jpg">Isobe Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18657" type="appears in" update="2010-06-09">
<rating votes="7">6.40</rating>
<name>Laughing Bull</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4683" picture="27279.jpg">Koyama Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18662" type="appears in" update="2010-06-09">
<rating votes="17">6.21</rating>
<name>Judy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18663" type="appears in" update="2010-06-09">
<rating votes="10">6.15</rating>
<name>Punch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2199" picture="21752.jpg">Tareki Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18681" type="appears in" update="2010-06-09">
<rating votes="11">5.13</rating>
<name>Bob</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18741" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="17">6.29</rating>
<name>Electra Ovilo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Electra is a veteran of the Titan War who first appears in Cowboy Bebop: Knockin` On Heaven`s Door. Her love for Vincent caused them to have a short-term relationship, during which Vincent transferred the vaccine to Electra. She is unaware of this until Vincent sets free the Nanomachines on the Monorail and she survives. She meets Spike by chance when he infiltrates a bio weapon lab fronting as a pharmaceutical company where she works. After a few more chance meetings, and witnessing his being shot and thrown from a monorail by Vincent, she teams up with the crew of the Bebop to put an end to Vincent`s intent to destroy the population of Mars. The samples of her blood are used to make the vaccine that is spread over Alba city. In the end, it is she who shoots Vincent and kills him. She cries for him when he admits he remembers her and their love for one another as he is dying.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>49549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3092" picture="23997.jpg">Kobayashi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50635" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Lee Samson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50636" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Renji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9516" picture="35189.jpg">Ishibashi Renji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50637" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Kottouhin`ya Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3281" picture="154160.jpg">Yoda Eisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50638" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Rasheed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34433" picture="128179.jpg">Mickey Curtis</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50639" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="2">1.33</rating>
<name>Reji no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50640" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Lylie Kisha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50641" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Harris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50642" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Honbuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50643" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Taisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50644" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Steve</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50645" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Caster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50646" type="appears in" update="2012-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2549" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2550" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7183" update="2004-06-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8544" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11643" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13275" update="2004-06-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13276" update="2004-06-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2001-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17556" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17557" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="3">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26502" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Movie Commentary</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26503" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Soundtrack Commentary</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26504" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character Profile - Spike</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26505" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character Profile - Faye</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26506" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character Profile - Ed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26507" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character Profile - Jet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26508" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard Comparison</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26509" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">AMV - Into the Darkness</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131998" update="2011-07-19">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131999" update="2011-07-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
