<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2193" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1978-03-18</startdate>
<enddate>1978-03-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Candy Candy: Haru no Yobigoe</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Candy Candy: The Call of Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Au pays de Candy : L`appel du printemps</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Кенди-Кенди: Зов весны</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キャンディ・キャンディ 春の呼び声</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Candy Candy - Kevään kutsu</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1913" type="Prequel">Candy Candy</anime>
<anime id="1915" type="Summary">Candy Candy: Candy no Natsuyasumi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="1094" type="Original Work">Igarashi Yumiko</name>
<name id="3637" type="Music">Watanabe Takeo</name>
<name id="8831" type="Original Work">Mizuki Kyouko</name>
</creators>
<description>* A continuation of the http://anidb.net/a1913 [Candy Candy television series].
Candy returns to Pony`s Home and she meets a girl who has lost her parents and doesn`t associate with the other kids. In order to cheer her up she decides to tell her about herself from the moment she was found by Miss Pony and sister Lane to her decision to leave the boarding school in England and walk her own path.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="67">4.34</permanent>
<temporary count="68">5.83</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>43034.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3624</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2801</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2507</identifier>
<identifier>pszppf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キャンディ・キャンディ#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>146244</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m078</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25162" type="main character in" update="2019-09-07">
<rating votes="27">7.69</rating>
<name>Candice White Adley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Candy is an orphan grown up in the orphanage "Pony`s Home". She has got golden blond hair, green eyes and freckles in her funny face. Candy is very kind-hearted, helpful, optimistic, cheerful and vivid and doesn`t have any inferiority complex because of being an orphan at all. So many people like her or love her very much. While being a teenager, she is adopted by the clan Adley, the biggest, very rich, influential and highly respected clan in the United States of America. From then on Candy must go through many troubles in her life. However, she never becomes dejected, but stays cheerful, diligent and optimistic.</description>
<picture>238080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3286" picture="24711.jpg">Matsushima Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35313" type="appears in" update="2019-09-07">
<rating votes="4">8.39</rating>
<name>Anthony Brown</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35314" type="appears in" update="2019-09-07">
<rating votes="4">6.55</rating>
<name>Terrence G. Grandchester</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3252" picture="24231.jpg">Tomiyama Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35315" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>William Albert Adley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3233" picture="171389.jpg">Inoue Makio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35316" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Archibald Cornwell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238118.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35317" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Alistair Cornwell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238116.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35319" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Eliza Leagan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8055" picture="77674.jpg">Nakatani Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35320" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Neil Leagan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25044">Komiyama Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35322" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Annie Brighton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35326" type="appears in" update="2019-09-04">
<name>Eleonor Baker</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6374" picture="30939.jpg">Kitahama Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35327" type="appears in" update="2019-09-02">
<name>Pony-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2247" picture="72125.jpg">Nakanishi Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35328" type="appears in" update="2019-09-02">
<name>Lane-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2795" picture="23209.jpg">Yamaguchi Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35329" type="appears in" update="2019-09-02">
<name>Jimmy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12580" picture="222815.jpg">Chijimatsu Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35331" type="appears in" update="2019-09-02">
<name>Mrs Leagan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2795" picture="23209.jpg">Yamaguchi Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35334" type="appears in" update="2019-09-04">
<name>Sister Grey</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2795" picture="23209.jpg">Yamaguchi Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21603" update="2009-07-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1978-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
