<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2203" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1965-03-20</startdate>
<enddate>1965-03-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gulliver no Uchuu Ryokou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gulliver`s Space Travels: Beyond the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Приключения Гулливера</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガリバーの宇宙旅行</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/movie/movie_gulliver/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2078" type="Music">Tomita Isao</name>
<name id="4135" type="Direction">Kuroda Yoshio</name>
</creators>
<description>Ted meets the aged professor Gulliver in a deep, dark forest. Accompanied by Mack the dog, a toy soldier called The General, and the Crow, the two set off on a journey to the Planet of Blue Hope in their spaceship the Gulliver.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="93">4.45</permanent>
<temporary count="94">5.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>178126.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1945</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2833</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2304</identifier>
<identifier>bpxwmj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/movie/movie_gulliver/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>141500</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3453</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m013</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7067" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-07">
<name>Gulliver`s Travels</name>
<description>Gulliver`s Travels is a prose satire by Irish writer and clergyman http://anidb.net/cr10263 [Jonathan Swift]. It is a satire both on human nature and on the "travellers` tales" literary subgenre. It is Swift`s best known full-length work and a classic of English literature. He himself claimed that he wrote Gulliver`s Travels "to vex the world rather than divert it".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="21616" update="2009-04-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119374" update="2010-06-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
