<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2210" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1969-03-18</startdate>
<enddate>1969-03-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nagagutsu o Haita Neko</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Puss-in-Boots</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Perix der Kater und die drei Mausketiere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Nagagutsu wo Haita Neko</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">長靴をはいた猫</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Wonderful World of Puss `N Boots</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Der gestiefelte Kater</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le chat botté</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il Gatto con Gli Stivali</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Кот в сапогах</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Kot w Butach (1969)</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Kocour v botách</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Ο Παπουτσομένος Γάτος</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Csizmás Kandúr</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Batuotas katinas</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2216" type="Sequel">Nagagutsu Sanjuushi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/movie/movie_nagagutsu/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4382" type="Music">Uno Seiichirou</name>
<name id="9088" type="Original Work">Charles Perrault</name>
</creators>
<description>* Adaptation of http://anidb.net/cr9088 [Charles Perrault]`s classic fairy tale.
The anime is about a clever musketeer feline in boots. His goal is to help the weak and defenseless, but his saving a mouse makes him the most wanted in all Catdom. On the run from the notorious Three Blunderers, Perro befriends a young miller`s boy, Pierre, and together, they decide to seek their fame and fortune. When they cross paths with the lovely Princess Rosa, Perro determines to get Pierre hitched to Her Royal Highness. But the wicked ogre, Lucifer, also has his sights on Rosa. Nonetheless, with the help of a band of comic mice thieves, Perro manages to get Pierre to become engaged to Rosa. But on the night of the full moon, Lucifer kidnaps the princess, and Pierre, Perro, and the mice bandits set off to rescue her.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="226">6.13</permanent>
<temporary count="226">6.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204426.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2279</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3092</identifier>
<identifier>bksgox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/movie/movie_nagagutsu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Puss_in_Boots_(1969_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>長靴猫シリーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2416</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>142792</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>984</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m025</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="21627" update="2017-04-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208208" update="2018-09-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Japanese Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208209" update="2018-09-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trilogy Original Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
