<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2213" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1970-07-19</startdate>
<enddate>1970-07-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaitei 3-man Mile</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">30,000 Miles Under the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Thirty Thousand Miles Under the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">20.000 leghe sotto i mari</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kaitei Sanman Mile</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">海底3万マイル</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Bulles sous les mers</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">20.000 Leguas de Viaje Submarino</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">30,000 ميل تحت سطح البحر</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">20 Mil Léguas Sob o Mar</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/movie/movie_kaitei3/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3637" type="Music">Watanabe Takeo</name>
<name id="5198" type="Original Work">Ishinomori Shoutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>Returning home from an ocean trip, young Isamu meets the beautiful sea-dweller Angel on a volcanic island. Attacked by a fiery dragon, Isamu and Angel escape on the observation boat See Through, and Angel invites Isamu to see her undersea kingdom of Atlas.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="39">4.60</permanent>
<temporary count="39">5.98</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204351.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3587</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9172</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3161</identifier>
<identifier>azptqt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/movie/movie_kaitei3/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>143299</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3449</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m038</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31117" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Cheetah</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69676.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31118" type="main character in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Isamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31119" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Angel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24676" picture="69690.jpg">Kobato Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31120" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Tuttle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24675" picture="69688.jpg">Hitomi Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31121" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Chitei Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31122" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Octopus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32725" picture="1447.jpeg">Umino Katsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31123" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Kaitei Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29508" picture="24699.jpg">Kitagawa Kunihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31124" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Senchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3237" picture="24219.jpg">Murakoshi Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31125" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Announcer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2981" picture="23711.jpg">Noda Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31126" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Isamu no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20566" picture="206821.jpg">Senou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31127" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Isamu no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3344" picture="2056.gif">Kaji Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21655" update="2010-04-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1970-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
