<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2223" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1975-07-26</startdate>
<enddate>1975-07-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Great Mazinger tai Getter Robo G: Kuuchuu Dai-Gekitotsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Great Mazinger Vs. Getter Robo G: The Great Space Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">グレートマジンガー対ゲッターロボG 空中大激突</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Great Mazinger - Les aventuriers de la galaxie</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il Grande Mazinga contro Getta Robot G - Violento scontro nei cieli</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="956" type="Other">Great Mazinger</anime>
<anime id="1271" type="Other">Getter Robo G</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="3354" type="Original Work">Dynamic Production</name>
<name id="5209" type="Music">Watanabe Chuumei</name>
<name id="3962" type="Music">Kikuchi Shunsuke</name>
<name id="4419" type="Original Work">Ishikawa Ken</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="93">4.50</permanent>
<temporary count="93">5.62</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3180.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4386</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2394</identifier>
<identifier>dafuzr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Great_Mazinger_tai_Getter_Robot_G:_Kuchu_Daigekitotsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>グレートマジンガー対ゲッターロボG_空中大激突</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2723</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>145144</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m064</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5562" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-12">
<rating votes="10">3.33</rating>
<name>Kabuto Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kabuto Shirou is Kabuto Kouji`s younger brother. Most of the time, Shirou`s role is to add some comic relief to the plot. His character acquires a bit more depth in Great Mazinger, as he becomes acquainted with his father Kenzou, who was previously thought to be dead. He pilots his own robot in Great Mazinger, the Robot Junior.</description>
<picture>22403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25075">Sawada Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32208" type="main character in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="10">3.28</rating>
<name>Tomoe Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoe Musashi is a fictional character from the mecha series Getter Robo. He is most famous for his sacrificial final battle that helped end the fight with the Dinosaur Empire. He has however, appeared in subsequent manga and stories due to his popularity and nostalgic quality.
He is an extremely hot-blooded young man and the pilot of the third Getter robot and the Getter machine "Bear". Musashi is short and quite fat, but also very physically strong. He leads his prefecture`s Judo team and has yet to be defeated in a match. Although he doesn`t seem like a likely candidate to pilot a Getter machine, Professor Saotome (the creator of the Getter) saw potential in Musashi and requested he pilot the third Getter. Reluctantly, he agrees and although he at first butts heads with his fellow pilots Nagare Ryouma and Jin Hayato (most especially the latter) he forms a very strong friendship with the two and often settles disputes (albeit often violently).
Despite his rather tough sounding personality and behavior however, Musashi is at his core a goofball. He often stumbles when on foot (a common seen trademark of overweight characters in anime at the time), has the most hilarious reactions to things he doesn`t understand, and often gives the series its lighter moments with his hijinks, such as sending his mother a picture of Saotome`s daughter Michiru and himself telling her they`re dating despite this being a fib. Musashi is in fact, quite infatuated with Michiru as is constantly hinted throughout the series. He seems to constantly struggle to ask her out but is often stopped by his awkwardness and shyness around women. Whether these feelings are returned or not is never depicted, although there are subtle hints that perhaps it may have. This is even teased in a recent OVA where it is implied that Musashi and Michiru were a couple. Musashi`s very combat uniform is quite humorous. As opposed to a space suit like the other two pilots, Musashi wears old Samurai or possible judo body armor that fits snugly over his bulky frame, and a construction helmet with goggles on it and a rather amateurish yellow cape (that is once again too small for him) worn over his "costume".
Sadly however, this is in most cases never meant to be. Throughout the series, despite his contributions and his likable personality, Musashi constantly feels like the odd one out in comparison to the skilled and determined Ryoma, and cool as ice Hayato. This deeply hidden insecurity comes to haunt Musashi in the final episodes of the first series when the Getter Robo proves ineffective. In a last desperate attempt to destroy the Dinosaur empire`s most hideous creation, the three Getter Machines plan to drop specially designed super bombs in unision to destroy the monster. However because of circumstances beyond his control Musashi botches up the mission and the plan fails...resulting in the Getter being damaged severely beyond repair. Despite initial anger, his comrades take it rather well but Musashi however is devastated. The Professor puts into motion one last, desperate plan using his daughter`s fighter and a modified version of the previous bomb for one last desperate attempt to destroy the beast. The mission however, is extremely dangerous and borderlines on suicide. Michiru accepts her duty, however before she can take off she finds that Musashi has stolen the fighter and despite her desperate pleas...executes the mission on his own to make up for his past failure. Because he had to dodge many attacks, the bomb fails to hit its target once again and in one last desperate action...Musashi suicide bombs the fighter to the inside of the monster`s mouth destroying both in the process.
Musashi`s death is devastating to the Getter crew and although newcomer replacement Kurama Benkei fills his position with flying colors, Musashi is often referenced to in the sequel series.
Although Musashi`s character is fondly remembered, what is perhaps Musashi`s most memorable trait is the fact he dies a very large number of different ways. Similar to the case of Tochiro Oyama of Captain Harlock (and Leiji Matsumoto`s universe in general) and later Kenny McCormick of South Park, Musashi has a tendency to have many different deaths depicted, throwing into question the actual canon death. Although his original death was tragic and is arguably considered the canon death, many viewers note that it almost feels like a running joke with how many times Musashi dies yet miraculously shows up in subsequent appearances. Some of his many deaths include:
* His original death by using a kamikaze tactic to kill the final creature in the series.
* In the short film Getter Robo G vs. Great Mazinger (although they never actually fight, but are rather allies), Musashi dies a bit more of a pitiful death at the beginning when a desperate alien catches Musashi`s machine off guard and kamikazes into it.
* In Change! Shin Getter Robo: the last day, Musashi is depicted as a much more serious character. He fights against the coming apocalypse to his best ability, but he is eventually crushed by the Invaders in his incapacitated Getter-3. The wrecked Getter-3 is later found 13 years later by Benkei and the OVA`s main characters, however Musashi`s body is never shown.
* In Neo Getter Robo vs. Shin Getter Robo, Musashi uses the all three of the Getter`s forms to fight off the Dinosaur Empire in New York City to stall until Shin Getter is activated. However, he is overwhelmed and as a last resort, he crushes the Getter`s core causing an explosion that wipes out almost all of the Dinosaurs - as well as all of Manhattan Island. This is pretty much the same end he faces in the original manga, though there the battle happens not too far from the Saotome Institute, to gain time for Getter Robo G being completed. Here, it is to allow the completion of Shin Getter Robo.
* In Shin Getter Robo (2004) (Also known as New Getter Robo), Musashi is not mentioned in name, however, someone who closely resembles Musashi gets brutally killed by Hayato Jin about 5 minutes into the second episode. In Musashi`s place there is a character by the name of Benkei Musashibou who is a mix of both Getter-3 pilots.
* In the Super Robot Wars various spinoffs, Musashi dies in many different ways but often miraculously appears in the next installment. This is mostly because most of Super Robot Wars installments take place in an alternate universe to each other, with the exception of continuing timelines such as the Classic Timeline or the Alpha series (where he died for real in Super Robot Wars Alpha 2 and only appears as a spirit in the next installment). One of the possible outcomes in Super Robot Wars Advance enables Musashi to actually survive until the end of its continuity, since it`s a standalone game unlike the Alpha series. It is still possible to let Musashi die in that game, though.
* In real Life, Musashi`s Voice Actor Toku Nishio died on July 16, 2005.
Musashi`s very role in the original series has become something of a long-going anime archetype as well. The trend that every team of super robot pilots (or super heroes in general) must always have "the fat guy" was arguably jump started by Musashi. Even in subsequent Getter installments, the team must always have a large character pilot the third machine as a tradition (except for special occurrences). Musashi`s immediate replacement Benkei is himself a large stature man, and Gai in both Shin Getter Robo vs Neo Getter Robo and Getter Robo Armageddon and other subsequent appearances is enormous in both size and girth, particularly in Neo Getter Robo vs. Shin Getter Robo. This "role" in team formations has been spoofed many times in anime, and it has appeared far less frequently in the recent decade, mostly due to fat characters becoming far more rarely seen in anime in general in recent years.</description>
<picture>82090.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32210" type="main character in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="24">4.28</rating>
<name>Saotome Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82087.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32211" type="main character in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="74">8.24</rating>
<name>Nagare Ryouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagare Ryouma is a fictional character created by Go Nagai and Ken Ishikawa. He is the protagonist and main pilot in the Getter Robo franchise. He is a hot-blooded youth in high school. He pilots the Getter-1, Getter Dragon, and Shin Getter-1 in the manga and anime.
Ryouma goes to high school with Musashi, Hayato, and Michiru. He travels to the Satome Research Institute on the day the Prototype Getter Robo is being tested. He witnesses the death of the Prototype Getter Robo team including the son of Professor Tomoe at the hands of the Evil Dinosaur Empire. He enlists the aid of Musashi Tomoe and Hayato Jin in order to pilot the real Getter Robo. Ryoma piloting the Getter-1 is key to battling the Dinosaur Empire. Ryouma and his friends fight the Dinosaur Empire until the final battle in which Musahi gives his life to defeat them.
Even after the defeat of the Dinosaur Empire, a new threat arises in the form of the Clan of the 100 Demons. The remaining members of the Getter Robo team get Benkei Kurama to pilot the last jet of the Getter Robo G. Ryouma pilots the Getter Dragon in the second series.
In the 1998 OVA series Getter Robo Armageddon, Ryouma was framed for the murder of Dr. Saotome. After a resurrected Dr. Saotome threatens to destroy the world, he is released from jail to commit the very murder he was accused of. Ryouma holds a grudge with Hayato; who not only committed the murder of Saotome, he also testified against him. After failing to stop a nuclear attack on Shin Dragon, he vanishes from Earth. He reappears 13 years later in an abandoned base located on the Moon. He rejoins the fight against The Invaders piloting a customized Getter, the Black Getter.
Ryouma appears as a supporting characters in Shin Getter Robo vs Neo Getter Robo. Mentally scarred after being tortured by the Dinosaur Empire and the death of Musashi, he quits the Getter Team and wanders Japan as a martial artist. He returns and helps the New Getter Team when the Dinosaurs Empire attempts to destroy Shin Getter Robo.</description>
<picture>71452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32214" type="main character in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="8">5.91</rating>
<name>Kuruma Benkei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A baseball player, pilot of the third robot in the second series.</description>
<picture>82086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32215" type="main character in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="31">8.39</rating>
<name>Jin Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin Hayato is a fictional character from the mecha series, Getter Robo. The aloof and seemingly anti-social Hayato Jin, displays considerable skill at various sports, but generally likes to be left alone. Despite this he eventually gets all the girls, including the Kyoryu Empire android spies. Hayato pilots the Jaguar Machine into battle with Ryoma Nagare and Musashi Tomoe. When combined with the others he pilots Getter 2. The machine reflects Hayato`s physical strength and speed.</description>
<picture>82084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21114" picture="39572.jpg">Yamada Shunji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32221" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="6">3.33</rating>
<name>Saotome Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82422.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32237" type="main character in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="8">9.63</rating>
<name>Tsurugi Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An orphan young man raised by Dr. http://anidb.net/ch32239 [Kabuto Kenzou], trained to be the pilot of Great Mazinger ever since he was young. At first shown only as a bad-tempered young man with a heart of gold under his hotheadedness, he later develops a strong jealousy against his adoptive brother http://anidb.net/ch5122 [Kabuto Kouji].
Tetsuya served as the main character in Great Mazinger and first appeared in the final episode of Mazinger Z.
He also appears in Violence Jack, where he is brutally killed by the motorcycle gang known as Hell`s Wind. This prompts his lover, http://anidb.net/ch32238 [Honoo Jun], to seek vengeance for him.</description>
<picture>215857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2981" picture="23711.jpg">Noda Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32238" type="main character in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="6">3.33</rating>
<name>Honoo Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honoo Jun is a fictional character featured in the works of mangaka Go Nagai. She is the Heroine character in the Super Robot series Great Mazinger and pilots the title female robot Venus A.
Honoo Jun showed up in the first episode of Great Mazinger. An orphan girl raised by Kenzo Kabuto along with Tetsuya Tsurugi, she is half Japanese, half black (her father was a black man, and Jun has an old picture of him) and because of that she often felt rejected as a child. She was trained to pilot the female robot Venus A to support Great Mazinger.
Unlike previous female character Sayaka, who was well-meaning and brave yet had no real self-defense skills, Jun is very capable of defending herself outside of the robotic battlefield, as she showed her martial arts skills when she managed to fight back an attack of many soldiers alone, even if she is captured at the end of the fight. She was also specifically trained to use Venus A in combat for years, unlike Sayaka who had to learn to use Aphrodite and Diana as the story progressed. But similar to Sayaka, she argues and fights with Tetsuya and has an active role in the series. Jun, with Venus robot has a considerable firepower: missile-fingers, breast-missiles, (rechargeable differently than Aphrodite A), photonic-rays; but, while being far powerful than Aphrodite A, she is regularly defeated by the enemy monsters, and often badly damaged. While Mazinger is away (often there are two monsters, one of the two on a diversive action, while the other attacks the Mazinger`s base), Venus often fights alone, and is saved only by Boss`s robot. Typically, when the two are almost destroyed, finally Mazinger comes and destroys the second monster, just in time to save his fellows.
Jun is oppressed by her origins, since her father was an Afro-American (probably a reflex of the US occupation of Japan), her skin is darker than the usual and this apparently led some racism against Jun in her childhood, as displayed by several episodes. But, maybe related to her mixed origins, Jun is also a `junonic` girl, her body seems quite strong and muscular (especially if compared with the tiny Sayaka), but still very sexy; she wears a white, short skirt and a tight t-shirt. Boss, already a Sayaka fan, cannot resist to her gorgeous appearance, and falls instantly in love when meets her; however, Jun never shares that feeling. Basically, she is attracted by Tetsuya and always faithfully devoted to help him; but he is too hastily concentrated to train himself and fight the enemy (since he was a kid, he was raised by Dr. Kabuto like a `lethal weapon`) and apparently, he has no time for the love.
* Kabuto Shiro: After Koji and Sayaka left for the United States, Jun acted as an older sister to Shiro.
* Tsurugi Tetsuya: Jun was Tetsuya`s partner. They were raised together by Kenzo Kabuto in the USA and she often expressed some degree romantic feelings for him, yet she still argued with him when she thought he was wrong.
* Venus A: The female robot in Great Mazinger Series. Unlike Aphrodite A, Venus A was designed for battle. Some times, Jun showed great skills piloting it as she saved Tetsuya some times and managed to cause serious damage to some enemies but the end resault was similar to Aphrodite A as she gets severely damaged and needs help.
* Motorcycle: Like most of Go nagai characters, Jun drives a motorcycle in the series.
* Jun shows up in Violence Jack: Hell`s Wind, where Tetsuya Tsurugi is brutally killed by the evil biker gang, Hell`s Wind, which causes her to seek vengeance.
* Jun showed up in the first two episodes of Mazinkaiser OVA and worked in the institute as an assistant. In the end of the second episode, she left with Tetsuya to help him recover from his wounds. She showed up again in the finale episode with Tetsuya and helped Sayaka, Boss, Shiro and the others by taking them to Juzo Kabuto`s lab and explaining to them every thing they found in there.
* Jun showed up again in the Mazinkaiser vs General of Darkness movie but this time piloting the original Venus A. She and Tetsuya are the only two that survived from the Mazinger army. As she fought to repel the attack to Sydney, Venus was destroyed and virtually dismembered by the enemy, but despite being seriously injured (the scythe handled by the monster that attacked her almost cuts her in half), Jun survived due to the Queen Star ejecting out.</description>
<picture>215859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8055" picture="77674.jpg">Nakatani Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32239" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-12">
<rating votes="6">6.73</rating>
<name>Kabuto Kenzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kenzou was the son of Kabuto Juuzou, the inventor of Mazinger Z, but working in secret he improved upon the original designs to create the more formidable Great Mazinger. After a laboratory experiment that went wrong, he and his wife are thought to be dead. However, he was instead turned into a cyborg by his father in order to keep him alive. To shield them from danger and psychological shock, Kenzou`s sons Kouji and Shirou are unaware of this and grow believing both of their parents are dead, and were raised by Juuzou.
Kenzou reveals the truth to both of them in the Great Mazinger series, first to Shirou, since Kouji was away for a big part of the series, and their relationship would cause conflict with his adopted son Tsurugi Tetsuya, who was raised by Kenzou together with his best friend Jun and comes to feel intensely jealous of Kenzou`s actual children, especially so of Kouji. Dr. Kabuto would eventually die in battle at the end of the series and Tetsuya and Koji fight together to avenge his death.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>10466.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21669" update="2006-02-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63111" update="2006-09-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
