<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2231" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1980-03-15</startdate>
<enddate>1980-03-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginga Tetsudou 999: Glass no Clair</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Claire of the Glass: Galaxy Express 999</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガラスのクレア 銀河鉄道999</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="484" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999</anime>
<anime id="485" type="Alternative Setting">Ginga Tetsudou 999 (1979)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="4542" type="Chief Direction">Nishizawa Nobutaka</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="4808" type="Music">Aoki Nozomi</name>
<name id="5122" type="Chief Designer">Urata Mataji</name>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
</creators>
<description>This short movie is a remake of the first half of episode 3 of Ginga Tetsudou 999.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="144">6.03</permanent>
<temporary count="146">6.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3184.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3630</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6653</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2429</identifier>
<identifier>fpkgen</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>銀河鉄道999_(アニメ)#.E3.81.9D.E3.81.AE.E4.BB.96.E3.81.AE.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E5.85.AC.E9.96.8B.E4.BD.9C.E5.93.81</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>147112</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21953</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2493" type="main character in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="434">8.57</rating>
<name>Maetel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of Queen Prometheum, ruler of a mechanised empire.</description>
<picture>38136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3703" picture="151656.jpg">Ikeda Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12667" type="main character in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="64">4.76</rating>
<name>Hoshino Tetsurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tetsuro Hoshino is a young boy who was born on Earth into poverty, and who wants nothing more than a machine body. He also wants revenge on Count Mecha, an evil man who was given a machine body and now hunts humans for sport, for killing his mother. As a street urchin, Tetsuro has no means to buy a machine body. However, he has heard that at the end of the Andromeda Galaxy, there exists a planet where such robot bodies are given away for free. All Tetsuro needs to do is get a pass on the Galaxy Express 999, the cosmic railway. And one day, Tetsuro meets the mysterious Maetel, who promises to give him her unlimited use pass for the Express on the condition that she be his travelling companion. Tetsuro happily agrees, and embarks with Maetel on an adventure across the stars. When Tetsuro starts out, he is every bit the whiny, immature, selfish child. However, the adventures he goes with Maetel on, the people he meets, and the sights he witnesses cause Tetsuro to slowly but truly grow into a strong, young man. Tetsuro also grows closer and closer to Maetel, and although the nature of their relationship might not be called romantic, they form a very strong bond of love. Though it is never explicitly stated, it is implied that Tetsuro is Captain Harlock`s son. The evidence for this includes Tetsuro`s mother saying that his father is alive but away for some reason, Captain Harlock`s mysterious attachment to Tetsuro, and simple physical resemblance.</description>
<picture>38140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12668" type="main character in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="21">7.54</rating>
<name>Claire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dining car waitress on the 999, Claire has a machine body made of clear crystal glass. Unlike others who gave up their humanity by choice, Claire was forced into this existence by her vain mother. She works on the 999 in order to save up enough money to buy back her human body, which is stored on Pluto.</description>
<picture>38141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12669" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-31">
<rating votes="66">5.55</rating>
<name>Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main crew member of the Galaxy Express 999. He is an alien being with an invisible body; only his eyes can be seen while he is wearing his conductor uniform. The Conductor prefers to go `strictly by the book` and frequently cites the Galaxy Express rule book, but occasionally ends up bending the rules and getting into adventures with Tetsurou and Maetel.</description>
<picture>38142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21677" update="2009-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1980-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
