<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2257" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2004-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kishin Houkou Demonbane</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">DemonBane OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機神咆吼デモンベイン</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4021" type="Other">Kishin Houkou Demonbane (2006)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.demonbane.com/special2/ova.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1354" type="Original Work">Nitroplus</name>
<name id="923" type="Animation Work">View Works</name>
<name id="6824" type="Character Design">Hashimoto Hideki</name>
<name id="5259" type="Character Design">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="814" type="Original Work">Kadokawa Shoten</name>
<name id="513" type="Direction">Masuo Shouichi</name>
<name id="1319" type="Music">Zizz Studio</name>
<name id="21973" type="Original Work">Digiturbo</name>
<name id="8567" type="Character Design">Nishii</name>
<name id="774" type="Animation Work">Group Tac</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Zanmataisei Demonbane adult visual novel game by http://anidb.net/cr1354 [Nitroplus].
Lily Bridge, a young journalist, arrives at Arkham City, hoping to find a big scoop. However, with all the strange things occurring around the city, only the exceptional findings are newsworthy, such as the mysterious mecha known as Demonbane. However, upon finding a small piece of machinery that seemed to be connected with the Hadou Combine, Lily is determined to find the truth. Little does she know, that she will have to enter a dark world, when involving herself with Demonbane and the powerful forces that control the city.
Note: Bundled with the DX edition of the PS2 game by the same name.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="748">2.59</permanent>
<temporary count="758">5.69</temporary>
<review count="1">3.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>3338.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4933</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1444</identifier>
<identifier>igtysd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.demonbane.com/special2/ova.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Demonbane#Kishin_Houkou_Demonbane_OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>斬魔大聖デモンベイン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>231</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1500" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>grimoire</name>
<description>A grimoire is a textbook of magic. Such books typically include instructions on how to create magical objects like talismans and amulets, how to perform magical spells, charms and divination and also how to summon or invoke supernatural entities such as angels, spirits, and demons.</description>
<picurl>229110.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1681" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-05">
<name>journalist</name>
<description>A journalist is a person who collects, writes, or distributes news or other current information to the public. A journalist`s work is called journalism. A journalist can work with general issues or specialize in certain issues; however, most journalists tend to specialize. For example, a sports journalist covers news within the world of sports, but this journalist may be a part of a news organization that covers many different topics.
A reporter is a type of journalist who researches, writes, and reports on information in order to present in sources, conduct interviews, engage in research, and make reports. Reporters may split their time between working in a newsroom and going out to witness events or interviewing people. Reporters may be assigned a specific beat or area of coverage.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4084" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-20">
<name>dark atmosphere</name>
<description>Usually metaphorical. Sometimes literal. At times both!
Typically this refers to the fact that the story is set in a grim, dog eat dog milieu — for example a decaying city.
Often the characters are just doing what they need to do to survive, with little or no expectation that their lives can be better. And often characters may feel they do not have any real choice in what they do.
And yes, occasionally the setting is actually dark — be it night or perpetually heavy cloudy sky and rain. It all adds to the oppressive, hopeless feeling of the show.
You probably will not feel uplifted or happy after watching this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="22299" update="2014-03-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
