<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2263" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2004-12-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ryuusei Sentai Musumet</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">流星戦隊ムスメット</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Musumet</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Musumet: Las justicieras</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.musumet.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="794" type="Animation Work">TNK</name>
<name id="7154" type="Direction">Kimiya Shigeru</name>
<name id="7016" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hara Masaharu</name>
<name id="7016" type="Character Design">Hara Masaharu</name>
<name id="7542" type="Series Composition">Taki Kouichi</name>
<name id="4251" type="Original Work">Mutsuki Juuzou</name>
<name id="786" type="Original Work">Wonderfarm</name>
<name id="5132" type="Music">Sakai Ryou</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, seven shooting stars fell on to the ground. The shooting stars were colored by seven colors, and they have terrible powers. Those who took the shooting star were tuned into monsters by embodying their desires.
Dr. Mishina and Dr. Kishiwada obtained red, green, and blue stars secretly, and they studied the stars. Finally, they could successfully control their power by putting a special helmet on.
The newly developed helmet, "Musumet", was as large as an automobile helmet. Putting Musumet on the head, it turned a person`s body into the strongest one on the earth. Furthermore, it received the signal from the brain and amplified the inherent power and ability unlimitedly.
To utilize the power of "Musumet", to keep the world peace, and to protect from the disasters caused by the remaining shooting stars, Dr. Mishima and Dr. Kishida founded a secret organization "MET". However, he died before he accomplished his aim.
The bereaved daughters, Aoi, Midori, and Kurenai, made up their minds to become Musmet in order to execute the father`s will.
Even if they turned into Musumet, their wearing wouldn`t change except helmets, gloves, and boots. Therefore, they had to go to the scenes wearing their own clothes. The girls had to go to the incident spots occasionally wearing school uniforms, occasionally gymnasium suits, occasionally swimming suits, depending the case, they had to go there even if they were naked, and they would do great jobs. On the other hand, at other times, they were ordinal adolescent girls who were dreaming of lovely meetings with boyfriends.
Whether would they cope with the world peace and boyfriends at the same time?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="32">3.38</permanent>
<temporary count="32">6.04</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3438.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4602</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1711</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1425</identifier>
<identifier>xniitl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.wonderfarm.co.jp/musume/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>流星戦隊ムスメット</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>474</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7057</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="44271" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Mishina Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3601" picture="38507.jpg">Kawase Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44272" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<name>Musume Blue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3601" picture="38507.jpg">Kawase Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44273" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Mishina Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6786" picture="79639.jpg">Oosawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44274" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Musume Green</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6786" picture="79639.jpg">Oosawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44275" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Mishina Kurenai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21995" picture="19755.jpg">Matsumoto Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44276" type="main character in" update="2012-05-04">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Musume Red</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21995" picture="19755.jpg">Matsumoto Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60817" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-05">
<rating votes="2">9.65</rating>
<name>Saotome Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60818" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-26">
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<name>Otome Cyan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60819" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-05">
<rating votes="2">6.96</rating>
<name>Saotome Marcia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60820" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-26">
<name>Otome Magenta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60821" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-05">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Saotome Kou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60822" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-26">
<name>Otome Yellow</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23149" update="2004-10-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなただけよっ! 恋に焦がれてるムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Só você! Um ardente coração de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata Dake yo! Koi ni Kogareteru Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24927" update="2004-10-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">染まりたい! 微妙なムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Tinja-me como quiser. Um delicado coração de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Somaritai! Bimyou na Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25138" update="2004-10-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛び込みたいの! 夏の日のムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogue-se na água. Um coração de menina num dia de verão</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobikomitai no! Natsu no Nichi no Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25139" update="2004-10-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守ってあげたい! 遠い日のムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Vou te proteger com ternura!. Um saudoso coração de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamotte Agetai! Tooi Nichi no Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26357" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">やっとわかった! 告白したいムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Finalmente eu entendo! Um coração aberto de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yatto Wakatta! Kokuhaku Shitai Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45882" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どこ? 見えなくなったムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Onde eu estou? Um coração cego de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doko? Mienaku Natta Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45883" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぜ? 迷路をさまようムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Por quê? Um coração errante de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naze? Meiro o Samayou Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45884" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしはここ! 燃え上がるムスメ心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Estou aqui meu amor! Um coração apaixonado de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Koko! Moeagaru Musume Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45885" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハロー! 麗しのオトメ達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Olá belas senhoritas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hello! Uruwashi no Otome-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45886" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トゥルーなラブをプリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eu quero um amor verdadeiro, por favor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True na Love o Please</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45887" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グッバイ マイ ラブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Adeus meu amor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goodbye My Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45888" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">届けオトメ心! 闇を貫けムスメ心!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Penetre na escuridão e envie o amor dos corações de menina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoke Otome Kokoro! Yami o Tsuranuke Musume Kokoro!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45889" update="2006-01-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムスメの真心, オトメの純真</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Corações Sinceros e Corações Puros</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musume no Magokoro, Otome no Junshin</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
