<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2270" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1982-03-13</startdate>
<enddate>1982-03-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sekai Meisaku Douwa: Aladdin to Mahou no Lamp</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Aladdin and the Magic Lamp</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">O Aladynie i Zaczarowanej Lampie</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Alaaddin`in Sihirli Lambası</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Aladdin to Mahou no Lamp</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="short">علاء الدين</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世界名作童話 アラジンと魔法のランプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aladdin and the Wonderful Lamp</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Aladin und die Wunderlampe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Aladin et la lampe merveilleuse</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La Lampada di Aladino</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Lampa Aladyna</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">علاء الدين والمصباح السحري</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Aladino e a Lâmpada Mágica</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Aladdin E A Lâmpada Maravilhosa</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Aladinova kouzelná lampa</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Aladdin en de Wonderlamp</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Aladdinin Taikalamppu</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Ο Αλαντίν και το Μαγικό Λυχνάρι</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Aladdin és a csodalámpa</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="36015" type="Music">Tsubonou Katsuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>This film stays very faithful to the original down to the smallest details, save for the kangaroo-rat that suddenly appears twenty minutes into the movie and subsequently follows Aladdin around, serving no purpose in the story but fulfilling the role of token animal mascot. The screenwriter needs no introduction; Akira Miyazaki single-handedly wrote five of the classic WMT series, including Perrine and Rascal, and participated in two others. The only other name among the staff that rings a bell, though, is Yukihide Takekawa, who was responsible for the music in the magnificent and unknown Unico pilot film.
The story takes some illogical and confusing jumps at the point where Aladdin begins to court the princess, and the extravagant animation that had characterised Toei films of the 60s, when Toei had the best animators around, had become a thing of the past long before this point; but this is still an above-average film, in large part because of the screenplay that stays so faithful to the original. The character designs are slightly more western-looking than one is accustomed to seeing in anime.
Source: http://web.archive.org/web/20050926172429/http://www.pelleas.net/dbman/db.cgi?db=wmt&amp;uid=default&amp;ID=128&amp;view_records=1</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="69">4.13</permanent>
<temporary count="69">5.78</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>150345.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3651</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3119</identifier>
<identifier>uubqdk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>148014</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="21685" update="2005-09-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>1982-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
