<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2293" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>40</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-01-13</startdate>
<enddate>1991-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Trapp Ikka Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Story of the Trapp Family Singers</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">La Novicia Rebelde</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">トラップ一家物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Trapp Family Story</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die singende Familie Trapp</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Les enfants du capitaine Trapp</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Cantiamo Insieme</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Cantemos Juntos</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Rodzina Trappów</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">لحن الحياة</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">A Família Trapp</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7154" type="Summary">Sekai Meisaku Gekijou Kanketsu Ban: Trapp Ikka Monogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="508247">I watched this many times when I was young and I found it very touching , I recommend it to those who like animes based on famous novels</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/kidstop/meisaku/trapp/trapp.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3639" type="Direction">Kusuba Kouzou</name>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="3653" type="Character Design">Seki Shuuichi</name>
<name id="5083" type="Music">Kazato Shinsuke</name>
<name id="10124" type="Original Work">Maria von Trapp</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the true story of the von Trapp family, the inspiration for Sound of Music.
The von Trapp family lives in the beautiful town of Salzburg, in Austria. Maria, a nun from the convent, is sent to the family as a private tutor for its seven mischievous children. She loves to sing songs.
Through music, Maria develops friendships with the children and becomes a member of the family.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="141">6.57</permanent>
<temporary count="146">7.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>146972.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1758</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1017</identifier>
<identifier>mmeqlb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/1601/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Trapp_Family_Story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トラップ一家物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89097</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>934</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2689" parentid="2641" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-02">
<name>1920s</name>
<description>During the 1920s, we had gangsters, Mafia, alcohol, and gambling prohibition.
The Corleones ruled that time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2691" parentid="2641" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-21">
<name>World War II</name>
<description>World War II, or the Second World War (often abbreviated WWII or WW2), was a global military conflict which involved most of the world`s nations, including all great powers, organised into two opposing military alliances: the Allies and the Axis. The war involved the mobilisation of over 100 million military personnel, making it the most widespread war in history. In a state of "total war," the major participants placed their entire economic, industrial, and scientific capabilities at the service of the war effort, erasing the distinction between civilian and military resources. Over seventy million people, the majority civilians, were killed, making it the deadliest conflict in human history.
The start of the war is generally held to be September 1, 1939, with the invasion of Poland by Nazi Germany and subsequent declarations of war on Germany by most of the countries in the British Empire and Commonwealth, and by France. Many countries were already at war before this date, such as Ethiopia and Italy in the Second Italo-Abyssinian War and China and Japan in the Second Sino-Japanese War. Many who were not initially involved joined the war later, as a result of events such as the German invasion of the Soviet Union, the attacks on Pearl Harbor and British colonies, and subsequent declarations of war on Japan by the United States, the Netherlands, and British Commonwealth.
In 1945, the war ended in a victory for the Allies. The Soviet Union and the United States subsequently emerged as the world`s superpowers, setting the stage for the Cold War which continued for the next 46 years. The United Nations was formed in the hope of preventing another world conflict. The acceptance of the principle of self-determination accelerated decolonization movements in Asia and Africa, while Western Europe itself began moving toward integration.
------
About the picture
Top left: Battle of Wuhan
Top right: Second Battle of El Alamein
Middle left: Battle of Stalingrad
Middle right: German dive bombers over Eastern Front winter 1943-1944
Bottom left: Wilhelm Keitel signing German Instrument of Surrender
Bottom right: Invasion of Lingayen Gulf</description>
<picurl>40430.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3763" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>Sekai Meisaku Gekijou</name>
<description>World Masterpiece Theatre is a Japanese TV anime staple that showcases an animated version of a different classical book or story each year. It originally aired from 1969 to 1997 and then resumed in 2007. WMT series were originally produced by http://anidb.net/cr833 [Mushi Production] and Zuiyo Eizo, and then by the latter`s successor http://anidb.net/cr728 [Nippon Animation], and originally air primarily on http://anidb.net/cr741 [Fuji Television].
The series has been known by various different names over the years, often reflecting changes to the sponsors, but "World Masterpiece Theatre" is the name most commonly used by viewers. Nippon Animation`s official English name for the series is The Classic Family Theater Series.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>234097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4616" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>based on real events</name>
<description>Contains content based on real-life events.
Depending on the creators` wishes those events may have been altered. In the most substantial cases, expect many things to have been changed from the original events.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="39057" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, 修道女志願です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Aspiration to be a Catholic Nun</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ankunft in Salzburg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arrivée au couvent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46831" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シスターとしての未来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Future as a Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine neue Aufgabe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une deuxième chance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46832" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">艦長と7人の子供たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Captain and His Seven Children</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Familie Trapp</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On fait les présentations</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46833" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">26人目の家庭教師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 26th Governess</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Streit mit der Baronesse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celle qu`on n`attendait plus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46834" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリアは騒ぎの張本人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maria is the Ringleader of Commotion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Marias traurige Geschichte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour en arrière</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46835" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷子とはらぺこ騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Riot and a Stray Child</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufregung im Hause Trapp</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Johanna a disparu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46836" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人は信じられない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unbelievable Adult</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die neue Hauslehrerin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comment apprivoiser les enfants</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46837" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">礼儀作法が大事です!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Etiquette is Important!?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Spielen verboten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fiancée du baron</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46838" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トラップ男爵の婚約者?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap Baron`s Fiance?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Prinzessin Yvonne</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bon exemple</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46839" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミシンとヴァイオリン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seweing Machine and Violin</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Schatz im Keller</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une machine à coudre et un violon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46840" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どろんこ遊びは最高!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Asobi is the Highest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein lustiges Picknick</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une démarche à la campagne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46841" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリア風チョコレートケーキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marias Style and Devil`s Food Cake</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schokoladentorte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le gâteau au chocolat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46842" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドン・キホーテの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don Quixote`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Fechtturnier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un cœur brisé</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46843" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルゴールの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret of the Music Box</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geheimnis der Spieluhr</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La statuette cassée</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46844" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルティナと熊のニコラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Martina and Her Bear Nicholoas</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Geburtstagsüberraschung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nicolette s`est noyée</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46845" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリア先生がいない家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">House Where Maria Doesn`t Exist</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Komm zurück Maria</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maria, revenez !</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46846" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷ついた子鹿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hurt Fawn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das verletzte Reh</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Werner et la faon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46847" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生きとし生けるもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One That is Assumed Living and Arranged</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lebwohl, kleines Reh</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fanfan la tulipe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46848" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イヴォンヌ姫のお土産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prince Yvonne`s Souvernir</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mit der Sprache des Herzens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour de Natacha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46849" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの人生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Each Life</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein böser Sturz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Personne n`est blessé</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46850" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トラップ男爵の決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap Baron`s Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Heimkehr aus dem Krankenhaus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le baron s`est enfin décidé</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46851" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1人で生きてゆけるの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can You Live Alone?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hedwig reißt aus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fugue d`Edwige</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46852" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使への願い事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wish to the Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Martinas größter Wunsch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Préparatifs de Noël</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46853" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス・キャロル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Carol</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fröhliche Weihnachten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Joyeux Noël</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46854" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白銀のアルプスにて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Silvery White Alps</title>
<title xml:lang="de">In den Alpen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sports d`hiver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46855" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレンジと花の苗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orange and Flower Seedling</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Nacht im Schloß</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une orange et une rose des Alpes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46856" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">昨日・今日・明日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Ausreißerin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De vieux souvenirs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46857" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いたずらアガーテ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischief Agathe</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Agathe, die Schuhe und die Schere</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Agathe et ses bêtises</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46858" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妻になる人, 母になる人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Person Who Becomes Wife and Mother</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Träume der Kinder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une épouse et une mère</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46859" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">結婚してくれますね!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marriage?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die entscheidende Frage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La demande en mariage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46860" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">神様の思し召し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desire and the Summons of God</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine neue Mutter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La période de réflexion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46861" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">七月の花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bride in July</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hochzeitsglocken</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mariage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46862" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Family</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die wahren Freunde</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une si jolie famille</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46863" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファミリー合唱団誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family Chorus Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der erste Auftritt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le concours de chant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46864" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌声は風にのって</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Singing Voice of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Radio</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un heureux événement</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46865" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナチス侵攻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nazi`s Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Fliege im Hals</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`honneur est sauf</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46866" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたらしいご挨拶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New greeting</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die neuen Lehrer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un régime sec</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46867" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハンスの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hans` Secrets</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geheimnis des Butlers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est la célébrité</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46868" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誇りと信念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boast and Belief</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vor der Flucht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin d`une époque</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46869" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さようならわが祖国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good-bye to the Mother Country</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nächtliche Flucht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un nouveau départ</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124148" update="2010-10-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1991-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124149" update="2010-10-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1991-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
