<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2339" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>18</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2004-12-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sweet Valerian</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スウィート・ヴァレリアン</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Słodki Walerian</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Sweet Valerian</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.aniplex.co.jp/sweetvalerian/</url>
<creators>
<name id="15233" type="Series Composition">Ooba Sayuri</name>
<name id="747" type="Main Character Design">Clamp</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Plan">Clamp</name>
<name id="26263" type="Music">Double Oats</name>
<name id="2194" type="Direction">Sakurai Hiroaki</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="1521" type="Character Design">Yamakawa Yoshiki</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on something by http://anidb.net/cr747 [CLAMP].
The Stress Team floats over the city, locating stressed out people and transforming them into monsters. To combat this, three young girls reluctantly transform into the Sweet Valerians, bunny defenders of justice.
Source: ANN
Note: Episodes 19 to 26 are DVD only and weren`t broadcast on TV back in 2004.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="209">2.99</permanent>
<temporary count="216">5.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3281.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3863</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2727</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1470</identifier>
<identifier>rgfkkx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.aniplex.co.jp/sweetvalerian/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sweet_Valerian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スウィート・ヴァレリアン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="22729" update="2006-05-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷろろ~ぐ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Prologue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22813" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">携帯電話ストレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cell Phone Stress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keitaidenwa Stress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23447" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バーゲン会場ストレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bargain Sale Stress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bargain Kaijou Stress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23677" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴァレリアンになっちゃった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Became Valerians</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valerian ni Nacchatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23942" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">人肌ラーメン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Popular Ramen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitohada Ramen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24417" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">満員電車でゆらりんストレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stress on a Shaky Crowded Train</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manin Densha de Yurarin Stress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26588" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, つつましく暮らしてます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Me and My Humble Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi, Tsutsumashiku Kurashitemasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27228" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, 代表取締役社長</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Me, the Company`s Director</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi, Daihyoutorishimariyaku Shachou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27229" update="2006-07-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, 不思議少女なの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Me, a Mysterious Girl?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi, Fushigi Shoujo na no?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35999" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ストレス団にもボスがいた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stress Group Has a Boss Too</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stress-dan ni mo Boss ga ita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36000" update="2007-01-07">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ズル休み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneaking Away from Work</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zuruyasumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36001" update="2006-11-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地味なジミー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plain Jimmy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jimi na Jimmy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36697" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とぐろ峠でカーチェイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Car Chase on the Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doguro Touge de Car Chase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36698" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あみだすぞ必殺技</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Make a Special Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amidasu zo Hissatsuwaza</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36699" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">う~ん, マリリアンヌ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mmmh, Maririan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uun, Maririan~</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37382" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴァレリアンに入りたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Become a Valerian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valerian ni Naritai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38035" update="2006-10-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパーストレスボス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Stress Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Super Stress Boss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38036" update="2006-12-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">やったね! スウィート・ヴァレリアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You did it! Sweet Valerian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yatta ne! Sweet Valerian</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82737" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙ストレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Universe Stress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Stress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82738" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴミはきちんと捨てろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Throw Away Your Trash!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomi wa Kichinto Sutero!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="83025" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">通販ストレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delivery Stress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuuhan Stress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90572" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">気になる少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intriguing Young Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ki ni Naru Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90573" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あのモンスターは?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Monster Is?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Monster wa?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90612" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ストレス解消温泉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stress-Rid Hot Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stress Kaishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90613" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">昔々のカチカチ山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Once Upon a Time at Mt. Kachi-kachi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukashi Mukashi no Kachi-kachi San</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90614" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンスターだらけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Covered in Monsters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monster Darake</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
