<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2340" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2005-04-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kappa no Kaikata</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kappa Caretaker</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カッパの飼い方</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">How to Breed Kappas</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.kappanokaikata.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="969" type="Animation Work">Picture Magic</name>
<name id="1125" type="Original Work">Ishikawa Yuugo</name>
<name id="4601" type="Series Composition">Miyazaki Nagisa</name>
<name id="4601" type="Direction">Miyazaki Nagisa</name>
<name id="9539" type="Music">Tsurugi Masaki</name>
<name id="5716" type="Character Design">Kusumoto Yuuko</name>
</creators>
<description>A young man passes a pet shop on his way home. He sees a kappa in the window, and decides to buy it on a whim. He brings the creature home, and names him Kaatan. He`s never owned a kappa before, so he relies heavily on a book he purchased on the subject of raising and training kappa. The books gives several good tips for bringing up a smart and well behaved kappa, and it all seems very simple. Unfortunately, putting these techniques into practice and actually making them work is not quite as easy as the book implies. Kaatan seems to understand things at first, but usually ends up either forgetting what he`s learned, or isn`t interested in learning in the first place. However, this particular young man has a lot of patience, and continues his possibly fruitless effort to raise Kaatan into be a pet he can be proud of.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="166">3.47</permanent>
<temporary count="168">5.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3279.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4492</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1883</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1615</identifier>
<identifier>krkmck</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kappanokaikata.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kappa_no_Kaikata</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>カッパの飼い方</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>522</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321273</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="23400" type="main character in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Kaatan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Watashi picked up Kaatan on a whim from Sakamoto-san`s pet shop. Like other kappas his age, Kaatan is cute, but a handful when it comes to training. Watashi tries to teach him but what Kaatan learns is not always what Watashi was trying to teach!</description>
<picture>58629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1995" picture="21297.jpg">Kanzaki Chiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23401" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-19">
<name>Sakamoto Misako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30014">Yamauchi Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23402" type="main character in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Watashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Watashi is a young salaryman living alone in Tokyo. He grew up with a kappa as a child in the mountains of Nara, which is maybe why he decided to get a young kappa and train it. He has a crush on Sakamoto-san.</description>
<picture>57257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="559" picture="41052.jpg">Hagiwara Masato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23404" type="appears in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Kyuu-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuu-chan is one of Sakamoto-san`s kappas that she is unable to sell, as he has a crack in his shell. In spite of this, Sakamoto-san had taken him from the breeder. After some initial fighting, Kyuu-chan has become good friends with Kaatan.</description>
<picture>58628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23405" type="appears in" update="2010-10-19">
<name>Yopparai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7237">Hirata Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23467" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Maa-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maa-chan is shy and introverted.</description>
<picture>58624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30014">Yamauchi Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23468" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Tamada-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamada-san is the proud owner of Kakkun.</description>
<picture>58626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24795" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Kakkun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kakkun is older and bigger than Kaatan and the others, as he is now 3 years old. He is quite intelligent and can even go shopping by himself. He acts as a big brother to the younger kappas and helps keep them out of trouble.</description>
<picture>58623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24796" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Hercules</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hercules is a grim-looking kappa who sits all by himself on a bench in the corner of the park. He is feared by humans, animals and kappas alike -- except Kaatan. This fear is well-founded, as he has shown that he has the skill to remove spirit balls from various living beings.
In reality, his actual name is Chii-chan, and he can`t even eat his spirit candy unless Miyo-chan feeds him. He desperately wants to learn to play the trumpet, but his beak is a bit of an impediment.</description>
<picture>58632.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22341" picture="58604.jpg">Takayama Yoshihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24797" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Josei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24798" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30014">Yamauchi Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24799" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Tadokoro-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tadokoro-san is a manager at an ironworks. He lost his wife and daughter in a traffic accident several years ago, and has only Maa-chan for company now. Because of this, he tends to spoil Maa-chan a little.</description>
<picture>58631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24800" type="appears in" update="2010-11-06">
<name>Miyo-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyo-chan is the kindergarten-going girl who owns Chii-chan aka Hercules.</description>
<picture>58625.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24802" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Kaatan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When http://anidb.net/ch23402 [Watashi] was still a young boy, his father found Kaatan as a young kappa, crying on the hill behind their house. After that, he was brought up almost as Watashi`s elder brother (as kappas grow much faster than humans). He was with the family for the passing of Watashi`s grandfather and father, and now stays with his aging mother.</description>
<picture>58617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7237">Hirata Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24803" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Pan Ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A baker frequented by http://anidb.net/ch23402 [Watashi]. He doesn`t seem to good at reading orders.</description>
<picture>58602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8994" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24804" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Isha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A doctor/veterinarian who treats kappas. He knows what he is doing, but he is quite expensive!</description>
<picture>58598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8994" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24805" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Kyodai Kappa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="559" picture="41052.jpg">Hagiwara Masato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24806" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Watashi no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch23402 [Watashi]`s elderly mother. She lives alone, with only the http://anidb.net/ch24802 [old Kaatan] for company.</description>
<picture>58608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22343" picture="58611.jpg">Araki Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24807" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Nikuya no Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A butcher frequented by http://anidb.net/ch23468 [Tamada-san].</description>
<picture>58601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8994" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23156" update="2005-03-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんを飼う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25059" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんと遊ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25199" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんをしつける (その1)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25563" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんをしつける (その2)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26187" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんをしつける (その3)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26244" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キューちゃんのこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26576" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">坂本さんとキューちゃんが来る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27428" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 01!) Breakfast</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27429" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="5">P2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">(Parody of ep 02!) Sumomomomo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27782" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんとキューちゃん友達になる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30290" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたん初めての散歩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 09</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30670" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたん公園デビュー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33695" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘラクレスと都市伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35875" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2004-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘラクレスと尻子玉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36328" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">尻子玉のこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36409" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕焼け小焼けと尻子玉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36556" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんの大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37780" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたん初泳ぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39302" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カッパの川流れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39565" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">息継ぎは難しい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40324" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マアちゃんのこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40622" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたん海へ行く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40751" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サメと尻子玉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40794" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたん夏バテする</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40860" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かっくんはじめてのお使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40861" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんはじめてのお使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40862" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かっぱとラッパ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40863" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かぁたんと田舎へ帰る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Raise a Water Imp 26</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
