<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2358" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1983-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>1983-07-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Xabungle Graffiti</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ザブングルグラフィティ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2357" type="Full Story">Sentou Mecha Xabungle</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=247</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Animation Production">Sunrise</name>
<name id="25816" type="Original Work">Suzuki Yoshitake</name>
<name id="4287" type="Music">Makaino Kouji</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Plan">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="147" type="Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3485" type="Character Design">Kogawa Tomonori</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="18">6.13</permanent>
<temporary count="18">6.50</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6511.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5303</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2476</identifier>
<identifier>gxshln</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=247</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4194</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>148637</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="45700" type="main character in" update="2013-08-26">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Jiron Amos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Main character of Xabungle. Jiron is a young man who witnessed his parents` murder at the hands of a breaker named Timp Sharon and swears revenge. Seeking to steal a Walker Machine, the Xabungle, he teams up with the Sand Rats group of bandits and is able to do so. Very headstrong, he ignores the "three day rule" imposed by the Innocent and makes multiple attempts to defeat Timp, often with disastrous results.
Over the course of the series Jiron is one of the Iron Gear`s most accomplished Walker Machine pilots and mid-way through the series he upgrades to the Gallier. He later becomes leader of the Solt organization rebelling against the Innocent.
Jiron is very dedicated to Elchi and attempts numerous times to rescue her following her capture by the Innocent, despite his allies disagreeing with him.</description>
<picture>89198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32843" picture="88844.jpg">Kotaki Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45701" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<name>Rag Uralo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Sand Rat group of bandits who assists Jiron in stealing the Xabungle and later joins him aboard the Iron Gear. Rag doesn`t hold much loyalty to the Iron Gear and has plans to steal it someday. At one point she leaves the Iron Gear and stays with Akon Akag, one of Kid Horla`s subordinates, but returns to it following his death. She later shows a lot of admiration for Katakam as well. She is often in conflict with Elchi.</description>
<picture>89200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2055" picture="21393.jpg">Shimazu Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45702" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Chill</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young girl who is a part of the Sand Rats group of bandits and joins up with the Iron Gear.</description>
<picture>89203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3701" picture="25016.jpg">Tarako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45708" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Arthur Rank</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Innocent, although Kashim King keeps him unaware of what is actually happening. Jiron and other members of the Solt organization desire to speak to him and they eventually take him from Kashim`s clutches, revealing the truth to him. Arthur`s good looks cause many of the female members of Solt to develop a crush on him. In bad health outside of the domes, Arthur nonetheless works to communicate to the Innocent that it is time to hand over the planet to the civilians and assists Jiron and the others in fighting against Kashim.
He sacrifices himself in order to return Elchi to normal, taking on the evil personality that had been implanted in her and jumps out of the Iron Gear to his death.</description>
<picture>89233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45711" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<name>Timp Sharon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A breaker who works for the Innocent to instigate conflicts. He is the man who killed Jiron`s parents, and as a result Jiron is obsessed with getting his revenge on him. Following multiple battles against Jiron he fakes his own death and disappears for a while. He later turns up again and battles the Iron Gear and Jiron multiple times to the end of the series.</description>
<picture>89230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45712" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Guiro Biel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guiro acts as an assistant to Timp Sharon on his landship late in the series.</description>
<picture>89189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3310" picture="24332.jpg">Mizutori Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45713" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Fatman Big</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elchi`s bodyguard and servant. He is obsessed with protecting her, and during the second half of the series when she is in the clutches of the Innocent he makes multiple attempts to rescue her and bring her back to normal. He is typically silent although he does speak some basic words along with Elchi`s name later in the series.
During the final battle he appears to have died while protecting Elchi, but to everyone`s surprise suddenly appears alive again in the final scene.</description>
<picture>89204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45714" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<name>Kotsett Memuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief mechanic on the Iron Gear, as well as its main pilot throughout the series.</description>
<picture>89205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3219" picture="228523.jpg">Hiromori Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45717" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<name>Maria Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A peaceful girl who takes care of orphans and grows vegetables. She is initially against fighting, but later in the series joins up with the Solt organization along with Medic Held, acting largely as a medic.</description>
<picture>89226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34641">Nomura Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45720" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Elchi Cargo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of Carrying Cargo, she becomes its captain following his death. Elchi is obsessed with culture and often has aspirations of abandoning the Iron Gear as a result, but continuously returns to it. She angers easily and is often in conflict with many members of the Iron Gear crew. In the second half of the series she is captured by the Innocent and brainwashed into desiring the destruction of the Iron Gear and the death of Jiron. She is given the Iron Gear-like landship Gear Gear, and later another landship which she calls the Carrying. She launches multiple attacks on the Iron Gear with these ships. She is often in conflict with her subordinates.

As the series draws to a close Elchi is captured by Jiron and the others. They are able to remove her brainwashing by shifting her new personality to Arthur Rank, and Elchi returns to her normal self. During the final battle she fights against Kashim and Viram but is blinded by an explosion.
</description>
<picture>89199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3240" picture="45305.jpg">Yokoo Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45721" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Blume</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Sand Rats group of bandits that helps out Jiron and joins him on the Iron Gear. Like Rag, Blume does not hold much long term loyalty to the Iron Gear and eventually decides to abandon it, temporarily acquiring his own landship. He later returns to the Iron Gear for the remainder of the series.</description>
<picture>89201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45722" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Dyke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Sand Rats group of bandits that helps out Jiron and joins him on the Iron Gear. Dyke is a helpful and loyal member of the team and occasionally assists with the piloting of Walker Machines.</description>
<picture>89202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3364" picture="52550.jpg">Yamashita Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45732" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<name>Kid Horla</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A breaker who worked under Carrying Cargo. He is obsessed with Elchi and desires for her to marry him. After his initial attempt to marry Elchi and take over the Iron Gear fails, he flees, then later works with the Innocent against the Iron Gear. His obsession with Elchi remains throughout the series.</description>
<picture>89231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45734" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Kassim King</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The elderly Kashim is de facto leader of the Innocent, being able to accomplish his ideals while hiding certain facts from true Innocent leader, Arthur Rank. Towards the end of the series he becomes the primary antagonist and makes multiple attempts to destroy the Iron Gear and Solt organization, as well as Arthur himself. It is his personality that was implanted into Elchi`s during her brainwashing.

During the final battle, Kashim`s plan to attack the Xabungle with a missile backfires when it causes other missiles to topple and go off, resulting in his death.
</description>
<picture>89236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45735" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<name>Geraba Geraba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A breaker who initially worked under Carrying Cargo, and acts as Kid Horla`s subordinate throughout the series.</description>
<picture>89238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="22173" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>1983-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155318" update="2013-10-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
