<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2359" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-07-23</startdate>
<enddate>2005-07-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Hagane no Renkinjutsushi: Shambala o Yuku Mono</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fullmetal Alchemist (2005)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fullmetal Alchemist: The Conqueror of Shambala</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fullmetal Alchemist: The Conqueror of Shamballa</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Стальной алхимик - Завоеватель Шамбалы</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Стальной алхимик - Фильм</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Цельнометаллический алхимик: Завоеватель Шамбаллы</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الخيميائي المعدني: محتل شمباله</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Metal Simyacı: Shamballa Fatihi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hagaren The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="short">钢炼剧场版</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">fma movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hagaren movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 鋼の錬金術師 シャンバラを征[ゆ]く者</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">钢之炼金术师剧场版 香巴拉的征服者</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist the Movie: Conqueror of Shamballa</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - Der Film: Der Eroberer von Shamballa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - The Movie: Conqueror of Shamballa</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist: Il Conquistatore di Shambala</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - El conquistador de Shambala</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">강철의 연금술사 - 샴발라의 정복자</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist The Movie: Conqueror of Shamballa</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - Dobyvatel Shambally</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Μεταλλικός Αλχημιστής, η Ταινία</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - Shamballa hódítója</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">แขนกลคนแปรธาตุ เดอะมูฟวี่ ฝ่ามิติพิชิตแดนสวรรค์</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - Cuceritorul Şambalei</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Стоманеният Алхимик - Завоевателят на Шамбала</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">剧场版 钢之炼金术师 香巴拉的征服者</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="979" type="Prequel">Hagane no Renkinjutsushi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9541" approval="1" total="11">Shingeki no Kyojin</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="377192">Full Metal Alchemist, nothing more to say. Must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/hagaren/hagaren-movie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="130" type="Direction">Mizushima Seiji</name>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
<name id="7788" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="670" type="Story Composition">Aikawa Shou</name>
<name id="1007" type="Original Work">Arakawa Hiromu</name>
<name id="7788" type="Character Design">Itou Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="29176" type="Chief Animation Direction">Katou Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>Münich, Germany, 1923. Two years have passed since http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward Elric] was dragged from his own world to ours, leaving behind his country, his friends and his younger brother, http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse Elric]. Stripped of his alchemical powers, all this time he has been researching rocketry together with http://anidb.net/ch12232 [Alphonse Heiderich], a young man very much resembling his own brother, hoping to one day find a way back home.
His efforts so far have proven fruitless, but when he hears that the Thule Society, an occult group strongly tied to the Nazi Party, discovered what could be a clue to the location of the legendary, mystical place called Shamballa, Edward`s hopes are renewed. Meanwhile, in his own world, Alphonse Elric ventures deeper into the mysteries of alchemy in search for a way to reunite with his older brother.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9285">7.04</permanent>
<temporary count="9395">7.92</temporary>
<review count="10">7.29</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221539.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4176</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>430</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1619</identifier>
<identifier>lsvrpq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/fullmetal-alchemist-shamballa</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/hagaren/hagaren-movie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fullmetal_Alchemist_the_Movie:_Conqueror_of_Shamballa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版_鋼の錬金術師_シャンバラを征く者</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7167</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fullmetal-alchemist-the-conqueror-of-shamballa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9403</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2392" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-18">
<name>manipulative</name>
<description>Enjoy controlling people without them knowing, usually tricking people into doing stuff for them</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3342" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-19">
<name>Nazis</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5885" type="main character in" update="2009-05-02">
<rating votes="872">8.35</rating>
<name>Edward Elric</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Edward, the "Fullmetal Alchemist", is the youngest State Alchemist in history of the country and the main character of the series. He and his younger brother, Alphonse Elric, scour the world in search of the Philosopher`s Stone in the hopes of restoring their bodies.</description>
<picture>24292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5908" type="main character in" update="2009-05-02">
<rating votes="521">6.18</rating>
<name>Alphonse Elric</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a human child who lost his body during an alchemic experiment to bring his deceased mother back to life, and had his soul "attached" to a suit of armor by his brother, Edward Elric.
Al`s blood seal lies just below the base of the neck at the back of the suit, on the inside. It is drawn with Ed`s blood. According to Edward, he needs to be careful whenever he reconstructs Alphonse`s body because he must keep the blood seal intact during the transmutation. If the blood seal is removed, Al`s soul will be lost.</description>
<picture>24291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5909" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="199">2.87</rating>
<name>Gluttony</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the first homunculi introduced in the series, typically appears in the company of http://anidb.net/ch6591 [Lust]. He is a large, simple-minded homunculus whose thoughts rarely stray far from eating. He has powerful jaws and acidic saliva, and can and will eat almost anything. He particularly likes eating people, and the only way he can find enjoyment in a battle is if he can eat his opponent afterwards.</description>
<picture>24242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6586" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-05">
<rating votes="646">8.49</rating>
<name>Roy Mustang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roy Mustang, the Flame Alchemist, is a State Alchemist and officer in the Amestrian State Military. A hero of the Ishval Civil War and http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward Elric]`s superior officer, Colonel Mustang is a remarkably capable commander who plans one day soon to become the next Führer of Amestris.</description>
<picture>24234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6587" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="432">8.12</rating>
<name>Riza Hawkeye</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant Riza Hawkeye is an officer in the Amestrian State Military as well as the personal adjutant and bodyguard of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Colonel Roy Mustang]. A sharpshooter and weapons specialist, Lt. Hawkeye is an invaluable asset to the Colonel both in office and on the battlefield and serves as his closest and most supportive subordinate.</description>
<picture>24235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6588" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-16">
<rating votes="480">7.31</rating>
<name>Winry Rockbell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Winry Rockbell is a close childhood friend of http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] Elric since their young life in Resembool, she is almost like a sister to the two and essentially their only family. An amateur surgeon and mechanical repair specialist/enthusiast, Winry acts as Edward`s rear line support as his personal automail engineer and mechanic, making sure his prosthetic right arm and left leg are always in good working order. Additionally, she provides a great deal of emotional support for the pair and somewhat plays the role of the love interest in the story.</description>
<picture>24236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6589" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="371">7.07</rating>
<name>Alex Louis Armstrong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alex Louis Armstrong, the "Strong Arm Alchemist," is a large and comically emotional State Alchemist who will burst into tears or joyous praise, given the right situation, and embraces others in an effort to console them. Because he is an extremely strong character, this usually causes great personal injury to others. Armstrong is very proud of his strength and of his muscular physique, frequently taking off his shirt so that he can flex for the benefit of others. As a final element of his comedic properties, he has the tendency to "sparkle"; when first appearing in a scene or taking off his shirt, pink stars radiate from his body. Despite his humorous tendencies, Armstrong can be very serious when the situation calls for it. He is not fond of violence and will try to end conflicts peacefully, and will break down and cry if an innocent person is killed.
Armstrong comes from a wealthy family of aristocrats who have earned renown in most professions. He has mastered many of his family`s talents for himself, and when displaying such a talent, he remarks it to have been "passed down the Armstrong line for generations." His alchemical skills also represent a remnant of his family`s history; by using a unique kind of brass knuckles, Armstrong can reshape any solid object that he punches. Armstrong is a valuable ally of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang] and the Elric brothers, even if they are not always happy to be in his emotional company. He takes his honor as a soldier and as a leader seriously, and always looks out for his peers` and subordinates` best interests.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>24237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6592" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="249">5.83</rating>
<name>Envy</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Envy is a genderless (though is referred to as `he` as well as `it`) homunculus who has the ability of shape-shifting. It uses this power to assume the form of any person and even copy their voice.
Envy is most comfortable in the "adorable" and "beautiful" form of an androgynous teenager. It usually serves as a spy, but abilities are also extremely useful for assassinations, as demonstrated by the murder of http://anidb.net/ch6590 [Maes Hughes]. Envy`s most frequently used assassination technique is to impersonate someone whom the target loved or cared about, and use the target`s hesitation as an opportunity to kill him or her. Envy may not be as smart as some of the other Homunculi, but is by no means an idiot. In fact, it can be just as good a puppet master as http://anidb.net/ch6591 [Lust]. But this is overshadowed by its cockiness and bad temper. Its temper can easily be set off by insulting his large and delicate ego, causing it to make mistakes.</description>
<picture>24240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="170535.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7783" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="134">7.33</rating>
<name>Van Hohenheim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Van Hohenheim is a brilliant and well-known alchemist. He is the father of http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] Elric. He left them and their mother http://anidb.net/ch7784 [Trisha] when Alphonse was a baby and Edward was very young. Years later, Edward still holds a grudge against him for abandoning his mother, which he believes contributed to her death.</description>
<picture>139750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8929" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<rating votes="63">4.43</rating>
<name>Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rose is a young woman introduced at the very start of the series. She is a devout believer in her town`s local faith, believing that serving the church will bring back her dead boyfriend. The Elric brothers` arrival in town opens Rose`s eyes to the church`s corruption and forces her to realize her boyfriend is not coming back. Rose does not appear again until much later in the series. In the manga she helps to rebuild the town, eventually reuniting with http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse Elric]. In the anime she instead becomes the mute "Holy Mother" of the townspeople, giving them a symbol of guidance as they rise up against the State Military. Rose loses her voice after being captured by a soldier of the military.</description>
<picture>28352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10164" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="51">6.27</rating>
<name>Pinako Rockbell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Pinako Rockbell is a surgeon and weaponsmith living and working in the town of Resembool in the eastern region of Amestris. Mixing her two specialties, Pinako is also a prominent automail engineer and presumably the founder of Rockbell Automail, a family-run automail atelier within the town. Pinako also happens to be the grandmother of http://anidb.net/ch6588 [Winry Rockbell] as well as the neighbor and close family friend of the Elrics - http://anidb.net/ch7783 [Van Hohenheim], http://anidb.net/ch7784 [Trisha], http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse]. As Winry`s only remaining blood relative after the death of her parents, and the closest adult to the Elric brothers after their mother`s passing and their father`s disappearance, Pinako acts as caretaker to the three youngsters, training Winry in automail engineering and serving as Ed and Al`s home base whenever they return to Resembool.</description>
<picture>30537.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1801" picture="146194.jpg">Asou Miyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10166" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="104">5.95</rating>
<name>Maria Ross</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch10167 [Denny Brosh] and Maria Ross are introduced when they are assigned to protect http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward Elric]. While Brosh is rather nosy and lazy, and has an enormous infatuation with Ross, Ross is serious with her job, to the point that she develops a maternal affection for Edward when she is protecting him. In the manga, Ross is framed by the homunculi for the death of http://anidb.net/ch6590 [Maes Hughes]. http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang] stages a prison break and then fakes her death, giving her a chance to flee to Xing. Before leaving, she asks that her family and Brosh not be told that she is alive so as to keep the secret from getting out. To repay Mustang for saving her life, Ross later returns to Amestris and helps him wage an assault on Central. In the first anime, Brosh and Ross later appear in the rebellion against http://anidb.net/ch10175 [King Bradley], saving various characters from execution.</description>
<picture>30540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10167" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="46">5.44</rating>
<name>Denny Brosh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Denny Brosh and http://anidb.net/ch10166 [Maria Ross] are introduced when they are assigned to protect http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward Elric]. While Brosh is rather nosy and lazy, and has an enormous infatuation with Ross, Ross is serious with her job, to the point that she develops a maternal affection for Edward when she is protecting him. In the manga, Ross is framed by the homunculi for the death of http://anidb.net/ch6590 [Maes Hughes]. http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang] stages a prison break and then fakes her death, giving her a chance to flee to Xing. Before leaving, she asks that her family and Brosh not be told that she is alive so as to keep the secret from getting out. To repay Mustang for saving her life, Ross later returns to Amestris and helps him wage an assault on Central. In the first anime, Brosh and Ross later appear in the rebellion against http://anidb.net/ch10175 [King Bradley], saving various characters from execution.</description>
<picture>30541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6096" picture="186251.jpg">Harada Masao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10168" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="70">7.21</rating>
<name>Sheska</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sheska is a mousy, bespectacled young woman who had previously worked in the National Central Library in Central City, but was fired for spending her time reading books instead of doing her job. http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] Elric seek her out to discover whether or not http://anidb.net/ch10165 [Tim Marcoh]`s research journal had been located in the library`s First Branch, which had been burnt down. After finding her trapped in her home under a collapsed mountain of books, Sheska confirms the Elrics` worst fears - that the book, which she herself had read cover to cover, had indeed been in the First Branch and, therefore, destroyed.
But, as they leave, visibly disheartened, Sheska reveals that she has a photographic memory and can recreate the book for them, exactly as it had looked when she read it. As a result, Sheska is able to recreate Marcoh`s notes in five days to such a degree of detail that, even though Marcoh wrote them in code, Edward is able to decipher their hidden truth.
When http://anidb.net/ch6590 [Maes Hughes] reveals that several court-martial records had been kept in the First Branch, Edward and Alphonse recommend Sheska for the task of recreating them, as she had read them as well. Thanks to this, Sheska is hired into the Amestrian military at a desk job in the records department.</description>
<picture>30542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2039" picture="41388.jpg">Wakabayashi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10172" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="230">7.64</rating>
<name>Izumi Curtis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Izumi Curtis is a skilled martial artist and alchemist living in the southern Amestrian town of Dublith where - with her husband http://anidb.net/ch10173 [Sig Curtis] - she runs a butcher shop. Though she doesn`t usually take on students, Izumi accepted http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] Elric`s plea to accept them as her apprentices and instructed them in alchemical theory and practice for six months.
Although Izumi takes apparent pride in being a housewife and introduces herself as such to anyone who asks, her attractive and humble exterior belies a fearsome disposition such that Ed and Al become terrified at the mere thought of her.
She is prone to swift acts of violence and is often seen doling out physical harm, though most acts of overexertion on her part are followed by a regurgitation of blood linked to an internal injury from a failed Human Transmutation several years before. As a result of this, she is one of the few characters able to perform alchemy without the aid of a Transmutation Circle. Izumi is among the strongest women (and indeed characters) in the series.
She also appears to enjoy travel (a trait she may have passed on to Edward), as many of her appearances in the series find her journeying outside her hometown. She even announces herself as a "travelling housewife".</description>
<picture>30546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="653" picture="18181.jpg">Tsuda Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10173" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="43">6.61</rating>
<name>Sig Curtis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sig is the large, doting husband of http://anidb.net/ch10172 [Izumi Curtis]. Together with his wife, he runs a Meat shop in Dublith and housed http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] Elric during their alchemy apprenticeship, though he himself is not an alchemist. Despite his perpetually angry-looking face, Sig is quite a nice person and laments the repellent nature of his visage. He is very devoted to and protective of Izumi, constantly worrying about her bad health and often needlessly rushing to her rescue when he senses danger (as he did when she was approached by Ulchi at Devil`s Nest and when she was "stabbed" by Van Hohenheim ) and becoming jealous when Izumi speaks fondly of other men. He has also been shown to be able to sleep with his eyes wide open. Sig has mentioned that he blames himself for not realizing sooner that Izumi had been experimenting with Human Transmutation.</description>
<picture>30547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3441" picture="149777.jpg">Sasaki Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10884" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="48">5.18</rating>
<name>Vato Falman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Warrent Officer Vato Falman is one of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang]`s most trusted subordinates. He was recruited by Mustang for his innate ability to remember almost every detail, allowing him to act as a sort of recording device that does not leave any physical evidence. Because his intellect is his area of expertise, he does not have much experience in the field, causing him to make rookie mistakes when in a combat situation. He is overly formal, causing some of his comrades to wish he would lighten up.</description>
<picture>45813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12232" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-12">
<rating votes="5">6.32</rating>
<name>Alphonse Heiderich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1984" picture="21284.jpg">Oguri Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14596" type="appears in" update="2018-01-07">
<rating votes="47">5.34</rating>
<name>Kain Fuery</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Master Sergeant Kain Fuery is one of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang]`s most trusted subordinates. He is overly kind in nature, both to people and to animals. He was recruited by Mustang for his technological expertise. As such, he primarily helps Mustang with communications, both in creating secure lines and tapping into others. He is transferred to Southern Headquarters when Mustang`s group is broken up by the homunculi. In the manga, he eventually defects from the military so that he can help Mustang overthrow http://anidb.net/ch10175 [King Bradley].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14597" type="appears in" update="2018-01-06">
<rating votes="86">6.85</rating>
<name>Jean Havoc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second Lieutenant Jean Havoc is one of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang]`s most trusted subordinates. He is usually seen smoking a cigarette, something that Arakawa developed prior to the series` start to help Mustang to create fire to fight homunculus Lust. He was recruited by Mustang for his loyalty and general sincerity, as well as his above average shooting skills. Because working for Mustang requires moving frequently and a complete dedication of time, Havoc has very little free time, and cannot maintain a relationship with a woman for very long.</description>
<picture>211683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14598" type="appears in" update="2018-01-07">
<rating votes="52">5.50</rating>
<name>Heymans Breda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second Lieutenant Heymans Breda is one of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang]`s most trusted subordinates. He was recruited by Mustang for his high level of intelligence, indicated by his talent with chess and other strategy games. Despite his intelligence, he still has an irrational fear of dogs. Breda is usually tasked by Mustang with jobs that require he travel abroad. He is transferred to Western Headquarters when Mustang`s group is broken up by the homunculi.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18552" type="appears in" update="2010-06-06">
<rating votes="25">5.21</rating>
<name>Wrath</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wrath differs greatly in the first anime and in the manga. In the manga and second anime, Wrath is the true identity of King Bradley. The first anime shows the origins of Wrath in Izumi Curtis`s attempt to revive her infant child. Her effort failed, and the infant`s body was taken beyond the Gate of Truth. There, the child, Wrath, grew up. When Edward Elric later lost his arm and leg while trying to revive his mother, Wrath took both for himself, which allowed him to use alchemy and escape to Amestris. Because of his ability to perform alchemy, Wrath can assimilate any sort of material or object into his body. Since the remains of his former body were used in his creation, Wrath lacks the weaknesses of the other homunculi, though both the Gate of Truth and the cries of a child have similar psychological effects on him. His Ouroboros tattoo is under his right foot,</description>
<picture>49229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22233" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="7">3.99</rating>
<name>Adolf Hitler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69721.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27697" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-23">
<rating votes="6">5.61</rating>
<name>Noah</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young traveling gypsy girl who Edward saves from being sold to the Thule Society. On the surface, she is proud of her heritage and lifestyle, but is unable to bear being discriminated for it. She has the ability to read the minds of others, becoming fascinated with Edward`s world after witnessing his memories of it. Believing she wouldn`t be discriminated in Edward`s world, Noah assists the Thule Society in opening the Gate based on information from Edward`s memories, but relents once Edward points out that his home is no utopia, and leaves Munich together with the Elric brothers.</description>
<picture>64289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38647" picture="165636.jpg">Sawai Miyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27700" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-23">
<rating votes="5">1.83</rating>
<name>Dietlinde Eckart</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52088" picture="208075.jpg">Katou Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27701" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="3">1.38</rating>
<name>Karl Haushofer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2080" picture="43095.jpg">Tsukayama Masane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27702" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="4">2.34</rating>
<name>Rudolf Hess</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27703" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="5">6.19</rating>
<name>Fritz Lang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27705" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="4">1.65</rating>
<name>Erik Jan Hanussen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27706" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-23">
<rating votes="5">7.11</rating>
<name>Gracia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27707" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-23">
<rating votes="4">3.68</rating>
<name>Hughes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27708" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="3">1.48</rating>
<name>Huskisson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="24719" update="2008-07-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30917" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<rating votes="1">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Metal Archer - The Movie 2004 (parody)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35316" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Munich, Germany, 1923. Two years have passed since Edward Elric was dragged from his own world to ours, leaving behind his country, his friends and his younger brother, Alphonse. Stripped of his alchemical powers, he has been all this time researching rocketry together with Alphonse Heiderich, a young man who resembles his own brother, hoping to one day find a way back home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719013</identifier>
<identifier>fullmetal-alchemist-the-conqueror-of-shamballa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35539" update="2008-07-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36079" update="2008-07-02">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">FMA Movie Trailer Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38134" update="2008-07-02">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">9.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告最新版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1 (a.k.a. Teaser 4)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokoku Saishinban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38211" update="2008-07-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41721" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61823" update="2010-02-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD extra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109766" update="2010-03-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154563" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Talk Session</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
