<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2389" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>61</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-11</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Black Jack (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Блек Джак (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Black Jack TV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BJ 04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bjtv</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブラックジャック (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">怪醫黑傑克</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Black Jack TV</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Black Jack</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">แบล็คแจ็คหมอปีศาจ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4377" type="Sequel">Black Jack 21</anime>
<anime id="11226" type="Prequel">Young Black Jack</anime>
<anime id="4049" type="Same Setting">Ray The Animation</anime>
<anime id="7544" type="Alternative Setting">Black Jack (2001)</anime>
<anime id="3506" type="Side Story">Black Jack: Futari no Kuroi Isha</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301890">Each episode is full of drama, emotions often bringing you to edge of tears - both from sadness and happiness. You don`t even have to follow the order of episodes, just choose whatever seems to be interesting by title and watch. Everyone should see at least few episodes of this. Even people who don`t like blood - medical scenes are shown in such way, that anyone should be able to watch them without feeling sick.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ytv.co.jp/bj/</url>
<creators>
<name id="723" type="Work">Tezuka Productions</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="3778" type="Main Character Design">Kamimura Sachiko</name>
<name id="6216" type="Chief Direction">Kuwahara Satoshi</name>
<name id="6275" type="Direction">Tezuka Makoto</name>
<name id="7118" type="Music">Matsumoto Akihiko</name>
<name id="829" type="Work">Yomiuri TV</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch10400 [Black Jack] is an unregistered doctor with a clouded, mysterious past. He works with his little assistant http://anidb.net/ch10401 [Pinoko] (who has a massive crush on the doctor), dealing with medical cases not very well known, which can be strange, dangerous, or not known at all. But he is a genius, and can save almost any of his patients` life (as long as they have the money for it, that is), and is known to many around the world, especially to those of medicine and science. He`s a man of science himself, and does not believe much until he has seen it, yet it is many times he is surprised by love and nature often overpowering the science he bases his life in.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="352">6.33</permanent>
<temporary count="357">7.16</temporary>
<review count="2">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>63149.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4408</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18669</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4071</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1617</identifier>
<identifier>myynoq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ytv.co.jp/bj/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Jack_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブラック・ジャック_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>520</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321471</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6972</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07G3HMN8D</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4136" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-03-05">
<name>sudden loli companion appearance</name>
<description>The main character meets a preadolescent girl in an unexpected way becoming a friend / partner of the main character.
(The term loli is short for Lolita meaning a girl in preadolescent age. Typical attributes are moe, cute, and innocent.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4244" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>healthcare and medicine</name>
<description>The anime contains themes related to healthcare, medicine, or the human body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10400" type="main character in" update="2016-01-04">
<rating votes="372">9.15</rating>
<name>Black Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Black Jack is a mysterious and charismatic young genius surgeon who travels the world performing amazing and impossible surgery. Because of his hatred of the hypocrisy and corruption of the medical establishment, Black Jack refuses to accept a medical license, and runs into frequent difficulties from the authorities, as well as from gangsters and criminals who approach him for illegal operations. Black Jack charges ludicrous fees for his services, and uses the proceeds for environmental projects and to aid the victims of criminals and corrupt capitalsts, but he rarely allows anyone to realize that he is a good person, preferring to be considered a heartless devil.</description>
<picture>3312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10401" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="88">3.49</rating>
<name>Pinoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pinoko, is a hyperactive, fiercely possessive little girl, who lives in Black Jack`s house, doing his cooking and laundry and serving as his nurse and assistant, and the only steady long-term companion the unlucky Dr. Black Jack has ever had, and just about the only person who can embarrass or joke with him. Insisting that she is the doctor`s wife despite her obvious youth, Pinoko puzzle to anyone who meets her, and especially to anime viewers who don`t know her origin and wonder why the grim and solitary Black Jack is living with what seems to be a cute, annoying little girl.</description>
<picture>31195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53192" type="appears in" update="2013-02-24">
<name>Sharaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3336" picture="177136.jpg">Satou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53193" type="appears in" update="2013-02-24">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Wato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53194" type="appears in" update="2013-02-24">
<name>Largo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="605" picture="226544.jpg">Ishii Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53195" type="appears in" update="2013-02-24">
<rating votes="3">1.00</rating>
<name>Honma Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79396" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-02">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63440.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="79398" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-01-05">
<rating votes="14">5.43</rating>
<name>Tezuka Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Osamu Tezuka`s anime/manga version of himself</description>
<picture>181241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79431" type="appears in" update="2016-09-10">
<name>Rock Holmes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the world of show business, it is common knowledge that actors who start out playing the role of children rarely make it to the top of their profession. This is because child stars, who are loved in the role of cute children, even if they grow, are burdened with the fate of having to continue showing the same image to audiences. In the same way, in the Manga of Tezuka Osamu, loveable, law-abiding characters like Kenichi and Atom were restricted to continuously playing the same role. But Rock is different. He was not simply a virtuous character. From the time he started performing in child roles, he never believed in the image that "a bright future will be born if only justice triumphs". "The world is full of inconsistencies. The world will not weep even if the fight for justice is lost and evil triumphs. Come spring the flowers will still bloom, the sunshine will still pour down in the summer." Rock was a boy who stared these realities in the face. As might be expected from a character that got his name from Sherlock Holmes, Rock is a highly intelligent young boy. That`s why he never had to trade on his charms even as he grew up. He concealed the malicious face of the devil under his handsome visage. He built up his character as the portrait of a villain. Part of the appeal of Tezuka Osamu`s Manga lies in the fact that such warped boy stars are incorporated into the stories, and in the inclusion of elements of profundity and philosophy.</description>
<picture>191106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83803" type="appears in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<name>Biwamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Biwamaru (sometimes Biwa Maru) is a blind, itinerant acupuncture doctor, who wanders around Japan curing all sorts of ailments with miraculous speed. He is extremely disheveled in appearance, dressed in rags and walking with a twisted stick as a cane, and a rough bundle on his back. Biwamaru is effectively, like Black Jack, an unlicensed doctor, since his practices are considered to be quackery by the medical establishment, while Biwamaru considers it barbaric to cut open a patient to cure them. This, as with Dr. Kiriko, Biwamaru is another nemesis who is too similar to Black Jack for the two to forgive their differences. Biwamaru also features in Tezuka`s best-known samurai manga, Dororo.
When Biwamaru came to Black Jack`s town in issue #126 `The Blind Doctor of Acupuncture,` (6/7/1976) it was hatred at first sight, as each dismissed the other as a quack, though neither was able to deny the effectiveness of the other`s treatments. To make matters worse, Biwamaru charges nothing for his services, in contrast with Black Jack`s outrageous fees, leading to criticism of Black Jack by the local community. Their interaction here effectively degenerated into each attempting repeatedly to prove that the other was a quack, and generally failing, though teaching each other bitter lessons about the limitations of their methods.
The two met again not long afterwards in issue #141, `Death of Hyojisai` (The Master Forger, Two People at the Thermal Bath) when they met at a hot spring and discovered that both of them, out of dedication to their work, made regular pilgrimages to see the same world-famous master forger, who made scalpels for the one and needles for the other. On discovering that the forger was sick, the two compete to cure him, while the forger, Hyojisai, uses his own illness to teach the two that, skilled as they are, both are powerless in the face of fate. It is a bitter experience for both of them. The trailer for the upcoming Two Dark Doctors movie indicates that the film will include scenes from this issue.
Notably, Biwamaru also appeared in Dororo as a blind musician and masters-swordsman. The crippled samurai Hyakkumaru, widely acknowledged as a prototype of Black Jack, encountered Biwamaru here and became his student in swordfighting, an interesting reversal of his role in Black Jack.
(Source: tezukainenglish.com)</description>
<picture>190082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3380" picture="187130.jpg">Nozawa Nachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83804" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-14">
<name>Honma Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of the late Dr. Honma who saved Black Jack`s life. Black Jack sees her as a sister and looks after her.
She is known as Kumi Yamashita in the manga.</description>
<picture>190091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3601" picture="38507.jpg">Kawase Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23041" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2004-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オペの順番 / 消えた針</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Order of Operations / The Vanished Needle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ope no Junban / Kieta Hari</title>
<summary>During a ferry accident, Black Jack Saves an Iriomote cat, a baby and a politician. The politician decides to take legal action against Black Jack but ironically, asks him to save his life later on.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527888</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>527790</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25764" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリの足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ant`s Legs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ari no Ashi</title>
<summary>A handicapped boy is inspired by a book to trek the incredibly long distance from Hokkaido to Osaka, all by himself. Much to his dismay, Black Jack accompanies the boy on his journey. Will the boy succeed in his journey?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527792</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25776" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひったくり犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thieving Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hittakuri Inu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25777" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お医者さんごっこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Playing Doctor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oisha-san Gokko</title>
<summary>Kong`s sister Chako has been diagnosed with an unusual case of tuberculosis. Chako, having heard about Black Jack from her brother, asks her brother to speak with Black Jack. Unable to find the doctor, Kong asks his friend Keaton from the drama club to pose as Black Jack and help raise her spirits. But will it save her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527794</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="25778" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">六等星の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sixth-Magnitude Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rokutousei no Otoko</title>
<summary>Black Jack is introduced to skilled, but neglected doctor, Dr. Shiitake. He works at Manaka Hospital whose staff is under investigation for embezzlement. During a fireworks accident, one man is injured. Black Jack`s fee is too expensive for the hospital, and the underestimated Dr. Shiitake is given the chance to prove himself. Can he step up to the challenge?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527796</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="27355" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある教師と生徒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Teacher and a Pupil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Kyoshi to Seito</title>
<summary>A boy who is afraid of his teacher, Mr. Muramasa, is hit by a motorcycle. The next day, he is forced to attend school. Mr. Muramasa hires Black Jack to operate on the boy`s legs. Learning that the boy is afraid of him, the teacher wanders into the street and is struck by a car. Can Black Jack save both the boy and the teacher?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527798</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="27610" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白いライオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Lion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Lion</title>
<summary>A white lion a the local zoo, Luna Luna, is sick. The lion`s keeper asks Black Jack to cure the sick cat but Black Jack refuses. It turns out the lion`s illness is caused by a brain tumor which also caused his fur to turn white. Can Black Jack save the doomed lion?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527800</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="28157" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の腕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle Arms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Ude</title>
<summary>A skilled sushi chef, Taku, wants to make the best sushi in Japan. His goal is to feed his blind mother. He is soon hit by a truck and loses his arms. The truck driver, Akira, forms an unlikely friendship with Taku and helps him on his journey to make the best sushi. Akira is then fatally injured by fire and ends up giving his arms to Taku.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527802</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="28318" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もらい水</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drawing Water</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moraimizu</title>
<summary>Pinoko and Sharaku befriend an old lady who is staying at her son`s hospital. After being kicked out of the hospital, she decides to spend some time in a summer house that she owns. But heavy rains cause a mudslide, and Black Jack rescues her. He forces her son to decide what`s really important to him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527804</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="29027" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">火の鳥伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of the Phoenix</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi no Tori Densetsu</title>
<summary>Black Jack and Pinoko fly to Asia to treat a 200-year-old man. Miriam, a relative of the man, wants to find the legendary phoenix which will grant everlasting life. The only thing is, 200-year-old man knows how to find the phoenix. Black Jack cures the old man, but the legend turns out to be a hoax. The man gained his long life from sheer will power, and the phoenix is really just a bird covered in luminescent bacteria.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527782</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="30034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャチの贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gift from a Killer Whale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shachi no Okurimono</title>
<summary>Black Jack recalls a memory about how he befriended the killer whale Toriton. One day at the beach, Black Jack discovered the injured Toriton. Falsely accused for attacking a fisherman, Black Jack comes just in time to save the killer whale.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527784</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34176" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">にいちゃんを返せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Give My Brother Back to Me!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nii-chan o Kaese</title>
<summary>Pinoko befriends an actor inside a monster suit that has a lymphatic problem that Black Jack treats. The actor`s brother Yukio mistakes Black Jack as part of a TV show that kidnapped his sibiling. Pinoko comes up with a plan; the actor "saves" Yukio from Black Jack and they escape.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527786</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34177" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海賊の腕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Pirate`s Arm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaizoku no Ude</title>
<summary>Ichinoseki is a local star gymnast who loses an arm to gangrene. Black Jack replaces it with a metal pincer. Ichinoseki becomes depressed, but his arm talks him into playing competitive shogi. Who is the voice behind the metal arm?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>527788</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34178" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">動けソロモン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Solomon, Come to Life!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugoke Solomon</title>
<summary>Pinoko is saved by Musashi, a lifeguard/animator, and becomes interested in his animation work. Musashi wants to make anime that truly appears to live, but when Musashi becomes ill, it`s up to Black Jack to save him... in exchange for his animation cels.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532532</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34179" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽りのウエディング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fake Wedding</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari no Wedding</title>
<summary>Michiru is a teenage girl dying of cancer. Her dying wish is to marry the next man she sees, and Black Jack enters at the opportune moment...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532534</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34180" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピノコ行方不明</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pinoko Goes Missing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pinoko Yukuefumei</title>
<summary>Pinoko befriends a burglar who has lost his job and family. She embarks on a journey with him to find his family. Believing she has been kidnapped, Black Jack pursues her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532536</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34181" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">声を失ったアイドル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Idol Who Lost Her Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koe o Ushinatta Idol</title>
<summary>Rei is the school`s star vocalist until something causes her to lose her voice. Black Jack operates, but she soon loses her voice again. Will she regain her beautiful singing voice?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532538</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34182" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メールの友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friendship by Mail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mail no Yuujou</title>
<summary>Although Jun is in wheelchair, he tells his Internet friend Tom he can play baseball. Jun asks Black Jack to heal his weak heart. The price is too high, but Jun`s friend Tom offers to pay Black Jack`s fee... at a high cost.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532540</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34183" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれ古和医院</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tale of Kowa Clinic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganbare Kowa Iin</title>
<summary>Black Jack is forced to take Pinoko to a local clinic for digestion medicine, and comes to assist Dr. Kowa, a country doctor, in a thyroid operation. The doctor reveals that he is an unlicensed doctor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532542</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="34184" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">山手線の哲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yamanote Tetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamanotesen no Tetsu</title>
<summary>Tetsu, the owner of Black Jack`s favorite cafe, tells the story of how he was a famous pickpocket chased constantly by a police detective.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532544</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40457" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">春一番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Wind of Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru Ichiban</title>
<summary>Kumiko loses sight in one eye due to glaucoma. Black Jack implants a cornea, but Kumiko starts to see the donor`s last sight...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532546</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40458" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピノコ大人計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ponoko`s Grown-Up Plans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pinoko Otona Keikaku</title>
<summary>Pinoko meets Tinq, a boy her age, and tries to start a relationship with him. Tinq has been diagnosed with an unusual condition and it`s up to Black Jack to save him. However, Pinoko may have an ulterior motive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532548</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40459" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">土砂降りのち恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love in the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doshaburi Nochi Koi</title>
<summary>Black Jack meets a Kiyomi, a pretty young physician, and the only doctor on her island. Kiyomi falls in love with Black Jack, but he knows the people on the island need her more than he needs her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532550</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40460" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナダレという挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Challenge Called Nadare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nadare to Iu Chousen</title>
<summary>A genetically-enhanced deer, Nadare, is attacking forest workers. In the past, the deer was befriended by a young doctor and treated as his own sibling however the deer injures a woman and it`s up to Black Jack to save her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532552</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40461" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コレラ騒ぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cholera Scare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cholera Sawagi</title>
<summary>Black Jack believes he may have cholera, so he quarantines himself, leaving Pinoko to take care of a patient for a few days. He soon finds out that his illness is connected to both Pinoko and the patient.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532554</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40462" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">そろばんの天才</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abacus Wizard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soroban no Tensai</title>
<summary>Black Jack recalls a story to Pinoko about the teacher and father of Eiji, a boy, whom he helped win an abacus competition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532556</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40463" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最先端ルームの悲劇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disaster in the Hi-Tech Room</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisentan Room no Higeki</title>
<summary>Black Jack, Pinoko and several rich men find themselves trapped in an underground, disaster-proof bunker. To make matters worse, the oxygen in the bunker is slowly being sucked out! Can Black Jack save them in time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532558</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40464" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">荒野の伝染病</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Epidemic in the Outback</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouya no Densen Byou</title>
<summary>Black Jack and Pinoko investigate a mysterious plague in Australia. Through a series of events, Black Jack contracts a deadly plague and realizes it is actually a parasite.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>532560</identifier>
<identifier>black-jack</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40465" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">命を生ける花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower Arrangement of Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi o Ikeru Hana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40466" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷雲の中のオペ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation in the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raiun no Naka no Ope</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40467" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">20年目の暗示</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Twenty-Years Past Suggestion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">20-nenme no Anji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40468" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い海の恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror of the Blue Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Umi no Kyoufu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40469" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">空からの侵略者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invaders from the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora kara no Shinryakusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40470" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">揺れる手術室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shaking Operating Room</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yureru Shujutsu Shitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40471" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">病院ジャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hospital Hijacking</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byouin Jack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40472" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">岬の家は未完成</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The House on the Cape Is Unfinished</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki no Ie wa Mikansei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40473" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イルカと強盗団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dolphins and Thieves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iruka to Goutou Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40474" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知なる者への挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenging the Unknown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michinaru Mono e no Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40475" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦争はなおも続く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War Goes On</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensou wa Nao mo Tsuzuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40476" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">人形と警官</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Doll and the Police Officer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningyou to Keikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40477" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オペと映画の奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle of an Operation and a Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ope to Eiga no Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40478" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">人生の誤診</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misdiagnosis of a Person`s Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei no Goshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40479" update="2011-07-01">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちぢむ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shrinking!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chijimu!</title>
<summary>After being summoned to a foreign land Black Jack faces a mysterious Illness that ravages man and beast, causing their bodies to waste away.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="41311" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピノコ誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of Pinoko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pinoko Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41418" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">笑い上戸の同級生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Laugh-Happy Classmate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warai Jougo no Doukyuusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42583" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">文化祭の用心棒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guardian of the Cultural Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bunkasai no Youjinbo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42584" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪原のヴァイオリン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Violin of the Snowy Plains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsugen no Violin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42585" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コマドリの少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robin and the Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komadori no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43349" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">人面瘡[そう]の本音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Face Sore`s Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinmensou no Honne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44380" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">引き裂かれた兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brothers Torn Apart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikisakareta Kyoudai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44381" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">噂の座頭医師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rumored Blind Doctor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwasa no Zagashira Ishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44635" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一瞬の目撃者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Momentary Witness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isshun no Mokugekisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44778" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロッカーのゆりかご</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Locker Cradle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Locker no Yurikago</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50577" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽り親子の幸運不運</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fake Family`s Joy and Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari Oyako no Kouun Fuun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67087" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">命のプラットホーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Platform of Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi no Platform</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67088" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">縫い目皮膚の提供者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Skin Donor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuime Hifu no Teikyousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67089" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピノコのお受験日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pinoko`s School Entrance Exam Journal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pinoko no Ojuken Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67090" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">老人と大木</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Old Man and the Big Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roujin to Taiboku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67091" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラッククィーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Queen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Black Queen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67092" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去ある二人めぐり逢い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter of the Couple Who Share a Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako Aru Futari Meguriai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67093" update="2007-03-26">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人のピノコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Pinokos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Pinoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67436" update="2014-06-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2006-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Episodes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112383" update="2010-01-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Karte NG Extras</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125035" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125036" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125037" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125038" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125039" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125040" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213050" update="2019-02-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">樹海のかまいたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kamaitachi in an Ocean of Trees</title>
<summary>In a peaceful town, a military base is set up and a project to build missile is carried out. However, for some reasons, innocent citizens are having their bodies slashed and getting killed.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
