<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="24" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2002-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">.hack//Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">dot hack sign</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">.hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Хак//Симбол</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">hack sign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">dot hack</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="short">Хак</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hackSIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sign</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">.hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">.hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">.hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">.hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">.hack//SIGN</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">.hack//SIGN</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="222" type="Sequel">.hack//Liminality</anime>
<anime id="7883" type="Same Setting">.hack//Quantum</anime>
<anime id="4324" type="Same Setting">.hack//Roots</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8692" approval="212" total="249">Sword Art Online</anime>
<anime id="9677" approval="111" total="122">Log Horizon</anime>
<anime id="11712" approval="23" total="35">Hai to Gensou no Grimgar</anime>
<anime id="13439" approval="9" total="13">Shichisei no Subaru</anime>
<anime id="13" approval="4" total="13">Noir</anime>
<anime id="99" approval="2" total="13">Serial Experiments Lain</anime>
<anime id="1654" approval="2" total="12">Madlax</anime>
<anime id="13246" approval="2" total="11">Tate no Yuusha no Nariagari</anime>
<anime id="4966" approval="2" total="10">El Cazador de la Bruja</anime>
<anime id="9998" approval="2" total="7">No Game No Life</anime>
<anime id="11261" approval="1" total="10">Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku o!</anime>
<anime id="13757" approval="1" total="9">Isekai Maou to Shoukan Shoujo no Dorei Majutsu</anime>
<anime id="13871" approval="1" total="9">Tensei Shitara Slime Datta Ken</anime>
<anime id="10816" approval="1" total="7">Overlord</anime>
<anime id="12603" approval="1" total="6">Death March kara Hajimaru Isekai Kyousoukyoku</anime>
<anime id="14068" approval="1" total="6">Conception</anime>
<anime id="10894" approval="1" total="6">Dungeon ni Deai o Motomeru no wa Machigatte Iru Darouka: Familia Myth</anime>
<anime id="9393" approval="1" total="6">Sen`yuu.</anime>
<anime id="6226" approval="1" total="5">Slap Up Party: Arad Senki</anime>
<anime id="1523" approval="1" total="5">Ragnarok The Animation</anime>
<anime id="9269" approval="1" total="5">Ixion Saga: Dimension Transfer</anime>
<anime id="13004" approval="1" total="5">Isekai wa Smartphone to Tomo ni.</anime>
<anime id="13896" approval="1" total="5">Hyakuren no Haou to Seiyaku no Valkyria</anime>
<anime id="5503" approval="1" total="4">Druaga no Tou: the Aegis of Uruk</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="495882">I personally love this anime, but I can`t help but feel that I only love it because of nostalgia factor alone. The soundtrack is the best soundtrack I`ve ever heard in an anime. Period. The anime as a whole is VERY original, but the story moves slow.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="43034">If you have played some old-school MMORPGs and met new friends through them, you owe it to yourself to watch //SIGN.
The Anime manages to capture some of the player interactions in those online worlds really well and touches on subjects like escapism, online vs. RL, anonymity and more. All the while a fantastic choral soundtrack accompanies the on-screen exposition.
Watching this, I recalled many moments of me playing Lineage 2 and Guild Wars (1) and spending time with my friends online.

The anime is definitely not for everyone though. The story is quite convoluted and there are quite a lot of uncertainties left at the end. If you`re looking for something more action orientated or fast paced, stay away from //SIGN or you`ll regret it. The exposition unravels reaaaaly slow and it`s very dialouge heavy. It focuses on the psychological and sociological aspects of MMOs, rather than their battles, quests or other gameplay elements.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="299048">A rare digital plot that has no end to it :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.beetrain.co.jp/contents/works/sign/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2479" type="Character Design">Ban Yukiko</name>
<name id="691" type="Direction">Mashimo Kouichi</name>
<name id="7851" type="Character Design">Oosawa Satoshi</name>
<name id="2473" type="Character Design">Iwaoka Yuuko</name>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="3740" type="Series Composition">Itou Kazunori</name>
<name id="749" type="Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
</creators>
<description>In the year 2005, a computer virus called Pluto Kiss completely shuts down and restricts the global internet network. In 2007, after extensive rescinding of the network, an online network game (MMORPG) called The World is created and released.
http://anidb.net/ch3547 [Tsukasa] suddenly awakens to find himself in The World, being able to feel, smell, touch, see and hear everything as if he was really there. He attempts to log out but fails to do so. Being unable to remember what has happened before he awoke, he wanders around aimlessly to find answers. While doing so, system moderators, the Scarlet Knights, suspect that he has been working with hackers, because of a tweaked cat-faced character he had been seen with. Tsukasa finds a magical item, that grants him the power to use the fearful Guardian that will protect him from any harm. To Tsukasa`s dismay it turns out that this guardian can not only easily defeat player characters in the game, but actually badly hurt players in the real world.
On his search for truth, Tsukasa encounters the friendly and supportive http://anidb.net/ch3661 [Mimiru], the wise, fatherly http://anidb.net/ch9953 [Bear], the manipulative http://anidb.net/ch9957 [BT], the unscrupulous http://anidb.net/ch9954 [Sora], the fun-loving http://anidb.net/ch9955 [Crim], and the mysterious http://anidb.net/ch9956 [Subaru], leader of the Scarlet Knights. When a mythical item called the Key of the Twilight turns out to be less of a myth, Tsukasa, questions whom he can really trust, and what the power to overcome The World`s system limitations actually entails...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6573">5.15</permanent>
<temporary count="6706">7.17</temporary>
<review count="19">8.06</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221346.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3770</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3532</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>605</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>48</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1143</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>862</identifier>
<identifier>hjhhmj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.beetrain.co.jp/contents/works/sign/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>.hack//Sign</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>.hack//SIGN</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>466</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>237599</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5287</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7859</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20362</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4178" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-06">
<name>manipulated memories</name>
<description>The protagonist finds out that his/her cherished memories are actually fake and have been implanted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6037" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-11">
<name>serious business</name>
<description>For some people it is just a card- or board game. For others it is not just a matter of life and death — it is much more important than that.
Serious business basically describes a situation, when a show revolves around an activity where a sizeable portion of the in-series population takes it far more seriously than it should. If something`s popularity rivals that of Elvis, or if there are mainstream schools devoted to it instead of teaching reading, writing, and arithmetic; it is serious business.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3547" type="main character in" update="2010-12-12">
<rating votes="16">6.01</rating>
<name>Tsukasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukasa was initially a cynical loner, and seemingly arrogant to the other players in The World. Tsukasa tended to avoid others as much as possible and didn`t take any enjoyment in leveling up or participating in events. In fact, his sole enjoyment seemed to come from defying the Crimson Knights. As Tsukasa was slowly befriended by Mimiru, Bear, and Subaru, he began to warm up to them, eventually seeking them out, as well as being sought out by Subaru who came to him for aid when she felt lost. By the end of the series, Tsukasa reveals the kind heart he had kept hidden for so long.</description>
<picture>60665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3661" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="12">6.20</rating>
<name>Mimiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mimiru is a female Heavyblade who appears in .hack//Sign. Her avatar appears as a teenage girl dressed in an armored bikini top, and a short skirt, with large greaves on her legs. Mimiru plays as a "tough-it-out-through-anything" player, who is poor at planning things out and following through on them. She meets Tsukasa and soon becomes one of the few he trusts and he eventually sees her as a friend. She also teams up with Bear, who she refers to as an "old man", and spends considerable time in the series attempting to figure out what Bear`s career is in real life.</description>
<picture>19519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8874" type="appears in" update="2010-03-24">
<rating votes="15">7.23</rating>
<name>Aura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9953" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-27">
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<name>Bear</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9954" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-27">
<rating votes="6">6.76</rating>
<name>Sora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9955" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-27">
<rating votes="9">6.89</rating>
<name>Crim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9956" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="20">6.09</rating>
<name>Subaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Subaru is a petite, blue-haired woman who wears a light blue dress. She has small, feathery wings that sprout out of her back, and has a red wave tattoo on her forehead. She possesses a regal-looking axe, but rarely uses it in combat, preferring to hold it as a type of scepter. In the episode Recollection, when she reminisces the early days of the Crimson Knights, she is shown to have a pink dress.
Subaru is soft spoken, but has a very determined personality. As the leader of the Crimson Knights, she is frequently called upon to settle disputes both inside and outside of the guild. Though she is aware of the power she wields, she is fiercely dedicated to her position and refuses to let such power change the way she acts. Subaru is very protective of The World`s players, and does her best to make The World a place that everybody can enjoy. Her strongest supporters are Silver Knight and Crim.</description>
<picture>30103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9957" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-27">
<rating votes="8">7.04</rating>
<name>BT</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15313" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-27">
<rating votes="17">3.87</rating>
<name>Ginkan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silver Knight is second-in-command of the Crimson Knights. As described by Frank Ellis he possesses a strong sense of justice (becoming overzealous at times), but is extremely naive, leading him to end up as more of a tool to be used by whoever is in control. He is extremely overprotective of Subaru. Silver Knight`s PC is an edited version of the standard Crimson Knight design.
Later in the series, he tells Mimiru that he is 23 and works in a video store.</description>
<picture>43718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31939" type="appears in" update="2011-05-06">
<rating votes="3">7.55</rating>
<name>Shouji An</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shouji An is the real life player behind Tsukasa. She is actually female. An was raised by her father after the death of her mother, and was physically and mentally abused by him. His abusive behavior also distanced her from her gender: he treated her like a boy, refusing to allow her to use feminine products and basic hygiene products. There are also subtle hints that her father is an alcoholic. After awaking from her coma, Sakuma Ryo, the player behind Bear, becomes her legal guardian and allows her to go to a boarding school. She meets with Mariko, Subaru`s player, and the two begin a relationship.</description>
<picture>71030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31940" type="appears in" update="2011-05-06">
<rating votes="3">8.52</rating>
<name>Misono Mariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misono Mariko is the real life player behind Subaru. She is a paraplegic girl who spends so much time in The World because it is the only place where she can roam freely on her own. At the end of the series, she meets Shouji An, Tsukasa`s player, and the two begin a relationship.</description>
<picture>71031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62877" type="appears in" update="2014-01-07">
<rating votes="2">2.79</rating>
<name>BlackRose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>in the game "The World", BlackRose is a female Heavy Blade character who meets Kite in the video game series. BlackRose is just starting on her adventure at the same time as Kite (though this is a fact she attempts to hide when they initially meet). The two clash immediately, but warm up to each other little by little. She reveals that her purpose for joining is to find a cure for the data bug that placed her brother in a coma. BlackRose is a young woman with a tough-as-nails attitude and can be a bit full of herself at times. Luckily, she has Kite alongside her to balance her out and keep her in check. In the anime .hack//Gift and .hack//Unison BlackRose is shown to have a sort of rivalry with Mimiru another heavy blade who shares a similar avatar. Her real name is Hayami Akira and is a member of the tennis team at her high school.</description>
<picture>148225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72881" type="appears in" update="2015-01-27">
<name>Balmung</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Balmung is one of the Descendants of Fianna and is a very famous player in The World.</description>
<picture>168047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72882" type="appears in" update="2015-01-27">
<name>Orca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orca of the Azure Sea, one of the Descendants of Fianna, is a legendary Blademaster that was famed for destroying the One Sin along with Balmung.</description>
<picture>168048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4004" picture="77763.jpg">Masutani Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72883" type="appears in" update="2015-01-27">
<name>Kite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kite is the main character of the .hack//Games.</description>
<picture>168049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1934" picture="186186.jpg">Aida Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82691" type="appears in" update="2016-06-27">
<name>Macha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187926.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="82692" type="appears in" update="2017-03-27">
<name>Helba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Helba is an infamous hacker that appears throughout the parts of the .hack series in The World R:1
Helba is a surprisingly tall female character that wears revealing clothing. She dons head-wear similar to a priest`s cap that covers her eyes. Her normally masked face is revealed in the second volume of XXXX.</description>
<picture>187927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82693" type="appears in" update="2016-06-27">
<name>A-20</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83492" type="appears in" update="2016-08-03">
<name>Harald Hoerwick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83493" type="appears in" update="2016-08-03">
<name>Onna Senshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83495" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Elk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83497" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Mia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83498" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Mistral</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83499" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Morganna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morganna is was a system created by Harald Hoerwick to oversee the birth of the Ultimate AI from the personality data of the players of The World. Upon realizing that she would have no purpose once Aura, the Ultimate AI, was born, she attempted to stall the growth of Aura indefinitely, resulting in many of the events in the .hack series.
Source: dothack.wikia.com</description>
<picture>190492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83500" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Lios</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83502" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Kaochin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="431" picture="23201.jpg">Nakayama Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83503" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Salue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83504" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Puchiguso</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Grunties (Puchiguso) are pig-like creatures that players of The World can raise in Root Towns as virtual pets. As a type of NPC, most Grunties can speak.
Source: dothack.wikia.com</description>
<picture>189687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23339" picture="62635.jpg">Kondou Mitsuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83505" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Mimika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mimika is a character controlled by 3 girls. They decided to create only this character for all of them, feeling that it would be much more special than if they made a character for each one of them.
Source: dothack.wikia.com</description>
<picture>190481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83506" type="appears in" update="2016-08-04">
<name>Aka no Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3893" picture="25603.jpg">Nagano Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83507" type="appears in" update="2016-08-04">
<name>Ao no Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6345" picture="30893.jpg">Kouno Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83508" type="appears in" update="2016-08-04">
<name>Ki no Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83512" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Kenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46531" picture="189659.jpg">Matsuo Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83514" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Kenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4728" picture="27583.jpg">Kobayashi Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83515" type="appears in" update="2016-08-03">
<name>Senshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83516" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mimika was controlled by three girls in their final year of high school named Mirei, Miruko, and Misaki. They shared the belief that they grew to become uninteresting girls that weren`t special in any way and felt that if they`d all created individual characters, they wouldn`t be able to progress very far in the game, so instead they took turns playing Mimika.
Source: dothack.wikia.com</description>
<picture>190482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23339" picture="62635.jpg">Kondou Mitsuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83517" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Miruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mimika was controlled by three girls in their final year of high school named Mirei, Miruko, and Misaki. They shared the belief that they grew to become uninteresting girls that weren`t special in any way and felt that if they`d all created individual characters, they wouldn`t be able to progress very far in the game, so instead they took turns playing Mimika.
Source: dothack.wikia.com</description>
<picture>190482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83518" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Mirei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mimika was controlled by three girls in their final year of high school named Mirei, Miruko, and Misaki. They shared the belief that they grew to become uninteresting girls that weren`t special in any way and felt that if they`d all created individual characters, they wouldn`t be able to progress very far in the game, so instead they took turns playing Mimika.
Source: dothack.wikia.com</description>
<picture>190482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83519" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Juukenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83543" type="appears in" update="2016-08-03">
<name>Jumon Tsukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83583" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Jumon Tsukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="688" picture="18295.jpg">Tanaka Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83584" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Jumon Tsukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31735" picture="229093.jpg">Kawasugi Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83585" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<name>Yari Tsukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46545" picture="189700.jpg">Katou Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84063" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Shoujo Kenshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84064" type="appears in" update="2016-08-25">
<name>Seinen Kenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3272" picture="172136.jpg">Mizushima Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Role Play</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Role Play</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rollenspiele</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jeux de rôle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Role Play</title>
<summary>Tsukasa is trapped in an MMORPG called The World. With his conscious inaccessible, Tsukasa attempts to find his purpose for being in the game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="253" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schutzengel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ange gardien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guardian</title>
<summary>Tsukasa’s inability to log out of the world worries Mimiru. The Crimson Knights, on the other hand, see Tsukasa as a threat.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="254" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Folklore</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Folklore</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Folklore</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Folklore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Folklore</title>
<summary>BT and Sora suspect that Tsukasa is somehow connected to a very important artifact, the Key of the Twilight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="256" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Wanted</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wanted</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gesucht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avis de recherche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wanted</title>
<summary>Tsukasa’s rampaging Guardian monster wreaks havoc in The World, and an edict from Subaru makes him a wanted man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="268" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Captured</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captured</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefangen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Capture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Captured</title>
<summary>Tsukasa finally tames his Guardian monster, but unbeknownst to him, someone is plotting his capture.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="509" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Declaration</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erklärung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La déclaration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Declaration</title>
<summary>Silver Knight disrupts any and all potential rendezvous between Subaru and Tsukasa. Subaru ponders the future of the Crimson Knights.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="668" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Begegnung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rencontre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Encounter</title>
<summary>Subaru carefully observes Tsukasa, gradually getting to know him. Sora mounts a rescue mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="669" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Reason</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reason</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vernunft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Raison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reason</title>
<summary>Mimiru encounters a novice player and offers her guidance in The World. This new relationship helps Mimiru uncover her own motivation for playing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="670" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="15">3.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Versprechen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La promesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promise</title>
<summary>Mimiru extends Tsukasa an invitation to meet; BT and Crim share an interesting encounter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="671" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Epitaph</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Epitaph</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Epitaph</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épitaphe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Epitaph</title>
<summary>An elite hacker proves instrumental in the quest for the Key of the Twilight, and Tsukasa gets stuck with a sick Grunty.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="672" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Compensation</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Compensation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ausgleich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La compensation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Compensation</title>
<summary>Bear’s shortcomings as a father may be the root of his concern for Tsukasa. Clues arise as the search for the Key of the Twilight continues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="673" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Party</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Party</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Party</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Party</title>
<summary>Mimiru, Bear, and Tsukasa join forces before embarking on a non-fighting quest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="674" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Entanglement</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entanglement</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verwicklungen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Enchevêtrement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Entanglement</title>
<summary>Tsukasa stumbles upon Aura, an advanced AI, that is being held captive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="675" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Twilight Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twilight Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Twilight Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`œil du crépuscule</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Twilight Eye</title>
<summary>A way to open the Twilight Eye is discovered, and the group decides to follow the new path unfolding before them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="676" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schloss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le château</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Castle</title>
<summary>After the Eye is opened, a secret area appears, complicating the group’s search for the key.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="677" recap="true" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Evidence</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evidence</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Beweis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La preuve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Evidence</title>
</episode>
<episode id="678" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Depth</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Depth</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tiefe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Abysse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Depth</title>
<summary>Tsukasa logs back into The World, only to discover that he cannot die. Shocked, he turns to Subaru for answers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="679" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Konflikt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le conflit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Conflict</title>
<summary>Crim refuses to meet BT outside of the game. Later, Tsukasa mounts a rescue attempt – and secrets are revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1648" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Recollection</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Recollection</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erinnerung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Recollection</title>
<summary>Subaru drifts aimlessly through The World, reflecting on her past experiences. Her connection with Tsukasa grows even stronger after an unexpected attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1649" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Tempest</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tempest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sturm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tempest</title>
<summary>Aura goes missing, Morganna attacks Tsukasa, and the search for the Key of the Twilight continues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2159" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fantôme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom</title>
<summary>Bear, Mimiru, and Subaru are attacked by yet another seemingly-unstoppable monster, but Balmung comes to the rescue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2312" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nachtwache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La veille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Eve</title>
<summary>Tsukasa is too frightened to pass through Helba’s gate, and Crim explains Subaru’s true life condition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2313" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Net Slum</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Net Slum</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Slums im Netz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cyber-sanctuaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Net Slum</title>
<summary>Upon arriving in Helba’s realm – Net Slum – the group is forced to defend Subaru from an attack by Morganna.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2345" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Catastrophe</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Catastrophe</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Katastrophe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Catastrophe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Catastrophe</title>
<summary>As the battle intensifies, the group seeks shelter in the Cathedral. Morganna summons Guardians to do her bidding.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2347" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Return</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rückkehr</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Return</title>
<summary>Drawing strength from Subaru, Tsukasa summons the courage to awaken Aura. Outside of The World, players share a true life encounter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3002" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verzweiflung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Désespoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Despair</title>
<summary>Tsukasa lingers in a catatonic state, and some immensely powerful monsters make their presence felt in The World.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7176" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Intermezzo</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intermezzo</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Intermezzo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Intermède</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Intermezzo</title>
<summary>Two years before Tsukasa’s arrival in The World, Mimiru encounters a mysterious character that helps her learn an important lesson about the game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11483" update="2010-04-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11484" update="2010-04-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12820" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Unison</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unison</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En chœur</title>
<summary>Tsukasa makes her first return to The World for a festive party hosted by Helba. Later, Subaru dances the night away, and Aura looks down from above.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
