<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2404" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2004-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">To Heart: Remember My Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">トゥハート Remember my memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ToHeart-r</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">th rmm</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ToHeart Remember my memories</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="414" type="Prequel">To Heart</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toheart-r.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1539" type="Direction">Motonaga Keitarou</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="910" type="Animation Work">AIC A.S.T.A</name>
<name id="8569" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirayama Madoka</name>
<name id="1905" type="Music">Nagaoka Seikou</name>
<name id="8569" type="Character Design">Hirayama Madoka</name>
<name id="1146" type="Original Work">Aquaplus</name>
</creators>
<description>Time flies by; http://anidb.net/ch5048 [Hiroyuki] and http://anidb.net/ch5049 [Akari] are 12th-graders now. Both of them and their friends have grown up gradually in someway, physically or mentally, but one of their best friends is missing: the life-like android, http://anidb.net/ch5050 [Multi]. To their surprise, Multi is brought to their campus again without notice. Yet, she is no longer the same Multi they have known...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="786">4.00</permanent>
<temporary count="799">6.61</temporary>
<review count="3">6.44</review>
</ratings>
<picture>5232.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4455</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>685</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1474</identifier>
<identifier>zfmcrp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toheart-r.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>To_Heart#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>To_Heart#To_Heart_.E3.80.9CRemember_my_Memories.E3.80.9C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>502</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7005</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3475" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-18">
<rating votes="38">5.44</rating>
<name>Yuzuhara Konomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konomi is the main female character, and is childhood friends with Takaaki. Although in the beginning of the game she is still in junior high school, she joins him in the same high school at the beginning of the new school term. Konomi has a friendly disposition, and is often smiling and happy. She sometimes tries hard at cooking, and enjoys being with Takaaki.</description>
<picture>19235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="134" picture="16880.jpg">Ochiai Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3481" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-18">
<rating votes="35">4.17</rating>
<name>Himeyuri Sango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sango is the older Himeyuri twin. She is one school year younger than the protagonist, and helped develop the next generation maid gynoids for Kurusugawa Electronics. While she is quite bright in the technical aspect, to others, she seems quite naive and almost childish. Despite her childish attitude, Sango appears to be the "older sister" of the pair and often gives advice to her twin sister, Ruri. Both her and Ruri, speak with an extremely strong Kansai dialect.</description>
<picture>19241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2945" picture="177565.jpg">Ishizuka Sayori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3482" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-02-18">
<rating votes="26">4.26</rating>
<name>Himeyuri Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruri is the younger Himeyuri twin. She is one school year younger than the protagonist, and is in the same class as Sango. She is fiercely protective and possessive of her sister, and when Sango finds herself attracted to Takaaki, Ruri becomes jealous and even hostile towards him. She is an excellent cook, as well. Unlike her twin sister, Ruri is not very bright and cannot develop robots.</description>
<picture>19242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4838" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5048" type="main character in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="10">3.23</rating>
<name>Fujita Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main male character and has a very dry attitude. He is surprisingly empathetic though, but usually shows it through his actions rather than what he says or how he acts towards people. Hiroyuki is also a childhood friend of Akari , and gradually throughout the storyline falls in love with her. He lives alone.</description>
<picture>21404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5049" type="main character in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="25">7.37</rating>
<name>Kamigishi Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroyuki`s childhood friend. She will almost always go to wake Hiroyuki up in the morning to go to school. She is especially fond of teddy bears, with special emphasis on the one that Hiroyuki gave her during their childhood. Both Akari and Hiroyuki have known each other since kindergarten and they are extremely close. She is very much in love with Hiroyuki and spends a lot of time around him. Akari likes to call Hiroyuki with the chan suffix attached, despite his occasional protests. Akari is very adept at cooking and is a member of the school`s cooking club.</description>
<picture>21403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5050" type="main character in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="22">6.25</rating>
<name>Multi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An experimental humanoid maid robot from the HM (Human Maiden) series robots made by Kurusugawa Electronics. She was sent to Fujita`s school to learn how to behave like a human. Multi is a very cheerful girl who loves to clean. Unfortunately, she isn`t very good at it nor household chores, which contradicts her purpose.</description>
<picture>21405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5051" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="15">5.59</rating>
<name>Nagaoka Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiho first met Akari, Hiroyuki and Masashi during the first year of junior-high school. She is more of a tomboy than Akari, and often finds herself at odds with Hiroyuki, but starts to develop feelings for Hiroyuki.</description>
<picture>21406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2140" picture="21615.jpg">Higuchi Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5052" type="appears in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="10">6.90</rating>
<name>Kurusugawa Serika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Kurusugawa family, which is quite wealthy and operates a conglomerate of companies in their name, including the labs which produced Multi and Serio. She speaks very quietly and it is very difficult to hear what she says unless standing right beside her - as a result, we often see Hiroyuki repeat what she just said.</description>
<picture>21407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5053" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="12">6.05</rating>
<name>Hoshina Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A native of Kobe and speaks the Kansai dialect. She has a very serious, responsible nature, and serves as the class president. Her seriousness is conveyed by her tightly bound hair and coke-bottle glasses, though she is quite pretty when she removes these features.</description>
<picture>21408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5054" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="12">5.87</rating>
<name>Matsubara Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A practitioner of a particular style of martial arts known as "Extreme Rules". However, because she doesn`t adhere to the more traditional martial arts such as Karate, she is spurned by the mainstream martial artists. She is still a very determined girl. She idolises Kurusugawa Ayaka since the latter also happens to practice the same "Extreme Rules" form of martial arts.</description>
<picture>21409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2138" picture="21613.jpg">Iizuka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5055" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="8">6.97</rating>
<name>Himekawa Kotone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with psychic powers, but is unable to fully control them. When she was introduced, it is revealed that she does not have control over her psychic powers; instead bottling them up until she can no longer restrain them anymore, causing devastation. She likes udon.</description>
<picture>21410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5056" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="17">5.49</rating>
<name>Miyauchi Lemmy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lemmy is half American, half Japanese - her full name is Lemmy Christopher Helen Miyauchi. She speaks Japanese with a stereotypical American accent, and often makes mistakes with the meanings of Japanese sayings. She also has a tendency to slip in English words during conversations when she has the chance. She also ends a lot of her sentences with "-ne" and overuses the word "fantastic".</description>
<picture>21411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2139" picture="25822.jpg">Kasahara Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5057" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="10">6.91</rating>
<name>Kurusugawa Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Serika`s younger sister. Despite looking similar, they have totally different character personalities. Ayaka is very outgoing and confident, and enjoys martial arts. They get along very well, but go to different schools and have different paths in life.</description>
<picture>21412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5058" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="8">5.32</rating>
<name>Serio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Multi`s younger sister: an advanced successor of Multi, but without emotions. Serio was sent with Ayaka to Sanyo Girls` School for field testing and speaks using formal Japanese. She is technically superior to Multi and is equipped with a satellite system capable of communicating with and storing data on the Kurusagawa mainframe host computer. Serio is more effective than Multi as a maid robot but because she lacks emotions, does not feel as human. She does have a heart, and tries to help people even though she may fail as she is unable to understand the complex emotional aspects behind them.</description>
<picture>21413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5059" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="7">6.03</rating>
<name>Satou Masashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroyuki`s closest male friend. He grew up with Hiroyuki and Akari, and attended the same kindergarten and Junior High School. He is adept at football and generally has a soft, friendly character.</description>
<picture>21414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11104" type="appears in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="6">5.79</rating>
<name>Sakashita Yoshie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of the karate club (where http://anidb.net/ch5054 [Aoi] used to be a member).</description>
<picture>33004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11145" type="appears in" update="2009-08-13">
<rating votes="11">5.98</rating>
<name>Hinayama Rio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinayama Rio spends time on getting part-time jobs, and is a fan of romance manga and anime. She is very self-sufficient, and has several part-time jobs including selling cakes at Christmas and delivering the paper. She has feelings for http://anidb.net/ch5048 [Hiroyuki]. She has the feature of "hair antennae" (a pair of long hairs that stick straight up), which is rampant in some anime but unique in this one.</description>
<picture>33108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12294" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-14">
<rating votes="8">4.83</rating>
<name>Nagase Gengorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Researcher of http://anidb.net/ch5050 [Multi] and http://anidb.net/ch5058 [Serio] from Kurusugawa Electronics.</description>
<picture>37211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12298" type="appears in" update="2010-12-18">
<rating votes="6">5.13</rating>
<name>Kamigishi Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch5049 [Akari]`s mother.</description>
<picture>46880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12299" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<rating votes="4">4.47</rating>
<name>Sebastian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch5052 [Kurusugawa]`s butler.</description>
<picture>140953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17016" type="appears in" update="2010-04-24">
<name>Kurusugawa Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2144" picture="21622.jpg">Maruyama Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17017" type="appears in" update="2011-03-24">
<name>Tomoko no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch5053 [Hoshina Tomoko]`s father.</description>
<picture>46815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17066" type="appears in" update="2012-02-06">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Aihara Mizuho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aihara Mizuho was a genius university student, working for Kurusugawa Electronics and creator of the emotion software for their android prototype HMX-11 a.k.a. http://anidb.net/ch17067 [Feel].
Mizuho appears only in a flashback scene; she died in a car accident years ago, leaving behind her heartbroken lover http://anidb.net/ch17068 [Nagase Yuusuke], and causing the HMX-11 project to be discontinued.</description>
<picture>46876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17067" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Feel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23285">Tagami Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17068" type="appears in" update="2010-04-25">
<rating votes="1">9.72</rating>
<name>Nagase Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17069" type="appears in" update="2010-04-25">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Miyauchi Cindy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Miyauchi Lemmy`s mother</description>
<picture>46879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="309" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23157" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Premonition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24829" update="2019-07-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">昔と, 今と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Then and Now</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukashi to, Ima to</title>
<summary>We are in a flashback where Hiroyuki first meets Multi. We later learn that Multi has lost her memory and that her mind is rejecting her memory from back then, so Hiroyuki tries really hard, but failed, but made a little progress.
Source: Wikipedia.org</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24929" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, 君は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Then, You...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite, Kimi wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25070" update="2019-07-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強さと, 優しさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strength and Kindness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyosa to, Yasashisa</title>
<summary>Aoi is training for the upcoming extreme tournament with Hiroyuki as her training partner and Kotone acting as her manager. Akai and Multi stop by and help to clean the shrine when Ayaka, who was out for a run as part of her training, invites Aoi to join her and be her sparring partner at her mansion for a special training camp to prepare for the tournament. While at the mansion Multi and Seiro are sent to pick strawberries. While there the head gardener comes down with heat exhaustion at which time a helpless Multi can only comfort the old man while her sister robot contact an ambulance by her link to a satellite installed in her head. This makes Multi wonder whether she is really any use as a robot.
Source: Wikipedia.org</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25991" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">越えるべき壁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wall That Must Be Scaled</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koerubeki Kabe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25992" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出の街, 思い出の人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remembered Town, Remembered People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide no Machi, Omoide no Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26061" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人の願い, 二人の夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Person`s Wish, Two People`s Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori no Negai, Futari no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26164" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボットの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Robot`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26495" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違う心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silent Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigau Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27447" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">長い夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagai Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27448" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">理解[わか]りあうために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Order to Understand Each Other</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakariau Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27449" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしの, 居場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Place</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no, Ibasho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27450" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの未来[あした]へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Their Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Ashita e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45951" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - Tomoko vs. Lemmy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45952" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - Shiho vs. Rio</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45953" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - Aoi vs. Ayaka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45954" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - Kotone vs. Serika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45955" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - Serio vs. Multi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45956" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - Multi vs. Akari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45957" update="2006-01-13">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Fighters - `X` vs. Akari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95411" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95412" update="2011-01-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
