<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2418" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-09-24</startdate>
<enddate>2004-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaleido Star: Aratanaru Tsubasa - Extra Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kaleido Star ~New Wings~ EXTRA STAGE</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">카레이도 스타: 새로운 날개 EXTRA STAGE</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Звездата на Калейдо - Специална сцена</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kaleido star ova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カレイドスター ~新たなる翼~ EXTRA STAGE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kaleido Star: Extra Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Kaleido Star: A Szomorú Hercegnő</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4123" type="Sequel">Kaleido Star: Legend of Phoenix - Layla Hamilton Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="635" type="Prequel">Kaleido Star</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="331735">Pretty much only for Rosetta/loli fans (and maybe for some Fool fans at most). Otherwise, ignore.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kaleidostar.jp/events/ova_s01.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3611" type="Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="1602" type="Animation Work">Gonzo Digimation</name>
<name id="115" type="Character Design">Watanabe Hajime</name>
<name id="4158" type="Character Design">Oizaki Fumitoshi</name>
<name id="1790" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Reiko</name>
<name id="3611" type="Original Plan">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="2149" type="Direction">Hiraike Yoshimasa</name>
<name id="115" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Hajime</name>
<name id="4158" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oizaki Fumitoshi</name>
<name id="4441" type="Music">Kubota Mina</name>
</creators>
<description>Sora Naegino has finally consolidated herself as Kaleido Stage`s greatest star ever, and a new star starts to shine as Rosetta Passel is selected to participate in the next attraction in a main role. But when things start to go wrong in the rehearsals, Rosetta starts to question her ability to take the role, as her own capacity to remain in Kaleido Stage. Meanwhile, Fool also struggles with his demons from the past.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="852">6.55</permanent>
<temporary count="857">7.47</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>5614.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4201</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1604</identifier>
<identifier>zhjkdz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kaleidostar.jp/events/ova_s01.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>カレイドスター#.E3.82.B7.E3.83.AA.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA.E6.A6.82.E8.A6.81</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>771</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="658" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>gymnastics</name>
<description>A competitive sport in which this character performs optional and prescribed acrobatic feats mostly on special apparatus in order to demonstrate strength, balance, and body control.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2280" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>acrobatics</name>
<description>Acrobatics is the performance of extraordinary human feats of balance, agility, and motor coordination.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4421" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>circus</name>
<description>A circus is a company of performers that may include clowns, acrobats, trained animals, trapeze acts, musicians, hoopers, tightrope walkers, jugglers, unicyclists and other object manipulation and stunt-oriented artists. The term circus also describes the performance which has followed various formats through its 250 year modern history. 
Philip Astley is credited with being the father of the modern circus when he opened the first circus in 1768 in England. Early circuses were almost exclusively demonstrations of equestrian skills with a few other types of acts to link the horsemanship performances. Performances developed significantly through the next fifty years, with large scale theatrical battle reenactments becoming a significant feature. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>169460.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7215" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="224">9.02</rating>
<name>Naegino Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sora is the primary protagonist of Kaleido Star. Her parents took her to Kaleido Stage when she was young. Although they died shortly thereafter, and Sora was adopted by her father`s cousin and his wife, Sora is inspired by this childhood memory to become a member of the Stage when she reaches adulthood. With her adoptive parent`s hesitant approval she travels to the United States to audition.
While Sora wanders around lost, her bag is stolen. As a consequence of chasing the thief and speaking to the police, she is late to the audition; Layla will not allow her to audition, but the owner Kalos gives her a chance to perform in the actual show. Most of the cast do not accept Sora at first because of the special circumstances through which she joins; Sora wins them over with persistence and hard work along with a magnetic personality.</description>
<picture>27386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8285" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="17">4.49</rating>
<name>Mia Guillem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mia wants to introduce more literature and drama into Kaleido Stage`s performances. She runs her own website devoted to the Kaleido Stage and provides information on the show and its performers. Sora and Anna joined the Kaleido Stage at the same time as Mia and the three of them are good friends. She is very close with her family, especially her grandmother, who was in the hospital at the same time Mia was making her stage debut.</description>
<picture>27400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8287" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="22">6.57</rating>
<name>Anna Heart</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of a struggling standup comedian, Anna joined Kaleido Stage at the same time as Mia and Sora, and the three of them are all good friends. Anna`s boyish appearance appeals to many of the Kaleido Stage`s female fans. Anna feels that it is her duty to introduce comedy to Kaleido Stage and wants to focus on playing comical parts. However Anna`s ideas for comedic improvisation are usually pretty far fetched and are promptly shot down by Sora and Mia before they get off the ground.</description>
<picture>27398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8288" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="21">1.73</rating>
<name>Ken Robbins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While he had ambitions of being a stage performer, Ken is a pretty fragile guy who cannot exercise or eat spicy foods due to a chronic heart condition. Despite this, Ken does everything he can to support the cast and crew of Kaleido Stage. Ken is Sora`s biggest supporter and does everything he can to help her out. While he really likes Sora, his timing of approaching her is always bad, dashing his hopes of getting with her. Ken shows exceptional promise as a show producer.</description>
<picture>27399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8289" type="main character in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="17">7.95</rating>
<name>Fool</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fool can only be seen by specially selected human beings... and the occasional baby seal. Fool is searching for a human being that is capable of executing a legendary performance that has killed performers in the past who failed to master it properly.</description>
<picture>130778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9218" type="main character in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="41">7.65</rating>
<name>Rosetta Passel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rosetta Passel is one of Sora`s many friends in the Kaleido Star anime. While she was raised in France, her original birth took place in Belgium. She has been a diabolo prodigy since she was nine years old, when she won her first diabolo tournament, and once went by the nickname of "The Diabolo Machine" due to her flawless performances and cold personality. Like Layla, Sora helps change Rosetta`s outlook on everything when they become friends. When Rosetta joins the main cast in the second season, she sees Sora as a role model figure and wants to be just like her while a strong sister like bond grows between them.</description>
<picture>28731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9219" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="42">5.33</rating>
<name>May Wong</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>May Wong is a new main character added to Kaleido Star during it`s second season titled New Wings. At first, May ultimately hates Sora and considers herself her rival. But later on, she accepts Sora as a friend and the two become close friends like Sora is with all of her friends. May is a really good cook and she is often seen singing quietly to herself while doing activities. She also makes up names for maneuvers and everything she does like bursting through doors or going down the elevator. She also has many younger brother and sisters that root for her. Her dreams were to "defeat" Sora and perform one day alongside Layla.</description>
<picture>28732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29118" type="appears in" update="2011-02-24">
<rating votes="10">3.17</rating>
<name>Leon Oswald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32047" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="5">2.14</rating>
<name>Yuri Killian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri, like Layla, is an experienced performer, yet he`s deeply traumatized by a terrible tragedy. His father, Arlon Brass, died attempting the Mystical Act, and he never forgave Kalos for letting his father die. Yuri plays a pivotal role in the second half of the first season when he betrays the stage, first by stealing away a good portion of the cast and later by buying out the stage and taking control of it. He later agrees to return it to Kalos if Layla and Sora accomplish the same Mystical Act that caused his father`s death; when they manage to do so, he fulfills his promise. In the second season, Yuri helps Sora get into the Circus Festival in Paris. He appears to be a bitter rival of Leon`s, and feels that he is responsible for the death of Leon`s sister, Sophie who was a lot like Sora in many ways.</description>
<picture>71239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32048" type="appears in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="6">7.08</rating>
<name>Sarah Dupont</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarah is the main singer of Kaleido Stage from the United Kingdom, as well as the building manager for the dorms where everyone lives. Many want Sarah to sign on a record label because she is so gifted in singing, but she stays true to Kaleido Stage. She is an avid fan of martial arts, and frequently proposes bizarre alternative methods to help Sora achieve her objectives.
Sarah is well acquainted with Kalos and has been with the Stage from the beginning, when she and Kalos were performing on the streets with another friend. This friend, Andy, returns once to try to persuade Sarah to leave Kaleido Stage with offering her a singing career, but she refuses.</description>
<picture>71240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32049" type="appears in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="11">5.22</rating>
<name>Kalos Eido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kalos is the head manager and boss of the entire Kaleido Stage and gives Sora many helpful pieces of advice throughout the anime. He also maintains high expectations of everyone he encounters. Before Kaleido Stage, Kalos was a stage magician and acrobat and used to perform on the street with Sarah and Andy; their past relationship is rather vague. Kalos founded Kaleido Stage with the money he got from the insurance company after he injured his fingers during an audition for a spot in Las Vegas. As a professional, he has strict standards when it comes to how things are run at the Kaleido Stage and how his performers should conduct themselves. While he`s firm in his decisions, occasionally he`ll give in and let people spread their wings as they please. Kalos is also the one who trained Yuri`s father, Arlon Brass, for the Mystical Act, but sadly this failed and Arlon died, traumatising Yuri and embittering him. He is the only person who can tell Layla and Sora how to train for the act.</description>
<picture>71241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32051" type="appears in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="3">3.18</rating>
<name>Marion Benigni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marion is a young girl living near the stage. Her father is a designer and engineer and works on the sets, but her mother Cynthia (a former trampolinist) is dead due to an accident. Like many of the others, Marion does not accept Sora at first (and specially when Sora attempts to use trampolines in her acts), but is quickly won over to her side. In the second season Marion begins to perform with the group on the Children`s Stage.</description>
<picture>71243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32052" type="appears in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="2">3.56</rating>
<name>Jonathan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jonathan is a baby seal that Sora picked up one day. Unable to keep pets, Sora tries to hide him. However, the secret is revealed and instead of kicking him out, Marion`s father Jake builds a tank for him. He is capable of doing many tricks and sometimes seems more coordinated than Sora, creating comical performances that the attending children love. During the second season, Jonathan becomes closer to Marion and refuses to perform with anyone else.</description>
<picture>71244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38408" type="appears in" update="2011-11-05">
<rating votes="3">4.94</rating>
<name>Jean Benigni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3231" picture="24214.jpg">Sugawara Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39945" type="appears in" update="2011-12-26">
<name>Macquarie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7067" picture="32080.jpg">Shima Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40540" type="appears in" update="2012-01-13">
<rating votes="2">8.44</rating>
<name>Barbara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29938" picture="223212.jpg">Kosaka Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40541" type="appears in" update="2012-01-13">
<rating votes="2">8.44</rating>
<name>Hannah</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4217" picture="151698.jpg">Yanagisawa Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="22484" update="2017-09-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">笑わない すごい お姫様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Amazing Princess Without a Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">웃지 않는! 굉장한! 공주님!</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A szomorú hercegnő</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warawanai Sugoi Ohime-sama</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">La fantástica princesa que no podía sonreír</title>
<summary>Fast forward to the future! Rosetta is on the verge of becoming a Kaleido Star, but when she loses the ability to see Fool, she fears that her dreams of sharing the spotlight with Sora may never come true!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155980" update="2013-11-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155981" update="2013-11-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
