<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2443" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2005-06-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahoraba: Heartful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">我們的仙境</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Mahoraba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mhd</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">まほらば -Heartful days-</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10288" approval="18" total="26">Bokura wa Minna Kawai-sou</anime>
<anime id="35" approval="9" total="16">Love Hina</anime>
<anime id="74" approval="4" total="6">Ai yori Aoshi</anime>
<anime id="2835" approval="1" total="11">Hachimitsu to Clover</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="78827">A quite gentle comedy, though not without a few dark undertones and with some of the more interesting characters found in anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="295259">this is one of the best anime i have ever seen it will survive a long time and hopefully they will make a second one ^^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/mahoraba/</url>
<creators>
<name id="123" type="Series Composition">Yamada Yasunori</name>
<name id="8451" type="Original Work">Kojima Akira</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="3744" type="Character Design">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="2965" type="Direction">Kimura Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="3744" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="12105" type="Music">Anne</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch13039 [Shiratori Ryuushi] wants to become a picture book writer, and he moves to an apartment, Narutaki-So, in order to go to an art school in Tokyo. Narutaki-so is an old Japanese style one-story house which does not fit the urban scenery. It is owned by the cousin of his mother, and the manager of the apartment is http://anidb.net/ch13038 [Aoba Kozue]. She is his second cousin, and they met each other when they were children although he does not remember her much. She is in the second grade of a high school attached to Aoba Junior College.
There are five people living in Narutaki-So: First, http://anidb.net/ch13034 [Chanohata Tamami] is living in room #1. She is a best friend of Kozue. Then, the resident of room #3 is http://anidb.net/ch13033 [Momono Megumi]. She is a kind of person who goes her own way. In room #5, http://anidb.net/ch13035 [Kurosaki Sayoko] and her daughter http://anidb.net/ch13036 [Asami] are living. Asami is in the first grade of junior high. Finally, in room #6, Haibara Yukio is living with his puppet, http://anidb.net/ch13037 [Johnny].
They are all characteristic and eccentric persons. However, in fact, the most eccentric person is Kozue, and she has a secret; when she is shocked about something, she changes her personality. Not knowing this, Ryuushi moves to Narutaki-So to realize his dream. But what kind of a new life will be waiting for him?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2049">6.76</permanent>
<temporary count="2070">7.79</temporary>
<review count="8">8.01</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228785.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4631</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>519</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1586</identifier>
<identifier>ztabjc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/mahoraba/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mahoraba#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>まほらば#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E3.80.8C.E3.81.BE.E3.81.BB.E3.82.89.E3.81.B0.E3.80.9CHeartful_days.E3.80.8D</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321612</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1027</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2005/mahoraba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>마호라바</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>我們的仙境</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9273</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2666" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>art school</name>
<description>The education in art plays an important part in this anime.
Art school is a general term for any educational institution with a primary focus on the visual arts, especially illustration, painting, photography, sculpture, and graphic design. The term applies to institutions with elementary, secondary, post-secondary or undergraduate, or graduate or postgraduate programs in these areas. They are distinguished from larger institutions which also may offer majors or degrees in the visual arts, but only as one part of a broad-based range of programs (such as the liberal arts and sciences). France`s École des Beaux-Arts is, perhaps, the first model for such organized instruction, breaking with a tradition of master and apprentice instruction when it was formed.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3981" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-27">
<name>ninja maid</name>
<description>This is an old tag for anime which had characters that were maids and also ninjas, or at least able to use ninjutsu. The tag will be removed once all maids in question are properly tagged. See also the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninja,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninja and maid] and the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninjutsu,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninjutsu and maid].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13033" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="5">5.83</rating>
<name>Momono Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Megumi attended Washida University for one year, but it turned out to be too expensive so she took a year off. Her hairstyle features an ahoge. She is now staying at Narutaki Sou all the time. She is in a long distance relationship with her Middle School boyfriend who is studying cinema overseas. She loves films (particularly poor attempts at horror) and in her room are lots of DVDs. She`s also a heavy drinker and likes to party with Johnny in Shiratori`s room, much to his dismay. In the manga her character is much more developed as she is portrayed with a darker past, in connection with her brilliant piano skills in which she comments have given her bad memories.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>38817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13034" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="8">6.43</rating>
<name>Chanohata Tamami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamami is close friends and classmates with Aoba Kozue. She always has a camera and takes pictures of embarrassing situations and Kozue. She is also an inactive member ("Ghost member") of the occult club, along with Kozue. She is very strong physically (usually K.O street punks in one hit), although she appears quite normal, if not short and weak. A perpetually smiling evil genius, Tamami is cold, sarcastic, cruel, manipulative, inconsiderate and condescending towards those she deem to be her moral/intellectual inferiors; which in other words mean everybody besides Kozue-Chan (and her other personalities). This is explained by her usually being isolated for her extreme geniuses before meeting Kozue. Of course, Tamami also goes to Seika Tandai Fuzoku High School with Kozue, and she says "desu" at the end of her sentences. In the manga, it is revealed that she is actually a very emotional person, crying all the while during Momono`s departure. (Whether she and Momono is especially close or she just loves everyone in Narutakisou is unknown). Her birthday is November 8 and at the start of the manga and anime, her age is the same as Kozue`s.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>38818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13035" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="7">8.55</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayoko has a very dark personality and is not very responsible. In the manga, she is initially suicidal, though this aspect of her character was cut out in the transition to the anime. (Also, none of her attempts at suicide are even remotely successful so they are normally just for gags.) Despite this change, however, she still remains irresponsible in both productions, but wants to make Asami happy and to live with her for a long time. Their room is filled with cardboard boxes, which they use as furniture and bedding, being extremely poor. Her father is a rich sculptor, with whom she became estranged in her youth over her choice of her husband; rather than let her parents choose a fiancé for her, she eloped with the estate`s gardener. Her favourite food is Mizuyoukan. Despite her evident uselessness throughout the series, she really cares for Asami. Though her age isn`t revealed in the manga, her birthday is October 17.
It should also be noted that despite her poor skills in living, she possesses great skills in stuffs like chess (to which Momono depicts as a useless skill in life) and in arts (capable of making artpieces out of almost anything (sand, snow, wood,...even food)), possibly inheriting her father`s skills. At the end of the manga, she is seen to work as a freelance sculptor, making an expensive looking wooden dragon. It is also revealed that she isn`t really lazy or bad at working but rather, simply having low or no confidence and motivation.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>38819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10423" picture="38443.jpg">Fujiwara Mioko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13036" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="5">5.76</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Asami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asami lives in room 5 with her adopted mother while her adopted father died when she was younger. She is a Junior High student. She keeps things together in spite of her mother`s problems, pulling most of the workload and keeping track of expenses. At the beginning of the series, she is twelve years old and her birthday is June 26.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>38820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4813" picture="45576.jpg">Tenjin Umi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13037" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-15">
<rating votes="3">6.85</rating>
<name>Haibara Yukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13038" type="main character in" update="2009-11-25">
<rating votes="11">8.13</rating>
<name>Aoba Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13039" type="main character in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="3">6.85</rating>
<name>Shiratori Ryuushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuushi, the male protagonist of the series, is an aspiring children`s book artist. He moved into Narutaki Sou so he could attend the Sumeragi Design School in Tokyo. Second cousins with Aoba Kozue. He had apparently met Kozue when the two were younger, but he doesn`t remember about this at the start of the series. In the beginning, he is eighteen years old and his birthday is September 9. His personality is both childish as well as passive to the point of never objecting when anyone does anything wrong to him which happens a lot.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>38823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20290" type="appears in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="5">8.59</rating>
<name>Erika Vermilion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the head of the occult research lab, of which Tamami, as well as Kozue is technically a member. She is never named and only referred to as "club president (ぶちょう, Buchou)" until the final chapter of the manga. "Erika Vermillion" is a stage name for her fortune-telling business. She has a masochistic slant as well, and painfully enjoys Tamami`s talent for insults and other unusual tortures.</description>
<picture>52447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="27401" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ鳴滝荘へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Narutaki Apartment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Narutaki-sou e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27402" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大切な場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Important Place</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taisetsu na Basho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27403" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんのひみつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ooya-san`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27404" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぬくぬく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snugly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nukunuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27440" update="2017-11-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27592" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネガポジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Negative Positive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nega Poji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27749" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">珠チェック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tama Check</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama Check</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27750" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かくれんぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hide and Seek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakurenbo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31808" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかいモノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shopping</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31809" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鳴滝荘のタカラモノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Narutaki Apartments Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Narutaki-sou no Takaramono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31810" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これくと!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Correct!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Correct!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31811" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏だ! 水着だ! 海水浴だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Summer! The Sea! Sea Bathing!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Da! Umi Da! Kaisuiyoku Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31812" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想い...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thoughts...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31813" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スケッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sketch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sketch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33847" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の終わりに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">End of Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Owari ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33848" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">...かも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">...Maybe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">...Kamo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35140" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">千客万来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flood of Customers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkyakubanrai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35820" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃーにゃーにゃー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meow Meow Meow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nya Nya Nya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35821" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そらのいろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Color of the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora no Iro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36171" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">親・子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Parent and Child</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oya Ko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36172" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園祭にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuensai Nite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36173" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなの一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone`s Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna no Tsuitachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37449" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大事...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Important Affair...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiji...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38017" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅葉の中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Among the Red Leaves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouyou no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38175" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bells</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38269" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告げる夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night of Revelation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsugeru Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38270" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まほらば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahoraba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125102" update="2010-11-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125103" update="2017-11-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150861" update="2017-11-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150862" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 梢編(short ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Kozue (Short Version)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Kozue Hen (Short Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150863" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Clip - Boku no Speed de (full length)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202090" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1時間スペシャル告知アバン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Original One-Hour Special Airing Intro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1 Jikan Special Kokuchi Avant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202970" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2006-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のまほらば劇場 ざ・びでお 6号室灰原由起夫編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahoraba Theater 5: Room 6, Haibara Yukio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Mahoraba Gekijou The Video: 6-goushitsu Haibara Yukio Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202971" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2005-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のまほらば劇場 ざ・びでお 1号室茶ノ畑編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahoraba Theater 4: Room 1, Chanohata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Mahoraba Gekijou The Video: 1-goushitsu Chanohata Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202972" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2005-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のまほらば劇場 ざ・びでお 5号室黒崎親子編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahoraba Theater 3: Room 5, Kurosaki Sayoko and Asami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Mahoraba Gekijou The Video: 5-goushitsu Kurosaki Oyako Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202973" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2005-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のまほらば劇場 ざ・びでお 3号室桃乃編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahoraba Theater 2: Room 3, Momono</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Mahoraba Gekijou The Video: 3-goushitsu Momono Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202974" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2005-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のまほらば劇場 ざ・びでお</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahoraba Theater 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Mahoraba Gekijou The Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202975" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 部長編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Club President</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Buchou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202976" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン サクラ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Sakura Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202977" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 棗編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Natsume</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Natsume Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202978" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 桃乃編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Momono</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Momono Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202979" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 原作者編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Original Author</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Gensakusha Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202980" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン ジョニー編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Johnny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Johnny Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202981" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 梢編(long ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Kozue (Long Version)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Kozue Hen (Long Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202982" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 黒崎親子編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Kurosaki Sayoko and Asami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Kurosaki Oyako Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202983" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 銀先生編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Shirogane-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Shirogane-sensei Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202984" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 灰原編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Haibara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Haibara Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202985" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワーニングアバン 珠実編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Warning: Tamaki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warning Avant: Tamaki Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
