<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="245" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-10-01</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Spiral: Suiri no Kizuna</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Spiral ~Bond of Inference~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Spiral ~Bond of Reasoning~</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Spirală</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Spiral ~Suiri no Kizuna~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">推理之绊</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スパイラル -推理の絆-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Spiral</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">스파이럴 ~추리의 띠~</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Spirála</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Spirál</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Spiral</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8855" approval="3" total="13">Hyouka</anime>
<anime id="266" approval="1" total="4">Meitantei Conan</anime>
<anime id="642" approval="1" total="3">Tantei Gakuen Q</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="622708">As others have pointed out, it`s a *highly* underrated anime with intelligent puzzles and interesting characters that you could fall in love with (but nonetheless never do, and that actually makes them even more interesting).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="386453">As everyone already mentioned: It really is a bit underrated, though i most probably know the reason why (the end).
Lordcero describes the anime really well and if you like some sort of mind games/battles and a whole lot of mystery, this anime is for you. But beware: "the sensation of incompleteness" yota71 mentioned is a real thing xD</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/spiral/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="3559" type="Original Work">Shirodaira Kyou</name>
<name id="6166" type="Direction">Kaneko Shingo</name>
<name id="4133" type="Character Design">Nakayama Yumi</name>
<name id="4133" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakayama Yumi</name>
<name id="6971" type="Music">Mitake Akira</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1437 [Narumi Ayumu] lives in the shadow of his older brother`s disappearance two years earlier. Now residing with his brother`s wife, police detective http://anidb.net/ch1445 [Narumi Madoka], Ayumu is constantly preoccupied by the last words his brother spoke: Blade Children. As a series of mysteries arise, Ayumu uses his formidable detective skills to solve the crimes. But it is always the larger mysteries that continue to loom over him. Who are the Blade Children? Why did his brother disappear?
Source: animeacademy.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1802">5.20</permanent>
<temporary count="1829">7.13</temporary>
<review count="5">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11875.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1066</identifier>
<identifier>byqwqh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/spiral/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Spiral_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スパイラル_〜推理の絆〜#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>209</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239782</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/159</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2002/spiral</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1437" type="main character in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="12">7.96</rating>
<name>Narumi Ayumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of Spiral, Ayumu is very intelligent, but is very introverted and has a lot of self-doubt. He fears that he cannot surpass his own perfect older brother and doubts himself to the point where he no longer believes he can do anything anymore without acting like his brother. He is a talented pianist like Kiyotaka, an excellent cook, and cares a lot for his sister-in-law Madoka.</description>
<picture>15909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1438" type="main character in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="16">7.30</rating>
<name>Yuizaki Hiyono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The infamous school journalist, Hiyono is the bubbly and energetic sidekick of Ayumu, always stuck to his side. Very clever and a quick-thinker, her confidence borders dangerously on overconfidence. She is extroverted and is Ayumu`s polar opposite, serving as one of the series` few comic-relief characters. Her skill with computers are as amazing as her hacking abilities and she has access to over one hundred resources. She blackmails Wataya often, and is very fond of Ayumu`s cooking. Hiyono is also one of the few who whole-heartedly believe in Ayumu; she also has a great deal of faith and loyalty in him that carries on for the whole series.</description>
<picture>15910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1439" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="9">7.39</rating>
<name>Eyes Rutherford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 17-year-old world-class pianist, he is second only to Kiyotaka Narumi, Ayumu Narumi`s older brother. He is seemingly cold-hearted but definitely not heartless. Eyes is quarter English and made his début in the musical world at the age of 14. He cares a great deal about the Blade Children and would do anything for them to survive at all costs.</description>
<picture>15911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1440" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="8">6.34</rating>
<name>Asazuki Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most arrogant, aggressive and most violent of all the Blade Children, Kousuke is usually the implementer of assassinations. Kousuke is very strong-willed and stubborn, choosing to fight the Hunters head-on rather than hide from them. He is not afraid to kill and does not really trust Eyes, resulting in arguments between them. While Rio Takeuchi calls him stupid, in reality Kousuke is very intelligent; after skipping most of elementary school, he still manages to catch up to secondary school level from reading and learning from books. Kousuke left middle school after a run in with a teacher. He is a childhood friend of Ryoko Takamachi.</description>
<picture>15912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1441" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-07">
<rating votes="13">6.69</rating>
<name>Takeuchi Rio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "midget" of the Blade Children, she resembles a 13-year-old child rather than her actual age, 16. Although Rio appears to be the most innocent of the Blade Children with her cherubic features and size, she is actually very shrewd and calculating. Rio knows how to create bombs, devise difficult plans and kill those she considers her enemies. Kanone even calls her a "fire pixie" in the manga for her small, impish appearance and skill with explosives. She is extremely intelligent and is able to escape from any sticky situation, no matter how small or tight it is. She is very straight-forward and has a crush on Eyes because he gives her "netted pattern" melons (her favourite food). Like Kousuke, she will not hesitate to kill people if she has to</description>
<picture>15913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1442" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="10">6.41</rating>
<name>Takamachi Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the most down-to-earth members of the Blade Children; Ryoko is a clever and athletic person, probably the most athletic of the Blade Children. She is a natural-born runner and can outrace almost anyone. She is a childhood friend of Kousuke Asazuki and, unlike the other Blade Children, she despises killing. She dislikes Eyes Rutherford due to past issues and cares deeply for Kousuke, though she has a tendency to use him as a punching bag and make him buy her food.</description>
<picture>15914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="212" picture="17029.jpg">Katou Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1443" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="6">7.31</rating>
<name>Kanone Hilbert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Blade Child with a dual personality. He can be cute and friendly or manipulative and insane. He was very close to Eyes. He would cry for Eyes when Eyes could not when they were young, but their friendship fell apart as they grew older and developed vastly different opinions on the fate of the Blade Children.</description>
<picture>15915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1444" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="7">5.09</rating>
<name>Shiranagatani Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A wealthy older man adopted Sayoko when she was a baby. She was shielded from the repercussions of being a Blade Child, but the truth behind her existence caused her to go inward, retreating into a world of silence and fear. But with each passing day, fate seems determined to once again drag her into the reality of the very violent existence of the Blade Children.</description>
<picture>15916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1445" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="12">7.20</rating>
<name>Narumi Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayumu`s sister-in-law and Kiyotaka`s wife, she works as a police detective but is usually outsmarted by Ayumu in most cases. Her investigation skills are remarkable, but because of work she is rarely at home and therefore can do no domestic work. She cares a great deal for Ayumu. She is pretty selfish, not quite aware of the pain her brother-in-law endures because of how much he cares for her since she is his only family now that Kiyotaka has gone missing. Madoka tries to keep Ayumu from getting too involved with the Blade Children, but proves to be another weak spot of Ayumu and is often left in the dark by Ayumu about situations concerning the Blade Children for her own safety.</description>
<picture>15917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1446" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="4">6.15</rating>
<name>Wataya Suemaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A detective in training, he works under Madoka and isn`t very smart as he jumps to conclusions without thinking about a situation thoroughly. He is regularly blackmailed by Hiyono and often hangs out with Madoka in a bar.</description>
<picture>15918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1447" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="4">4.20</rating>
<name>Shiranagatani Raizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1448" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="6">4.50</rating>
<name>Shiranagatani Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="209">Ootake Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1449" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="3">2.80</rating>
<name>Sonobe Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1450" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="5">4.40</rating>
<name>Hatsuyama Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1451" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="6">4.99</rating>
<name>Adachi Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1452" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="3">2.80</rating>
<name>Imazato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1453" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="7">4.77</rating>
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="204" picture="170798.jpg">Okada Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1454" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="4">4.43</rating>
<name>Kanzaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hunter on the police force only seen in the anime. He is constantly pressuring Madoka, telling her to quit or putting her on smaller cases, causing her to gripe about it to Wataya at the local bar.</description>
<picture>15926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="213" picture="17030.jpg">Mizuno Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1455" type="appears in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="3">2.26</rating>
<name>Hunter-A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2855" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の聖樹館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Manor of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A "shi no seijukan"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Seijukan</title>
<summary>After Sonobe is mysteriously attacked, a murder takes place in Sayoko`s home. Leading us further into the questions: What are the Blade Children and is Sayoko really a Blade Child?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2856" update="2019-07-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の螺旋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spiral of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A végzet spirálja</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Rasen</title>
<summary>What are the Blade Children? A question that has plagued Ayumu`s mind for two years. But now Ayumu has been accused of attempted murder. Who really pushed the mysterious Sayoko off the ledge? Who is Sonobe and why is he determined to make Ayumu look like the bad guy?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3660" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪われた子供たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cursed Children</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Elátkozott gyermekek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Norowareta Kodomo-tachi</title>
<summary>Eyes Rutherford has skyrocketed to the pinnacle of success, but he holds a dark secret; one that could take him down with it. What does Eyes know, and how does he know Kiyotaka?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3677" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じる者の幸福</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Happiness of Those Who Believe</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A hit virága</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjirumono no Koufuku</title>
<summary>Sonobe has wound up dead! Now Ayumu and Hiyono are determined to dig up some dirt on this crime. While searching for the killer they meet the ever cocky Kousuke. There`s more to this guy than Ayumu knows: Kousuke is a Blade Child! And if things didn`t seem weirder he also knows Kiyotaka!!
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3944" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧の死刑台</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty Gallows</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Halál a levegőben</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no Shikeidai</title>
<summary>The mystery of the Blade Children continues. Mr. Imazato informs Ayumu about the Blade Children. But before he can reveal anything a mysterious person takes away his life. The Blade Children refuse to let anyone stand in the way of their mysterious destiny. The only person that is the key to their salvation is Ayumu.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3945" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">包囲網(ほういもう)の死角</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blind Spot in the Web</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Rés a hálón</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houimou no Shikaku</title>
<summary>The mystery of Imazato`s murder gets underway. However there`s a hidden danger as Hiyono becomes the next target of the Blade Children. Can Ayumu protect Hiyono from certain death? All this and more.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4479" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じぬ者の選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Choice of the Nonbeliever</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A hitetlenek választása</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjinumono no Sentaku</title>
<summary>Ayumu has been issued yet another challenge by the Blade Children. A challenge that could most definitely be Ayumu`s greatest and deadliest one yet. Meanwhile at the police station Madoka tries to get in to Kiyotaka`s file but instead learns that there`s a chance that Adachi, Sonobe, and Imazato possibly have something to do with Kiyotaka`s mysterious disappearance. Who were these three really and can Ayumu and Hiyono actually defeat the Blade Children once and for all?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4480" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敗者ばかりの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day of the Defeated</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Vesztesek napja</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haisha Bakari no Hi</title>
<summary>After leaving Hiyono in the hands of the Blade Children, Ayumu begins to wonder if all these dangerous games really are worth the chance of Hiyono getting killed. Madoka remembers her promise to Kiyotaka: To always be there for Ayumu no matter what. After which Ayumu returns to the hospital for the chance to save Hiyono. What will Ayumu suggest?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4764" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きみにできるあらゆること</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Things That Are Possible To You</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Bármit, amire képes vagy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ni Dekiru Arayuru Koto</title>
<summary>After losing to Rio last time, Ayumu makes a comeback. Since each side has something the others want (Hiyono and the tape) another game is devised, this time by none other than Ayumu. After the game begins, Rio rushes off to catch up to Hiyono while Kousuke heads off to intercept the damning tape. When Rio pushes Hiyono onto a train it now seems like certain death for Ayumu. With a bomb around his neck and Hiyono on a moving train how will Ayumu get out of this alive!?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4778" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たった一つの冴えたやり方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Only One Wise Action</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Egyetlen ügyes húzás</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatta Hitotsu no Saeta Yarikata</title>
<summary>The game is underway, but the victor is still unknown. As Kousuke rushes to intercept the damning tape from Ayumu`s control, Rio decides to meet Ayumu face to face to see the game to the end.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4779" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ｸﾞｯﾄﾞﾅｲﾄ ｽｲｰﾄﾊｰﾂ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodnight Sweetheart</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Jó éjt, kedvesem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goodnight Sweetheart</title>
<summary>Ayumu has finally won the battle. Rio confesses a few things. Once she gets back to the hospital Eyes offers Ayumu a deal.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5339" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乾いた瞳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dry Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Szárazon maradt szemek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaita Hitomi</title>
<summary>It`s Christmas time and the Blade Children receive an ominous warning: The Hunters are coming! Eyes seeks help from an old friend and sends a word of caution to Ayumu. Who are the Hunters and the Blade Children and who are friends and who are foes?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5571" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Overture ~序曲~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overture</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Nyitány</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Overture: Jokyoku</title>
<summary>A Hunter has come to assassinate the Blade Children. Eyes, Ayumu and Kousuke become partners. Ayumu might help to save the mysterious leader of the Blade Children. Can they unravel the mysterious assassins` plot before it`s too late?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5738" recap="true" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甘き香り陽炎に似て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shimmering Fragrance</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Édes illat remegő forróságban</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amaki Kaori Kagerou ni Nite</title>
<summary>Ayumu`s got a day off from school which gives him enough time to try and piece together the mystery of the Blade Children. With extreme reluctance Ayumu is intrigued with the recent events leading up to the Blade Children. As they go back through the school year, the story of Spiral begins to come closer together.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5739" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライク・ア・スワン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like A Swan</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Mint a hattyú</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Like a Swan</title>
<summary>The Hunters grow more and more desperate to annihilate the Blade Children. As if that wasn`t all, a high stakes game pits an old friend of Eyes` and Eyes himself against each other. Rutherford prepares to strengthen his defenses against the Hunters.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6031" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まねかれざる訪問者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moving Targets</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Hívatlan vendégek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manekarezaru Houmonsha</title>
<summary>A transfer student comes to the Academy and much to the dismay of Ayumu, it`s Kousuke. But it`s all forgotten when Ayumu discovers Hiyono and Rio have been kidnapped by the Hunters. Now, it`s up to Ayumu, Kousuke, and Ryoko to save them.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6044" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗闇のスキャナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Watcher in the Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Sötétben figyelő szemek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurayami no Scanner</title>
<summary>Ayumu, Ryoko, and Kousuke enter the abandoned hospital where Hiyono and Rio are being held. But the Hunters have traps set up on each and every floor. Will this trio save the girls before it`s too late?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6142" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘆きの天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lamenting Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Szomorú angyal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nageki no Tenshi</title>
<summary>Rio and Hiyono are safe for now after the kidnapping. After which all seems well until Kanone shows up in Japan, which is a surprise to Ayumu. Before Ayumu can soak in the consequences of Kanone`s arrival, Sayoko becomes more involved than ever.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6285" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心の鏡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mirror of the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A lélek tükre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Kagami</title>
<summary>A Hunter has his eyes set on a different target: Sayoko! Can Ayumu and Eyes save Sayoko, and disarm the bomb in time before the Blade Children suffer an agonizing defeat?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6549" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ささやく影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whispering Shadows</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Suttogó árnyak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasayaku Kage</title>
<summary>Kousuke makes the dumbest decision of his life: taking on a Hunter face to face. Will Kousuke be killed or can he be saved by Ayumu?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6978" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心の砕ける音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of a Breaking Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A kettéhasadt szív hangja</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Kudakeru Oto</title>
<summary>Ayumu must face his most powerful enemy yet; someone he`d least suspect! The Blade Children plan an attack against the Hunters. And Madoka has encountered someone from the past, who`s got intentions that are far worse than death.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7596" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面の告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A maszk vallomása</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen no Kokuhaku</title>
<summary>The final showdown between the Blade Children and the Hunters is underway. A Hunter is on the police force and a betrayer in the Blade Children`s midst. Who are these two, and can the Hunters` assassination attempts pay off at last?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7675" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">止まない雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Relentless Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">El nem múló eső</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamanai Ame</title>
<summary>Finally a link for the missing Kiyotaka presents itself: a kidnapper. Ayumu also has to find Madoka before it`s too late. But the Blade Children are sinking deeper and deeper into peril. Will Ayumu be able to save them before it`s too late?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7745" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高い城の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man in the High Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A fellegvár ura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takai Shiro no Otoko</title>
<summary>Madoka is being held captive by Kanone. Ayumu has to pass three tests to bring his sister-in-law to safety. From a train then to a boat and finally a warehouse filled with fireworks, and into the hands of Kanone.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7757" update="2019-07-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アヤメの凍て解く音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of an Iris Freezing and Melting</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Mikor a fagyos írisz kiolvad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayame no Ite Toku Oto</title>
<summary>The final battle between Ayumu and Kanone takes place. Will Ayumu defeat Kanone and find happiness in himself?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44710" update="2011-08-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44711" update="2011-08-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
