<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2462" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>8</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>1995-02-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Seiki GPX Cyber Formula Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Future GPX Cyber Formula ZERO</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gpx zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新世紀GPXサイバーフォーミュラZERO</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2149" type="Sequel">Shin Seiki GPX Cyber Formula Saga</anime>
<anime id="2463" type="Prequel">Shin Seiki GPX Cyber Formula Double One</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=128</url>
<creators>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="621" type="Direction">Fukuda Mitsuo</name>
<name id="3630" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
</creators>
<description>A freak accident during the 12th Cyber Formula World Grand Prix causes Hayato Kazami to miss the rest of the season, and critically injures both his body and his will to continue racing. Hayato`s longtime friend, Asuka Sugo, helps nurse him back to health, and in return he proposes to her and promises her that he would never race again. But as time goes on, Hayato begins to doubt whether he really wants to retire, and decides to make a comeback after all. And with the 13th Cyber Formula World Grand Prix now underway, he must struggle to regain his racing form, regain the trust of Asuka, whose promise he broke, and thwart the malicious intents of Henri Clayton. All the while, the reason behind Hayato`s accident begins to unveil itself: the "Zero Zone."</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="133">6.93</permanent>
<temporary count="133">7.65</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4370.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4230</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1393</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>745</identifier>
<identifier>isrhsn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=128</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Future_GPX_Cyber_Formula#OVA_series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新世紀GPXサイバーフォーミュラ#OVA.E3.82.B7.E3.83.AA.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4053</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2767" parentid="2759" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-12-12">
<name>formula racing</name>
<description>Formula racing is any of several forms of open-wheeled single-seater motorsport. The origin of the term lies in the nomenclature that was adopted by the FIA for all of its post-World War II single-seater regulations, or formulæ. The best known of these formulæ are Formula One, Formula Two, and Formula Three.</description>
<picurl>147039.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11350" type="main character in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Kazami Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hayato was introduced to the world of Cyber Formula when by accident he became the registered driver of the Cyber Formula car Asurada, designed by his father while he recovered it from the hands of mercenaries. The Cyber System registers a unique user for the vehicle at the time of activation and the it would take a week to reformat the vehicle for another driver. This was not an option as the race was to be held much sooner. This forces the Sugo Grand Prix team to go with Hayato as the driver for the license race over the team`s driver at the time, Akira Hiyoshi. After earning his licence to compete in the Cyber Grand Prix, Hayato becomes the youngest driver to ever compete in the Grand Prix, at the time.
(Taken from Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>33816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9195" picture="33999.jpg">Kanemaru Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11353" type="main character in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="29">8.07</rating>
<name>Sugou Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2586.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11355" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Kaga Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bleed Kaga was a former `Crash Racer` racing on the fringes of recognized professional racing. These racing often dangerous and resulting in death gave him a plethora of skills he passed on to then rookie driver Hayato Kazami when they met on the highways of Japan. They quickly became friends which was complicated when Bleed, always chasing the big money made the jump to the new Aoi ZIP Formula team formed when Aoi began to lose confidence in their rising star Naoki Shinjyo. Bleed and Hayato would first be friends then rivals as their goals in racing began to clash.
(Taken from Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>33822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11356" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Sugou Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11357" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-11">
<rating votes="6">9.26</rating>
<name>Shinjou Naoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoki Shinjyo is a highly successful two-time European F3 Champion before making the switch the Cyber Formula racing after being scouted by Aoi Formula boss, Kyoko Aoi. After passing the Japanese qualifying rounds he makes his debut in America during the 2015 season with high hopes for both him and his team.
(Taken from Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>129310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11358" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-25">
<name>Karl Richter von Randoll</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karl Richter von Randoll is the eldest child of one of the most prominent families in his native Austria. From an incredibly wealthy background he excelled at all sports and endeavors until he took the challenge of Cyber Formula while chasing Asuka Sugo. Nicknamed the `Amadeus of the Circuit` or simply `Genius` he wins his debut race humiliating Naoki Shinjyo in the process and establishes himself as a contender for the 2015 title. An early rival to Hayato Kazami and a spoiled brat, he finds a purpose in his life through Cyber Formula and forms real lasting friendships.</description>
<picture>33826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11397" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-11">
<rating votes="10">3.93</rating>
<name>Jounouchi Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1823" picture="20708.jpg">Adachi Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11398" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-29">
<name>Jackie Gudelian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11399" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-29">
<name>Franz Heinel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11400" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-12">
<name>Edehi Bootsvorz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33594" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-20">
<rating votes="12">5.54</rating>
<name>Aoi Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="22857" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢の限界領域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Limit Zone Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu no Genkai Ryouiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22858" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再びサーキットへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Circuit Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi Circuit e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22859" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1995-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの未来へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Respective Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Mirai e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22860" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉ざされた明日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Closed Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tozasareta Ashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22861" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽だまりの中で...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hidamari no Naka de...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22862" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天馬(ペガサス)の翔くとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The flight of the Pegasus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pegasus no Habataku Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22863" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘への序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Overture to Death Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou e no Jokyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22864" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただ勝利の為に...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simply Because of Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tada Shouri ni Tame ni...</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
