<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2478" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2005-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tsukuyomi: Moon Phase</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Фаза Луны</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">월영</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tsukuyomi Moonphase</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">月咏</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">tsukuyomi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">TMP</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">月詠 -MOON PHASE-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Moon Phase</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6773" approval="9" total="16">Dance in the Vampire Bund</anime>
<anime id="4350" approval="4" total="11">Chocotto Sister</anime>
<anime id="3214" approval="2" total="4">Karin</anime>
<anime id="5586" approval="1" total="10">Vampire Knight</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="301225">I watched this in 2018 as it was on my list ever since it came out and I would say this show is for fans only because it has loads of loli and moe stuff in it. The story is somewhat underdeveloped as it`s about a runaway vampire girl and her dense not-so-much slave boy who has to face her father`s servants in battle because they`re ordered to bring her back. That`s pretty much the main story for the entire series. The romance is also underdeveloped so don`t expect too much of that. It never gets too exciting unless your cheeks turn red at the appearance of Loli girl wearing cat ears doing moe stuff while sometimes wearing gothic lolita outfits. If you`re a lolicon that wants to see a show about vampires, this show is for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="578033">It`s a good anime if you like vampires and such with a little bit of romance here and there.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="27592">If you like loli, neko mimi, moe and vampires them this anime is for you! If not, go back to your shounen stuff (onepi, naruto,  DBZ, etc...).

This work is definitely not for everyone, only the hardcore otaku or sometimes the so called "moetard" can really appreciate the finer points of this masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="112454">Great anime! ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="237651">A great love story between a stubborn girl and dense boy; one of the best romancing comedies with a slice of magic and a lovely artistic style. I love vampires!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/flyingdog/tsukuyomi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="59" type="Chief Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="1604" type="Character Design">Aizawa Masahiro</name>
<name id="683" type="Series Composition">Sekijima Mayori</name>
<name id="1604" type="Chief Animation Direction">Aizawa Masahiro</name>
<name id="1565" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oota Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="10856" type="Original Work">Arima Keitarou</name>
<name id="43398" type="Music">Kume Daisaku</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr10856 [Arima Keitarou], published in Comic Gum by Wani Books.
http://anidb.net/ch21409 [Morioka Kouhei] wanted to become a photographer, but all pictures he took were of ghosts. While visiting an old castle in Germany he met a vampire girl, http://anidb.net/ch10077 [Hazuki].
Hazuki was confined in the castle. She tried to suck Kouhei`s blood to make him her slave, but somehow it didn`t work. However, because he happened to break the device to seal her into the castle, Hazuki successfully escaped from the castle and left for Japan to look for her mother.
When she arrived to Japan, she went to Kouhei`s house, in which he was living with his grandfather, and began to live with them forcefully. Because Kouhei had also lost his mother during his childhood, Hazuki reminded him of his childhood and helped her to look for her mother. Then, another vampire girl, http://anidb.net/ch21405 [Elfriede], and http://anidb.net/ch21411 [Count Heinrich von Kinkell] came and began to try to take her back.
Source: AnimeNfo (edited)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2829">6.04</permanent>
<temporary count="2861">7.47</temporary>
<review count="4">5.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221985.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4311</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2580</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>343</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1514</identifier>
<identifier>tjluht</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/tsukuyomi/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/flyingdog/tsukuyomi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tsukuyomi:_Moon_Phase</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>月詠_-MOON_PHASE-#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>486</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321275</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6976</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/731</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2004/tsukuyomi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20047</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>8991</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2983" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body sharing</name>
<description>A character shares the same body with another entity. Usually this is due to a secret/hidden identity either due to DNA/blood, a ritual, an item or some freak accident.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3663 [body snatcher].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4136" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-03-05">
<name>sudden loli companion appearance</name>
<description>The main character meets a preadolescent girl in an unexpected way becoming a friend / partner of the main character.
(The term loli is short for Lolita meaning a girl in preadolescent age. Typical attributes are moe, cute, and innocent.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10077" type="main character in" update="2009-06-30">
<rating votes="36">8.57</rating>
<name>Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10078" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-30">
<rating votes="14">7.84</rating>
<name>Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11444" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-11">
<rating votes="5">7.35</rating>
<name>Haiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haiji is Hazuki`s guardian spirit. Haiji originally belonged to Kohei`s mother Shizuru, but the little spirit guardian lost most of her memories of Kohei`s mother when she was reassigned to Hazuki. Her name was "Akuda" and she had the form of a cat when she belonged to Shizuru.</description>
<picture>34121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5009" picture="28633.jpg">Yamazaki Vanilla</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11445" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="7">6.28</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hazuki`s younger sister, Arte envies her because of the attention their family dedicates to her older sister, and because of it Arte is determined to deprive Hazuki of everything and everyone she truly cares for, taking by force or destroying completely.</description>
<picture>34122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21404" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="3">7.75</rating>
<name>Anzai Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiromi is a childhood friend and co-worker of Kouhei`s, assigning various photo jobs to him.</description>
<picture>54556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21405" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="9">7.20</rating>
<name>Elfriede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elfriede is Kinkell`s daughter and servant. She is also a Ludo, a human who was converted into a vampire. She is able to summon creatures and monsters.</description>
<picture>54570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21406" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="3">3.38</rating>
<name>Midou Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouhei`s cousin and a powerful exorcist in his own right.</description>
<picture>54561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21407" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Midou Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21408" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Midou Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21409" type="main character in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="9">5.48</rating>
<name>Morioka Kouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouhei is a photographer who, due to an accident involving paranormal forces in his early childhood, is oblivious to spirits and the supernatural (which he specializes in photographing).</description>
<picture>54565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21410" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<rating votes="5">7.75</rating>
<name>Midou Ryuuhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuuhei is Kouhei`s grandfather and a powerful spiritualist and exorcist. Kouhei lives in his household, which is located in an antique shop.</description>
<picture>54566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21411" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<name>Heinrich von Kinkell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the minions of Hazuki`s family. He is able to control and bend light which allows him to create illusions.</description>
<picture>54567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21412" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-05">
<name>Midou Yayoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yayoi is a powerful exorcist from the Midou family.</description>
<picture>54568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21413" type="appears in" update="2010-09-05">
<name>Vigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Guardian of Schwarz Quelle Castle.</description>
<picture>54569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93517" type="appears in" update="2018-02-01">
<name>Shizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11016" picture="39570.jpg">Nagahori Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93518" type="appears in" update="2018-02-01">
<name>Seine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93519" type="appears in" update="2018-02-01">
<name>Morioka Kouhei (Shougakusei)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93528" type="appears in" update="2018-02-11">
<name>Haiji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5009" picture="28633.jpg">Yamazaki Vanilla</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93529" type="appears in" update="2018-02-01">
<name>Midou Torajirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93573" type="appears in" update="2018-02-03">
<name>Henshuuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="318" picture="69041.jpg">Iijima Hajime</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93614" type="appears in" update="2018-02-04">
<name>Mario</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93620" type="appears in" update="2018-02-05">
<name>Midou Koharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7641" picture="32436.jpg">Maruyama Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93621" type="appears in" update="2018-02-05">
<name>Vargas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93633" type="appears in" update="2018-02-07">
<name>Jeda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212749.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41" picture="16630.jpg">Yanagi Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23160" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, 私のシモベになりなさい♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Be My Slave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Watashi no Shimobe ni Narinasai</title>
<summary>Seeking to understand why he couldn’t capture a hauntingly beautiful young girl on film, Kouhei stumbles into a medieval castle and a world he cannot comprehend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24828" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24932" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">御主人様とお呼びなさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call Me Mistress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goshujin-sama to Oyobinasai</title>
<summary>In order to free Hazuki, Kouhei sets out to destroy the crystal orb - the source of the castle guardian’s power. Meanwhile, Seiji joins the battle from outside the barrier.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25076" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, 私といっしょに暮らしてくださいね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Let`s Live Together</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Watashi to Issho ni Kurashite Kudasai ne</title>
<summary>Kouhei and Hazuki seek out the young vampire’s childhood home, so that she may fulfill her last promise to her mother - the same mother who abandoned her  two years past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25211" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, ...キスしたくなっちゃた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, I Feel Like Kissing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama... Kiss Shitakunacchata</title>
<summary>The return of the full moon has stirred Hazuki’s thirst for blood. When Kouhei won’t give her what she wants, the little vamp sets out on the hunt.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25740" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, ふるふるふるむーん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, It`s a Full, Full, Full Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Furufurufuru Moon!</title>
<summary>Elfriede, a servant of Count Kinkel, has come to retrieve Hazuki and return her to the castle. The little vampire proves to be less than agreeable, and a fierce and furry battle begins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26207" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさまと京都で... うふ♡わくわく♡♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Throbs in Kyoto with Big Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama to Kyoto de... ufu! Wakuwaku!</title>
<summary>Kouhei’s family, Hazuki, and Haiji seek mystical assistance at the Mido home in Kyoto. When Elfriede arranges a clandestine rendezvous with Kouhei, Hazuki steps in to set things straight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26208" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">......だって欲しかったんだもん♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">...Well, I Wanted It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">...Datte Hoshikattandamon</title>
<summary>Finding Kouhei a pitiful excuse for a slave, Hazuki uses her powers to brainwash another unsuspecting soul into following her every command. When Kouhei finds out, a painful fight ensues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26358" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母様がきてくれた! うれしい♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother Came to See Me! Happy!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaa-sama ga Kitekureta! Ureshii</title>
<summary>Hazuki finds herself unprotected after her hopes are painfully manipulated by Count Kinkel. Kouhei and his grandfather must charge into battle to save her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26777" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, 私を夢から助けて... あねがい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother! Please Save Me from This Dream!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Watashi o Yume kara Tasukete... Onegai</title>
<summary>While Gramps and Elfriede join forces and take on Count Kinkel, Kouhei finds Hazuki and wakes her from an enchanted slumber. Unfortunately, the girl who rises to greet him isn’t who he had hoped for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26778" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆるさない... 初めてのシモベのくせに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unforgivable! You`re My First Slave!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurusanai... Hajimete no Shimobe no Kuse ni</title>
<summary>With Kouhei at death’s door, Hazuki agonizes over her attempt to kill him and is haunted by the relentless voice of her alter-ego, Mistress Luna. Is it truly her fate to lead a cursed life?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26779" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, 安静にしてなきゃダメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Get Some Rest!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Ansei ni Shitenakya Dame</title>
<summary>Concerned for her servant’s health, Hazuki embraces her catty nature and rises to the challenge - Literally! But when Gramp’s condition takes a turn for the worse, this kitty proves to have some fierce claws.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26780" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">1.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆるせないの, あいつだけは...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Forgive Him! Not Him</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurusenai no, Aitsu Dake wa...!</title>
<summary>Kouhei, Seiji, and Hazuki must set aside their fears and travel to the little vampire’s childhood home. As Kinkel warps reality, each turns against the other, forcing Hazuki to try and drive him away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="27224" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, みんなで伯爵を倒しましょうね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Let`s All Defeat the Count</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Minna de Hakushaku o Taoshimashou ne</title>
<summary>The battered heroes head out into the day to defeat Kinkel. But when a vampire has managed to survive for over 900 years, his death will not be an easy one. Whose bluff will be called in the end?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="27226" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさまといっしょに...... お散歩したいです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Go for a Walk with You, Big Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama to Issho ni...... Osanpo Shitai Desu</title>
<summary>Hazuki`s behavior is growing increasingly odd. While Elfriede wonders if she has turned to her alter-ego to escape her guilt, Kouhei realizes how much he misses the other side of Hazuki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="27701" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, "せきにん"とってくださいね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, You Must Take Responsibility</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, "Sekinin" Totte Kudasai ne</title>
<summary>With both sides of Hazuki battling for control, Elfriede convinces the young vampire to seek out another servant under the full moon’s light. Kouhei heads out into the night after her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="27786" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, どうしてもフルフル堂のネコミミ饅頭じゃなくちゃだめなんです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Have to Eat Cat-Ear Buns!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Big Brother, I Must Have Cat-ear Buns from Furufuru-do</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Doushite mo Furufuru Dou no Nekomimi Manjuu Janakucha Dame Nandesu</title>
<summary>Hazuki reveals yet another hidden talent: the ability to suppress her presence. In her absolute stillness, Kouhei finds the perfect subject for his photography. Unfortunately, Hazuki’s self-doubt soon creeps in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="28230" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, なんでこんなことになるわけ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Why Is This Happening?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Nande Konna Koto ni Naru Wake!?</title>
<summary>During the quiet hours of the night, Elfriede unburdens her soul to Gramps. Kouhei, feeling powerless to protect Hazuki should another vampire come after them, decides to take his training into his own hands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="28982" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤッホー・ハイホー・今, 会いに行きますね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yahoo! Hi-ho! I`ll See You Soon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yahoo! Haihoo! Ima, Ai ni Ikimasu ne</title>
<summary>Kouhei’s intense training in the mystical arts pays off. When Hazuki is set upon by a demon up on the mountain heights, it’s the servant to the rescue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="29079" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お山の日 湯けむりのサル ねこのヒゲ ...で, あんたたち誰?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day on the Mountain: Monkey in the Spa; the Cat`s Whiskers... and Who Are You?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyama no Hi: Yukemuri no Saru - Neko no Hige... de, Anta-tachi Dare?</title>
<summary>Kaoru, jealous of the bond between Kouhei and Hazuki, seeks to capture her betrothed’s attention by copying the antics of the young vampire. It’s a feline fetish under the full moon!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="29844" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おじいさま, どーしてそんな格好してるんですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grandfather, Why Are You Dressed Like That?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ojii-sama, Doushite Sonna Kakkou Shiterundesuka?</title>
<summary>Seiji returns bearing grim news of the world outside, but the danger has arrived before the warning. As her servant lies broken at the hands of another, Hazuki flies out into the unknown to save him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="30250" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, それってどこの地方の手まり唄?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Where Is This Nursery Rhyme From?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Sorette Doko no Chihou no Temari Uta?</title>
<summary>Hazuki and Hikaru rush unheeding into the arms of the enemy, and Yayoi and Seiji hurry to their aid. Kouhei is at the mercy of the child vampire, as the defender of the mountain watches from the forest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="30510" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 1 Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30511" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 2 Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30520" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, そんなひとだったんですか!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Didn`t Know You Were Like That</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Sonna Hito Dattandesuka!?</title>
<summary>Forbidden from killing Luna, Mistress Arte decides to kill the servant instead. Yet the Mido family hides its own share of dark secrets, for the truth behind Kouhei’s lack of psychic prowess is revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="33102" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, わたしってそんなにヘンですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, Am I That Scary?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Watashitte Sonna ni Hen Desuka?</title>
<summary>Kouhei cannot reconcile the little vampire he has grown to love with the monster before his eyes. As the Puppet Master attacks, Hazuki must embrace Kouhei - and Kouhei must embrace his fear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="33700" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サヨナラ, おにいさま...... 私, ホントに帰っちゃうよ?帰っちゃうよ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good-bye Big Brother... I`m Going Back? I`m Really Going Back?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Onii-sama...... Watashi Honto ni Kaecchau yo? Kaecchau yo?</title>
<summary>The castle which had been Hazuki`s cage for so long appears, summoned by her acceptance of her fate. Yayoi, Hikaru, and Haiji follow her in while Gramps and Elfriede struggle to keep the castle from leaving.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="34021" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35492" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, 最終会だそうですよ・ずっと私のシモベでいてくださいね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother, They Say It`s the End! Will You Always Be My Slave?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Big Brother, They Say This Is the Final Episode! Be My Slave Forever, Will You?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Saishuukai Da Sou Desu yo. Zutto Watashi no Shimobe de Ite Kudasai ne</title>
<summary>Life for the Mido family returns to normal. Ryuuhei welcomes friends and family to celebrate, but plans go astray as the full moon feast begins. Kouhei might have to save the day one last time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38099" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47147" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おにいさま, ゆらゆらきらきらどんぶらこ これって, なーんだ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother... Up and Down in the Sun, Floating Away. What Is It?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-sama, Yurayura Kirakira Donburako Korette, Naan Da?</title>
<summary>In this zany spoof, the Mido house has been relocated to the middle of the ocean. While no one but Seiji seems to notice anything wrong with this, the rest go along with their off beat day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="84460" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C26</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118169" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118170" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C33</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118171" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C34</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150874" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C32</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150875" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Creditless Ending of Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150876" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C31</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150877" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C28</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150878" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150879" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C36</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150880" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C37</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150881" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C29</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150882" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C35</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150883" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C30</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150886" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150887" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150888" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150889" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150890" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150891" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150892" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150893" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150894" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150895" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150896" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150897" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1q</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150898" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1p</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150899" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150900" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1n</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150901" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1m</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150902" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C25</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1w</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150903" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C24</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1v</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150904" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1u</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150905" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1t</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150906" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150907" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1r</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150919" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music CM BEST COLLECTION</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150920" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ringtone CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150921" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music CM 2 [Kanashii Yokan][Nami no Toriko ni Naru You ni] Nami no Toriko ni Naru You ni ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150922" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music CM 1 [Kanashii Yokan][Nami no Toriko ni Naru You ni] Kanashii Yokan ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150923" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music CM [Neko Mimi Mode]</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150924" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 13 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150925" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 12 30s CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150926" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 12 15s CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150927" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 11 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150928" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 10 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150929" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 9 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150930" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 8 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150931" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 7 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150932" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 6 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150933" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 5 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150934" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 4 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150935" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Phase 3 CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150936" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV ep2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150937" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 early annoucement ver. 30s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150938" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 early annoucement ver. 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150939" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ep 25 Avant Title</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
