<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2494" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-09-18</startdate>
<enddate>2003-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Guitar o Motta Shounen: Kikaider VS Inazuman</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Boy with the Guitar -Kikaider VS Inazuman-</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ギターを持った少年 -キカイダーVSイナズマン-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="981" type="Prequel">Kikaider 01 The Animation</anime>
<anime id="980" type="Character">Jinzou Ningen Kikaider The Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="826" type="Unknown Relation">SME Visual Works</name>
<name id="1211" type="Original Work">Ishinomori Shoutarou</name>
<name id="2954" type="Direction">Konno Naoyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr1211 [Ishinomori Shotaro]`s original INAZUMAN manga story The Boy with the Guitar.
Continuing where Kikaider 01 the Animation left off, Jiro is still wandering the streets trying to fight off any evil inclinations that Gill`s submission chip left in him. Upon meeting a local high school boy Jiro attacks him, only to find out that the boy is Inazuman. Inazuman doesn`t want to destroy Jiro, but he can`t just leave Jiro alone.
Source: ANN
Note: Released as a special feature on the collector`s DVD box set of the Kikaider OAV.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="52">4.97</permanent>
<temporary count="52">6.21</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3052.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2659</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="22985" update="2004-08-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
