<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="25" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2000-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Heppoko Jikken Animation Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Weird Anime Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Quack Experimental Anime Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Animation expérimentale Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Excel Saga Animazione Sperimentale</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Excel Saga: Animación Absurda y Experimental</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Извращенное экспериментальное аниме Эксель Сага</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Експериментално Аниме: Ексел Сага</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">迷糊女战士</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="short">Эксель Cага</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Excel</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">へっぽこ実験アニメーション エクセル・サーガ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Excel Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Excel Saga</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="65" type="Side Story">Puni Puni Poemi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="70" approval="14" total="27">Abenobashi Mahou Shoutengai</anime>
<anime id="7529" approval="12" total="25">Panty &amp; Stocking with Garterbelt</anime>
<anime id="3468" approval="12" total="13">Gintama</anime>
<anime id="4144" approval="4" total="9">Renkin San-kyuu Magical? Pokaan</anime>
<anime id="358" approval="2" total="5">Tenchi Muyou! GXP</anime>
<anime id="149" approval="2" total="5">Dragon Half</anime>
<anime id="639" approval="2" total="4">Mousou Kagaku Series: Wandaba Style</anime>
<anime id="2840" approval="2" total="3">Zettai Seigi Love Pheromone</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="1" total="7">School Rumble</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="232437">Crazy fun all the time, but it might be hard to follow it`s fast pace. &lt;br /&gt;You never know what`s going to happen next.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="498732">The true classic of Parody animes, nothing beats it in this department. But beware, if you`ve not watched a few dozens of animes, especially those of the 90`s, you`ll probably be only struggling to read the subtitles when Excel speaks.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="351443">One of the funniest anime series I`ve ever seen.  Requires a slightly warped sense of humor.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="594612">While a handful of episodes just after the second half (but not the end) were somewhat lacking - the overall experience of Excel Saga was great! I will miss this anime... Recommended to anyone who wants absolute off-the-wall insanity (about 70% of the time). 

P.S. The bonus episode is D-E-F-I-N-A-T-E-L-Y only for adults and/or those with a strong body and psyche... It`s still X-rated awesome!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293382">A weird anime that has its ups and downs.  I thought the special was very suprising.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="112996">The best of the oddball comedies by far. This series is a riot from start to finish.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="144655">I don`t guarantee that you will like it but it is the craziest anime ever made,from the craziest author.It blends other animes and movies,like madmax, though the result is amazing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="128" type="Character Design">Ishino Satoshi</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="7422" type="Original Work">Rikudou Koushi</name>
<name id="3963" type="Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="2341" type="Music">Masuda Toshio</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1468 [Excel] is a hyper-enthusiastic girl employed by the super-secret organization http://anidb.net/ch7556 [Across] with the aim to take over the world. And she will do anything for her beloved http://anidb.net/ch13839 [Ilpalazzo], the leader of Across. In this endeavour she is joined by the constantly near-death-skimming http://anidb.net/ch7795 [Hyatt], the next-door neighbour boys, http://anidb.net/ch7357 [Nabeshin] the director, http://anidb.net/ch13838 [Menchi] the puppy, http://anidb.net/ch5010 [Pedro] the immigrant worker and the Grand Will of the Macrocosm!
Note: http://anidb.net/e1903 [Episode 26] was never shown on Japanese TV, it was added as a DVD bonus instead.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4314">6.30</permanent>
<temporary count="4381">7.50</temporary>
<review count="4">7.95</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221233.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>398</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>379</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>157</identifier>
<identifier>tksjsd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Excel_Saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エクセル・サーガ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159477</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3216</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6929</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20414</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="178" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-28">
<name>insane</name>
<description>Insanity, craziness, or madness is a spectrum of behaviors characterized by certain abnormal mental or behavioral patterns. Insanity may manifest as violations of societal norms, including a person becoming a danger to themselves or others, though not all such acts are considered insanity; likewise, not all acts showing indifference toward societal norms are acts of insanity.
In modern usage, insanity is most commonly encountered as an informal unscientific term denoting mental instability, or in the narrow legal context of the insanity defense.
A more informal use of the term insanity is to denote something or someone considered highly unique, passionate or extreme, including in a positive sense. The term may also be used as an attempt to discredit or criticise particular ideas, beliefs, principles, desires, personal feelings, attitudes, or their proponents, such as in politics and religion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-18">
<name>talks too fast</name>
<description>This character speaks with a pace so frenetic that it can get hard to follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5988" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>living with the villain</name>
<description>Both, hero and villain have their secret identities. They live next door, go to the same school, work at the same place or even are best friends. But little do they know that in another part of their life they are the worst enemies. And yet they just do not recognize each other when they are out of their costumes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1468" type="main character in" update="2008-12-22">
<rating votes="64">8.82</rating>
<name>Excel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fast-talking, wise-cracking heroine, who was initially the sole minion of ACROSS, joining immediately after graduating from high school, dying, and being resurrected several times. Excel approaches her work with an excess of determination and enthusiasm, but an utter dearth of foresight and understanding. She is in quick succession impossibly lucky and impossibly unlucky, but she never manages to complete a mission without help, and even her successes are usually attained by happenstance. She has a tendency to speak extremely quickly, and in the anime, interject English words into her dialog.</description>
<picture>15945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5010" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="20">7.68</rating>
<name>Pedro Domingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo..."</description>
<picture>21300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7357" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-26">
<rating votes="184">7.42</rating>
<name>Nabeshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3963" picture="25823.jpg">Watanabe Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7556" type="appears in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="2">6.79</rating>
<name>Across</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>"Secret ideological organization", aimed to conquer the city of Fukuoka as a first step towards world domination.</description>
</character>
<character id="7795" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="30">7.77</rating>
<name>Hyatt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyatt is transported from space to Earth by the Puuchuus and becomes the junior officer of ACROSS. Throughout the series she is constantly on the verge of death; occasionally dying completely only to recover shortly afterwards.</description>
<picture>26825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9099" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="550">8.22</rating>
<name>Lum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum (also referred to in some Western versions as Lamu - since her name in Japanese is technically pronounced "Ramu") is the second main protagonist of the series. She is a beautiful Oni alien who is capable of flying and generating electrical shocks and even lightning. She is extremely popular and is famous for ending her sentences with ~daccha (loosely translated as "yes?" or "you know?"). Except when in her school girl`s uniform, she usually wears a sexy outfit consisting of a tiger-striped bikini and knee-high go-go boots. While generally good-natured, sweet, faithful, and innocent, Lum also has a very hot temper and she is extremely jealous. Her dream in life is to live in a "Sweet Home with Darling" in which she keeps house and raises babies while Ataru, her "Darling," works a job. Unfortunately, Lum`s idea of "cooking" is to take very spicy ingredients like jalapenos, cayenne peppers and Tabasco sauce and irradiate them with an alien energy bazooka until they carbonize into inedible, crystallized nuggets. As an alien she has access to many bizarre gadgets whose use she really doesn`t understand all that well, leading to comic results. Differences between human and "Invader" physiology also drive many stories, like the time Lum`s horns begin to grow larger after she is bitten by a cow, or the time she becomes drunk by eating pickled plums.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10864" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="19">8.61</rating>
<name>Snufkin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Snufkin is http://anidb.net/ch10839 [Moomintroll]`s best friend, who goes south every winter and returns in the spring. He is the son of the Mymble and the Joxter, and is half-brother to The Mymble`s Daughter and http://anidb.net/ch10861 [Little My].
Snufkin is an adventurer and a vagabond, admired by those who are small and shy. He wears old green clothes and a wide-brimmed hat that he has had since birth, lives in a tent, smokes a pipe, and plays the harmonica. He also has a great dislike for The Park Keeper, and the many regulation signs and fences he puts up. At one point he sabotages The Park Keeper by planting Hattifatteners in his garden, causing them to grow and drive him out.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209545.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13838" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="11">8.90</rating>
<name>Menchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Menchi is Excel`s "pet" dog that also fulfills the role of "emergency rations". Despite numerous threats, Excel comes to care for her after a fashion. Hyatt, though, more intently views Menchi as a ration. In the manga, Menchi gains an apparent ally in Elgala, who nevertheless views her as an emergency food supply. Several anime and manga plots, notably episodes ten and nineteen, revolve to some extent around Menchi, her past, and her quest to escape Excel.</description>
<picture>40796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13839" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-05">
<rating votes="14">7.73</rating>
<name>Ilpalazzo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ilpalazzo is the leader of ACROSS. Lord Ilpalazzo often prefaces his orders and speeches by proclaiming, "The world is corrupt!" He has little patience for Excel, often assigning complex operations to Hyatt. While presented as a mostly dark and serious character in the original manga, the anime lightens the tone with the recurring gag that, despite all his scheming, Ilpalazzo really has nothing to do while Excel and Hyatt are out on missions: he is often seen pursuing surprisingly ordinary hobbies like learning to play the guitar and arranging domino blocks. These foibles notwithstanding, Ilpalazzo is no ordinary human being, as testify his yellow, cat-like eyes and seemingly supernatural powers exhibited in episode twenty-five; the manga would later reveal him to be a survivor of the ancient lost civilization of Solaria. Discrepancies between the two media aside, both manga and anime make it clear that Lord Ilpalazzo suffers from severe psychological disorders, most notably multiple personality disorder.</description>
<picture>42524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13840" type="appears in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="5">8.86</rating>
<name>Rikdo Koshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The author of the Excel Saga manga has only one appearance in the story proper of the anime - namely, when he is killed in the first episode by Excel under orders from Lord Ilpalazzo. He does, however, appear at the beginning of every episode, voluntarily—usually—giving his approval to the episode`s ostensible genre. Also, as a parody of the struggle manga artists often find themselves in with anime adaptations of their work, Nabeshin and Rikudo come to blows, especially towards the anime`s end.</description>
<picture>46166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="232" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火星から来た女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman from Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La femme qui vient de Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La mujer de Marte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasei kara Kita Onna</title>
<summary>When an adorable alien invasion force appears in the skies above F City, Excel springs into action! During the chaos, Nabeshin and Space Butler work together for the good of a sleeping princess.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="233" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">視聴率強化週間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Increase Ratings Week</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plus d`audimat !</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Semana de aumento del índice de audiencia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shichouritsu Kyouka Shuukan</title>
<summary>Today’s episode of Excel Saga is a desperate grab for ratings, and you know what that means: A swimming pool full of bouncing babes in barely-there bikinis!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="234" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボウリング娘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bowling Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bowling girls !</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Las chicas del boliche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bowling Musume</title>
<summary>Excel and Hyatt head to the bowling alley after Il Palazzo suggests using sports as a tool to further his agenda. Unfortunately, the plan might end up in the gutter when terrorists strike. Get it? Gutter? Strike? Bowling!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="235" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひっこめ! 青春!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Butt out, Youth!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Debout les jeunes !</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Apártate juventud!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikkome! Seishun!</title>
<summary>Excel’s old high school is overrun by troublemakers and thugs. She and Hyatt quickly straighten the delinquents out, but they might swing and miss on the next mission: turning the school’s pitiful baseball team into winners!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="236" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大市街partII</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big City Part II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Big City - Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La gran ciudad - Parte II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daishigai Part II</title>
<summary>It’s time for a crime-ridden tale of revenge set on the dirty city streets. Veteran detective Purin’s tough exterior hides a secret, and while the gang works with the gumshoe, Excel has to save Hyatt from a couple of crooks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="237" recap="true" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新春年忘れかくし芸大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Year`s Year-End Party Hidden Talent Contest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouvel an - concours de talents</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La fiesta de año nuevo del fin de año del concurso de talentos ocultos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinshun Toshiwasure Kakushigei Taikai</title>
<summary>It’s a star-studded New Year’s recap episode featuring a talent competition between Excel and Hyatt. Sit back and enjoy all of your favorite moments from the first twelve installments of Excel Saga.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="238" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メンチの大冒険2 ~80時間世界一周~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Menchi`s Great Adventure 2: Around the World in 80 Hours</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tour du monde en 80 heures</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La gran aventura de Menchi 2 ~La vuelta al mundo en 80 horas~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Menchi no Daibouken 2: 80-jikan Sekai Isshuu</title>
<summary>Menchi sails to the United States, where she undertakes an around-the-world adventure with a young heiress. The journey won’t be easy - there’s a deadly assassin on their tail!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="239" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やりにげ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Will Not Be Held Responsible</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une issue difficile</title>
<title xml:lang="es">No nos haremos responsables</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yarinige</title>
<summary>Koshi Rikdo tells the Excel Saga production team to wrap it up! With the series coming to an end, Watanabe finally makes his move on Hyatt, and Excel prepares for her climactic confrontation with Il Palazzo!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1886" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">六道神士殺害計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koshi Rikdo Assassination Plot!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Complot meurtrier</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Plan para asesinar a Koshi Rikudo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rikudou Koushi Satsugai Keikaku</title>
<summary>Excel works toward Il Palazzo’s newest goal: the elimination of all comic book artists! In the course of her mission, she dies a few times and rescues a dog that she might eat for dinner.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1887" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の毒々大脱走のいけにえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sacrificial Lamb of the Venomous Great Escape of Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`agneau sacrificiel de la grande évasion venimeuse de l`Enfer</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El chivo expiatorio de la gran huida hostil del infierno</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku no Dokudoku Daidassou no Ikenie</title>
<summary>Deep in the jungle, Excel is held captive by a small army of soldiers.  Il Palazzo sends Hyatt to deal with the situation - and she fails completely. But the guerillas have a bigger problem: Nabeshin!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1888" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブへな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Puny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Eau de rose</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Amor insignificante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Hena</title>
<summary>Watanabe wants to get romantic with Hyatt, but he might not have the moves to make it happen - especially when it turns out his moves are actually being controlled by controlled by Il Palazzo!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1889" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おもしろい巨塔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Interesting Giant Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande tour intéressante</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La interesante torre gigante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoshiroi Kyotou</title>
<summary>City Hall is in the manipulative clutches of a secret mastermind. Can Excel and Hyatt defeat the dangerous deviant and untangle the web of political corruption? Meanwhile, zombie attack!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1890" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寒が冬いぜ!! ~遭難編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cold Is Winter! Snowed Under Episode</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le froid est hivernal</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El frio es invierno! Un episodio cubierto de nieve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samu ga Fuyui ze!! Sounan Hen</title>
<summary>Wandering within a snowy mountain range, the gang struggles to survive! As Excel and Hyatt hunt for food, Iwata, Watanabe, and Sumiyoshi familiarize themselves with some high-powered laser guns.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1891" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下道のメロディ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melody of the Underground Passage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mélodie en sous-terrain</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Melodía del pasaje subterráneo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikadou no Melody</title>
<summary>Horror lurks in the slimy tunnels beneath the city! As Excel and the gang navigate the dark corridors, hordes of adorable aliens prepare to pounce. Can their monstrous alien queen be stopped before she gives birth to an army?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1892" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メンチの大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elegy to the Dogs</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`élégie des chiens</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La gran aventura de Menchi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Menchi no Daibouken</title>
<summary>After escaping Excel’s hungry clutches, Menchi begins searching for her previous owner. Unfortunately, the little dog goes straight from the frying pan and into the fire when she starts running with a pack of strays.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1893" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テコイレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prop</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sang neuf</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Soporte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tekoire</title>
<summary>The ratings are floundering once again, so it’s time to introduce another new character: Ropponmatsu, a robotic cutie with a knack for defusing bombs. Unfortunately, that’s bad news for Excel - she’s planning to blow up City Hall!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1894" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もっと! てこいれメモリアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">More! Prop Memorial</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Encore plus de sang neuf</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Más! Conmemoración de soporte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motto! Tekoire Memorial</title>
<summary>There’s a new Ropponmatsu on the scene, and while she’s way more annoying than the previous model, she’s just in time to stop Il Palazzo’s newest explosive plot - a plot that involves Excel in a panda costume.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1895" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">AIをとりもどせ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Back Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amours synthétiques</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Regresen el amor!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai o Torimodose!</title>
<summary>It’s hard to keep a good Ropponmatsu down! Both models have returned, and this time they find themselves developing feelings for Excel and Hyatt, thanks to some sketchy programming.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1896" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメーションUSA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Animation USA</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Animation USA</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La animación en Estados Unidos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Animation USA</title>
<summary>After Excel and Hyatt arrive in America, their recon mission is derailed by Excel’s not-so-hot grasp of English. And when the girls find themselves tangling with the Mafia, they’re forced to unleash some epic cartoon violence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1897" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">市立戦隊ダイテンジン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Municipal Force Daitenzin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Daitenjin, les guerriers de la mairie</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Fuerza municipal de Daitenzin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiritsu Sentai Daitenjin</title>
<summary>Watanabe’s gang is forced to suit up as a squad of high-tech, masked crime-fighters to keep the streets safe. Unfortunately, city-wide destruction might be inevitable, thanks to the explosive power of their new costumes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1898" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よりぬきペドロさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Best of Mr. Pedro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pedro Sélection</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Lo mejor del señor Pedro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yorinuki Pedro-san</title>
<summary>The time has arrived to reflect on all that Pedro has endured. But this isn’t an ordinary recap show; there’s plenty of new stuff, too, including the reappearance of Nabeshin!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1899" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美儒歩K</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Visually Appealing Type</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Visual K</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Atractivo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Visual-kei</title>
<summary>The big-wigs at ACROSS send a rock n’ roller named Key to give a message to Il Palazzo. Key wants to deliver the information in a song, but first he must find the proper inspiration. Can Excel motivate him to complete his mission?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1900" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵略, おふくろ様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion, Mother</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les envahisseurs !</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Invasión madre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinryaku, Ofukuro-sama</title>
<summary>After so many missteps, it appears Il Palazzo might finally succeed in conquering the city! There’s only one final obstacle: a war between rival Puchuu factions could destroy the place before ACROSS can take it over.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1901" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世紀末征服者伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of the End of the Century Conqueror</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La légende du conquérant</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La leyenda del conquistador de final de siglo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seikimatsu Seifukusha Densetsu</title>
<summary>A great city is now a wasteland, and the remnants of humanity struggle to survive a rising tide of violence and anarchy. Within the rubble of civilization, there is but one hope for the future. Unfortunately, it’s Excel!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1902" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きみのためなら死ねる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For You, I Could Die</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour toi je peux mourir</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Por usted podría morir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Tame Nara Shineru</title>
<summary>Stricken with a case of amnesia in the aftermath of her devastating encounter with Il Palazzo, Excel must fight to remember her forgotten past - and find a way to make her former boss pay for his betrayal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1903" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="26">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やりすぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going Too Far</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On dépasse les limites</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Exterminación</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yarisugi</title>
<summary>Prepare to witness the most over-the-top insanity ever. This very special episode of Excel Saga doesn’t cross the line of decency. No, this episode gleefully stomps the line of decency into a disgusting, oozing pulp!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16850" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣スポット集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen Spotshuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16851" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エクセル♥ガールズ CMコレクション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Excel Girls CM Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Excel Girls CM Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16852" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ へっぽこ大嘘CM -アクション映画編-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Fake Movie CM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Heppoko Oouso CM: Action Eiga Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16853" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ へっぽこ大嘘予告編 -純愛バージョン-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Fake Movie Preview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Heppoko Oouso Yokokuhen: Jun`ai Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16854" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ VICTOR &amp; OURS アニメフェスティバル オープニング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Victor &amp; Ours Anime Festival Opening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Victor &amp; Ours Anime Festival Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16855" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ OA時OP / 完全版OP 徹底比較!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Opening Comparison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: OA-ji OP / Kanzenban OP Tettei Hikaku!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16856" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ ぷにぷに♥ぽえみぃ 続報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Puni Puni Poemy Follow-up Report</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Puni Puni Poemy Zokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16857" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ ナベシン&amp;北山P だらだらと「ぽえみぃ」を語る その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Puni Puni Poemy Talk 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Nabeshin &amp; Kitayama P Daradara to "Poemy" o Kataru Sono 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16858" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ 久しぶりの大嘘CMシリーズ 「ダイテンジンスペシャル」 特番ウソ予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Fake Preview 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Hisashiburi no Oouso CM Series "Daitenjin Special" Tokuban Uso Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28351" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ ぷにぷに☆ぽえみぃ 情報コーナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Puni Puni Poemy Information Corner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Puni Puni Poemy Jouhou Corner</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28352" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第01話予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Preview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 1 Wa Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30764" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">(ITA DVD Bonus 01) Flashback di Esopo</title>
<title xml:lang="it">(ITA DVD Bonus 01) Flashback di Esopo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30765" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">(ITA DVD Bonus 02) Una botola socchiusa ai confini dell`Across</title>
<title xml:lang="it">(ITA DVD Bonus 02) Una botola socchiusa ai confini dell`Across</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35332" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 2 Easter Eggs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45423" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1999-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45424" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1999-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45425" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Live</title>
</episode>
<episode id="89115" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b (Episode S1)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120859" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120860" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138913" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">サントラ&amp;ドラマCD CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soundtrack CM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sontra &amp; Drama CD CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138914" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ 徹底比較その2 OA通常バージョン VS OA第1話限定バージョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Opening Comparison 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Tettei Hikaku Sono 2 OA Tsuujou Version vs. OA Dai 1 Wa Gentei Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138915" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ ぷにぷに☆ぽえみぃ コーナー 小林, J.C.STAFFを訪問する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Puni Puni Poemy Behind The Scenes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Puni Puni Poemy Corner Kobayashi, J.C.Staff o Houmon Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138917" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷにぷに☆ぽえみぃ 大どたんば情報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Puni Puni Poemy Information</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Puni Puni Poemy Daidotanba Jouhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138927" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Japanese Piracy Warning</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138932" update="2012-04-17">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけ (秘)OVA新作情報 (一部大嘘)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus: Fake Secret OVA Information</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake: Maruhi OVA Shinsaku Jouhou (Ichibu Oouso)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
