<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2508" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-09-25</startdate>
<enddate>1993-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tenchi Muyou! Ryououki Omatsuri Zen`ya no Yoru!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">tenchiova1.1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">天地無用! 魎皇鬼 お祭り前夜の夜!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tenchi Muyo! The Night Before the Carnival!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Tenchi Muyo! The Night before the Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Tenchi Muyo - Ryo-Ohki - Épisodes 7-8</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">천지무용! 양황귀 축제 전날 밤!</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Tenchi Muyo! Esperando a Ryu-Oh</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2509" type="Sequel">Tenchi Muyou! Ryououki (1994)</anime>
<anime id="205" type="Prequel">Tenchi Muyou! Ryououki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20080720074226/http://www.anime-int.com/works/tenchimuyou/ova/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4254" type="Direction">Yatagai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="1235" type="Character Design">Kajishima Masaki</name>
<name id="1235" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kajishima Masaki</name>
<name id="1905" type="Music">Nagaoka Seikou</name>
</creators>
<description>A few days after Kagato is defeated everything returns to normal. http://anidb.net/ch8917 [Ryouko] finds http://anidb.net/ch10340 [Mihoshi] and http://anidb.net/ch8918 [Sasami] reading shoujo manga, which Sasami mistakes as guides on how to win a boy`s heart... Earth style. So Ryouko decides to try out the ideas from the manga to win over Tenchi. But http://anidb.net/ch8916 [Aeka] finds out what her rival Ryouko is doing and tries to take advantage of the same method. Naturally, the results are less than satisfactory for all involved...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1374">6.70</permanent>
<temporary count="1382">7.47</temporary>
<review count="1">9.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>245604.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>920</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1146</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20080720074226/http://www.anime-int.com/works/tenchimuyou/ova/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.aicanime.com/products/tenchi/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tenchi_Muyo!_Ryo-Ohki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天地無用!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3738" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-05">
<name>aliens living on earth</name>
<description>There`s an alien or a hive of aliens blending into society near you!</description>
<picurl>70750.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8916" type="main character in" update="2015-12-16">
<rating votes="179">5.21</rating>
<name>Masaki Aeka Jurai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aeka is typically shown as the beautiful first princess of the planet Jurai who has fallen in love with the title character, Masaki Tenchi. Aeka is portrayed as being modest, well mannered, traditional, and aristocratic, but can also be snobbish (her proper accent is evidence of her aristocratic upbringing). She can also be very fierce when she feels that anyone or anything she cares for is in danger, such as Tenchi or her younger sister Sasami, of whom she is very protective.
Aeka is a rival of Ryouko for Tenchi`s affections. Often the conflict between the two comes out of their decidedly different personalities and backgrounds, with Ryouko being more blunt, open and sexual in her attempts to gain Tenchi`s love. The level of the rivalry can vary between being equatable to a pair of bickering siblings to an all-out feud. Ryoko`s teasing and efforts often bring out some of Aeka`s worse aspects. However, there are times when Aeka puts aside her rivalry whenever Tenchi is in danger, such as the battle with Kagato.</description>
<picture>28319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="557" picture="228659.jpg">Takada Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8917" type="main character in" update="2015-12-16">
<rating votes="779">7.15</rating>
<name>Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While details of her character differ between the various series, Ryouko is typically shown as an attractive, semi-reformed powerful space pirate who is madly in love with the series main character, Masaki Tenchi. In the various series, Ryouko is portrayed as being impulsive, hedonistic (with a penchant for sake), poor-mannered, often immodest, recklessly violent, and hot-tempered although she sometimes reveals her more emotional and vulnerable side.
In the anime, Ryouko universally holds an intense rivalry with the character Aeka, who also fights for Tenchi`s affections. Often the conflict between the two comes out of their decidedly different personalities, with Ryouko being the tomboyish troublemaker and Aeka being the well-mannered, but often snooty aristocrat. The level of the rivalry can vary between being equitable to a pair of bickering siblings to an all-out feud.</description>
<picture>28321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8918" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-16">
<rating votes="177">8.24</rating>
<name>Masaki Sasami Jurai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The younger sister of Aeka and so is also a princess of Jurai. Within the family group Sasami usually takes on the dual role of younger sister/mother. She may be the most responsible of the group and takes care of all the cooking duties. She has a rarely-seen mischievous streak within her however, and takes great delight in fooling the older girls. She has teal-coloured hair tied in long pigtails with melon pink eyes.</description>
<picture>28323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9722" type="main character in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="227">4.86</rating>
<name>Masaki Tenchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenchi is the crown prince of Jurai and the grandson of a Juraian prince named Yosho and an Airaian priestess named Airi. He gains possession of a "Master Key" called `Tenchi`, also known as the Tenchi Sword (Tenchi-ken), that can form a lightsaber-like blade. He later receives a special ring from Tsunami that can create a Juraian battlesuit for him and acts as a "Guardian System", protecting him. Tenchi also has the innate ability to create kou-ou-yoku ("Light Hawk Wings"), and the ill-defined ability of Material-Energy Conversion.
Tenchi initially lives in the city with his father to attend school and visits his grandfather`s shrine every summer, where he trains to become a Shinto priest and learns his family`s special style of swordsmanship.
Tenchi suffers a great deal of stress as he tries his hardest to be a gentlemen while most of the women within the household will take the opportunity to display their attraction for him.</description>
<picture>29487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9725" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="164">7.57</rating>
<name>Ryou-Ouki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryou-Ouki`s appearance is similar to a cross between a cat and a rabbit, and for this reason Ryou-Ouki is commonly referred to as a cabbit.
Ryou-Ouki is usually a shapechanger, but the shapes, aside from the "cabbit" form, vary according to the series. Ryou-Ouki `s background and other traits vary considerably from one series to another.</description>
<picture>2349.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9732" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="272">7.79</rating>
<name>Hakubi Washuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakubi Washuu is a self-proclaimed greatest scientific genius in the universe. Her character differs depending on the continuity, though she sometimes displays a number of innate powers which she rarely uses, preferring to solve problems with reason or technology. In all incarnations, Washuu has also shown to be somewhat prudent and is generally trickier to fool than Tenchi or the other girls, which makes it harder for her to fall into an enemy trap. In all three Tenchi series Washu had also created an inter-dimensional laboratory in the closet of the Masaki house, although her laboratory is a lot bigger in the OVA series than in both of the TV series.</description>
<picture>29497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1901" picture="186579.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10332" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-12">
<rating votes="89">7.01</rating>
<name>Masaki Katsuhito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly known as Masaki Youshou Jurai, he fled Jurai over 700 years ago to "retire" on Earth. He was once the greatest swordsman on Jurai. Currently Katsuhito is a Shinto priest who is not only training Tenchi to be a Shinto priest but also training him in Jurai swordsmanship. Youshou had a marriage arranged with half-sister Aeka, but left. At the time, not all Juraians liked the idea of mixed blood heritages (he is part human, on his mother`s side) and he used Ryouko`s attack as an excuse to slip away to Earth. In the OVA, he expected that Aeka was trying to track him down and arranged for Tenchi to fight Ryouko so that his grandson would go in his place to Jurai. Although he had dropped contact with his parents, he was still in touch with Seto (through whom he was able to send Tennyo and Kiriko, among others, into space via the Galaxy Police) although her collusion in his plans is not known. While he appears to be of advanced age, his grey hair and lined face are merely an illusion hiding his true form, which he shows to only a select few (such as his mother).
He is in a common law marriage with Airi and has two children from that union called Minaho and Kiyone. He has married at least one other woman in the past (named Kasumi, and possibly Funaho`s niece), and his descendants along that line include Nobuyuki, Rea, and Kiriko.</description>
<picture>30912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10334" type="appears in" update="2017-11-20">
<rating votes="15">4.47</rating>
<name>Azaka</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Aeka`s guardians, in the form of floating logs. They can generate a barrier that allows them to protect Aeka and paralyse their target, though their powers pale in comparison to the power held by the Royal Trees of Jurai.</description>
<picture>30919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10335" type="appears in" update="2017-11-21">
<rating votes="15">4.47</rating>
<name>Kamidake</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Aeka`s guardians, in the form of floating logs. They can generate a barrier that allows them to protect Aeka and paralyse their target, though their powers pale in comparison to the power held by the Royal Trees of Jurai.</description>
<picture>30920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10336" type="appears in" update="2009-07-12">
<rating votes="38">3.86</rating>
<name>Masaki Nobuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenchi`s father, and works in the city as an architect. Although he has shown that he is less responsible than his son, Nobuyuki does care deeply for Tenchi, and after losing his wife, Nobuyuki has worked hard to raise him. He is also a Peeping Tom and tries to encourage Tenchi to be more active and not as shy towards women.</description>
<picture>30922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10340" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-12">
<rating votes="253">5.04</rating>
<name>Kuramitsu Mihoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mihoshi is known as one of the finest officers in the Galaxy Police, but her career soon hit a major roadblock after an incident hinted at in the 4th episode of the 1st OVA, and the 4th episode of the 3rd one. Now she suffers from frequent difficulties to focus on a single thought track and, due to her clumsiness, she causes a lot of collateral damage during her assignments, which eventually causes Mihoshi to be demoted. The desk of the Section 7 commander is covered with misconduct reports and bills from all the damages she causes. As a result, she is assigned to a special area of the galaxy, the Sol system, which is Juraian territory, in the vain hope that she wouldn`t cause any more trouble.</description>
<picture>30928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10533" type="appears in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Nobeyama Kachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5074" picture="156840.jpg">Kitagawa Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10535" type="appears in" update="2009-07-19">
<name>Yukinojou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31533.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23027" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1993-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<summary>Life is chaotic at the Masaki household as Ayeka and Washu plant a spaceship, Ryoko makes a play for Tenchi, and Mihoshi is tricked into reporting back to GP Headquarters.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81673" update="2010-10-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81675" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
