<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2538" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>38</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-03-19</startdate>
<enddate>1995-02-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pretty Soldier Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Bishoujo Senshi Sailormoon Super</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SM S</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sms</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">美少女戦士セーラームーン S</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">美少女战士S</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sailor Moon (saison 3)</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Sailor Moon e il Cristallo del Cuore</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Сейлормун - супервоин</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Czarodziejka z Księżyca: Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">A Navegante da Lua S</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Sailor Moon S</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Varázslatos álmok S</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เซเลอร์มูน S</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Sailor Moon S</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2540" type="Sequel">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Super S</anime>
<anime id="2539" type="Prequel">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon R</anime>
<anime id="11665" type="Alternative Setting">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Crystal Season III</anime>
<anime id="2151" type="Side Story">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S: Kaguya-hime no Koibito</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276924">My favorite one!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
<name id="990" type="Work">Toei Agency</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="3636" type="Original Work">Takeuchi Naoko</name>
<name id="3166" type="Music">Arisawa Takanori</name>
<name id="4280" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Ikuko</name>
<name id="3648" type="Direction">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7321 [Sailor Moon] and the senshi are up against a new set of villains: the http://anidb.net/ch8303 [Death Busters] (http://anidb.net/ch8309 [Professor Tomoe], http://anidb.net/ch8313 [Kaorinite], the http://anidb.net/ch8318 [Witches 5], http://anidb.net/ch8328 [Mistress 9], http://anidb.net/ch8459 [Pharaoh 90]). The Death Busters plan to rule the world by using the energy from the pure heart crystals of innocent victims, but Sailor Moon and the senshi must stop them. The outer senshi (http://anidb.net/ch7502 [Neptune], http://anidb.net/ch7497 [Uranus], http://anidb.net/ch7524 [Pluto], http://anidb.net/ch7522 [Saturn]), also make an appearance, although Pluto appeared briefly in Sailor Moon R.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1738">6.20</permanent>
<temporary count="1756">7.30</temporary>
<review count="1">9.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>32963.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>80</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8756</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>532</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360</identifier>
<identifier>dzbaoi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/sailor_moon_s/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Sailor_Moon_S_episodes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>美少女戦士セーラームーンS#.E7.AC.AC3.E3.82.B7.E3.83.AA.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA.EF.BC.88S.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2243</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89008</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1126</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4738</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01N3UZLN5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5988" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>living with the villain</name>
<description>Both, hero and villain have their secret identities. They live next door, go to the same school, work at the same place or even are best friends. But little do they know that in another part of their life they are the worst enemies. And yet they just do not recognize each other when they are out of their costumes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6017" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>perpetual ongoing</name>
<description>No end in sight!
No matter what the genre may be or what the storyline consists of, this series just keeps on going... and on... and on.
The obvious downside to this is the lack of story-related focus, usually some vague goal is simply never reached. This lack of conclusion can tend to annoy, making the whole series pretty much pointless.
Examples: One Piece, Naruto, Bleach, Detective Conan, Dragon Ball (Z), or Pocket Monsters (Pokemon).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7320" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="341">7.40</rating>
<name>Tsukino Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukino Usagi is a carefree schoolgirl who can transform into the de facto leader of the series` primary heroines, the Sailor Senshi.</description>
<picture>154978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7321" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="358">7.40</rating>
<name>Sailor Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7326" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="302">7.57</rating>
<name>Mizuno Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7330" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="177">7.56</rating>
<name>Sailor Mercury</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7335" type="main character in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="240">8.06</rating>
<name>Hino Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hino Rei is the real identity of http://anidb.net/ch7337 [Sailor Mars]. She works as a miko at the Hikawa Shrine, and is shown to have an affinity with two crows who live there, named Phobos and Deimos (the same as Mars` two moons).
Rei is fiery, boy-crazy, practical and ambitious, longing to one day become a singer, model, and voice actress envisioning herself as ultimately getting married.
Rei and Usagi have a very tempestuous relationship and argue frequently. Though these arguments are usually petty, early in the series Rei tries to take Usagi`s role as Senshi Leader. Her loyalty to Usagi becomes much stronger later in the series, and affection replaces the earlier resentment.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>154972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7337" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="137">7.53</rating>
<name>Sailor Mars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7341" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="197">7.65</rating>
<name>Kino Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7342" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="171">7.36</rating>
<name>Sailor Jupiter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7344" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="212">6.99</rating>
<name>Aino Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7345" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="178">7.58</rating>
<name>Sailor Venus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7374" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-28">
<rating votes="114">5.76</rating>
<name>Chiba Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiba Mamoru is an university student who live in the same town as Usagi. They hate each other initially but later become lovers.
Chiba Mamoru is the reincarnation of http://anidb.net/ch9313 [Prince Endymion] and the civilian identity of http://anidb.net/ch7375 [Tuxedo Kamen]. In the 30th century, he will be known as http://anidb.net/ch7487 [King Endymion].</description>
<picture>137248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7375" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-22">
<rating votes="85">7.25</rating>
<name>Tuxedo Kamen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tuxedo Kamen is a fictional character and one of the primary protagonists of the Sailor Moon metaseries. He disguises himself in order to support the series` central heroines, the Sailor Senshi.
Wearing a mask to conceal his identity, he interferes with enemy operations, offers the Senshi advice, and sometimes physically aids them in battle.
Like the Senshi, Tuxedo Mask possesses a power item like theirs: a Sailor Crystal, which gives him guardianship over the planet Earth.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>135712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7455" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<rating votes="20">6.26</rating>
<name>Yon Shuugoshin no Senshi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The four senshis of the inner planets, and the single senshi of the moon.
The name "Yon Shuugoshin no Senshi" is from the manga, the group is never given a name in the Anime.</description>
<picture>202926.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7463" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-26">
<rating votes="132">3.54</rating>
<name>Chibiusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7464" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-26">
<rating votes="47">5.07</rating>
<name>Sailor Chibi Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7481" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="162">6.89</rating>
<name>Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7486" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="17">6.44</rating>
<name>Neo-Queen Serenity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7487" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="8">6.27</rating>
<name>King Endymion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7490" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="75">7.13</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7495" type="appears in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="8">5.92</rating>
<name>Gaibu Taiyoukei Senshi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The senshis of the four outer planets.
The name "Gaibu Taiyoukei Senshi" is from the manga, the group is never given a name in the anime</description>
<picture>1119.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7496" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-21">
<rating votes="39">7.70</rating>
<name>Ten`ou Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7497" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="64">8.21</rating>
<name>Sailor Uranus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruka is a stubborn, protective individual, but is also strong-willed, capable, charming, lesbian, and occasionally even doting. She is formally introduced in the third story arc, although she appears in silhouette alongside Sailor Neptune in the final episode of Sailor Moon R. She is the second tallest of the Sailor Senshi at 5`9", just behind Sailor Pluto at 5`10".
Haruka is a racecar driver, even though she is barely sixteen years old when she appears. However, the timing of her birthday to the Japanese school year means she is one grade ahead of the Guardian Senshi.</description>
<picture>2653.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7500" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-22">
<rating votes="37">6.94</rating>
<name>Kaiou Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7502" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="58">6.87</rating>
<name>Sailor Neptune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7521" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="46">7.05</rating>
<name>Tomoe Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2914.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7522" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="44">7.54</rating>
<name>Sailor Saturn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4030.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7523" type="appears in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="27">5.81</rating>
<name>Meiou Setsuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4105" picture="39793.jpg">Kawashima Chiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7524" type="appears in" update="2015-03-14">
<rating votes="70">6.27</rating>
<name>Sailor Pluto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4105" picture="39793.jpg">Kawashima Chiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7749" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="33">7.31</rating>
<name>Princess Serenity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26691.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8303" type="appears in" update="2013-11-16">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Death Busters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>145895.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8309" type="appears in" update="2013-01-23">
<rating votes="15">6.73</rating>
<name>Tomoe Souichi Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59722.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8313" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<rating votes="12">3.78</rating>
<name>Kaolinite</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="579" picture="25835.jpg">Uemura Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8318" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Witches 5</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="8321" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="8">3.18</rating>
<name>Eudial</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8322" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="9">3.43</rating>
<name>Mimete</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8324" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="4">1.44</rating>
<name>Tellu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8325" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="5">1.95</rating>
<name>Viluy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8326" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="6">2.49</rating>
<name>Cyprine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8327" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="4">2.19</rating>
<name>Ptilol</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2139" picture="25822.jpg">Kasahara Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8328" type="appears in" update="2014-01-08">
<rating votes="9">4.34</rating>
<name>Mistress 9</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mistress 9 is a malevolent entity from "Tau Ceti Star System" who has come to Earth to help open a gateway for her master, Pharaoh 90. She is called the "Messiah of Silence" and possesses Hotaru Tomoe`s body (to varying degrees of intensity).
In the manga, the Death Busters are frequently striving to awaken Mistress 9. When the Death Busters first visited Professor Tomoe (as he was reconstructing his daughter Hotaru`s body), one of the objects they gave him was an egg that contained Mistress 9. He implanted it within Hotaru`s body. The consequence of this for Hotaru is a permanently frail physical state. She occasionally suffers from seizures that are soothed at first by an amulet given to her by Tomoe (he tells her it is an heirloom, but it is more likely to be a fragment of the Tau Crystal) and later by the Ginzuishou. When Chibiusa shows it to Hotaru, Mistress 9 becomes aware of it and later grabs it from Chibiusa, sending her into a coma.
When Mistress 9 overpowers Hotaru`s body, it becomes that of a grown woman. Her facial features are maniacal and there is little resemblance to the girl whose body she has taken over. Her purpose is to create an opening to the Tau Ceti Star System so that Pharaoh 90 can access and assimilate himself into Earth.
Once all of her allies have been killed and she is confronted by Sailor Moon and the Outer Senshi, her plan begins. Mugen Gakuen itself is ripped apart, throwing the unconscious bodies of Mercury, Mars, Venus and Jupiter into the air (they come to rest on a structure that Kaolinite previously used for divination). She then attempts to escape Hotaru`s body (meaning that her power will be able to flow freely) but is surprised to find that the soul of Hotaru still exists within the body and is inhibiting her from leaving it. Nonetheless she swallows the souls of the Guardian Senshi whereupon Hotaru retrieves their Heart Crystals along with that of Chibiusa and escapes to return them to their owners. While she is doing this, Mistress 9 is able to leave Hotaru`s body, ripping it apart in the process. Her true form is of a gigantic monster with a ghoulish head and an indistinct body.
She absorbs all of the Senshi`s attacks and opens the door for Pharaoh 90, who begins to smother the planet. Mistress 9 is assimilated into the lava (which presumably is Pharaoh 90) and just when all seems lost, Sailor Saturn rises from it. When she sets her glaive into the ground, both Pharaoh 90 and Mistress 9 experience intense pain and paralysis. Saturn uses the attack Death Reborn Revolution to drain their power and they both rise into the sky to escape back to Tau. Saturn follows them and commands Sailor Pluto to seal the door forever. Pluto does this and assures that Mistress 9 and Pharaoh 90 can never reach Earth again.
In the anime, Professor Tomoe allows Mistress 9 to possess Hotaru`s body after a freak accident kills her. He himself becomes possessed by a Daimon named Germatoid, although it is unclear if Germatoid completely controls him or aspects of his original personality still exist. Mistress 9 occasionally controls Hotaru, sequences in which her eyes become blank and her hands sparkle with red energy. Strangely enough, the victims of these occurrences are usually Daimons sent to collect heart crystals for her. Eventually, Hotaru steals Chibiusa`s Heart Crystal, rendering Chibiusa close to death, and becomes Mistress 9 to the shock of Uranus and Neptune, who were expecting Sailor Saturn.
She kills the underling Kaolinite, and sends Germatoid after the Senshi. She then attempts to use a large machine (similar to the one Tomoe created prior to possession) to guide Pharaoh 90 to Earth so that he may destroy it. Sailor Moon tries to stop her and Professor Tomoe, now freed from Germatoid, attempts to reach her, still seeing her as Hotaru. She attacks both of them but is injured by energy emanating from the machine. Professor Tomoe takes her in his arms and Hotaru`s spirit begins to respond. Mistress 9 attempts to subdue her once again but Hotaru`s memories of both her father and of Chibiusa prove to be overpowering. The black star insignia on her forehead shatters, revealing the sign of Saturn beneath it. Mistress 9`s body then vaporizes, leaving Saturn in its place.
Whilst in the manga Mistress 9`s human form seemed only to be Hotaru`s body contorted due to the presence of the entity, the anime Mistress 9`s form seems to be her genuine body, somewhat similar to Chibiusa`s transformation into Black Lady.
In the original anime, Mistress 9`s voice is provided by Yuko Minaguchi, who also provided Hotaru`s voice. In the English dub, she is played by Susan Aceron. In the musicals two actresses have played her: Tomoko Inami and Chinatsu Akiyama.</description>
<picture>27456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8459" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="4">4.24</rating>
<name>Master Pharaoh 90</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Master Pharaoh 90 is a malevolent alien from "Tau Ceti Star System;" further details on its origins are unknown. It appears only as a huge black sphere with tentacles.
In the manga, Pharaoh 90`s goal is to merge itself with the planet Earth and make it his home. In the anime, it wants simply to destroy it by bringing about the Silence. Pharaoh 90 is the one who provided the daimon egg of Mistress 9 to Professor Tomoe, taking advantage of Tomoe`s desire to save his daughter. In reality, Pharaoh 90 simply needed to provide a body for Mistress 9 so that she, in turn, could open a portal for Pharaoh 90. Pharaoh 90 was destroyed by Sailor Moon and Sailor Saturn in the anime, but in the manga, it is simply driven back to Tau Ceti by Saturn and then sealed away forever by Sailor Pluto.
Like all of the head villains in the manga, Pharaoh 90 is later revealed to be an incarnation of Chaos, the ultimate enemy of the series.</description>
<picture>153014.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8693" type="appears in" update="2018-08-24">
<rating votes="40">6.07</rating>
<name>Oosaka Naru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4777" picture="171384.jpg">Kakinuma Shino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8694" type="appears in" update="2018-09-02">
<rating votes="29">5.82</rating>
<name>Umino Gurio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Umino Gurio is Usagi`s classmate. His defining characteristic is his glasses, which have odd swirls in them, denoting their thickness.
He is a know-it-all, and he keeps Usagi informed on current events, new students, gossip, and any other information she might appreciate.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>223098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8772" type="appears in" update="2018-08-25">
<rating votes="25">5.56</rating>
<name>Furuhata Motoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3235" picture="25824.jpg">Satou Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9070" type="appears in" update="2013-04-23">
<rating votes="12">4.93</rating>
<name>Rei no Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandpa Hino is Hino Rei`s grandpa. In the anime, he is ... goofy. Consequently, he and Usagi get along very well. He energetically encourages temple visitors to buy lucky charms, make wishes, pray, etc. Rei gets very worried about him because he is very junpy and physical for a man his age. But despite his goofiness, he does manage to come down to Earth when the situation warrants it.</description>
<picture>135768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9252" type="appears in" update="2018-09-30">
<rating votes="18">5.03</rating>
<name>Kumada Yuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9313" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="12">5.06</rating>
<name>Prince Endymion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28826.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9641" type="appears in" update="2013-10-21">
<rating votes="9">3.34</rating>
<name>Furuhata Unazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Furuhata Unazuki is the younger sister of Furuhata Motoki. She first appears in episode 69 (episode 23 of second season) and is mistaken as a rival love interest for Mamoru.
She works as a waitress at the Crown Fruit Parlor, where the Sailor Senshi spend much of their free time.</description>
<picture>144625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4028" picture="47997.jpg">Hara Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104237" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<name>Mikuuji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4940">Abe Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104238" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<rating votes="1">9.04</rating>
<name>Nekonneru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5052" picture="200415.jpg">Kataishi Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104239" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<name>Miharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2139" picture="25822.jpg">Kasahara Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104271" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<name>Steering</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="486" picture="235171.jpg">Koyama Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104272" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<name>Kameda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104273" type="appears in" update="2019-07-08">
<name>Waitress</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236020.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104390" type="appears in" update="2019-07-12">
<name>Octave</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4947" picture="28470.jpg">Fukai Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104551" type="appears in" update="2019-07-21">
<name>Ousouji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104816" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Daiheart</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104817" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Takao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236892.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104818" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236893.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104819" type="appears in" update="2019-08-03">
<name>Shikaisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104875" type="appears in" update="2019-08-06">
<name>Scar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3271" picture="171421.jpg">Emori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104876" type="appears in" update="2019-08-06">
<name>Joseito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236996.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104961" type="appears in" update="2019-08-10">
<name>Doburin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6040" picture="186218.jpg">Maruta Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105177" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<name>Yamada Katsutoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8058" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105178" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<name>Taiyan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4722">Oono Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106132" type="appears in" update="2019-10-12">
<name>Toden</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9649" picture="77764.jpg">Maruo Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23214" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球崩壊の予感? 謎の新戦士出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premonition of the Apocalypse: The Mysterious New Guardians Appear</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lernen fällt schwer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouvelle bataille</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`inizio di una nuova battaglia</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El comienzo de la nueva batalla</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Начало новой битвы</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Nowa walka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Houkai no Yokan? Nazo no Shin Senshi Shutsugen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23215" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のロッド誕生! うさぎの新変身</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rod of Love Is Born: Usagi`s New Transformation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der neue Mondstab</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La baguette du cœur lunaire</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un nuovo scettro</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La nueva transformación de Bunny</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Рождение нового жезла</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Koty</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Rod Tanjou! Usagi no Shin Henshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23217" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うさぎの憧れ! 優美な天才みちる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usagi`s Idol: The Graceful Genius Michiru</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Konzert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`idole</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il concerto</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El ídolo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мой идеал</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usagi no Akogare! Yuubi na Tensai Michiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23218" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純な心を守れ! 敵味方三つ巴乱戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect the Pure Heart: The Three-Way Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der erste Kuss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier baiser</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il primo bacio</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Hay que salvar el corazón puro</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Первый поцелуй бывает в жизни только раз</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pierwszy pocałunek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pure na Kokoro o Mamore! Teki Mikata Mitsudomoe Ransen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23219" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のおたすけはムーンにおまかせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Moon Help with Your Love Problems</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Du schaffst es, Umino</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force des sentiments</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La coppia del cuore</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Un profundo afecto</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Настоящая любовь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Otasuke wa Moon ni Omakase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23220" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冷酷なウラヌス? まことのピンチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coldhearted Uranus: Makoto in Danger</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Falscher Verdacht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une guerrière en danger</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Morea in pericolo</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Patricia esta en peligro</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Макото в опасности</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikoku na Uranus? Makoto no Pinch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23221" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水のラビリンス! ねらわれた亜美</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Labyrinth of Water: Ami Targeted</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Wettschwimmen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`esprit de compétition</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una gara con se stessa</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El dilema de Amy</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Водный лабиринт</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Labyrinth! Nerawareta Ami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23222" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達を救え! ムーンウラヌス連合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Save Our Friends: Moon and Uranus Join Forces</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Motocross-Rennen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`union fait la force</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La trappola</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Lazos de unión</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Лучше, когда все вместе</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi o Sukue! Moon Uranus Rengou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23223" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男の優しさ! 雄一郎, レイに失恋?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man`s Kindness: Yuichiro Heartbroken by Rei</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebeskummer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mal d`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La gelosia</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Enamorada</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Любовная лихорадка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko no Yasashisa! Yuuichirou, Rei ni Shitsuren?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23224" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">S[セーラー]戦士をやめたい!? 美奈子の悩み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Quit Being a Sailor Guardian: Minako`s Dilemma</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Einfach nur glücklich sein</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la recherche du bonheur</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La pallavolo</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Felicidad individual</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Личное счастье</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sailor Senshi o Yametai!? Minako no Nayami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23225" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うさぎ涙! 誕生日にガラスの靴を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usagi in Tears: A Glass Slipper for My Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bunnys Geburtstag - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les chaussures de verre (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le scarpette di cristallo (prima parte)</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Zapatos de cristal(1ª parte)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Хрустальные туфельки, часть 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usagi Namida! Tanjoubi ni Glass no Kutsu o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23226" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪われた純[ピュア]な心! うさぎ絶体絶命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stolen Pure Heart: Usagi`s Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bunnys Geburtstag - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les chaussures de verre (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le scarpette di cristallo (seconda parte)</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Zapatos de cristal(2ªparte)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Хрустальные туфельки, часть 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ubawareta Pure na Kokoro! Usagi Zettai Zetsumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23227" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やって来たちっちゃな少女戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Arrival of a Small Pretty Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die neue Kriegerin Chibimoon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour de la petite guerrière</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Chibiusa piccola guerriera</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Ha llegado la pequeña Chibi Luna</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Маленький воин — Сейлор Малышка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yattekita Chiccha na Bishoujo Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23228" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達を求めて! ちびムーンの活躍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making New Friends: Chibi Moon`s Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freunde finden ist schwer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En quête d`amitié</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cercasi amici</title>
<title xml:lang="es">En busca de amigas</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">В поисках верных друзей</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi o Motomete! Chibi Moon no Katsuyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23229" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">力[パワー]が欲しい! まこちゃんの迷い道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want Power: Mako Lost in Doubt</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gemeinsam sind wir stark</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tous pour un</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Uniti si vince</title>
<title xml:lang="es">No estás sola</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Человек не может жить в одиночку</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Power ga Hoshii! Mako-chan no Mayoi Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23230" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命のきずな! ウラヌスの遠い日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bond of Destiny: Uranus`s Distant Past</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erste Begegnung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lien fatal</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le due guerriere</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Lazos fatales</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Смертельная связь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Kizuna! Uranus no Tooi Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23231" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">芸術は愛の爆発! ちびうさの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Art Is an Explosion of Love: Chibi-Usa`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kleine Künstler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un artiste en herbe</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il piccolo artista</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La pequeña artista</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Юная художница — Малышка Банни</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Geijutsu wa Ai no Bakuhatsu! Chibi Usa no Hatsukoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23254" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うさぎのダンスはワルツに乗って</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usagi Dancing to the Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Party</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entrez dans la danse</title>
<title xml:lang="it">A tempo di walzer</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Danzad, danzad, danzad</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Танцуй, танцуй, танцуй</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usagi no Dance wa Waltz ni Notte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23255" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃の刻[とき]! 明かされた互いの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shocking Moment: Everyone`s Identities Revealed</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Enttarnung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révélation</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Giù la maschera</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Revelación</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Страшная тайна</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki no Toki! Akasareta Tagai no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23256" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウラヌス達の死? タリスマン出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Death of Uranus and Neptune: The Talisman Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Talismane</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Destin</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La tragedia</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Condenadas</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Обречённые на смерть</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uranus-tachi no Shi? Talisman Shutsugen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23257" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖杯の神秘な力! ムーン二段変身</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Holy Grail`s Mystical Power: Moon`s Double Transformation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der heilige Gral</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Saint Graal</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Coppa Lunare</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El Grial</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Святой Грааль</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seihai no Shinpi na Chikara! Moon Nidan Henshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23258" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真の救世主[メシア]は誰? 光と影のカオス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Is the True Messiah? Chaos of Light and Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Licht und Schatten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ombre et lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una nuova amica</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Luces y sombras</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Свет и тьма</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin no Messiah wa Dare? Hikari to Kage no Chaos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23259" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖気漂う家! 美少女ほたるの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A House Filled with Evil Presence: The Beautiful Hotaru`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschung für Bunny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret d`Olivia</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una ragazza misteriosa</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El secreto de Andrea</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Секрет Хотару Томо</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youki Tadayou Ie! Bishoujo Hotaru no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23260" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドル大好き! 悩めるミメット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love Idols: Mimete`s Dilemma</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mimets grosser Traum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas de chance Babette</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`audizione</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Mala suerte para Mimet</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Звёздный час Мимет</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol Daisuki! Nayameru Mimete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23261" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沈黙の影!? あわき蛍火のゆらめき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow of Silence: The Pale Glimmer of a Firefly</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Seltsame Kraft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Olivia à l`hôpital</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`ombra del silenzio</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La sombra del silencio</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Под покровом тьмы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinmoku no Kage!? Awaki Hotaru Hi no Yurameki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23262" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐のち晴れ! ほたるに捧げる友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunny Skies After a Storm: A Friendship Dedicated to Hotaru</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Picknick</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La grandinata</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Después de la tormenta</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">После бури</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi Nochi Hare! Hotaru ni Sasageru Yuujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23263" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">より高くより強く! うさぎの応援</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Higher and Stronger: A Cheer from Usagi</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Brief</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un espoir pour l`avenir</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il salto con l`asta</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Bravo Andrea</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Овация для героя</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yori Takaku Yori Tsuyoku! Usagi no Ouen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23264" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔空の戦い! セーラー戦士の賭け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Inside the Demonic Space: The Sailor Guardians` Gamble</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ungewollte Reise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde parallèle</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Nello spazio</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Espacio alterado</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Параллельное измерение</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makuu no Tatakai! Sailor Senshi no Kake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23265" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沈黙のメシア覚せい? 運命の星々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Messiah of Silence Awakens? Stars of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sailorsaturn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand Saturne apparaît</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sailor Saturn</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El destino de las estrellas</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">У каждой звезды свой рок</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinmoku no Messiah Kakusei? Unmei no Hoshiboshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23266" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異次元からの侵略! 無限学園の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Invasion from Another Dimension: Mystery of Mugen Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mimets Ende</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`école des surdoués</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La scuola dei misteri</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Misterio en la escuela Mujen</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Загадка школы Мюген</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ijigen kara no Shinryaku! Mugen Gakuen no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23288" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心を奪う妖花! 第三の魔女テルル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bewitching Flower That Steals Hearts: Tellu, the Third Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefährliche Blumen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La plante monstrueuse</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una nuova tattica</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Planeta mortal</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Растение-чудовище</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro o Ubau Youka! Daisan no Majou Tellu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23289" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛を信じて! 亜美, 心優しき戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Believe in Love: Ami, the Kindhearted Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Tücken der Technik</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Science et amour</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il test nazionale</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Creo en el amor</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Главное — верить в любовь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai o Shinjite! Ami, Kokoro Yasasiki Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23290" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破滅の影! 沈黙のメシアの目覚め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow of Destruction: The Messiah of Silence Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mistress 9</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éveil</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il risveglio</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El despertar</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пробуждение Мессии</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hametsu no Kage! Chinmoku no Messiah no Mezame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23291" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫り来る闇の恐怖! 苦戦の8戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Coming Terror of Darkness: Struggle of the Eight Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Messias der Stille</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande prêtresse</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Despota</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El terror del silencio</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Наступление тьмы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semari Kuru Yami no Kyoufu! Kusen no 8 Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23292" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝く流星! サターンそして救世主</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shining Shooting Star: Saturn and the Messiah</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Chibiusa ist gerettet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sauveur</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Faraone</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El Mesías</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пришествие Мессии</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayaku Ryuusei! Saturn Soshite Kyuuseishu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23293" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しき命! 運命の星々別かれの時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Life: Parting of the Stars of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein neues Leben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nouvelle vie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una nuova vita</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Nueva vida</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Начало новой жизни</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashiki Inochi! Unmei no Hoshiboshi Wakare no Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23294" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士の自覚! 強さは純な心の中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Guardian`s Realization: Strength Lies Within a Pure Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Liebe siegt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une fête pour Camille</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La festa d`addio</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El secreto de la tenacidad</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Секрет могущества</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi no Jikaku! Tsuyosa wa Jun na Kokoro no Naka ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23295" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素敵な美少年? 天王はるかの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Handsome Boy? Haruka Tenoh`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer ist Haruka?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Garçon et fille</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ragazzo o ragazza?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Él o ella</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мальчик или девочка?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki na Bishounen!? Ten`ou Haruka no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26673" update="2012-08-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27339" update="2012-08-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">5.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27622" update="2012-08-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Japanese Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27856" update="2012-08-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Japanese Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119997" update="2012-01-15">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女戦士セーラームーンS メモリアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sailor Moon S Memorial</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S Memorial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121394" update="2010-08-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 01-07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124688" update="2010-10-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening (English Version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188851" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 01-06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188852" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 07-12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188853" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 13-18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188854" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 19-23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188855" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 24-28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188856" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 29-33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188857" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers Episodes 34-38</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
