<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2550" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>20</episodecount>
<startdate>1983-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>1983-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Time Bokan Series: Itadakiman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">タイムボカンシリーズ イタダキマン</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2504" type="Same Setting">Time Bokan Series: Yatterman</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/itadakiman.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="830" type="Work">Tatsunoko Production</name>
<name id="3974" type="Original Work">Kuri Ippei</name>
<name id="4249" type="Series Composition">Sakai Akiyoshi</name>
<name id="3986" type="Chief Direction">Sasagawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="6669" type="Music">Jinbo Masaaki</name>
<name id="6393" type="Music">Yamamoto Masayuki</name>
<name id="6468" type="Character Design">Amano Yoshitaka</name>
<name id="6512" type="Original Work">Tatsunoko Pro Kikakushitsu</name>
</creators>
<description>The story begins in the year of 20XX. Oshaka School in Kamakuland is a prestige school of the world where only those who are pure and clearheaded descendants of Priest Sanzo`s clan may be admitted. As for the familiar villain trio, they are in firm belief that they are genuine descendants of Priest Sanzo`s clan although actually they are of uncertain lineage. They study hard to enter the school in spite of their repeated failure. One day three intelligent children are called in by the principal and asked by Shakyamuni dwelling in his body to find missing puzzle copperplates scattered all over the world and complete the puzzle board to heighten honor of Oshaka School. The conversation, however, is overheard by the villain trio and they decide to forestall those selected youngsters. Then they happen to meet with a brilliant boy named koochan who appears handy and so they take him with them and attempt to take away puzzle copperplates from a goblin. At the same time they try to win the goblin over to their side and attack our heroes together. Being aware of the evil scheme, Koochan transforms himself into Itadakiman and fights bravely to drive the wicked trio away.
Source: official site</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13">5.19</permanent>
<temporary count="14">5.28</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5787.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1747</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5344</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2036</identifier>
<identifier>dxkcwp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/itadakiman.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4952</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89331</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="33522" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡ウルサイユのバラ物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33523" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オシャカ学園危機イッパツ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshaka Gakuen Kikiippatsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33524" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エッ! ヤンヤンに赤ちゃんが?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">E! Yan-Yan ni Aka-chan ga?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33525" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋ピューター花嫁作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33526" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">かんぱい! ぼっちゃん先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33527" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園ガジガジパニック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33528" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">こんこん·らぶストーリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33529" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">あげられない! これだけは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33530" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんなことアリ?! 大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33531" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">見せてはダメよ! その秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33532" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜子ちゃんも女でありんす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33533" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドッキリ水着コンテスト!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokkiri Mizugi Contest!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33534" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">笑って笑ってネアカになれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33535" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それを食ったらおしまいよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33536" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">きれいな町には罠がある!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirei na Machi ni wa Wana ga Aru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33537" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プッシュマンVSターサン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pushman vs. Tarsan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33538" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イタダキマンよどこへ行く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itadakiman yo Doko e Iku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33539" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の天ドン山を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33540" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">一休山のイタダキクイズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33541" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">浜辺のキッスにご用心!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125544" update="2010-11-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1983-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125545" update="2010-11-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1983-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
