<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2605" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2005-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou Sensei Negima!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magic Teacher Negima</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Magister Negima</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Волшебный учитель Нэгима!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mahou Sensei Negima</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Магічний вчитель Неґіма!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">negi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">msn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">negima</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法先生 ネギま!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">魔法老師</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Negima!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Magister Negi Magi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le maître magicien Negima !</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Magister Negi Magi</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">คุณครูจอมเวท เนกิมะ!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5868" type="Sequel">Mahou Sensei Negima! Shiroki Tsubasa Ala Alba</anime>
<anime id="35" type="Same Setting">Love Hina</anime>
<anime id="4565" type="Alternative Setting">Negima!?</anime>
<anime id="4510" type="Side Story">Negima!? Haru Special!?</anime>
<anime id="4812" type="Side Story">Negima!? Natsu Special!?</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="35" approval="37" total="62">Love Hina</anime>
<anime id="4835" approval="18" total="29">Nagasarete Airantou</anime>
<anime id="1057" approval="2" total="3">Maburaho</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="487488">If you`ve read the manga, you`ll probably be disappointed at the ending. And if you haven`t, do yourself a favor and read it instead of watching this. The first episodes are the same as the first few volumes of the manga, and it goes on much longer and gets better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="283320">its pretty ok for starters. seriously watch it before watching negima!? neo.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="469237">Negi-sensei, a 10 years old teacher, having to deal with a lot of bigger students. I must say the series left me with a good feeling after watching it, but this only due to the very very good second half (ep 14 and on). Some may also like the first half of it, but I felt kind of bored at a lot of moments. Recommended for all of you comedy fans.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.negima.ne.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="860" type="Original Work">Akamatsu Ken</name>
<name id="1857" type="Series Composition">Ookouchi Ichirou</name>
<name id="3569" type="Music">Mitsumune Shinkichi</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="9762" type="Character Design">Katou Hatsue</name>
<name id="5332" type="Chief Direction">Habara Nobuyoshi</name>
<name id="4601" type="Direction">Miyazaki Nagisa</name>
</creators>
<description>The 9-year-old http://anidb.net/ch4675 [Negi Springfield] is a wizard-in-training, and needs only to pass one more test in order to become a Master Wizard. Unfortunately, his final task is a bizarre one — to become a English teacher at an all-females boarding school. As soon as he arrives, he completely embarrasses one of his students, http://anidb.net/ch4680 [Kagurazaka Asuna], and replaces the teacher she loves, which garners her hatred. To make matters worse, Asuna learns that Negi is a wizard, and promises to tell unless he helps her out. But, as things turn out, circumstances force them to work together: from fighting evil wizards to helping the class pass their final exam...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3921">5.26</permanent>
<temporary count="3971">7.29</temporary>
<review count="5">6.46</review>
</ratings>
<picture>227552.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4380</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4306</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>157</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1654</identifier>
<identifier>wqyuag</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.negima.ne.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Negima!_Magister_Negi_Magi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法先生ネギま!_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321609</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3281</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2097</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4675" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="97">4.24</rating>
<name>Negi Springfield</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>9-year-old prodigy Negi Springfield has a bachelor`s degree and magical powers, but he`s sadly unprepared for his newest challenge! teaching English to a class full of teenage girls! A soft-spoken and kind lad, Negi wants to do well in his new position and he just might if he can quit crossing hot-headed rabble-rouser Asuna. He`s still got some kinks to work out in his spell casting and his lesson plan, but Negi`s a good kid with a great heart. Most of the girls instantly take to him, though he may need to keep some distance. And if any of the students find out about his wizardly training, he`ll be transformed into a furry ermine!</description>
<picture>72757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4676" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="70">5.53</rating>
<name>Albert Chamomile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Negi`s friends come in all shapes and sizes, occasionally even small, furry, foul mouthed, with a cigarette habit and a penchant for panty stealing! The little white weasel is invaluable as a confidant to Springfield, and Chamo is an integral part of some of Negi`s biggest battles and plans. Chamo spends a lot of time prodding the lad into pactios with the girls in 2-A. Of course, since the magic spells involve the young sorcerer getting a kiss, you can never really tell if Chamo is trying to help strengthen Negi`s chances as a warrior or if he`s just trying to get Springfield some romance in his life. Knowing Chamo, it`s probably both!</description>
<picture>20791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4677" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="14">3.19</rating>
<name>Konoe Konoemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The School Dean and Konoka`s grandfather, which likely played a role in his decision for Negi to live with his granddaughter and Asuna. What has been indicated is that he is a kind-hearted man, but extremely strict. He is also the chief of the Kantou Magic Association. The Dean`s hobby is arranging omiai for Konoka to choose a future fiancée, despite Konoka not wanting to. He even offered the position to Negi.</description>
<picture>20792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3321" picture="228645.jpg">Tsujimura Mahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4678" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="11">3.06</rating>
<name>Takahata T. Takamichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The teacher Negi replaced at Mahora Middle School. This is not to say that he is not in the school, however - he has appeared several times throughout, though he has become the new art teacher for the time being. Takahata told Asuna shd magical non-wizard status. Like Nagi, he addressed her as "princess" before erasing her memory.</description>
<picture>20793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4679" type="appears in" update="2009-03-09">
<rating votes="14">5.17</rating>
<name>Minamoto Shizuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Negi`s advisor at Mahora Gakuen. She primarily attempts to be a motherly figure while Negi adjusts to the school, slowly leading him into the different aspects of his job.</description>
<picture>20794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4680" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="199">6.91</rating>
<name>Kagurazaka Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuna Kagurazaka`s mouth may be big, but her attitude is bigger. A quick tempered redhead with a tough exterior, Asuna`s brash personality serves her well in her constant struggles with her class rival, Ayaka. Asuna usually reserves her softer side for the unrequited longings she expresses toward Professor Takahata, her former teacher. It doesn`t sit well when the manly object of her affection is replaced with a new instructor! Little Negi Springfield. Her misfortunes seem to stack up when the kid is around, and her hostility and suspicion toward the brainy boy lead her to a startling discovery! She soon finds Negi`s destiny in her hands. Will she take the steps to make the magician to disappear?</description>
<picture>72769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4681" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="210">7.96</rating>
<name>Miyazaki Nodoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiding from the world behind a sheet of hanging bangs, mousy bookworm Nodoka is painfully shy, especially around men. Rather than face Negi Springfield, the newest professor at Mahora Academy, Nodoka would probably prefer to vanish into the school`s vast library forever. Something is stirring in the quiet girl, though! something she cannot explain. Whatever these odd feelings, they are tied to Negi; if the lass could ever untie her tongue, perhaps a special relationship with the little magi awaits!</description>
<picture>72788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4682" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="100">6.99</rating>
<name>Aisaka Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Expelled, staying home sick, a printing mistake on the class roll! The girls of 2-A can think of a thousand reasons why none of them have met Aizaka Sayo at school. But, Sayo`s been there all along! and longer! A ghost stuck for 60 years at Mahora after an accidental demise, Sayo is a melancholy observer of the crazy goings on in 2-A. Life is a hazy memory, and until Kazumi looks into it, Sayo doesn`t recall her death. With a little help from the class reporter, the little spirit might finally be able to participate in some of the fun she has had to witness from the sidelines! and from the other side!</description>
<picture>72761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4683" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="61">5.70</rating>
<name>Akashi Yuuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An athletic girl who plays basketball and is often seen together with Makie, Ako, and Akira (i.e. the sports clubs group). Her father is Professor Akashi, one of the Mage-teachers at the Academy. She is very close to him, to the point of feeling jealousy about other women. Despite this fact, she knows nothing about magic herself.</description>
<picture>72762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1873" picture="20970.jpg">Kimura Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4684" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="61">5.78</rating>
<name>Asakura Kazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Outgoing Kazumi Asakura is the resident ace reporter of 2-A. The spunky news-hound is always ready with a camera to capture the action, and definitely knows a hot scoop when she sees one! Upon discovering the name Sayo Asakura on the class roll, the redhead decides to dig up the dirt on her seemingly missing classmate. The story she finds might cause her to rethink her paparazzi style. Even better, what the intrepid reporter uncovers might finally release the mysterious Sayo from her strange wallflower limbo!</description>
<picture>72763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1874" picture="36205.jpg">Sasagawa Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4685" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="167">7.72</rating>
<name>Ayase Yue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dry and deadpan, slacker Yue is best friends with Nodoka and Haruna. Often prodding Nodoka into escalating her tense relationship with Negi, Yue supports her buddy to the point of sometimes complicating matters. A lover of books, though a pretty indifferent student, Yue is the leader of the Dummy Force; the group of five girls from 2-A with the lowest grades. There is a chance that Yue has the slight tingling of feelings for Negi, but her loyalty to Nodoka helps keep her emotions in check.</description>
<picture>72764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4686" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="44">5.69</rating>
<name>Izumi Ako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A shy athletic girl. She does not consider herself anyone special and is one of the better-behaved members of the class. She has some talent with a bass guitar. Despite working as a nurse assistant, she has a fear of seeing blood. She has a large scar across her back, which she makes every effort to hide from others and is the source of her low self-confidence, as she believes that the mark makes her ugly and unwanted.</description>
<picture>72765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1875" picture="151654.jpg">Yamakawa Kotomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4687" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="51">5.85</rating>
<name>Ookouchi Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall, athletic, and very quiet girl in the swimming club. She is so good at swimming that the Mahora High School swimming club is already looking to recruit her. She is a friend of Makie, Ako, and Yuna, although she is not always comfortable with Yuna`s stunts (for example, being forced to dress as a bunny-girl).</description>
<picture>72766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4688" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="51">4.50</rating>
<name>Kakizaki Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the class` cheerleaders, Madoka and Sakurako, and a member of the chorus club. She loves shopping and hates carbonated drinks. She also has a fondness for karaoke. Misa also has some "adult" tendencies, far more than any of the other girls in the class. She also likes to tease the Narutaki twins; she thinks that their reaction is "cute". She is the only girl in the class to have a steady boyfriend. Misa also enjoys dressing up Negi or other classmates in embarrassing outfits, including turning Negi into a kitsune female and several costumes for Ako to send to "Nagi Springfield".</description>
<picture>72767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4689" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="51">3.90</rating>
<name>Kasuga Misora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hyperactive tomboy in the track and field club, who had rivalled Asuna in the class sprint runs. She always wears a crucifix and is sometimes seen wearing a nun`s habit.</description>
<picture>72770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1877" picture="23186.jpg">Bandou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4690" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="112">6.86</rating>
<name>Karakuri Chachamaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Some girls get their ears pierced; some of them get missile launchers installed! At first glance it might be hard to notice that Chachamaru is anything more than Evangeline`s robotic minion, but there`s more to this lass than silicon and bolts. Her reputation outside of the school is far different than what Negi could have imagined. When the little magi and Asuna set out to battle the girly automaton, Negi must second-guess his plan to disable her. In the end, the computer in Chachamaru`s head just might lose out to her very human-seeming heart.</description>
<picture>72771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4691" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="50">3.97</rating>
<name>Kugimiya Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The serious one of the three cheerleaders in the class. She makes sure that the other cheerleaders (especially Sakurako) do not get into any trouble. She likes gyuudon and silver accessories and generally into Western music (currently is a fan of Avril Lavigne from notes), but hates playboys and is mildly obsessed with her husky voice. Her surname is usually the target of nickname making (which Madoka does not like) from her classmates.</description>
<picture>72772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1884" picture="21002.jpg">Deguchi Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4692" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="98">6.63</rating>
<name>Kuu Fei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The silly, fun-loving Chinese warrior girl of the class. Although appearing to be an idiot who seems to speak more with her fists than with her mind, Kuu`s abilities are top-notch making her one of the more dangerous students in the class. Becoming an early trusted ally of Negi Springfield (as well as a member of his "Baka Rangers"), she also teaches him the means of her arts in order to help him progress in his own training. She is also infamous with her appetite and her obsession with nikuman from fellow "Chinese" classmate Chao Lingshen.</description>
<picture>72773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19681" picture="35374.jpg">Tanaka Hazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4693" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="122">7.01</rating>
<name>Konoe Konoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konoka is about as sweet and kind as girl can be. A supportive and teasing best friend and room-mate to Asuna, Konoka is one of the first pupils to warm up to Negi by offering him the chance to move-in with her and Bells. The granddaughter of Mahora`s Dean Konoe, Konoka carries within her a big secret and must be protected by a hidden guardian in class. Lately, her childhood pal Setsuna has been giving her the cold shoulder. What`s behind the friction?</description>
<picture>72774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4694" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="67">7.00</rating>
<name>Saotome Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bookish cohort of Yue and Nodoka in the Library Explorers Club, Haruna is a bit of a rumourmonger. She can often be found holding a saucy manga under her arm; sometimes one of her own creation! Fancying herself a matchmaker, Haruna assists Yue in pushing Nodoka toward a confession of her desire for Negi.</description>
<picture>72775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4695" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="167">7.64</rating>
<name>Sakurazaki Setsuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>It`s the quiet ones you have to watch out for and intense Setsuna Sakurazaki is definitely a girl worth keeping an eye on. A childhood friend of class sweetie Konoka, Sakurazaki has been forcing distance between the former buddies and Konoka can`t figure out why. While on a class trip to Kyoto, Negi begins to suspect that not all is what it seems with Setsuna. It seems the girl is privy to some very secret knowledge. A kendo expert and apparent magic user as sharp and lethal as a polished blade, Setsuna lurks in the shadows for a reason! and when Konoka is attacked, Sakurazaki is obviously involved! Will she turn out to be a trusted ally or a dangerous foe?</description>
<picture>72776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4696" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="94">6.92</rating>
<name>Sasaki Makie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An energetic (and rather childish) rhythmic gymnast and one of the more prominent of the Sports Girls in the class. Although interested in cute things such as teacher Negi Springfield, her encounters with him lead her to become connected to various magical and supernatural phenomenon without truly knowing anything going on. Her connections with Negi also drive her into occasional confrontations with fellow Negiholic Ayaka Yukihiro.</description>
<picture>72777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4697" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="50">4.06</rating>
<name>Shiina Sakurako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most cheerful of the three cheerleaders in the class. She likes Negi, but only because she thinks he is cute. She loves karaoke and her pet cats, Cookie and Biscuit (translated as Kukki and Bikke in katakana) and is in the lacrosse club. As a hobby, Sakurako gambles a lot (it was probably a habit instilled in her younger days).</description>
<picture>72778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1879" picture="20977.jpg">Oomae Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4698" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="69">6.34</rating>
<name>Tatsumiya Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the daughter of the keepers of the Tatsumiya shrine (which is on campus), and works part-time there as a priestess (miko) and exorcist, employing guns with spellbreaker bullets as her tool of exorcism. She is not particularly sociable, keeping to herself most of the time and not engaging in conversation. She is a skinflint, and does not readily spend money unless she has to, or if there is a way to get a discount. She is also a mercenary, and mostly takes on contracts that pertain to hunting/destroying/exorcising demons and ghosts but will take on any job as long as she is paid well.</description>
<picture>72779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1880" picture="207856.jpg">Sakuma Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4699" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="66">6.53</rating>
<name>Chao Lingshen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lingshen Chao is the type of techie that will someday create a robot that designs a program which builds a computer capable of curing the common cold! but, for now her research is limited to Electro-Umbrellas and water-proofing her classmate Chachamaru.An opportunity arises, though, for her to help right a wrong. All the tinkering in Mahora`s labs may finally pay-off if the newest project Lingshen has created with Satomi works like it should!</description>
<picture>72780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6786" picture="79639.jpg">Oosawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4700" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="84">7.30</rating>
<name>Nagase Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Negi retreats to the woods to gather his thoughts after a shocking confrontation with one of his students, the little magi is surprised to run into yet another of his charges, Kaede Nagase! Exuding a Zen-like calm and a maturity well beyond her years (not just because of her much discussed bust!), Kaede spends her free time training in the forested mountains. Exactly what she is training for, she will not tell. But at least she`s good at keeping information under wraps, because she soon figures out Negi`s magical secret! With Kaede`s wisdom and guidance, Negi may just be able to grasp some hidden truths! Springfield may be the teacher, but Kaede is responsible for the lessons today.</description>
<picture>72781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4701" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="43">7.87</rating>
<name>Naba Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A gentle, motherly, and loving, yet strange girl (she seems to have a problem with people calling her "old"). She is a kind person to everyone, volunteers at the daycare center in Mahora City and is in the Astronomy club. She is a good cook, and has exceptional domestic skills. Even though she is very nice, she can be sometimes be equally scary.</description>
<picture>72782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1881" picture="20979.jpg">Kobayashi Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4702" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="66">5.02</rating>
<name>Narutaki Fuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The prankster twins Fuka and Fumika are some of the smallest and, frankly, most immature girls in 2-A. Their youthful nature might be the reason that the duo get along with Negi so well. After setting a booby trap on Springfield`s first day as a teacher, the Narutaki twins set quite a precedent of unpredictability for the lad. Fans of loooooong campus tours as members of Mahora`s Walking Club, you can often find the twins goofing around with their friend Kaede. Fumika tends to go along with her older and more outspoken sister Fuka`s plans, but make no mistake! Both of these girls are capable of trouble!</description>
<picture>72783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4703" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="67">5.45</rating>
<name>Narutaki Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The prankster twins Fuka and Fumika are some of the smallest and, frankly, most immature girls in 2-A. Their youthful nature might be the reason that the duo get along with Negi so well. After setting a booby trap on Springfield`s first day as a teacher, the Narutaki twins set quite a precedent of unpredictability for the lad. Fans of loooooong campus tours as members of Mahora`s Walking Club, you can often find the twins goofing around with their friend Kaede. Fumika tends to go along with her older and more outspoken sister Fuka`s plans, but make no mistake! Both of these girls are capable of trouble!</description>
<picture>72784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1882" picture="73150.jpg">Kanou Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4704" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="53">3.86</rating>
<name>Hakase Satomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Working with Lingshen, Satomi Hakase spends her days creating amazing technologies, some impractical! some genius! When the young scientist and her brainy cohort create a time-machine, a world of opportunity opens up at the perfect moment. Combining Negi`s magic and Satomi`s tech savvy, there may be a chance to correct one of the greatest tragedies to ever strike 2-A. It`s going to be risky, but Satomi`s research is sound! usually!</description>
<picture>72785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4705" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="97">7.04</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Chisame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chisame is a cynical observer of the odd goings on in 2-A, placing herself above the standard zaniness inherent of a gaggle of teenaged girls being led by a preteen boy. Her classmates view her as reserved and surly... though the rest of the world may have a slightly different opinion. When Chisame retires to her room and whips off the nerdy glasses, she leads a surprising double-life as the legendary net idol Chiu! Using her computer smarts and web savvy, Chisame rides a wave of sexy costumes and online journals to the #1 spot in internet popularity polls! That is, until a group of cute and fresh contenders makes quite a stir with their new homepage!</description>
<picture>72786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1883" picture="20991.jpg">Shimura Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4706" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="267">8.84</rating>
<name>Evangeline Athanasia Kitty McDowell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Evangeline Athanasia Kitty McDowell is a student in 2-A, but also an ageless, centuries-old, true-blooded vampire on whom the Thousand Master, http://anidb.net/ch11898 [Nagi Springfield], used a powerful curse. Now that his young and inexperienced son, http://anidb.net/ch4675 [Negi Springfield], is close at hand as her homeroom teacher, she sets out to draw his blood in order to lift the curse, which binds her to Mahora Academy perpetually and keeps her from exercising her enormous magical powers.</description>
<picture>72787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4707" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="38">4.24</rating>
<name>Murakami Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sweet yet shy girl who is an actress in the theatrical club. She loves acting but dislikes her ad-libs as well as her own appearance because her body is not very `mature`-looking.</description>
<picture>72789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4708" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="122">8.26</rating>
<name>Yukihiro Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pretty girl with a palatial estate, Class President Ayaka might seem like a girl to be envied! But a lot of her peers don`t know the sadness she holds in her heart after the loss of a family member early in life. Ayaka`s lifelong rival Asuna knows her secret and surprisingly takes steps to bring some joy into the blonde`s life. Of course, that joy also comes with a visit from a rambunctious group of junior high girls who end up wreaking havoc at her fancy home. A good student and a slight control-freak, Ayaka maintains a crush on Negi that often ends up putting the lad in some uncomfortable situations!</description>
<picture>72790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4709" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="39">4.47</rating>
<name>Yotsuba Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A gentle cook. She enjoys cooking and is in the cooking club. She also cooks at Chao Bao Zi, a restaurant operated out of a streetcar that sells meat buns and other foods with Chao, Hakase, Ku, and Chachamaru. She is also the school dining officer. A very nice and hard-working person, Satsuki is liked by everyone in Mahora, even Evangeline (who sees the rest of the class as a pack of air-headed beasts) and Nitta (who views the middle school students, especially the ones from 3-A, as rowdy kids who need to be disciplined at all times). Her very presence creates an atmosphere of serenity, and she can quickly put a stop to fights even between the hot-headed students in the High School and University martial arts clubs. Satsuki`s dream is to have her own restaurant, as she likes making people happy through her food.</description>
<picture>72791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9653" picture="21012.jpg">Inoue Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4710" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="54">3.70</rating>
<name>Zazie Rainyday</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A silent acrobat, and one of the most mysterious girls of the class. Nothing much is known about her, as she rarely associates with anybody, and even when she does, she rarely talks.</description>
<picture>72792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1886" picture="21014.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11562" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="42">5.89</rating>
<name>Anna Yurievna Cocolova</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anna Yurievna Cocolova, more commonly known as Anya, is Negi`s childhood friend. She secretly has a crush on Negi, and is the only other student who graduated with Negi that has been named. She lives in Wales, but she is probably Russian, since her entire name is Russian. Her specialty is fire based magics.
She`s a year older than Negi and their friendship dates from as long as they can remember. It has been noted that Anya is one of the few people who Negi speaks with informally. Anya also helped Negi pack for his trip to Japan.</description>
<picture>72759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11839" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="12">2.98</rating>
<name>Fate Averruncus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fate Averruncus first appeared in Kyoto Arc. He was intrduced as one of Chigusa`s henchmen, but soon made clear that he is far more dangerous than one would suspect. He is well versed in both western and eastern magic, as well as in close combat. Fate can be considered one of the strongest characters introduced up to date. That time in Kyoto, only Evangeline`s timely appearence allowed the heroes to fend him off. As for his personality, he is overly polite and yet, shows hints of being rather short-tempered later in the series. Eva stated that he moves like a construct, which hints at his artificial nature.
Averruncus returns to take the place of the main antagonist in ~Another World~.</description>
<picture>35870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11898" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="15">6.04</rating>
<name>Nagi Springfield</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagi Springfield is the main protagonist`s father, famous by the name of The Thousand Master, the strongest mage, the hero who saved the magic world. When one man tried to describe the Ala Rubra (basically, Nagi and his companions), he went through the weaknesses of all its members, and finally added, "Tidbit no.4. The redhaired mage has no weaknesses. He`s invincible."
Nagi went missing 10 years ago, last seen in the Middle East. Though considered dead by many, he suddenly appeared to save Negi when his village was overrun by demons.</description>
<picture>130774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16175" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<rating votes="31">7.91</rating>
<name>Nekane Springfield</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Negi`s cousin, often referred to as his onee-chan (sister), although he sees her more as a mother. Her gentle personality is largely based on interpretations through disjointed flashbacks, so it is hard to identify precisely what she is like. What has been indicated however is that she took on more of a motherly role in his life, as at one time she even risked herself to protect him from harm. She is someone that Negi cares greatly for and respects a lot. It has also been shown that she lost both her legs below the knees after having them partially turned into stone.</description>
<picture>45319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="23694" update="2005-08-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2004-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Introduction I</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27221" update="2005-08-26">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2004-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Introduction II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27352" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Asinus in cathedra</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Asinus in cathedra (The Blockhead in the Professor`s Chair)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`âne dans la chair du professeur</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คุณครูมือใหม่</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asinus in Cathedra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27584" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Omne initium est difficile</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Omne initium est difficile (Every Beginning Is Difficult)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tous les débuts sont difficiles</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จะเริ่มอะไรใหม่ๆ นี่ยากจัง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omne Initium Est Difficile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27895" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Amantes, amentes</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amantes, amentes (Lovers, Lunatics)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amants, fous</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รักหลง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amantes, Amentes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28205" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Nullus est instar domus</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nullus locus est instar domus (No Place Is Like Home)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On n`est jamais mieux que chez soi</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไม่มีที่ไหนเหมือนบ้านเรา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nullus Est instar Domus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28852" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fama volat</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fama volat (Rumor Flies)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Renomée vole</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตำนานเล่าขาน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fama Volat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29335" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">A fronte praecipitium a tergo lupi</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A fronte praecipitium a tergo lupi (Between a Rock and a Hard Place)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un précipice devant, un loup derrière</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หน้าเนื้อใจเสือ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Fronte Praecipitium a Tergo Lupi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30030" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fallaces sunt rerum species</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fallaces sunt rerum species (The Appearances of Things Are Deceptive)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`apparence des choses est trompeuse</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รูปลักษณ์ที่หลอกลวง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fallaces Sunt Rerum Species</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30268" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Omnes una manet nox</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Omnes una manet nox (One Night Befalls All of Us)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nuit attend chacun d`entre nous</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ราตรีที่เฝ้าคอย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omnes Una Manet Nox</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30660" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Te capium, cunicule sceleste!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Te capiam, cunicule sceleste! (I`ll Get You, Wascally Wabbit!)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je t`aurai, maudit lapin !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ต้องจับให้ได้เจ้ากระต่ายเจ้าเล่ห์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Te Capium, Cunicule Sceleste!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31930" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ubi concordia, ibi victoria</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ubi concordia, ibi victoria (Where There Is Harmony, There Is Victory)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Là où il y a l`harmonie, il y a la victoire !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สามัคคีคือพลัง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ubi Concordia, Ibi Victoria</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34019" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Cum tacent clamant</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cum tacent clamant (When They Are Silent, They Are Shouting)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand ils se taisent, ils crient</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความเงียบดังกว่าเสียง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cum Tacent Clamant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34157" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Aut disce aut discede</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aut disce aut discede (Either Learn or Leave)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apprends ou va-t-en</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จะเรียนหรือจะถอย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aut Disce Aut Discede</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35340" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Tamdiu discendum est, quamdiu vivas</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tamdiu discendum est, quamdiu vivas (We Live and Learn)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous apprenons toute notre vie</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ชีวิตคือการเรียนรู้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamdiu Discendum Est, Quamdiu Vivas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35724" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Amicitiae nostrae memoriam spero sempiternam fore</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amicitiae nostrae memoriam spero sempiternam fore (I Hope the Memory of Our Friendship Will Be Eternal)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`espère que le souvenir de notre amitié sera éternel</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ขอให้ความทรงจำแห่งมิตรภาพของเรายิ่งยืน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amicitiae Nostrae Memoriam Spero Sempiternam Fore</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35876" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Amicus certus in re incerta cernitur</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amicus certus in re incerta cernitur (A Reliable Friend Is Perceived in an Uncertain Situation)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est dans le malheur qu`on reconnaît ses vrais amis</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เพื่อนในยามยากคือเพื่อนคนสำคัญ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amicus Certus in Re Incerta Cernitur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36076" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Amor tussisque non celantur</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amor tussisque non celantur (Love and a Cough Are Not Kept Secret)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amour et un rhume ne se cachent pas</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความรักมันยากจะห้ามเหมือนการไอ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amor Tussisque Non Celantur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36319" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Nihil difficile amanti</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nihil difficile amanti (Nothing Is Difficult for a Lover)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rien n`est difficile pour ceux qui s`aiment</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไม่มีอะไรยากหากเรารักกัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nihil Difficile Amanti</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36448" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Amor ordinem nescit</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amor ordinem nescit (Love Does Not Recognize Rank)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amour ignore l`ordre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รักออกแบบไม่ได้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amor Ordinem Nescit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36660" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Verba volant, scriptamanent</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Verba volant, scriptamanent (Words Fly Away, Those Written Remain)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les paroles s`envolent, les écrits restent</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คำพูดไม่จีรัง จดหมายยั่งยืน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Verba Volant, Scriptamanent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36690" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Nisi credideritis, non intelligetis.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nisi credideritis, non intelligetis (Unless You Have Believed, You Will Not Understand)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À moins d`avoir la foi, tu ne comprendras pas</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หากไม่มีศรัทธาก็มิอาจล่วงรู้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nisi Credideritis, Non Intelligetis.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37447" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Nil desperandum!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nil desperandum (It Must Not At All Be Despaired)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Inutile de désespérer !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อย่าท้อถอย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nil Desperandum!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37672" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Difficile est tristi fingere mente jocum</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Difficile est tristi fingere mente jocum (It Is Difficult to Make a Joke with a Sad Mind)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Difficile de plaisanter l`esprit triste</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ยากที่จะทำให้คนเศร้าหัวเราะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Difficile Est Tristi Fingere Mente Jocum</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37904" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Memento mori</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memento mori (Remember to Die)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">N`oublie pas de mourir</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความทรงจำที่หายไป</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Memento Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37933" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Et arma et verba vulnerant</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Et arma et verba vulnerant (Both Weapons and Words Wound)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les armes comme les mots blessent</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทั้งอาวุธและการลงโทษอันแสนเจ็บปวด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Et Arma et Verba Vulnerant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37934" update="2011-07-02">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahou Sensei Negima [Memory Collection]</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38208" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Mors certa, hora incerta.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mors certa, mora incerta (Death Is Certain, the Time Is Uncertain)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mort certaine, heure incertaine</title>
<title xml:lang="th">มรณะนั้นแน่นอน แต่เวลานั้นแปรปรวน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mors Certa, Hora Incerta.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38376" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Non mihi, non tibi, sed nobis.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Non mihi, non tibi, sed nobis (Not for Me, Not for You, But for Us)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas pour toi, ni pour moi, mais pour nous</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไม่ใช่เพื่อฉัน ไม่ใช่เพื่อเธอ แต่เพื่อเร</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Non Mihi, Non Tibi, Sed Nobis.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39909" update="2016-11-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Introduction III</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62107" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62108" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62109" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62110" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62111" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62112" update="2011-07-02">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62114" update="2011-07-02">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62115" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62116" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62117" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62118" update="2019-01-12">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62187" update="2006-09-03">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonus - PV- Kagayaku Kimi e ~ Peace</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90297" update="2008-04-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Characters Apresentation</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
