<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2624" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>14</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-08-21</startdate>
<enddate>1998-01-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">B`t X Neo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">btx neo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">B`T X(ビート・エックス) NEO</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">B`t X Neo</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="945" type="Prequel">B`t X</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/search/index.php?pdt_no=320</url>
<creators>
<name id="867" type="Original Work">Kurumada Masami</name>
<name id="3119" type="Character Design">Motohashi Hideyuki</name>
<name id="5581" type="Character Design">Koizumi Noboru</name>
<name id="6531" type="Character Design">Higashide Futoshi</name>
<name id="4244" type="Series Composition">Suga Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3514" type="Animation Work">Kyokuichi Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="3579" type="Direction">Kamegaki Hajime</name>
<name id="3119" type="Chief Animation Direction">Motohashi Hideyuki</name>
<name id="6622" type="Music">Anzai Fumitaka</name>
</creators>
<description>B`t X Neo picks up right where B`t X`s storyline left off.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="147">4.56</permanent>
<temporary count="155">6.53</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>195762.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3279</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1736</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2745</identifier>
<identifier>dxxytv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/search/index.php?pdt_no=320</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B't_X#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B'T_X_NEO#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88129</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1118</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="24061" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ONE FOR ALL!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One for All</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un pour tous !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">One For All!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24062" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊将VS魔将</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Knights vs. The Evil Knights</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gardiens spirituels contre démon de la guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reishou VS Mashou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24063" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅蓮の炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning Red Flame!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les flammes rougissantes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guren no Honoo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24064" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面の告白!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confessions of a Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plus de lumière !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen no Kokuhaku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24065" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">失われた過去を求めて!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search for a Lost Era!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cherche la passé disparu !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ushinawareta Kako o Motomete!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24066" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来の記憶!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of the Future!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mémoire du futur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai no Kioku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24067" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢幻の恐怖!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fear of the Illusions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rêve de l`effroi !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugen no Kyoufu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24068" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lair of the Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le hurlement du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Houkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24069" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一条の光!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Streak of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un morceau de lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichijou no Hikari!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24070" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">血の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les liens du sang !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi no Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24071" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と憎しみの地!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Land of Love and Hate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La terre de la haine et de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Nikushimi no Chi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24072" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラッドの奇跡!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miracles of the Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le miracle du sang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blood no Kiseki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24073" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メール リヒト! (もっと光を)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mehr Licht (more light)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La confession du masque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mehr Licht! (Motto Hikari o)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24074" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">A PIECE OF THE SUN!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Piece of the Sun!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un morceau du soleil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Piece of the Sun!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24075" update="2005-09-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
