<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="263" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-05-25</startdate>
<enddate>2002-05-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Megami Kouhosei Special Curriculum: Nakama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Megami Kouhosei OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">CfG ova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">女神候補生 スペシャルカリキュラム ~仲間~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pilot Candidate: Comrades</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">The Candidate for Goddess (OVA) - Kameraden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Candidate for Goddess - OAV - Camarade</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="253" type="Full Story">Megami Kouhosei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="5509" type="Character Design">Yamaoka Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="5509" type="Direction">Yamaoka Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="5509" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamaoka Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="6367" type="Original Work">Sugisaki Yukiru</name>
<name id="6978" type="Music">Asakawa Tomoyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>The world is being attacked by the mysterious beings called Victims — giant space monsters sent to destroy Zion and all its inhabitants. Zion`s only defence are the five Goddesses — sentient mecha, each bonded to her own pilot and repairer. With a high pilot turnover, it is up to the Goddess Academy (GOA) to train young candidates with special abilities called EX to one day become a pilot of a Goddess. Candidate #88, Zero has joined the GOA and deep, dark mysteries and secrets soon unfold between Zero, the pilots and candidates, and the Goddess Ingrid as the Victims attack again. We rejoin Zero and the Goddess pilots in the thick of battle, continuing to safeguard the planet.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="486">3.17</permanent>
<temporary count="492">6.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>12128.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>887</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Candidate_for_Goddess</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>女神候補生</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>238829</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3473</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>pilot-candidate</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10161" type="main character in" update="2009-07-03">
<rating votes="6">6.75</rating>
<name>Kizna Towryk</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The personal Repairer for the practice ingrid Zero pilots. Kizna wants to be Zero`s equal, and not inferior to him. Sometimes, Kizna talks like a man, but because of her rational personality, the other mechanic girls in her class look up to her. She has dexterous fingers and makes an excellent mechanic. She really likes sweet things. Kizna has artificial fox ears because in her childhood, she had an accident that damaged her ears.</description>
<picture>30533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2940" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<summary>The series is retold from the point of view of one of the Goddess Pilots.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742703</identifier>
<identifier>pilot-candidate</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211677" update="2019-01-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial</title>
<summary>A 10s commercial promoting volume 1-5 of the manga, followed by the the 4 DVDs and 6 VHS tapes of the TV series.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
