<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2635" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-07-29</startdate>
<enddate>1991-06-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Karasu Tengu Kabuto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">鴉天狗カブト</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Crow Demon Kabuto</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Raven Goblin Kabuto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カラス天狗カブト</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2636" type="Side Story">Karasu Tengu Kabuto: Ougon no Me no Kemono</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="220389">Not for everybody. If u like it u will love it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510860">good old school 90`s anime. Really only for people who like older anime &amp; lots of action.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="1905" type="Music">Nagaoka Seikou</name>
<name id="873" type="Original Plan">Terasawa Buichi</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="510" type="Character Design">Urushihara Satoshi</name>
<name id="873" type="Original Work">Terasawa Buichi</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="5817" type="Direction">Fukuda Kiyomu</name>
</creators>
<description>Those who have the blood of the Karasu Tengu (Crow Goblin) in their veins must forever fight against the powers of darkness. Along with four other holy ninja warriors Genbu (Black Snaky Tortoise), Suzaku (Red Phoenix), Seiryu (Blue Dragon), Byakko (White Tiger), Karasu Tengu Kabuto fights against the evil god Kuroyasha (Black Night Demon) Douki and his underlings such as Junin-shu (Top Ten Warriors).
Their battle continues through generations...
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="36">4.73</permanent>
<temporary count="36">6.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11903.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>198</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2243</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2765</identifier>
<identifier>mdkpjc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Karasu_Tengu_Kabuto#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>カラス天狗カブト#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="24164" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえる妖剣飛竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36152" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一天四神ここに見参!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67478" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の城塞! 鬼面城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67479" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決死! 呑霊山への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67480" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極魔殿の宝刀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67481" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吠えよ打竜牙! 応えよ女紋獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67482" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪船大亀甲現わる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67483" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甦れ竜神! 青龍の手に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67484" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ朱雀! 南の守護神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67485" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天狗の四神 荒海に集結せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67486" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めよ竜卍船! 海底の眠りより</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67487" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">龍卍船発進せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67488" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦!! 龍卍船対鬼面城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67489" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道鬼・新たなる野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67490" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">隠形鬼のいけにえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67491" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凶悪・鬼忍びの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67492" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空翔ける黄金の馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67493" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐るべき蛇骨地蔵堂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67494" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蜃気楼の中の鬼真珠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67495" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壮絶・カブトの危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67496" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼界ヶ島・地獄への潜入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67497" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪奇・白面怪童の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67498" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死を呼ぶ鏡地獄の鬼双子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67499" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪異・黄金大魔像現る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67500" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の黄金魔像対竜卍船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67501" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激烈!! 地底大決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67502" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血塗られた城塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67503" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天狗の宿星落ちるとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67504" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新鬼面城の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67505" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五光星の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67506" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊海賊船・黒羊丸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67507" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">万窟城・死のからくり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67508" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘・カブト対天双星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67509" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天道星・巨木魔人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67510" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の森・清元寺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67511" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿敵!! 朱雀対夜叉姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67512" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜卍船火山に消ゆ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67513" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱き四神の魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67514" update="2010-07-01">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月面に散る...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67516" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カブトと四神 ~燃えよニューヒーロー!~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67517" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">壮絶!魔界との戦い ~カブト対道鬼~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67518" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐るべき道鬼の野望 ~戦え・カブトと四神~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67519" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の使者・黄金魔像 ~決戦・カブト対道鬼~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67520" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の五光星落つ ~道鬼の野望再び~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67521" update="2010-05-22">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の門開くとき ~最終決戦・カブト対道鬼~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67524" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Spanish Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67525" update="2007-02-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Spanish Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
