<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2654" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1980-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>1981-03-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nils no Fushigi na Tabi</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Wspaniała podróż Nilsa Holgerssona</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Nils Holgerssons underbara resa genom Sverige</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="short">Nils Holgersson</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="short">Nils Holgersson</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ニルスのふしぎな旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Wonderful Adventures of Nils</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Wunderbare Reise des kleinen Nils Holgersson mit den Wildgänsen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le merveilleux voyage de Nils Holgersson au pays des oies sauvages</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Nils Holgersson</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Cudowna podróż</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Nils Holgersson</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مغامرات نيلز</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Nils Holgersson</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Nils Holgersson</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Peukaloisen retket</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Το θαυμαστό ταξίδι του Νίλς Χόλγκερσον</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">נילס הולגרסון</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Nils Holgersson csodálatos utazása a vadludakkal</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Nils ve Uçan Kaz</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Minunata călătorie a lui Nils Holgersson prin Suedia</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Подорож Нільса Гольгерссона з дикими гусьми</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7428" type="Summary">Nils no Fushigi na Tabi Gekijouban</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1980/tv_001.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="5110" type="Character Design">Okada Toshiyasu</name>
<name id="4122" type="Chief Direction">Toriumi Hisayuki</name>
<name id="6001" type="Music">Chito Kawachi</name>
</creators>
<description>This is the story of an annoying little lad that tortures the animals in his fathers farm. One day he captures a leprechaun which he starts to toy with. The leprechaun escapes him and puts a curse on the boy which gets turned into a dwarf. To escape the anger of the farm animals, he leaves with a flock of wild geese and travels with them. This is how the series begins... As it progresses the boy begins to discover a new greater world which moulds him into a new person.
Source: www.imdb.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="212">5.06</permanent>
<temporary count="214">6.57</temporary>
<review count="1">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>93715.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1417</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2151</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1984</identifier>
<identifier>zbzvbn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1980/tv_001.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20110605102741/http://pierrot.jp/english/title/nils.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Wonderful_Adventures_of_Nils_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ニルスのふしぎな旅</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1858</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89402</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="17392" type="appears in" update="2010-05-02">
<name>Nils</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nils is a boy about 14 years of age. His chief delight is to eat and sleep; and after that, he likes best to make mischief.
One day though, he and his pet hamster Carrot are turned small in size, by a elf Nils had just caught.</description>
<picture>47342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17393" type="main character in" update="2010-05-02">
<name>Nils</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nils` shrinked form.</description>
<picture>47347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="25326" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父をさがすガチョウ番の子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goose Guard Child Looking for His Father</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Asa, la gardeuse d`oies</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25327" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツルの舞踏会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crane`s ball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête du printemps</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25328" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鳥達の恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bird Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le printemps en Laponie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25329" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">森を作った大男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Man Who Built a Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Asathor et les géants</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25330" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">危ないニルス! 山火事だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Look Out, Nils: A Mountain Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le feu de forêt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25331" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さようならアッカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Akka</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`adieu des oies sauvages</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25332" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">空からの救援隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rescue Party from the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le manuscrit perdu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora kara no Kyuuentai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25333" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">湖の火祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lake Fire Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`inondation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25334" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密を知ったニルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nils Discovers a Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une décision difficile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25335" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンのプレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wild Goose`s Present</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`or sur le rocher</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25336" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">5羽の偵察隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patrol of Five</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La dispute des oiseaux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25337" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オオカミの襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wolf Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vieille Maline</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25338" update="2005-06-06">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">満月の幽霊屋敷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haunted House on a Full Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jardin enchanté</title>
<title xml:lang="sv">Det övergivna barnet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25339" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉じこめられたバタキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bataki Shut In</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataki, pris au piège</title>
<title xml:lang="sv">Den förtrollade trädgården</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25340" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネズミの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of the Mice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les rats noirs et les rats gris</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25341" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あとを追わないでゴルゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Follow Me, Golgo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`adieu de Gorgo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25342" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">腹ぺこニルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hungry Nils</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les jours de pluie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25343" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">くたばれレックス番犬作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Damn Watchdog Rex</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chien de garde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kutabare Rex Banken Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25344" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カラスのボスを決めろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Choose a Crow Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La corneille</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25345" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">焼きたてのパンの味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Taste of Freshly Baked Bread</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La faim</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25346" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニルスの子守</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nils`s Lullabye</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`aventure dans la grotte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25347" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の日の出来事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Event on a Stormy Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le paysan au cœur dur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Hi no Denkigoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25348" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月夜に浮かぶ幻の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom Town Appearing on Moonlit Nights</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ville au fond de la mer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25349" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">欲張りカラスと金貨のつぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greedy Crow and the Coin Bowl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de Sunnerbo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25350" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">森の妖精</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster of the Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le réveillon chez les animaux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25351" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀色に光る海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sea Shining Silver</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pacte avec la mouette</title>
<title xml:lang="sv">Havets silver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25352" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歩く銅像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walking Lead Statue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme de bronze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25353" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レックスの悪だくみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rex`s Evil Scheme</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nuit sur le fleuve</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25354" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">なつかしの我が家へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To My Old Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour à la maison</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25428" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わんぱくニルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischevious Nils</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Lutin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wanpaku Nils</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25429" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガチョウに乗って</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Riding a goose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Smirre, le renard</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25430" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちいさくなったニルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shrunken Nils</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`appel des oies sauvages</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25431" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">森のリスのSOS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SOS of the Forest Squirrels</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les petits écureuils</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25432" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モルテンの大ピンチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morten`s big pinch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le château de Vittkoevle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25433" update="2007-11-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鳥の体力テスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bird Strength Contest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi des oies sauvages</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25434" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">捕らわれの大ワシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrested Eagle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gorgo, l`aigle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25435" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">しんまいパパのモルテン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morten the Rookie Papa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La petite oie perdue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25916" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モルテンの婚約</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morten`s Engagement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les fiançailles de Martin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Morten no Kon`yaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25917" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レックスの新しい旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rex`s New Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`adieu de Smirre</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25918" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大洪水, 白鳥の湖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flood of Swan Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le roi des cygnes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25919" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄谷のヒツジ達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goats of Hell`s Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trou de l`enfer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25920" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お天気魔女のいたずら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Testy Witch`s Prank</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sorcière</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25921" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">日が暮れないラプランド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lapland, Land Where the Sun Never Sets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`été en Laponie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25922" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">森を追われるふたごのクマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bear Twins Who Prowl the Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chez les ours</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25923" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘビの仕かえし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snake`s Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sans Défense</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25924" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モルテンの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morten`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Doux comme un mouton</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25925" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">街角でうたうニルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nils Singing on a Streetcorner</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Clément, le violoniste</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25926" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">太陽と氷の精の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of the Spirits of Sun and Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand engourdissement</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25927" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">湖がなくなる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lake Disappears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand lac aux oiseaux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25928" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あまえん坊の子ジカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spoiled Fawn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poil-Gris</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25929" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1980-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おとりにされた子ガモ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ransomed Duck Child</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jarro sert d`appât</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25930" update="2007-08-08">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1981-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">村まつりのよびもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Main Event of the Village Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le maréchal ferrant du Dalarna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25938" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dutch Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25939" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dutch Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120328" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Hebrew Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120329" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Hebrew Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123917" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1980-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123918" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1980-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
