<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="267" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-04-25</startdate>
<enddate>2003-02-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yoru ga Kuru! Square of the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Square of the Moon: The Night is Coming!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Karree des Mondes</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Cuadrado de la Luna</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">밤이 온다</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">夜が来る! Square of the MOON</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Square of the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Square of the moon</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="725" type="Unknown Relation">Green Bunny</name>
<name id="1172" type="Original Work">Alice Soft</name>
<name id="852" type="Animation Work">Shinkuukan</name>
<name id="5516" type="Character Design">Yamamoto Sawako</name>
<name id="10316" type="Direction">Okuno Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1172" type="Music">Alice Soft</name>
<name id="22527" type="Music">Hirose Michitoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the erotic game by http://anidb.net/cr1172 [Alice Soft].
Strange monsters start to appear on the streets, raping women.
How is all that connected with the appearance of a second moon in the sky, that`s what http://anidb.net/ch65157 [Ryou] is about to find out.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="253">4.07</permanent>
<temporary count="256">5.94</temporary>
<review count="1">4.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2052.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4889</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1702</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2623</identifier>
<identifier>omnfxf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>499</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65148" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Kirara</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65149" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Chiro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65150" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Haiji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65151" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-02">
<name>Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244185.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65152" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Gotou Emi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65153" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Shinkai Taketo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65154" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Hoshikawa Tsubasa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="44305">Nitta Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65155" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Izumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="39500" picture="22097.jpg">Hazuki Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65156" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Kedouin Makoto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65157" type="main character in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Hamura Ryou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65158" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Kouya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65159" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Sakaki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65160" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Souji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65161" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Mizuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65162" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Kouichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="39295" picture="53971.jpg">Sasano Hazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65163" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Momose Souichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="65164" type="appears in" update="2014-02-24">
<name>Misato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="37221" picture="31329.jpg">Misaki Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2945" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">双つの月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Moons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sou no Tsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2946" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪つの月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Side of the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokoshima no Tsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17649" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陵の月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon of the Imperial Tomb</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryou no Tsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20151" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽の月(ほのかのつき)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pale Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoka no Tsuki</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
