<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2687" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-05-25</startdate>
<enddate>1996-05-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Haou Taikei Ryuu Knight: Adeu Legend Final</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Lord of Lords Ryu Knight: Adeu`s Legend Final</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">覇王大系リューナイト アデュー・レジェンド・ファイナル</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="542" type="Character">Haou Taikei Ryuu Knight</anime>
<anime id="616" type="Character">Haou Taikei Ryuu Knight: Adeu Legend</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=191</url>
<creators>
<name id="4231" type="Original Work">Itou Takehiko</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="5654" type="Music">Oku Keiichi</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
<name id="3722" type="Direction">Dokite Tsukasa</name>
<name id="6487" type="Character Design">Soeta Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="6488" type="Music">Kanezaki Jun`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: Considered as episode 17 of Lord of Lords Ryu Knight: Adeu`s Legend series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="60">4.50</permanent>
<temporary count="61">6.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>167402.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1851</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2667</identifier>
<identifier>jhoyoq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=191</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4228</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162326</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4808</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2439" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>PIC NEEDS IMPROVEMENT</name>
<description>This entry has a poor picture and needs to have it replaced by a higher-quality alternative. Causes may include: it is too small; its colours or lighting are bad; it has excessive compression or other encoding issues; it is from non-anime sources (anime/char); the face is hard to see (char/creator); the hair/eye/skin colours do not match the anime (char); it does not represent their usual appearance (char); among others. If you can, please swap a better picture in and remove this tag. Thank you.</description>
<picurl>224875.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3020" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-01">
<name>chibi ED</name>
<description>Some or all of the endings feature chibi versions of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="24853" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉ダンジョンの決闘!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen Dungeon no Kettou!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
