<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2696" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2005-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Speed Grapher</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">極速攝殺</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">速写者</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SG</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スピードグラファー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Speed Grapher</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Speed Grapher</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Speed Grapher</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Speed Grapher</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Speed Grapher</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4906" approval="41" total="53">Darker Than Black: Kuro no Keiyakusha</anime>
<anime id="1003" approval="10" total="19">Gungrave</anime>
<anime id="9127" approval="6" total="15">Psycho-Pass</anime>
<anime id="1551" approval="5" total="11">Boukyaku no Senritsu</anime>
<anime id="5446" approval="2" total="8">Ayakashi</anime>
<anime id="14574" approval="2" total="7">Cop Craft</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="13">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="82103">Surprisingly good for something that sounds so boring, photography.  Actually turned out to be a lot more action packed than I thought it would be.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="459074">True, you will probably need time to get used to this anime but i think that it`s worth while. I even teared up at the end. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="359130">AMAZING!!!  Just watch this series please!  I was a little unsure at first but this is awesome!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="291829">Just finished watching it .... to be honest ... I had this anime on my PC about 3 months before actually watching it ... I downloaded it, because I was searching for something to watch (to kill time), but it turned out really good ...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="559673">another underated anime... this is a fine piece of work and a must see for grown up audience.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="269300">Terribly underrated again, its a must, one of the few animes, i just went through in one go!
Certainly i`m wondering if I will find something this good so soon, again... will I?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="728642">As everyone else says - this is seriously underrated. You have endearing characters with a well executed background story of political corruption, you have very imaginative action and progression with every episode (just one look back episode, which I have to say was well executed). The only downside was that it got a little confusing for me towards the end, just a little before it got back on track. I liked the ending. Could have been a little better but it wasn`t entirely anti-climactic. Must See - seriously, if you`re not hooked by the 2nd episode I would be very surprised!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="282239">Ending.. Its the ultimate win!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/0502.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="735" type="Original Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="3569" type="Music">Mitsumune Shinkichi</name>
<name id="3754" type="Character Design">Ishihama Masashi</name>
<name id="4333" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Shin</name>
<name id="4401" type="Direction">Sugishima Kunihisa</name>
</creators>
<description>Ten years after the Bubble War, the dichotomy between the rich and the poor in the world becomes more prominent and Japan is no exception. The rich seek to satisfy their desires and derive pleasure for themselves, and Tokyo has materialised into such a city as a result.
http://anidb.net/ch20023 [Saiga Tatsumi], once a war photographer, works for http://anidb.net/ch19916 [Ginza Hibari] in the capitalist state of Tokyo. He infiltrates the Roppongi Club, a secretive base located in the red district area of the city, to collect information. However, he was caught in the process and brought forward to a girl called http://anidb.net/ch20024 [Kagura] who was in the midst of a ritual. His contact with Kagura awakens his special ability: the power to make things explode when photographed. In order to unravel the mystery behind the Roppongi Club and Kagura, Saiga begins his solitary struggle.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4251">6.20</permanent>
<temporary count="4310">7.58</temporary>
<review count="10">7.03</review>
</ratings>
<picture>70363.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4579</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>198</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1650</identifier>
<identifier>bjjpae</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/archives/speed-grapher/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/speed-grapher/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Speed_Grapher</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>SPEED_GRAPHER</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7362</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1656" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>corrupt</name>
<description>The character is spiritually or morally impure and may accept payment or other benefits for services or material which the recipient is not due, under law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3149" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-15">
<name>journalism</name>
<description>Journalism is the work and distribution of reports on the interaction of events, facts, ideas, and people that are the "news of the day" and that informs society to at least some degree. The word applies to the occupation (professional or not), the methods of gathering information, and the organizing literary styles. Journalistic media include: print, television, radio, Internet and, in the past, newsreels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5930" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shounen ai</name>
<description>At least one male character has a romantic or sexual interest in another male character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19916" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="20">6.49</rating>
<name>Ginza Hibari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20023" type="main character in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="18">7.57</rating>
<name>Saiga Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4689" picture="170829.jpg">Takada Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20024" type="main character in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="21">6.50</rating>
<name>Tennouzu Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20513" picture="45925.jpg">Saitou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20025" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="16">8.53</rating>
<name>Suitenguu Chouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20026" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="4">8.32</rating>
<name>Tsujidou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20030" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="5">2.21</rating>
<name>Tennouzu Shinsen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20031" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="3">3.93</rating>
<name>Niihari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20032" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="4">5.57</rating>
<name>Makabe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20033" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="1">5.70</rating>
<name>Togoshi Seijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20034" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="5">2.83</rating>
<name>Bob</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20035" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="4">6.82</rating>
<name>Ryougoku Genba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20036" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="2">1.26</rating>
<name>Ekoda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2207" picture="41549.jpg">Makishima Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20037" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="1">5.70</rating>
<name>Shiina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20040" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="2">1.49</rating>
<name>Goutokuji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20512" picture="53878.jpg">Mori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20042" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="1">3.48</rating>
<name>Nishiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20045" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<name>Shirogane Katsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20048" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="5">1.36</rating>
<name>Koganei Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3240" picture="45305.jpg">Yokoo Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20049" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<name>Mizunoguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20499" picture="172621.jpg">Gou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20050" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<name>Yurigaoka Ran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20051" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Kanda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20052" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<name>Tsurumaki Miharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="489" picture="43165.jpg">Okamoto Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20053" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<name>Ochiai Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20054" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="3">1.12</rating>
<name>Kamiya Katsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4683" picture="27279.jpg">Koyama Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="34050" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="5">9.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35723" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">背徳都市</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Depravity City</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die korrupte Stadt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cité corrompue</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La città corrotta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haitoku Toshi</title>
<summary>When Saiga infiltrates a secret pleasure-club for Tokyo’s elite, he will ignite a chain of events that could force the entire ruling class to their knees.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35750" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">唸る札束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goddess of Greed</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wehklagen des Banknotenbündel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Billets gémissants</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Soldi e gemiti</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unaru Satsutaba</title>
<summary>Kagura’s haunted by nightmares where she participates in twisted rituals, playing the part of a powerful Divine Goddess. Unbeknownst to her, the terrifying visions are far from imaginary.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35848" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">写殺爆撮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Film Like a Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tod im Sucher</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Photos explosives</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Scatto esplosivo, foto mortale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shasatsu Bakusatsu</title>
<summary>During a depraved ceremony beneath Tokyo, a kiss from Kagura gives Saiga the strange power to use his camera as a weapon. Can he rescue the Divine Goddess and get them to the surface alive?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36078" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">略奪少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lethal Headshot</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das ausgebeutete Mädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille dérobée</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La fanciulla da rapire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryakudatsu Shoujo</title>
<summary>When Saiga slips under Suitengu’s nose to free Kagura, her captor is not pleased. He sends Shirogane to ensnare Saiga in a deadly dance under the night’s sky.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36321" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイヤモンド夫人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Best Friend of Diamonds</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Madame Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La femme-diamant</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La signora diamante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diamond Fujin</title>
<summary>Saiga hides Kagura at a seedy nightclub. Meanwhile, another Euphoric hunts for the girl: Madam Koganei, a high-class woman who fuels her power by swallowing diamonds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36519" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならダイヤモンド夫人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Out of Focus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf Wiedersehen Madame Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, femme-diamant</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Addio, signora diamante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Diamond Fujin</title>
<summary>Madam Koganei seems impervious to Saiga’s attacks. Not only is she virtually unbreakable, but the diamond’s reflective quality makes it impossible for Saiga’s camera to focus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36591" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猟奇ドリル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Picture</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Drill des grotesken Jägers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Frissons morbides</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Trapani macabri e grotteschi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryouki Drill</title>
<summary>Saiga and Kagura visit Doctor Ryogoku, hoping he can find a medical explanation for the strange Euphoric powers. As Saiga gets lost in disturbing memories of war, the doctor makes a startling diagnosis!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36630" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神楽のともし火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dentophobia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Licht von Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lumière de Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La fioca luce di Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagura no Tomoshibi</title>
<summary>With Kagura’s health failing, an unexpected house call from the demented Dentist is the last thing Saiga needs. The photographer will have to perfect his shooting skills to pass this sadistic drill.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37303" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湯殿にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Into the Bath</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Badeort</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aux sources</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Alle terme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yudono nite</title>
<summary>Saiga and Kagura visit a remote spa, where Kagura learns some shocking truths about her origins. But the most startling revelation is a glimpse into the human side of powerful Shinsen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37624" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水天宮来る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suitengu Cometh</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Suitengu kommt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suitengû arrive</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Arriva Suitengu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suitenguu Kuru</title>
<summary>Saiga and Kagura’s search of an abandoned research lab is interrupted by Suitengu. Back in the city, Ginza makes a shady pact with Kagura’s mother and prepares to join the party.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37700" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハハキトク スグカエレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother Critical</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mutter liegt im Sterben, komm sofort zurück</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ta mère est mourante, reviens immédiatement</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tua madre è in agonia, torna subito a casa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha Kitoku Sugu Kaere</title>
<summary>Saiga falls unconscious into Ginza’s hands after telling her where Kagura is hiding. The rogue cop will stop at nothing to claim Saiga as her own  - even if it means turning Kagura over to the enemy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37701" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">左手に抱かれて眠れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Left Hand Lullaby</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schlaf in meinem linken Arm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endors-toi en tenant ma main gauche</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Dormi nella mia mano sinistra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hidarite ni Idakarete Nere</title>
<summary>Suitengu is on the verge of taking control of the Tennozu Group by marrying Shinsen. Kagura must break out of the floating research facility and warn her mother before it’s too late.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38070" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀座番外地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ginza the Lawless</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ginzas Extratour</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ginza sans adresse</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fuoriprogramma per Ginza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginza Bangai Chi</title>
<summary>New light is shed on the Euphoria Syndrome after Saiga and Ginza visit an eccentric colleague of Dr. Ryogoku. Meanwhile, Suitengu continues his plan to seize control - by marrying Kagura instead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38071" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人妻神楽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wedding Photographer</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ehefrau Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kagura mariée</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Kagura si sposa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitozuma Kagura</title>
<summary>Suitengu’s got everything in place for the wedding: a church, a priest, and a star-studded guest list. The only thing the groom didn’t plan for is the photographer running away with the bride.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38568" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">濡れ女地獄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell Is a Wet Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Hölle der nassen Frau</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`enfer de la femme ruisselante</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`inferno della sirena</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nure Onna Jigoku</title>
<summary>Saiga and Kagura are running blind, with the whole country on the look-out for them. But it’s one mysterious woman with a tragic past who threatens to drag the photographer to his watery doom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38748" recap="true" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">半期決算報告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audit the Wicked</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Veröffentlichung des Halbjahresberichts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rapport semestriel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Rendiconto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanki Kessan Houkoku</title>
<summary>Suitengu has all he needs to initiate the next phase of his plan: releasing a new drug that simulates Kagura’s kiss and makes the public lose control of their desires.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38749" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神成金</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reaper and the Nouveau Riche</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Sensenmann der Neureichen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort enrichie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un villano rifatto diventa il dio della morte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami Narikin</title>
<summary>Suitengu reflects on the tragic events that shaped him into the man he has become. In recalling the strange, sordid ghosts of his past, the motives for his future endgame come into focus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38750" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第三局</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fates and Fists</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die dritte Phase</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Troisième partie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La terza fase</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisan Kyoku</title>
<summary>As the Tennozu Group gets rich off of their new product line, Saiga and Kagura set sail for a fresh start in a new land. But before they can vanish in the wind, they`re dragged back to Tokyo by a powerful new ally.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39786" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘とくちびる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lips and Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lies and Lips</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mensonges et lèvres</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Baci e bugie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso to Kuchibiru</title>
<summary>Saiga agrees to testify at the Parliamentary hearing if his conditions are met. But after a chance meeting with a young idealist named Joe, Saiga resolves to bring down Suitengu himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39787" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グッドバイブレーション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good Vibrations</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Good Vibrations</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Good vibration</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Buone vibrazioni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Good Vibration</title>
<summary>As Saiga fights a ruthless Euphoric posing as a friend, Kagura is attacked by the one who was supposed to cure her. Meanwhile, Ginza finds a shocking name on the membership list of Suitengu’s club.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40903" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総理の朝食</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Hail the Glutton</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Frühstück des Premierministers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le petit déjeuner du premier ministre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La colazione del primo ministro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souri no Choushoku</title>
<summary>As war breaks out in the skyscrapers of Tokyo between two powerful Euphorics, a depraved killer holds Ginza captive and Prime Minister Kamiya reveals his plans - and true face - to Kagura.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="41097" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オカネクダサイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Money, Money, Money</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gib mir Geld</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Donnez-moi de l`argent</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Soldi, per favore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okane Kudasai</title>
<summary>As Suitengu continues his assault on the Prime Minister’s mansion, Saiga races to Kagura’s aid. Loyalties are tested and not everyone rises to the occasion.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="41098" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">札束の墓標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tender Grave</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Grab aus Geld</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tombeau de billets</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una lapide di banconote</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satsutaba no Bohyou</title>
<summary>With all the country’s leaders locked within the secret club, Japan is without a government. Intent on destroying Suitengu and claiming the spoils, outside forces step into the vacuum and invade.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="41099" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">六本木クライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Roppongi Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Roppongi-Krise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La crise de Roppongi</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Roppongi Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roppongi Crisis</title>
<summary>The final showdown between Suitengu and Saiga reaches its climax. If Suitengu executes his plan, the streets of Tokyo will be paved with fire and the global economy will be changed forever.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86309" update="2010-08-16">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">English Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105128" update="2010-08-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105129" update="2010-08-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105130" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105131" update="2009-07-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105439" update="2010-08-16">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="105440" update="2010-08-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
