<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="27" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-02-21</startdate>
<enddate>1994-05-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aa! Megami-sama!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ah! My Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Oh! My Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">오! 나의 여신님 OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ах! Богиньо моя!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">我的女神</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">AMG</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">OMG</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="short">omg ova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ams ova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AMS</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">aams</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ああっ女神さまっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Oh My Goddess!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Oh! My Goddess - OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ah! My Goddess - OAV</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Oh, Mia Dea!</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ah, mi Diosa!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Моя богиня!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Ah! Minha Deusa</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Ach! Má bohyně</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เทพธิดาอลเวง</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="206" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Aa! Megami-sama!</anime>
<anime id="2533" type="Alternative Setting">Aa! Megami-sama! (2005)</anime>
<anime id="186" type="Side Story">Aa! Megami-sama! Chicchaitte Koto wa Benri Da ne!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10529" approval="3" total="10">Shinmai Maou no Testament</anime>
<anime id="8062" approval="2" total="14">Astarotte no Omocha!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="160105">Very sweet and amusing anime, but sometimes the humor can feel strained and `over the top`.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="416202">One of the all around truly great anime/manga series.  Romantic with a soul, but doesn`t take itself too seriously.  You won`t be disappointed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109384">this really has the classic feel, it is well pased and give a very `old skool` feel

watch it, you will be sweeped!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="219874">If you love Ranma, Kimagure Orange Road, Urisei Yatsura those classic anime you will definitely love this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="86398">dont ask what this is about or if its worth buying just do it!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="158874">Nostalgic and lovable!
MUST SEE!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="53116">Classic. If you haven`t seen this yet, WHY NOT?!?  Go!  Do it!  Now!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/goddess/ova/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="1466" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsubara Hidenori</name>
<name id="3652" type="Direction">Gouda Hiroaki</name>
<name id="8155" type="Music">Yasuda Takeshi</name>
<name id="817" type="Original Work">Fujishima Kousuke</name>
<name id="1466" type="Character Design">Matsubara Hidenori</name>
</creators>
<description>Be careful what you wish for!
College freshman http://anidb.net/ch2215 [Morisato Keiichi] gets more than he bargained for when dialling for dinner and gets an unexpected delivery — http://anidb.net/ch2234 [Belldandy], a real live, honest to goodness Goddess! Belldandy grants him a wish, and Keiichi decides that what he really needs is a girlfriend just like Belldandy. And that is exactly what he gets. The mysterious Ultimate Force that enforces all Wish Contracts comes into play, and Keiichi and Belldandy are now inseparable. That is when Keiichi remembers that his dorm has a strict rule: no women allowed!
Can Keiichi and Belldandy find a new place to live? Will everyone buy the story that she is a foreign student? And does Keiichi have the guts to put the moves on a woman who is literally divine?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4266">6.06</permanent>
<temporary count="4384">7.52</temporary>
<review count="8">6.70</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221558.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>53</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>49</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7</identifier>
<identifier>spwtcj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/goddess/ova/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Oh_My_Goddess!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ああっ女神さまっ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88344</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4494</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1221" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-28">
<name>scooter</name>
<description>A scooter is a type of motorcycle with a step-through frame and a platform for the rider`s feet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>218044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2343" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>ojou-sama laugh</name>
<description>A type of haughty laughter typical of rich young girls, as well as older rich women. Generally sounds like a high-pitched "OHOHOHOHOHOHO".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2890" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>foot fetish</name>
<description>Anime contains scenes which revolve around foot-fetishism.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3650" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-08-10">
<name>living together with god</name>
<description>Divine roommate</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4462" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>barefoot</name>
<description>This character never seems to wear any shoes — possibly a martial artist that prefers to stay in close contact with the ground, or a girl from the country now living in the city.
Alas, under more dire circumstances this can also be a sign of real poverty.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6039" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-18">
<name>piggyback ride</name>
<description>One of the protagonists (usually male) gives another character (usually female) a ride on the back. Can be interpreted as a sign of closeness or endearment in a romance setting.
Reasons: The female character is exhausted from previous running, or has a fit of anaemia, or hurt herself and no longer can walk.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6090" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Norse mythology</name>
<description>Norse mythology, or Scandinavian mythology, is the body of mythology of the North Germanic people stemming from Norse paganism and continuing after the Christianization of Scandinavia and into the Scandinavian folklore of the modern period. The Norse mythology consists of tales of various deities, beings, and heroes derived from numerous sources from both before and after the pagan period, including medieval manuscripts, archaeological representations, and folk tradition. [...]
Most of the surviving mythology centres on the plights of the gods and their interaction with various other beings, such as humanity and the jötnar, beings who may be friends, lovers, foes and/or family members of the gods. The cosmos in Norse mythology consist of Nine Worlds that flank a central cosmological tree, Yggdrasil. Units of time and elements of the cosmology are personified as deities or beings. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2215" type="main character in" update="2015-02-19">
<rating votes="233">3.72</rating>
<name>Morisato Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morisato Keiichi is a 21-year-old Engineering student at Nekomi Technical Institute. He has a natural aptitude for anything mechanical, and is brilliant when it comes to engineering. Keiichi is a member of the NIT Motor Club. Keiichi is a good person with a good heart. He is nice to everyone regardless of how they treat him or what they do. He is very forgiving of Skuld and Urd; despite the amount of trouble and grief they cause him.</description>
<picture>168975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2234" type="main character in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="819">8.93</rating>
<name>Belldandy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Belldandy is exceptionally kind-hearted, even for a goddess. She can easily sense other people`s emotions and tries her best to be empathetic to all those around her, displaying a combination of "serene beauty and acceptance". She rarely holds a grudge and is always willing to forgive anyone who does injury to her.</description>
<picture>43148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2237" type="main character in" update="2018-06-01">
<rating votes="573">8.66</rating>
<name>Urd</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urd is Belldandy`s older half sister and is the second Goddess to appear to Keiichi. Unlike her younger sister Belldandy, Urd is very impulsive and headstrong. Belldandy describes Urd as being very passionate about everything she does. Urd is a great believer in the idea that the `End justifies the Means`. Urd`s impulsiveness often makes her act first without fully considering the consequences.</description>
<picture>168963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2240" type="main character in" update="2015-02-19">
<rating votes="349">4.94</rating>
<name>Skuld</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skuld is the younger sister of Belldandy and is the third Goddess to appear to Keiichi Morisato. Skuld is an engineering genius, capable of building just about anything out of the most mundane parts under most limited resources. Skuld regularly clashes with her sister Urd, particularly when it comes to Belldandy`s relationship with Keiichi. However, the two sisters do love each other and will work together to solve a problem or stave off a mutual threat.</description>
<picture>168962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6957" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="43">3.73</rating>
<name>Mishima Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mishima Sayoko is a popular girl at Nekomi Tech, to the point where she considers herself the "queen" of the school. She is also quite rich, coming from a wealthy family. She has her own apartment and an expensive car, and gets to throw lavish parties with very important people. When Belldandy appears, all the guys` attention turns to her rather than Sayoko. Mishima begins to get jealous of Belldandy and wants to make her upset by seducing Keiichi, even though she does not have any interest in him. She even goes to the lengths of teaming up with Toshiyuki Aoshima and Marller to bring her down. Gradually, as the series progresses, she becomes less and less antagonistic, even offering Keiichi relationship advice and foiling Marller`s schemes. It seems as though she develops feelings for Keiichi at the beginning of season 2 when she did not feel as lonely when he was with her. Sayoko has seen both Urd and Belldandy use their powers, although she now believes that Belldandy is a witch. She is shown to have much pride, and seems to almost enjoy competing with Belldandy at times.</description>
<picture>1963.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="15085" picture="44410.jpg">Asami Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7527" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-19">
<rating votes="65">4.84</rating>
<name>Morisato Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morisato Megumi is Keiichi`s younger sister. She attends the Nekomi Institute of Technology (NIT), like Keiichi, as an engineering student. Megumi is also a very skilled mechanic and motorcycle driver. She goes on to become the "queen" of bike racers around Nekomi. Belldandy has remarked that she sees a similarity between Megumi and Skuld, and that she would like to see Skuld learn some things from Megumi.</description>
<picture>168974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15324" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="20">1.33</rating>
<name>Aoshima Toshiyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoshima Toshiyuki is a playboy around the Nekomi Institute of Technology campus and http://anidb.net/ch6957 [Sayoko]`s cousin. He is enamoured by http://anidb.net/ch2234 [Belldandy] and tries often to steal her away from http://anidb.net/ch2215 [Keiichi], going as far as to set up a rival motor club. In the TV series, he and his cousin Sayoko can be identified by the super cars that they drive.</description>
<picture>80422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15325" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="42">2.96</rating>
<name>Ootaki Hikozaemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ootaki Hikozaemon and http://anidb.net/ch15326 [Tamiya Toraichi] are the directors of the Motor Club. They make life very hard for Keiichi by passing on a lot of work to him. However, they have a great deal of respect for Keiichi`s abilities both as a mechanic and a driver. In the manga, they pass the directorship of the Motor Club to Keiichi. They were also both in love with the original director of the motor club, Fujimi Chihiro. However, she rejected both of them for the sake of the club.</description>
<picture>1979.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15326" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-23">
<rating votes="46">2.37</rating>
<name>Tamiya Toraichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamiya Toraichi and http://anidb.net/ch15325 [Ootaki Hikozaemon] are the directors of the Motor Club. They make life very hard for http://anidb.net/ch2215 [Keiichi] by passing on a lot of work to him. However, they have a great deal of respect for Keiichi`s abilities both as a mechanic and a driver. In the manga, they pass the directorship of the Motor Club to Keiichi. They were also both in love with the original director of the motor club, Fujimi Chihiro. However, she rejected both of them for the sake of the club.</description>
<picture>1964.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="929" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MOONLIGHT AND CHERRY BLOSSOMS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moonlight and Cherry Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Clair de lune et fleurs de cerisier</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Лунный свет и вишнёвый цвет</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moonlight and Cherry Blossoms</title>
</episode>
<episode id="930" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1994-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FOR THE LOVE OF GODDESS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Love of Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour l`amour d`une déesse</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">За любовь богини</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">For the Love of Goddess</title>
</episode>
<episode id="931" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">EVERGREEN HOLY NIGHT</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evergreen Holy Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La promesse éternelle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ночь, когда меняются судьбы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Evergreen Holy Night</title>
</episode>
<episode id="932" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BURNING HEARTS ON THE ROAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burning Hearts on the Road</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cœurs brulés en piste</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пламенные сердца на дороге</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Burning Hearts on the Road</title>
</episode>
<episode id="933" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MIDSUMMER NIGHT`S DREAM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Midsummer Night`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le songe d`une nuit d`été</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сон в летнюю ночь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midsummer Night`s Dream</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22281" update="2015-04-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="2">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Extras</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88306" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1993-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95679" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1993-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95680" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1993-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95681" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1993-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95682" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1993-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
