<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="271" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-10-10</startdate>
<enddate>2002-12-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Haibane Renmei</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">灰羽連盟</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">灰羽聯盟</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Charcoal Feather Federation</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">La Federazione delle Piume Cineree</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Alas Grises</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">La Federación de las Plumas de Carbón</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Альянс Пепельнокрылых</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Альянс Серокрылых</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">잿빛 날개의 연맹</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">하이바네 연맹</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">회색 날개의 연맹</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Przymierze szarych skrzydeł</title>
<title xml:lang="ca" type="synonym">Ales Grises</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Съюзът на Среброкрилите</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Товариство сірокрилих</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Союз сірокрилих</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Альянс Попелястокрилих</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">هایبانه رنمی</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Haibane</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HR</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">灰羽連盟</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Haibane Renmei</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Haibane Renmei - Ailes Grises</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ailes Grises</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ali Grigie</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Союз Серокрылых</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Haibane renmei: Stowarzyszenie szaropiórych</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">بال گچی ها</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="575" approval="82" total="119">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</anime>
<anime id="6564" approval="30" total="61">Angel Beats!</anime>
<anime id="2659" approval="17" total="41">Aria the Animation</anime>
<anime id="6783" approval="16" total="34">Sora no Oto</anime>
<anime id="3433" approval="9" total="31">Mushishi</anime>
<anime id="7409" approval="7" total="16">Colorful (2010)</anime>
<anime id="112" approval="6" total="29">Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi</anime>
<anime id="4345" approval="5" total="18">Dennou Coil</anime>
<anime id="11712" approval="2" total="9">Hai to Gensou no Grimgar</anime>
<anime id="1810" approval="1" total="4">Kurau Phantom Memory</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="32">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="268960">Definitely for those that like more complexity and a in-depth philosophy on how to deal with regrets and loss. It seemed very reflective and It really kept me thinking about my own trials in life.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="92088">Has a very good story and great character development. I also liked the mysteriousness of the world, with all the little details.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="507045">The lasting memory I take from this beautiful anime series is to appreciate the ability we have to love or cherish a precious few people in our lives. There are bonds formed by characters that are deeply touching and made more special by the constant threat of the unknown world beyond the wall along with other mysterious elements.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="280616">heart warming piece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="322430">I love the concept of this anime. wish i knew more about the place and outside the walls</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="306405">One of the reasons why I came back from a long hiatus of anime. Animation is always gonna be spectacular because artists get better every generation but storytelling is a gift.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="66705">Söpö ja melko rauhallinen anime. Surullinen, muttei muistaakseni kovin ahdistava.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="353610">Still `that` one anime I can never forget about gotta say it`s my all time favorite show for many reasons.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="784472">Contemplative and evocative work about finding one`s place. Full of atmosphere and questions that it doesn`t outright answer, there`s no doubt this one should leave you thinking for long after you watch it. For anyone who likes to analyze themes and symbolism this is an absolute must.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="333550">A good one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="253985">Great and unique story as well as drawing style! Definetly a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="304289">Haibane Renmei is a classic masterpiece. One of the most interesting animes I`ve ever seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="170697">Great story and heart-warming .. ^_^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396387">So really unusual storyline. 
Watching it you have that gorgeous sensation that leads you to watch it all in a row!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="40085">This one`s a definite must see. Truly unique and deep fantasy story with interesting characters and fitting soundtrack. One of my all-time favorites. Simply great!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="412755">The symbolism throughout this anime is unlike anything else. It`s really a must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516146">I`m not aware of any anime like this one. If you want thrills &amp; chills, you needn`t bother. But if you want to see anime that is art, you should be here. ABe again creates amazing characters that will haunt you forever. One of my very favorites.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="101469">Everything by yoshitoshi abe is just great. It`s always very abstract and thought provoking, I always like the open feel the series that feature his artwork.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geneon-ent.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/haibane/</url>
<creators>
<name id="777" type="Animation Work">Radix</name>
<name id="3905" type="Series Composition">Abe Yoshitoshi</name>
<name id="777" type="Work">Radix</name>
<name id="3905" type="Original Work">Abe Yoshitoshi</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="6297" type="Direction">Tokoro Tomokazu</name>
<name id="7033" type="Character Design">Takada Akira</name>
</creators>
<description>In a long-forgotten walled town, humans coexist with the Haibane, angelic-like beings of unknown origin. http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] becomes the newest Haibane, after she awakens from a strange dream and finds herself hatching from a massive cocoon. With no memories of her previous life, Rakka struggles to adjust to her new surroundings, however burning questions remain in the back of her mind. What are Haibane and what is their purpose? What lies beyond the huge, forbidden town walls? Thus Rakka begins her wistful journey of self-discovery and wonderment.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7462">8.12</permanent>
<temporary count="7541">8.24</temporary>
<review count="14">7.67</review>
</ratings>
<picture>238806.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1871</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1091</identifier>
<identifier>mcwkso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.geneon-ent.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/haibane/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Haibane_Renmei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>灰羽連盟</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>460</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240089</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5625</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="215" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>lonely</name>
<description>Loneliness is an unpleasant feeling in which a person feels a strong sense of emptiness and solitude resulting from inadequate levels of social relationships. However, it is a subjective experience. Loneliness has also been described as social pain — a psychological mechanism meant to alert an individual of isolation and motivate her/him to seek social connections.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2302" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-19">
<name>helpful</name>
<description>This character is serviceable for an end or purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3378" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>redemption</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3834" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>impending death -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>At least one character in this show is going to or very likely to die soon because of a http://anidb.net/t2574 [terminal illness], of a http://anidb.net/t2874 [disaster] such a http://anidb.net/t2925 [war], an http://anidb.net/t5466 [epidemic] (including the zombie apocalypse), or of other life-threatening reasons. Please assign the appropriate disaster tags to the anime, the terminal illness tag to the relevant characters, and any other relevant or necessary replacement tags to the corresponding entities, and then remove this tag from the anime in question. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4582" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-01-21">
<name>only the beginning</name>
<description>The anime shows a full story, but leaves the story line itself unfinished, ending at a point which could easily be seen as a hint for a possible sequel, where none exists.
Note: Only for anime that have no sequel and are stand-alone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4907" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>small town</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5104" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-11-22">
<name>vignetted picture</name>
<description>In photography and optics, vignetting is a reduction of an image brightness or saturation at the periphery compared to the image center, usually caused by faulty optics.
Although vignetting is normally unintended and undesired, it is sometimes purposely introduced for example in comics, animation or video games as a creative, false camera effect, such as to draw attention to the center of the screen.</description>
<picurl>43292.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5914" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-05">
<name>afterlife</name>
<description>The afterlife is the continued existence of an essential part of an individual`s identity or consciousness after the death of the body. When people continue existing beyond the death of their physical bodies, they may or may not keep interacting with the realm of the living and/or retain their memories. It is possible for them to start a new life without a physical body in a spirit realm, and they may or may not be able to understand that they`re already dead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9898" type="main character in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="53">8.09</rating>
<name>Rakka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A new arrival at Old Home, Rakka struggles throughout the series to "find herself", and has trouble escaping from curiosity about her past. She forms many friendships, but her closest is with Reki.</description>
<picture>29979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9899" type="main character in" update="2010-12-28">
<rating votes="81">8.98</rating>
<name>Reki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reki is a mother figure to the other Haibane of http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home]. She has been a Haibane for seven years, longer than any of the others except for http://anidb.net/ch14484 [Nemu].
Reki cannot remember her "cocoon dream", and is troubled by her past at Old Home and by nightmares. She is the only known Haibane of Old Home born with stained wings, showing that she is "sin-bound"; she uses a dye to keep this a secret from everyone except for Nemu and http://anidb.net/ch14494 [Kuramori] (who got the dye recipe from http://anidb.net/ch14488 [Washi]).
When her guardian Kuramori left Guri, Reki ran away and became a Haibane of the http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory] for a while.</description>
<picture>1161.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14480" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="14">7.36</rating>
<name>Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mechanically inclined tomboy, Kana works at the clock tower in the center of town. Kana has been a Haibane for four years.</description>
<picture>44933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4428" picture="26693.jpg">Miyajima Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14481" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="9">6.48</rating>
<name>Kuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the "older" Haibane. She develops a close friendship with Rakka and has been a Haibane for two years.</description>
<picture>44932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14482" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="1">3.94</rating>
<name>Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Young Feathers in Old Home. His name Shouta is short for shootokeeki (ショートケーキ), meaning shortcake, which he claims to have seen in his cocoon dream whereas http://anidb.net/ch14483 [Dai] assumes it`s just his favorite food.</description>
<picture>61421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14483" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<name>Dai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Young Feathers in Old Home. His name Dai is short for daiku (大工), meaning carpenter, which is his career aspiration for the future.</description>
<picture>61419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14484" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="10">6.86</rating>
<name>Nemu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Haibane who has lived longest at http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home]. Her friends tease Nemu because she is always sleeping, and in fact her name comes from the verb nemuru (眠る = to sleep) as she slept even in her cocoon dream.
She is a friend of http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki], works at the http://anidb.net/ch26017 [library], and has been a Haibane for nine years.</description>
<picture>44935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14485" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<name>Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Young Feathers in Old Home. Her name Hana means flower (花), as becoming a florist is her career aspiration for the future.</description>
<picture>61420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2387" picture="22211.jpg">Tokunaga Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14486" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-20">
<rating votes="10">6.64</rating>
<name>Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A serious, but occasionally mischievous and funny, Haibane. She works in a bakery in town and has been a Haibane for three years.</description>
<picture>43211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14487" type="appears in" update="2010-12-28">
<name>Ryoubo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old woman in http://anidb.net/ch26018 [Guri] working as Housemother at http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home]. She is taking care of the http://anidb.net/ch26156 [Young Feathers], with http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki] being her assistant.</description>
<picture>61418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5099" picture="29011.jpg">Takeguchi Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14488" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<rating votes="4">8.37</rating>
<name>Washi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"washi" simply means "speaker" and he is a very important character intended to be the intermediate between the haibane and the togas.</description>
<picture>4168.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14489" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<name>Tokeiya no Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Clockmaker is an old man who owns a shop in the clock tower of the town of http://anidb.net/ch26018 [Guri]. http://anidb.net/ch14480 [Kana] works as his apprentice; he is strict with Kana because he sees potential in her. Kana addresses him as oyakata (親方 =master).</description>
<picture>61464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14490" type="appears in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="4">4.56</rating>
<name>Cafe Master</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2978" picture="23607.jpg">Katougi Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14491" type="appears in" update="2010-03-20">
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<name>Sumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14492" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="7">5.31</rating>
<name>Hyouko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Prominent member of the second, co-ed group of Haibane in http://anidb.net/ch26018 [Guri] (who live at the http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory] "nest"). Was a friend of http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki] in the past.
His name Hyouko probably is written "雹湖" in kanji (with "雹" = "hyou" = "hail", i. e. falling ice balls, and "湖" = "ko" = "lake") as he explains during episode 7 when Rakka mistakes his name for "hiyoko" ("雛" = "chicken", not exactly the way a rough young male likes to be addressed).
Five years ago Hyouko tried to help Reki climb over the wall of the town of Guri; he fell down a ladder in the process and was severely injured. Both he and Reki were enjoined from visiting the other`s nest because of this incident.</description>
<picture>44937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14493" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="4">5.98</rating>
<name>Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Haibane from http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory], and a close friend of http://anidb.net/ch14492 [Hyouko]. Has an ongoing grudge against http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki] for her past endangerment of Hyouko, but is willing to talk with http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] and others.</description>
<picture>44936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3294" picture="223278.jpg">Mizuno Manabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14494" type="appears in" update="2010-12-28">
<rating votes="6">8.36</rating>
<name>Kuramori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Haibane who cared for the young http://anidb.net/ch26153 [Nemu] and http://anidb.net/ch26151 [Reki]. Despite her delicate health, she was kind and helpful to them.
Especially to Reki, as she collected the herbs required for the dye to hide Reki`s black wings even though she collapsed in her way back to http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home].</description>
<picture>44934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26002" type="appears in" update="2010-12-25">
<rating votes="7">8.24</rating>
<name>Furugiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Old-Clothes Dealer is a young man living in the town of Guri. The Haibane (who can`t use new goods) get their clothing from his shop (which shows a "Haibane Renmei" sign next to its door), in exchange for a page of their notebook.
Despite lamenting most of the time he`s a nice guy and gives Haibane in need a "special service". He`s particular fond of http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] and acts as her support when possible.</description>
<picture>61414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2406" picture="83146.jpg">Kuriyama Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26003" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Shinshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old Gentleman. He helps http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] who has fallen in the street.</description>
<picture>61415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="318" picture="69041.jpg">Iijima Hajime</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26004" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<name>Panya Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Bakery Shopkeeper who runs an old bakery in the town of Guri together with http://anidb.net/ch26014 [his wife], and as such http://anidb.net/ch14486 [Hikari]`s employer.</description>
<picture>61416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42110" picture="25419.jpg">Fujiwara Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26005" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<name>Panya Juugyouin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The employee at the http://anidb.net/ch26004 [bakery] of the town of Guri.</description>
<picture>61417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2406" picture="83146.jpg">Kuriyama Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26011" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Old Home</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Old Home apparently has been used as a kind of boarding school a long time ago; now it serves as "nest" for a group of Haibane. There are other such locations in the town of Guri, one of them being the http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory].
At the beginning of this story, five older Haibane are living at Old Home, with the newcomer http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] being the sixth "companion" there. There`s also group of young Haibane called "Young Feathers" living there who are taken care of by the oldest Haibane http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki] and the only human at Old Home, the old http://anidb.net/ch14487 [Housemother].</description>
<picture>61434.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26012" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<name>Haikoujou</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of the "nests" in the town of http://anidb.net/ch26018 [Guri] where Haibane are living, the Abandoned Factory (located on the opposite side of town from http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home]) is known for its inhabitants being a bit rough and unrefined.
As this isn`t the proper place for children, the younger Haibane from here are taken care of at Old Home and only visit the factory a few times a year.</description>
<picture>61424.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26014" type="appears in" update="2010-12-29">
<name>Baker`s Wife</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The http://anidb.net/ch26004 [baker`s] wife.
(She does have three dialog lines but isn`t listed in the official credits.)</description>
<picture>61429.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26015" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<name>Bakery</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The oldest bakery of the town of Guri, run by the http://anidb.net/ch26004 [baker] and http://anidb.net/ch26014 [his wife], and employing (at least) one http://anidb.net/ch26005 [human worker] plus one http://anidb.net/ch14486 [Haibane]. This is one of the few places in Guri where Haibane can work for their living.</description>
<picture>61431.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26016" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<name>Library Boss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A superior of http://anidb.net/ch14484 [Nemu] in the library.
(He does have one dialog line when http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] reports Nemu`s illness to him but isn`t listed in the official credits.)</description>
<picture>61432.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26017" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<name>Toshokan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The library of Guri, the place where http://anidb.net/ch14484 [Nemu] works together with her senpai http://anidb.net/ch14491 [Sumika].
http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] works there for a while as well, ending up contributing to the "Beginning of the World".</description>
<picture>61433.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26018" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Guri</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The town of Guri is inhabited mostly by humans but also by a small number of "nests" for humanoid beings with wings on their back, called "Haibane" (灰羽 = Ashen Wings).
The town is surrounded by a huge wall, and none of the inhabitants may leave the town or even know what`s outside. Only the Touga, humans hiding behind masks, occasionally visit the town from outside in order to trade goods but they`re not allowed to speak inside the town, and the only one able to communicate with them (through hand signs) is the leader of the Haibane Renmei, the http://anidb.net/ch14488 [Washi].</description>
<picture>61435.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26030" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Kyaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A customer in the used clothes shop. interrupting a conversation between the http://anidb.net/ch26002 [Old-Clothes Dealer] and http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka].</description>
<picture>61454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="589" picture="186167.jpg">Takeuchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26033" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="2">2.91</rating>
<name>Haibane Fangirl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female customer at the http://anidb.net/ch26002 [second-hand clothes shop], pestering http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] about being a lucky charm for the townspeople.
(Strangely enough no one is credited for this role even though this is a crucial scene of the story.)</description>
<picture>61460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26034" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="2">4.10</rating>
<name>Crepe Vendor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A citizen of Guri who sells crepes, and is driving away the crows.
(He has two dialog lines but no one is credited for these.)</description>
<picture>61463.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26151" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="4">8.54</rating>
<name>Reki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reki as child, back in the days when http://anidb.net/ch14494 [Kuramori] was still living in http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home].</description>
<picture>61558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26153" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="1">6.83</rating>
<name>Nemu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nemu as child, back in the days when http://anidb.net/ch14494 [Kuramori] was still living in http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home].</description>
<picture>61560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26154" type="appears in" update="2011-01-02">
<rating votes="1">6.83</rating>
<name>Haikoujou no Haibane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of http://anidb.net/ch14492 [Hyouko]`s haibane friends from the http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory] (in the scene with http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki] at the bridge).</description>
<picture>61569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4728" picture="27583.jpg">Kobayashi Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26155" type="appears in" update="2010-12-28">
<rating votes="1">8.20</rating>
<name>Haikoujou no Haibane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A male Haibane of the http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory]. He welcomes his visitors http://anidb.net/ch9898 [Rakka] and http://anidb.net/ch14483 [Dai] with some fireworks.</description>
<picture>61570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2203" picture="172688.jpg">Obi Yukimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26156" type="appears in" update="2010-12-28">
<name>Nen-Shou Gumi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Young Feathers (年少組, literally "Group of Few Years") are the younger ones amongst the Haibane of http://anidb.net/ch26011 [Old Home]. Unlike the older Haibane, these kids don`t have to work for their living, and are taken care of by http://anidb.net/ch9899 [Reki] and the old http://anidb.net/ch14487 [Housemother].
As the Haibane of the http://anidb.net/ch26012 [Abandoned Factory] can`t take care of their younger ones they send them to Old Home as well, and these kids visit their home only few times a year.</description>
<picture>61571.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2990" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">繭・空を落ちる夢・オールドホーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cocoon / Dream of Falling from the Sky / Old Home</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Kokon / Der Traum, vom Himmel zu fallen / Old Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cocon - Tomber du ciel - Vieille maison</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кокон — Сон о падении с неба — Старый Дом</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kokon; Sen o spadaniu; Stary dom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayu - Sora o Ochiru Yume - Old Home</title>
<summary>A girl is falling from the sky, head down; yet she isn`t scared. A bird tries to hold her with his beak; she calmly tells him that this is of no use. Then suddenly, the clouds open and she can see the ground getting nearer... Finally, the girl awakes from this strange dream, finding herself in a new world where she has to face a lot of questions and some uncomfortable experiences, ending up with her getting two gray wings on her aching back, a halo, and a name.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3847" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寺院・話師・パンケーキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Temple / Communicator / Pancakes</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tempel / Washi / Donuts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Temple - Communicateur - Crêpes</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Храм — Переговорщик — Булочки</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Świątynia; Łącznik; Bułeczki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiin - Washi - Pancake</title>
<summary>After trying to pick up Reki for lunch, Rakka has to go to the temple of the Haibane Renmei; Hikari accompanies her to return the halo mold. Rakka learns that a good Haibane has to find a job, so she starts by helping Reki with the little kids at school. Later, Rakka volunteers to buy pancake as snack after lunch, and "little senpai" Kuu guides her to visit Hikari at work in the bakery.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3848" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">街と壁・トーガ・灰羽連盟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Town and Wall / Toga / Haibane Renmei</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Stadt und ihre Mauer / Die Tooga / Der Haibane-Verband</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ville et mur - Toga - Haibane Renmei</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Город и стена — Плащи — Союз Серокрылых</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Miasto i mur; Toga; Haibane renmei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Machi to Kabe - Tooga - Haibane Renmei</title>
<summary>Everyday life is about to start for the new Haibane Rakka. She learns about the human city of Guri, the wall that surrounds it (which Haibane must stay away from), the Haibane Renmei (who take care about the Haibane`s life and problems), and about other things - such as how to put on a dress or sleep at night when you have wings on your back.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4260" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneak Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4481" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴミの日・時計塔・壁を越える鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trash Day / Clock Tower / Birds Flying over the Walls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tag des Mülls / Glockenturm / Vögel, die über die Mauer fliegen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jour des poubelles - Horloge - Vol au-dessus des murs</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">День мусора — Часовая башня — Птицы, которые летают за стену</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dzień wyrzucania śmieci; Wieża zegarowa; Ptaki przelatujące nad murem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomi no Hi - Tokeitou - Kabe o Koeru Tori</title>
<summary>Today it`s the energetic Kana whom Rakka visits at work as apprentice in the town`s clock tower. Still disturbed from her dream about a crow, Rakka learns a number of things, such as why Kana chose this job and why she doesn`t want to feed the crows - but not what`s beyond the wall, as even the clock tower in the center of the town isn`t high enough for that. And why can Rakka remember how to ride a bicycle but not a single one of the songs she used to sing?</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4482" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">図書館・廃工場・世界のはじまり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Library / Abandoned Factory / The Beginning of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Bibliothek / Die alte Fabrik / Der Anfang der Welt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bibliothèque - Usine abandonnée - Début du monde</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Библиотека — Заброшенная фабрика — Рождение мира</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Biblioteka; Opuszczona fabryka; Początki świata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshokan - Haikoujou - Sekai no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Finally, Rakka is helping Nemu and her superior Sumika at the library. She learns that there are other Haibane living in Guri and how Reki had contact with them a long time ago. At night, Rakka is asking herself even more questions; her joint secret with Nemu won`t actually answer much of these. And like others did before, she is looking for the "Beginning of the World".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4545" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の終わり・雨・喪失</title>
<title xml:lang="en">End of Summer / Rain / Loss</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sommerende / Regen / Verlust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fin de l`été - Pluie - Perle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Конец лета — Дождь — Утрата</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Koniec lata; Deszcz; Strata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Owari - Ame - Soushitsu</title>
<summary>Wishing to no longer be dependent on the guest room, Rakka is looking for her own room at Old Home. Winter is close, so Kuu gives Rakka an overcoat that has always been too large for her to wear it, and a hint where to find the most suitable room for her. They both missed breakfast, so Reki provides them with lunch packets. Then a storm arises, and in the dangerous Western Woods a mysterious light ascends into the sky.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4589" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷跡・病・冬の到来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scar / Illness / Arrival of Winter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Narbe / Krankheit / Wintereinbruch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cicatrice - Maladie - Hiver</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Шрам — Болезнь — Приход зимы</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Blizna; Choroba; Nadejście zimy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuato - Yamai - Fuyu no Tourai</title>
<summary>While everyone else lives on as if nothing happened, Rakka can`t forget her friend whose room she regularly cleans like her own. So she avoids the other Haibane and even eats out alone. At town, Hyouko asks her about the light from the forest and whether it was Reki who departed; the mood she is in, Rakka can`t just stand this boy being glad. Anyway, Rakka has a new problem to worry about: Her wings. But this brings her an ally who knows this issue only too well.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4645" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bird</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vögel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`oiseau</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Птица</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kruk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tori</title>
<summary>Rakka is drowning in doubts and questions even though Reki is doing the best she can to help her. But two incidents, at the thrift shop and in the streets of Guri, drive Rakka away from her friends, towards the place she was told not to go. Finally she is forced to remember what she had forgotten - but given her location, will this be of any use now?</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4711" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">井戸・再生・謎掛け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Well / Rebirth / Riddle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Brunnen / Renaissance / Rätsel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Puits - Renaissance - Énigme</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Колодец — Возвращение к жизни — Загадка</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Studnia; Odrodzenie; Zagadka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ido - Saisei - Nazo Kake</title>
<summary>While the other Haibane search for Rakka in the snow of the night, the girl finds a helping hand from an unexpected side once again. Even after having been freed from the well and understanding the meaning of her dream, there is still a riddle to be solved before she can find forgiveness for her sin. But first of all, she has to pay the price for having touched the wall.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5168" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラモリ・廃工場の灰羽達・ラッカの仕事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuramori / Haibane of Abandoned Factory / Rakka`s Job</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kuramori / Die Haibane aus der Fabrik / Rakkas Arbeit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kanamori - Haibane de l`usine - Travail de Rakka</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Курамори — Серокрылые с заброшенной фабрики — Работа Ракки</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kuramori; Haibane z opuszczonej fabryki; Praca Rakki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuramori - Haikoujou no Haibane-tachi - Rakka no Shigoto</title>
<summary>Rakka is very ill after her forest adventure; Reki can do nothing but wait, remembering the time when Kuramori took care of her. When Rakka`s fever doesn`t go down, Reki chases to the temple, receiving answers to questions she didn`t even ask. Even the Haibane of the Abandoned Factory care about the "girl with the weird hair", and Midori delivers Hyouko`s present. Finally Rakka is ordered to the temple to receive her punishment for touching the wall.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5169" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別離・心の闇・かけがえのないもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Parting / Darkness in the Heart / Irreplaceable Thing</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschied / Die Dunkelheit im Herzen / Unentbehrliches</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Séparation - Ténèbres du cœur - Chose irremplaçable</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Разлука — Тьма в сердце — То, что ничем не заменишь</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Rozstanie; Mrok w sercu; To co niezastąpione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Betsuri - Kokoro no Yami - Kakegae no Nai Mono</title>
<summary>A Young Feather by the name of Dai has to return to the Abandoned Factory; Rakka accompanies him there. But neither Midori nor Reki are willing to tell her what happened to separate these two groups of Haibane that once used to be friends. After her work in the temple, Washi tells Rakka that Reki is waiting for her. And when Rakka visits the library to report that Nemu has caught a cold, Sumika shows her an ancient petrified book with strange, unknown symbols... which Rakka has seen before.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5253" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鈴の実・過ぎ越しの祭り・融和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bell Nuts / Passing of the Year Festival / Reconciliation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Glockennüsse / Jahresfest / Versöhnung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Noix - Festival du Nouvel An - Réconciliation</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Орешки-колокольчики — Фестиваль проводов года — Примирение</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Orzechowe dzwoneczki; Nowy Rok; Pojednanie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzu no Mi - Sugikoshi no Matsuri - Yuuwa</title>
<summary>The End Of Year Festival is near. Reki gives Hyouko a white bell nut, and Rakka finally learns what happened at the wall five years ago. Inside the temple Rakka hears a familiar voice and suddenly understands the meaning of these mysterious symbols. Washi gives her two precious wooden boxes, and what`s more: her true name and identity. Everyone enjoys the festival except for Reki who stays at Old Home. But Rakka won`t give up easily.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="5277" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="35">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レキの世界・祈り・終章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reki`s World / Prayer / Epilogue</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rekis Universum / Gebet / Epilog</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Monde de Reki - Prière - Épilogue</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мир Рэки — Молитва — Последняя глава</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Świat Reki; Prośba; Epilog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reki no Sekai - Inori - Shuushou</title>
<summary>After the festival everyone went to sleep, so it`s time for Reki to make her final decision. Rakka is shocked by the revelation and successfully expelled from the dark room. The final battle will be fought with a piece of paper, an open window, a book, and a faint memory from the cocoon. Will the stone be torn apart when the light arrives?</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22851" update="2012-02-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34304" update="2010-09-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2002-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34305" update="2010-09-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2002-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34306" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51363" update="2014-11-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Image Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111375" update="2009-11-12">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Commercial 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111376" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Creators` Interview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
