<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2714" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-01-25</startdate>
<enddate>2002-01-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Digital Juice</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mix Juice</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Дигитальный сок</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Цифровой Сок</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Skaitmeninės Sultys</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">デジタルジュース</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="713" approval="10" total="11">Manie-Manie: Meikyuu Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="2972" approval="8" total="8">Genius Party</anime>
<anime id="10896" approval="5" total="5">Nihon Anima(tor) Mihon`ichi</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.studio4c.co.jp/works/digitaljuice/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1461" type="Direction">Andou Hiroaki</name>
<name id="1657" type="Direction">Kobayashi Osamu</name>
<name id="5760" type="Direction">Ohara Hidekazu</name>
<name id="10917" type="Direction">Tanaka Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="14013" type="Direction">Yaginuma Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="5760" type="Character Design">Ohara Hidekazu</name>
<name id="276" type="Character Design">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="276" type="Direction">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="47300" type="Music">Kicell</name>
<name id="738" type="Animation Work">Studio 4C</name>
</creators>
<description>* Six artists active in the areas of animation, commercials, comic books, video games, and cinema were invited to serve as directors of this collection of short animated films. This omnibus DVD contains an unadulterated "100% condensed juice", incorporating the most innovative technology and an edgy sensibility.
KEIKAKU (2`08") — http://anidb.net/cr5760 [Ohara Hidekazu]
Ohara Hidekazu is known for his unique animations in commercials for products such as CC Lemon and Qoo bottled water. The intense action of this film takes place in a town in the Muromachi era. The beauty of his style, from the timing of the action to the patterns on the costumes (kimono), is worthy of note.
Chicken`s Insurance (3`24") — http://anidb.net/cr1461 [Andou Hiroaki]
This original work by Andou Hiroaki, a major production of http://anidb.net/cr738 [Studio 4°C], makes use of CGI direction. This confident use of computer graphics breaks through existing frameworks of animation in a variety of ways, and presents animation supposedly produced by chickens.
TOJIN KIT (2`09") — http://anidb.net/cr10917 [Tanaka Tatsuyuki]
This is the preview footage for the first original work by Tanaka Tatsuyuki, who has been involved in original drawing, continuity, story boards, and character design for a number of animated films. The unique world portrayed in the comic book version of this story comes to life in animated form.
In the Evening of a Moonlight Night (2`35") — http://anidb.net/cr14013 [Yaginuma Kazuyoshi]
This is the first original work by Yaginuma Kazuyoshi, who has been in charge of countless original drawings for animated films and who has also worked as a computer graphics animator. Superb colour and sound effects add much to this tale of a girl and two boys
Table &amp; Fishman (5`18") — http://anidb.net/cr1657 [Kobayashi Osamu]
The moment they encounter an infinity symbol, the two characters, Jack and Stefany, find themselves racing rapidly into the infinite in this love story by Kobayashi Osamu, who has worked in illustration and design in areas such as commercials, video games, and animated films.
The Saloon in the Air (4`26") — http://anidb.net/cr276 [Morimoto Kouji]
These are experimental images that Morimoto Kouji created in 3D using live action footage. The setting is a saloon that floats in the sky. The events that unfold one evening as bizarre characters gather in the saloon are recounted from the point of view of the main character, Wine-chan.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="628">3.32</permanent>
<temporary count="629">5.63</temporary>
<review count="1">4.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>3690.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4511</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1105</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3684</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/pages/08.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/en/pages/08.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kojimorimoto.net/fr/video.php?id=dimension_loop#video1</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2890" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>foot fetish</name>
<description>Anime contains scenes which revolve around foot-fetishism.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35823" type="main character in" update="2011-08-21">
<name>Chicken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Chicken Insurance salesman, selling insurance for the soul.</description>
<picture>47617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35870" type="main character in" update="2011-08-21">
<name>Fishman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fishman is the grotesque form Jack is reduced to after his epic rock-paper-scissors duel with the Mini Prince.</description>
<picture>48168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35871" type="main character in" update="2011-08-21">
<name>Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jack is the hero of the story, a rough-and-ready gambler and bandit, out to take down the Lord of the Bugs. In the end, he fights a one-time, winner-takes-all duel with the Mini Prince.</description>
<picture>48167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35872" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<name>Mini Prince</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A strange little creature who comes out for the final duel with Jack.</description>
<picture>48175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35873" type="main character in" update="2011-08-21">
<name>Stefany</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stefany joins Jack on his quest after being held up by him at gun point -- penniless and with nothing of value, all she has to offer him is a kiss and her love.</description>
<picture>48173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35874" type="main character in" update="2011-08-21">
<name>Table</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="25644" update="2008-02-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">圭角</title>
<title xml:lang="en">KEIKAKU</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46713" update="2008-09-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元ループ(SOSﾚｽｷｭｰﾊﾞｰｼﾞｮﾝ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dimension Loop: S.O.S Rescue Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen Loop: S.O.S Rescue Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88316" update="2015-04-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月夜の晩に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Evening of a Moonlit Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukiyo no Ban ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88317" update="2015-04-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">table &amp; fishman</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Table and Fishman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Table and Fishman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88318" update="2015-04-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空中居酒屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saloon in the Air</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuchuu Izakaya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88319" update="2015-04-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陶人キット 予告編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TOJIN KIT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujin Kit Yokokuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88320" update="2015-04-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チキン保険に加入ください</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chicken`s Insurance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chicken Hoken ni Kanyuu Kudasai</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
