<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2733" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2005-10-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tsubasa Chronicle</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Chronicle of the Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Хроника Крыльев (сезон первый)</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">رحلة الأجنحة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tsubasa Chronicles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tsubasa Reservoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tsubasa Reservoir Chronicles</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">cotw</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">trc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Tsubasa</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ツバサ・クロニクル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tsubasa: RESERVoir CHRoNiCLE</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Tsubasa Chronicle (1. Staffel)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Tsubasa Chronicle</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Tsubasa, Las Crónicas de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Tsubasa Chronicle</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Tsubasa: As Crónicas de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Tsubasa Reservoir Chronicles</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">สึบาสะ สงครามเทพข้ามมิติ</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="official">TSUBASA - RESERVoire CHRoNiCLE</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Tsubasa</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4046" type="Sequel">Tsubasa Chronicle Dai 2 Series</anime>
<anime id="4032" type="Same Setting">xxxHOLiC</anime>
<anime id="102" type="Alternative Setting">Cardcaptor Sakura</anime>
<anime id="127" type="Alternative Setting">Magic Knight Rayearth</anime>
<anime id="170" type="Alternative Setting">Kidou Tenshi Angelic Layer</anime>
<anime id="6258" type="Alternative Setting">Kobato.</anime>
<anime id="30" type="Alternative Setting">X (2001)</anime>
<anime id="465" type="Alternative Setting">RG Veda</anime>
<anime id="841" type="Alternative Setting">Clamp Gakuen Tanteidan</anime>
<anime id="2534" type="Alternative Setting">Wish</anime>
<anime id="2893" type="Alternative Setting">Clover</anime>
<anime id="12" type="Alternative Setting">Chobits</anime>
<anime id="457" type="Alternative Setting">Tokyo Babylon</anime>
<anime id="451" type="Alternative Setting">Fushigi no Kuni no Miyuki-chan</anime>
<anime id="429" type="Alternative Setting">X</anime>
<anime id="423" type="Alternative Setting">Rayearth</anime>
<anime id="3317" type="Side Story">Gekijouban Tsubasa Chronicle: Tori Kago no Kuni no Himegimi</anime>
<anime id="4514" type="Other">Clamp in Wonderland 2 1995-2006</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6288" approval="5" total="11">Pandora Hearts</anime>
<anime id="556" approval="2" total="3">Shinpi no Sekai El-Hazard TV</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="448549">A collaboration of CLAMP characters intertwining in an elaborate plot of lost romance, forged friendships, hidden secrets, and the truth of inner strength. Follows the manga to an abrupt end, however none the less worth watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313575">Good action adventure shounen with really nice plot. Highly recommended.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/tsubasa/</url>
<creators>
<name id="749" type="Animation Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="691" type="Direction">Mashimo Kouichi</name>
<name id="3580" type="Series Composition">Kawase Toshifumi</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the http://anidb.net/cr747 [Clamp] manga Tsubasa: RESERVoir CHRoNiCLE.
Sakura, a princess from the Clow Kingdom, lost her memory due to a strange incident that happened within an archaeological dig in her home country. In order to regain her memory, Yukito, the Kingdom`s mage, sent her childhood best friend, Syaoran, to seek help from the witch, Yuuko. Yuuko tells Syaoran that he has to travel from one alternate reality to another to collect fragments of Sakura`s memory. However, even if Sakura regains her memory, she will have no recollection of Syaoran. Along the journey, Syaoran and Sakura meet Kurogane, a warrior who was exiled from his country, and Fay, a mage who wants to move from one reality to another in order to escape from his King. The four characters end up traveling together and an exciting journey through time and space begins.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5566">6.39</permanent>
<temporary count="5656">7.74</temporary>
<review count="13">6.48</review>
</ratings>
<picture>150171.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4591</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1682</identifier>
<identifier>sakpxt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/tsubasa/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tsubasa:_Reservoir_Chronicle#TV_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ツバサ・クロニクル#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>563</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322468</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7197</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4236" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-16">
<name>crossover episode</name>
<description>Usually refers to the fact that one or more characters on this title come from other separate titles — often from series by the same creator/studio. Something like a "guest star", but in a more important role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4477" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>communication with the dead</name>
<description>This character is able of some manner of communication with the dead, or at least with one dead person. This includes talking to the dead, seeing the dead, outright mediumship, or any form of unidirectional or bidirectional form of communication that ordinary characters are not generally able to achieve.
This does not apply in environments where characters are expected to be dead, or where nobody is alive to begin with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="859" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="1667">8.91</rating>
<name>Ichihara Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Being one extremely experienced in her industry, Yuuko is not foolish enough to give away her real name like Watanuki. That aside, Yuuko has served as a major catalyst for Watanuki`s transformation, acting somewhat as his mentor. She loves to drink and eat Watanuki`s wonderful cooking and dragging Watanuki on crazy outings at the drop of a hat.</description>
<picture>130737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="860" type="appears in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="513">6.44</rating>
<name>Watanuki Kimihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An orphaned boy cursed with the ability to see spirits, Watanuki entered into an agreement with Yuuko to work for her in exchange for the fulfilment of his wish - to never see spirits again. However, despite the fact that he hates his ability, Watanuki often goes out of his way to help people that he comes into contact with because of his power, even when he is not required to do so by his job. He is also very independent, because he has had to live alone for most of his life, and is an excellent cook and housekeeper.</description>
<picture>130738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="865" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="67">6.66</rating>
<name>Moro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maru and Moro are the two girls that led Watanuki into Yuuko`s shop. It isn`t stated whether they were created by Yuuko, Clow Reed, the both of them, or someone else entirely, but since they have no souls and cannot leave the shop, it can be assumed that they were created there.</description>
<picture>130741.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="866" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="67">6.66</rating>
<name>Maru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maru and Moro are the two girls that led Watanuki into Yuuko`s shop. It isn`t stated whether they were created by Yuuko, Clow Reed, the both of them, or someone else entirely, but since they have no souls and cannot leave the shop, it can be assumed that they were created there.</description>
<picture>130740.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="868" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="216">7.90</rating>
<name>Larg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While the white Mokona left to travel the worlds with the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group, the black Mokona stayed behind to act as a liaison between the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group and Yuuko. Mokona likes to be around Yuuko, drink with her and eat the meals that Watanuki has made, and mostly chirps in with Maru and Moro. Yuuko has mentioned that the Mokonas were created a very long time ago by herself and Clow Reed, in preparation for a future event - the arrival and subsequent journey of the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group - as well as to stop Fei Wong Reed`s plans and save "two futures".</description>
<picture>15187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="426" picture="44708.jpg">Kikuchi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2165" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-11-18">
<rating votes="360">8.49</rating>
<name>Chii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chii is a Chobit, a type of persocom that is far more technologically advanced than regular persocoms, and who are said to possess true machine intelligence rather than relying on the execution of pre-loaded software programs like other persocoms.</description>
<picture>43625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4555" type="appears in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="139">6.53</rating>
<name>Sumomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A miniature "mobile persocom"—the equivalent of a laptop computer. Wearing an outfit that makes her resemble a genie, she is programmed to be cute and tends to be quite hyperactive, for example leading Hideki in wakeup exercises each morning and dancing when she is in standby mode.</description>
<picture>20635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4565" type="appears in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="101">6.17</rating>
<name>Kotoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another laptop persocom like Sumomo, but she was custom-built by Yoshiyuki and has much higher specifications than Sumomo.</description>
<picture>20645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7021" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-21">
<rating votes="147">7.53</rating>
<name>Soel</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="426" picture="44708.jpg">Kikuchi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7156" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="145">8.18</rating>
<name>Shaoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kept asleep in a liquid chamber at Fei Wong Reed`s palace, with his left eye covered by an eyepatch, his hands and arms by binding spells and wearing clothes marking Fei Wong Reed`s bat symbol. In fact, this Shaoran is the original while the Shaoran at Sakura`s side is only a clone that Fei Wong Reed created. This Shaoran is of Clow Reed`s bloodline, the son of Sakura and Shaoran from another dimension (from CCS), and can thus use magic.
He gave his eye and with it half of his heart to his clone to stop Fei Wong`s plan temporarily, hoping that this action could create a true heart in the clone. Because he had given his eye Shaoran was able to witness all the events the clone did. He was depicted as a villain (it was believed that he was controlling the clone`s actions, while it was only the clone`s true nature showing) until it was discovered that the protagonist Shaoran is his clone. Now the real Shaoran is the story`s protagonist. This Shaoran is able to summon a sword, the same one used by his father and he also uses the same spells.</description>
<picture>60839.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="7157" type="main character in" update="2009-11-10">
<rating votes="164">7.08</rating>
<name>Shaoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An excellent martial artist and an aspiring archaeologist with extensive knowledge of various languages, histories, and artefacts. His right eye is blind; sometimes, in mysterious dreams, he can see out of the eye and look at a person he recognises as himself in endless mirrors. Shaoran was found in his childhood wandering the streets without a memory, before he was discovered and adopted by Fujitaka (Sakura`s father in Cardcaptor Sakura), who recently passed away, leaving his foster son to continue his great work. He obtained his sword Hien during his stay at Ooto, which he learned to use from Kurogane, and learned his fighting abilities from now-enemy Seishirou, who can also travel between worlds and says he is looking for vampires.
As a clone, he has no mind or consciousness and exists only to collect all of Sakura`s feathers and to return them to her. Of all the clones created by Fei Wong Reed, he is the closest to what Fei Wong Reed intended. Although he has no magic of his own, he does, however, possess the ability to store and use magic. After the real Shaoran was released and arrived in Tokyo to face him the clone gouged out one of Fay`s eyes in order to absorb his magical power.</description>
<picture>25462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7158" type="main character in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="195">6.72</rating>
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Princess of Clow Country. Sakura is a cheerful, selfless, and stronghearted being. She states if there was ever something that she could do, she would try her absolute best. She possesses a mysterious power, namely her "wings" that can actually change the world, though no-one understands what that means. Her wings are the manifestation of her soul, namely her heart and memories. She is targeted by Fei Wong for that very power. After losing her memories, Shaoran gave up their relationship in order to save her. Meaning, even if she regains all of her memories, the one that she would never retrieve would be the knowledge of Shaoran`s existence. She is unusually excellent at games of chance, whether it`s her mysterious power or, as Chun Hyang mentioned in the Country of Koryo, extremely lucky from being "a favourite of the gods," meaning she gets such good fortune from being one of the gods` favourite daughters. Her main goal is to find the clone of Shaoran, who has now separated from the group.</description>
<picture>60838.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7159" type="main character in" update="2009-05-23">
<rating votes="204">8.35</rating>
<name>Kurogane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rough-mannered ninja from the world of Nihon, a world based on ancient (Japan), exiled for his recklessness. He originally possessed the replica of Ginryuu, a sword, before giving it to Yuuko as price for his deal with her. He obtained a new sword in Ooto called the Souhi, and taught Shaoran the skills of sword fighting and sensing attacks from the left. In the grand scheme of the series, he is considered `Yuuko`s pawn`. Fei Wong Reed murdered Kurogane`s mother in an attempt to make a deal with him, his servitude for the return of his mother. However, this plan was thwarted by Yuuko and Tomoyo when Yuuko warns Tomoyo of this event. This warning leads to Tomoyo ending Kurogane`s mad rampage and Kurogane becoming one of her ninjas. He also acquired the Ginryuu replica from Tomoyo as the original was to be buried with his mother in place of his father`s corpse.</description>
<picture>25465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7160" type="main character in" update="2013-07-03">
<rating votes="262">7.99</rating>
<name>Fay D. Flourite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A laid-back mage from the Country of Selece. He is on the run from King Ashura (a crossover character from RG Veda), whom he put into a near-eternal slumber. Although he seems happy-go-lucky and pretends to know less than he does, there is more to him than meets the eye. His assistant in Selece, currently guarding against the awakening of Ashura, is a very organic-looking Chii (a crossover character from the series Chobits) It is also revealed that Fay created Chii according to his mother`s looks.</description>
<picture>60741.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7161" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="64">8.77</rating>
<name>Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The princess of a feudal country called Nihon who sends the ninja Kurogane on the quest that causes him to join the dimension travelers. Tomoyo is the Tsukuyomi, a powerful miko sorceress responsible for maintaining the wards of Nihon that protect the country from demons. She is also a dreamseer with the ability to see into other people`s, to enter another`s dreams, can send trans-dimensional messages through dreams and is able to see the future in her dreams. However, she gave up her dreamseer power to Yuuko as the price for bringing Kurogane, Fay, Shaoran and Mokona to Nihon. Another incarnation of her appears In Piffle World, where she retains much of her nature from Daidouji Tomoyo in Cardcaptor Sakura.</description>
<picture>60819.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7163" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="4">5.31</rating>
<name>Souma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60823.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7165" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="12">4.45</rating>
<name>Seishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious traveller from Shaoran`s past who also gained the power to travel between worlds from Yuuko. He is currently searching for the vampire twins and, like his younger brother, He is a treasure hunter, not a vampire hunter like originally believed. His abilities include summoning Oni to fight for him. He is able to perform these abilities with the help one of Sakura`s feathers, which Shaoran failed to retrieve in their encounter in Ooto country. An experienced fighter, Seishirou was also the one to teach Shaoran his kicking techniques, and apparently can kick just as well.</description>
<picture>60830.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9935" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="2">1.69</rating>
<name>Ryuu-Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The young king of the dragon tribe of the west, Ryuu-Ou reluctantly inherited the throne since his grandfather was too sick to continue ruling. He joined Yasha-Ou, Ashura, and Souma after they accidentally ended up in his kingdom, in the hopes of getting a chance to fight against Yasha-Ou, the strongest warrior in Heaven. Ryuu-Ou wields the Ryuu clan`s king`s sword Ryuuga-tou (Dragon Fang sword) that controls water and can smash rocks despite being entirely blunt. When revealed to be one of the Six Stars, he decides to stick with the others despite the risk to his clan, even though he is the only one not holding a personal grudge against Taishakuten.
He is killed by the true Ashura right after the latter awakens. His real name is Naga, having taken on the name of Ryuu-Ou when he became the leader of his tribe.
Ryuu-Ou also appears in Tsubasa -RESERVoir CHRoNiCLE- as a monster hunter (Onigari).</description>
<picture>30076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10227" type="appears in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="17">5.90</rating>
<name>Kishuu Arashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A foundling girl raised by Shintou priests at Ise Jinguu and the the Dragon of Heaven most immediately in touch with Princess Hinoto. Called the "Hidden Priestess of Ise", her specialty is sword fighting, a massive sword emerging from her left hand. Despite her cold, stoic front, Sorata falls in love with her, and ultimately she comes to reciprocate.
She also appears as a crossover character in Tsubasa Chronicle, as a retired miko married to Sorata in the Hanshin Republic, and again as a miko associated with the Tower faction in Tokyo Revelations.</description>
<picture>30666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10388" type="appears in" update="2016-06-04">
<rating votes="20">8.78</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Sorata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arisugawa Sorata is an upbeat teenager possessing considerable occult abilities, raised by the Shingon Buddhist monks of Kouyasan after being taken away from his mother at a young age. A gourmand, he was frequently in trouble at the shrine for stealing food between meals (insisting that he couldn`t wait until dinner), and is also a competent cook. It was prophesied that he would protect Kamui with his life, but that he would die for a woman; the first time he meets Arashi, he decides she will be the one. An incessantly friendly young man, he wears down the resistance of both Kamui and Arashi and worms his way into their affections, despite their initial coldness and his own unrefined Kansai dialect. He is surprisingly perceptive, being able to read both Kamui and Arashi`s thoughts from their facial expressions, and with Kamui, is able to discern that other forces besides the Dragons of Earth may be working against them.
In Tsubasa Chronicle, he appears several times as a prominent crossover character. In the first instance he appears as a history teacher married to Arashi, and acts as host to Syaoran and his companions in the Hanshin Republic as a repayment to a debt he owed to Yuko the Dimension Witch. He also appears as a Dragonfly Racer in the Piffle World, and also as one of the seven fighters in the Tower Faction in Tokyo Revelations.</description>
<picture>187385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10936" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="28">3.10</rating>
<name>Fei Wong Reed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60820.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="242" picture="238968.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="8">4.12</rating>
<name>Kyle Rondart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60826.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11877" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-14">
<rating votes="10">6.50</rating>
<name>Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Touya is the older brother of Princess Sakura and the young king of the Kingdom of Clow.
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>60827.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11878" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="6">7.15</rating>
<name>Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The kind and respectful High Priest of Clow Country and a close friend of Touya.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>60824.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11879" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="3">3.53</rating>
<name>Saitou Masayoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60825.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11880" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="14">4.56</rating>
<name>Chun Hyang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fiery young girl who dares to oppose the corrupt Ryanban, a government official, and his son. Chun Hyang`s mother was a powerful sorceress, but was unfortunately defeated by the Kiishim, a sorceress under the control of the Ryanban.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>60841.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12014" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="16">4.81</rating>
<name>Xing Huo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fei Wong`s assistant. Not much about her is known besides the fact she is Fei Wong`s assistant and was somewhat also a "failed creation".</description>
<picture>60833.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12490" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="12">5.76</rating>
<name>Emeraude</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emeraude is the current pillar (and princess) of Cephiro. Little else is revealed concerning her nature until the climax of the first series, although she is highly loved by her subjects.
The Pillar of Cephiro must spend every waking moment of their existence praying for Cephiro`s benefit.
It is revealed that she was once a noblewoman of Cephiro, and had later used her power as the Pillar to prevent her younger brother Ferio from being punished for stealing something from her. He had forgotten she was his sister because, at his own request, she had used her magic to help him forget about her so he would not miss her or feel sorrow, and asked that she in turn forget him, so that she could focus her thoughts and prayers only on Cephiro.</description>
<picture>37735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12494" type="appears in" update="2009-10-23">
<rating votes="16">5.01</rating>
<name>Primera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Primera is a fairy who has acted as Lantis`s guardian ever since he saved her from a monster attack. She`s very jealous and possessive of Lantis and thus harbors a deep dislike for Hikaru. From the start, Mokona likes to tease Primera, causing her to greatly dislike Mokona.
When Hikaru and Lantis start to become friendly with each other, she pops up to stop them out of jealousy, but Mokona either chases her away or eats her and later spits her out. She can use low-level healing magic when necessary.
Primera makes an appearance in Tsubasa in the Hanshin Republic and is later mentioned in the country of Piffle, by Shogo Asagi. Rather than being tiny, she is the size of a normal human.</description>
<picture>37681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12511" type="appears in" update="2009-10-24">
<rating votes="6">7.43</rating>
<name>Caldina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caldina is a dancer who speaks with an Osaka accent (which is translated as a deep Southern accent in the English dub, due to the translations including words like "y`all"), wears extremely skimpy clothing, and has an endless passion for money (several notable similarities to Naga from Slayers).
Zagato hires her as an assassin after his other minions fail; in addition to her dancing skills, she is an accomplished illusionist and hypnotist.
In the anime she has great affection for Ascot, whom she treats as a naive younger brother, and she joins him in deserting Zagato.
It is revealed in the second manga series that she is native to Chizeta.
It`s also been shown that Caldina is incredibly good at cards and other games of chance. Romantically, Caldina becomes involved with Lafarga in both versions of the series.
Caldina also appears in Tsubasa -RESERVoir CHRoNiCLE- as a bartender.</description>
<picture>37702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25402" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-07">
<rating votes="14">5.06</rating>
<name>Nekoi Yuzuriha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nekoi Yuzuriha is a 14-year old schoolgirl descended from the keepers of the Mitsumine Shrine, masters of Inugami, dog spirits. She is attended by her own personal Inugami, Inuki, who is invisible to any but others with occult powers. Energetic and kind, she is able to defuse many of the latent tensions among the Dragons of Heaven and especially between them and Kamui. Before she comes to Tokyo no one outside of her immediate family is able to see Inuki, but when she gets there the first person who sees him is the Dragon of Earth Shiyuu Kusanagi, and she falls in love with him.
In combat she makes use of Inuki, who can attack with great speed, and can additionally transform himself into a sword which Yuzuriha can use. Her barrier field has the shape of a cylinder.
Yuzuriha also appears in Tsubasa Chronicle, first as a player in the virtual reality world of Edonis paired with Kusanagi, and again in Tokyo Revelations as a fighter with the Tower faction.</description>
<picture>59996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25403" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-04">
<rating votes="11">7.28</rating>
<name>Shiyuu Kusanagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiyuu Kusanagi is a soldier in the Japanese Self-Defence Forces who is telepathically linked to the plants and animals of the Earth, and thus strongly resents humanity`s destruction and pollution of the natural world. Although he is one of the Dragons of Earth, unlike his compatriots he believes all life is sacred and is opposed to its wanton destruction. He is the first person outside of Yuzuriha`s family to see her normally invisible dog Inuki, and as such she falls in love with him. He does not seem to reciprocate completely, but nevertheless is very protective of her, saving her several times from death at the hands of the other Dragons of Earth.
He also appears twice in Tsubasa Chronicle, first as a virtual reality player in Edonis country paired with Yuzuriha and again in Tokyo Revelations as part of the City Hall faction.</description>
<picture>187394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5300" picture="29409.jpg">Ishimoda Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36721" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="5">4.08</rating>
<name>Asagi Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A guy who fights with his gang for a bridge agains Mohicans in the town where Masayoshi lives.</description>
<picture>60821.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36722" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="4">2.10</rating>
<name>Kani Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A guy who fight with his gang for a bridge against Shougo`s gang in the town where Masayoshi lives.</description>
<picture>60835.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36723" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<name>Teshita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Mohican Team.</description>
<picture>55465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36724" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Touya in the first world. He works togerher with Yukito in Hoshizuki restaurant.</description>
<picture>55481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36725" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Yukito in the first world. He works togerher with Touya in Hoshizuki restaurant.</description>
<picture>55483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36728" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Shin`eitai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Fans and guardians of Primera.</description>
<picture>55514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="4728" picture="27583.jpg">Kobayashi Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36729" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="2">4.67</rating>
<name>Chun Hyang no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chun Hyang`s mother.</description>
<picture>60840.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36730" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="2">1.71</rating>
<name>Ryoushu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The lord of Nayutaya country.</description>
<picture>60842.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36731" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="2">1.71</rating>
<name>Ryoushu no Musuko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of the lord of Nayutaya country.</description>
<picture>60843.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36802" type="appears in" update="2011-09-22">
<rating votes="1">5.04</rating>
<name>Sorata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Sorata in the second world, Nayutaya.</description>
<picture>56349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36803" type="appears in" update="2011-09-22">
<rating votes="4">5.71</rating>
<name>Arashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Arashi in the second world, Nayutaya.</description>
<picture>56370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36804" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="3">6.29</rating>
<name>Kyishim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A witch who is captived inside the castle by Lord.</description>
<picture>60831.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36910" type="appears in" update="2011-09-22">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Mitteishuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Secrets agents who control feudal lords in the Nayutaya country.
The group consists of:
Imonoyama Nokoru (妹之山残) who is originally from Clamp Gakuen Tanteidan series and appeard also in X movie.
Takamura Suou (鷹村蘇芳) who is originally from Clamp Gakuen Tanteidan series and appeard also in X movie.
Ijuuin Akira (伊集院玲) who is originally from 20 Mensou ni Onegai (20面相におねがい!!) manga and appeared also in Clamp Gakuen Tanteidan series and in X movie.</description>
<picture>58233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="396" picture="151685.jpg">Nakagawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36911" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="4">9.16</rating>
<name>Sakura no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura`s father.</description>
<picture>60828.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3272" picture="172136.jpg">Mizushima Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36912" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="2">5.88</rating>
<name>Fujitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shaoran`s adoptive father.</description>
<picture>60837.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36913" type="appears in" update="2011-09-22">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kai Gyo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monstrous fish from third country, Kiri country (霧の国), Shaoran and others visited.</description>
<picture>58264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37718" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="5">4.77</rating>
<name>Grosum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mr. Grosum owns most of the land in the town.</description>
<picture>60822.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37719" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<name>Chouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayor of the town.</description>
<picture>68606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20255" picture="52681.jpg">Shinohara Daisaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37720" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<name>Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owner of the bar in the town.</description>
<picture>68607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3125" picture="24097.jpg">Mitsuo Senda</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37721" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="2">1.53</rating>
<name>Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36755">Nakano Chikayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37722" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Wakamono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young man (wakamono) from the town, probably the leader.</description>
<picture>68631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37723" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kiifa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who wants to win the tournament.</description>
<picture>68641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37724" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="2">4.22</rating>
<name>Sharume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with a curse.</description>
<picture>68643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37725" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="2">2.67</rating>
<name>Suguyaru Ka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Express Department.</description>
<picture>68755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2253" picture="172548.jpg">Kanda Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37726" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kangeisuru Ka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Welcome Department.</description>
<picture>68757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20418" picture="53724.jpg">Toudou Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37729" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Erii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The informant of the city.</description>
<picture>60832.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="7008" picture="240891.jpg">Hayashi Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37747" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="4">5.83</rating>
<name>Souma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Souma in Edonis Country.</description>
<picture>60829.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37756" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="2">4.67</rating>
<name>Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Touya in Edonis Country. He visited Cat`s Eye cafe with Yukito.</description>
<picture>69115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37758" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Yukito in Edonis Country. He visited Cat`s Eye cafe with Touya.</description>
<picture>69116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37759" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<name>Kani Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Kani Otto in Edonis Country. He is a mover who brought the piano to the cafe with his crew.</description>
<picture>69123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37760" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Sang Yung</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The version of Saitou Masayoshi in Edonis country. He works in a shop where swords are sold.</description>
<picture>69128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37761" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Rou Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Old shopkeeper (rou tenshu) who sells swords.</description>
<picture>69133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37762" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="5">4.39</rating>
<name>Oruha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oruha is a singer in Clover.</description>
<picture>60834.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37769" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="2">8.22</rating>
<name>Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Manager of Fairy Park.</description>
<picture>60836.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37770" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Old woman (rouba) from the last country they visited in Tsubasa Chronicle.</description>
<picture>69262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3608" picture="24899.jpg">Maeda Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37771" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Shinzou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The voice of God in temple.</description>
<picture>69263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="688" picture="18295.jpg">Tanaka Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37772" type="appears in" update="2011-10-15">
<name>Mago</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandson of the old woman.</description>
<picture>69264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="33335" update="2019-08-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="34">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">必然のデアイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destinies Converge</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine unvermeidliche Begegnung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`inévitable rencontre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การพบพานภายใต้พรหมลิขิต</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitsuzen no Deai</title>
<summary>When Syaoran returns to his home for a change of clothes after studying the ruins, he meets his dearest and closest childhood friend Sakura, the princess of Clow Kingdom. She convinces him to stay longer, and the two wander the town shopping together. At the end of their excursion, she attempts to confess her love for him, but is interrupted and forced to return to the castle. When Syaoran returns to the ruins, he is surprised to find Sakura there. A mysterious force begins to draw her into the wall and causes her memories to manifest themselves in the form of feathers. When he pulls her to safety, her memories scatter across the dimensions. The priest Yukito tells him to seek out the help of the Dimensional Witch and sends the two to the dimension in which she resides. Upon arriving there, two others soon follow: Kurogane who is exiled from his dimension for killing excessively and Fai D. Flourite who is running away from the king of his dimension.
Source: Wikipedia.org</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="33336" update="2019-08-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="22">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦うチカラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power to Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kraft zu Kämpfen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force de combattre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">พลังในการต่อสู้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakau Chikara</title>
<summary>Transported to the modern day Japan, Syaoran, Kurogane, and Fai ask the Dimensional Witch, Yuuko Ichihara, to grant their wishes. Syaoran wishes to travel to many worlds to restore Sakura`s memories. Kurogane wishes to return to his own world. Fai wishes to travel to a world that is not his own so as to avoid meeting his king. Yuuko tells them that although their intentions are different, their wishes are the same. In order to have their wish granted, each must pay a price. She asks Syaoran to pay with his relationship with Sakura which would result in Sakura losing her memories of Syaoran, Kurogane to pay with his sword Ginryuu, and Fai to pay with the tattoo on his back. Though hesitant, each pays their respective price, and in return she gives the group a white creature named Mokona Modoki who holds the power to cross to random dimensions. The group sets off to another dimension where a gang war is about to commence between two groups led by Kanio and Shougo respectively who use a power called Kudan that can manifest itself as a familiar. A boy named Masayoshi finds them and brings them to safety. When Fai gives Syaoran one of Sakura`s feather, taking it off Syaoran`s shirt, the feather is blown by a stray blast. After running into the fray to retrieve the feather, Syaoran finds that he too possesses the power Kudan and interferes with the fight.
Source: Wikipedia.org</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="33337" update="2019-08-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="18">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破魔のカタナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword of Demon Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schwert, das Dämonen besiegt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sabre du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดาบพิฆาตอสูร</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hama no Katana</title>
<summary>Sorata Arisugawa and Arashi Kishu find Syaoran, Fai, Kurogane, and Sakura (still unconscious but better) and take them to their apartment building. After some rest and less suspicious clothes, the three go around town looking for Sakura`s memory fragments. However, Kurogane spots someone who looks like Princess Tomoyo and chases after her. After losing sight of the girl as well as Syaoran and Fai, Kurogane meets the gang from before and a fight ensues.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="33338" update="2019-08-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汚れなき放浪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Innocent Wandering</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der unschuldige Vagabund</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La disparition</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การรอนแรมอันพิสุทธิ์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegarenaki Hourou</title>
<summary>Sakura is awake and is checking out the town. However, she wakes up without Syaoran, Fai, Kurogane, and Mokona knowing it until it was too late. Things get worse when the leader of the invading gang recognizes her from his encounter with Syaoran and concocts a devious scheme.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="34275" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35484" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35834" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔術師のバトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of the Mage</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Kampf der Magier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un combat de magiciens</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การต่อสู้ของพ่อมดจอมคาถา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majutsushi no Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35891" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泣かないナミダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unshed Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tränen, die man nicht weint</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le réveil de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">น้ำตาที่เก็บซ่อน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakanai Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35892" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砕けたカタミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Broken Memento</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das zerbrochene Andenken</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs flous</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ของดูต่างหน้าที่แหลกสลาย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kudaketa Katami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36167" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神の愛娘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">God`s Beloved Daughter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gottes geliebte Tochter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bénie des dieux</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ลูกรักของพระเจ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami no Manamusume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36327" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖しきオンナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess of Shadows</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die verdächtige Frau</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une femme inquiétante</title>
<title xml:lang="th">นางพญาแห่งเหล่าภูติ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayashiki Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36639" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別離のカガミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mirror of Separation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Spiegel des Abschieds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le miroir des adieux</title>
<title xml:lang="th">กระจกแห่งการอำลา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Betsuri no Kagami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36688" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選ばれたアシタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chosen Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der auserwählte Morgen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ultime combat</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อนาคตที่ถูกเลือก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erabareta Ashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36724" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暖かなエガオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Warm Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das warme Lächeln</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un sourire réconfortant</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รอยยิ้มอันอบอุ่น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atatakana Egao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37630" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まぼろしのオトギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Advocate of Illusions</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Phantom Mädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un conte de fée chimérique</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตำนานลวง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Otogi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37631" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実のレキシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Truth in History</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Geschichte der Wahrheit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révélation</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ประวัติศาสตร์ที่แท้จริง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjitsu no Rekishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37785" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じるココロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heart That Believes</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das glaubende Herz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La trahison du Dr Kyle</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จิตใจที่เชื่อมั่น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjiru Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38037" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強さと優しさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strength and Kindness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Stärke und Freundlichkeit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La malédiction des dieux</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความเข้มแข็งและ ความอ่อนโยน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyosa to Yasashisa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38242" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜の国のカフェ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demon Hunters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Café im Land der Kirschblüten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des cerisiers en fleur</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ร้านน้ำชาในดินแดนแห่งซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Kuni no Cafe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38859" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃんことワンコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cats and Dogs</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kätzchen und Hündchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entre chiens et chats</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เจ้าเหมียวกับเจ้าโฮ่ง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanko to Wanko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38860" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生きるカクゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resolution to Live</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Entschlossenheit zu Leben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force de vivre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความมุ่งมั่นที่จะมีชีวิต</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikiru Kakugo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38861" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">午後のピアノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Afternoon Piano</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Klavier am Nachmittag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Piano à l`heure du crépuscule</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เปียในยามบ่าย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gogo no Piano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39294" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼児のスガオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon`s True Face</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das wahre Gesicht der Oni</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le visage du monstre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il vero volto dell`Oni</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โฉมหน้าของอสูร</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni no Sugao</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40320" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消せないキオク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Indelible Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unauslöschliche Erinnerungen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenir ancré</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ricordi che non possono essere cancellati</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความทรงจำที่ไม่อาจลบเลือน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kesenai Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40850" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えゆくイノチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fading Life</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das schwindende Leben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et la vie s`achève</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Vite che scompaiono</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ชีวิตที่ต้องตายจาก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieyuku Inochi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41086" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘のヤイバ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blade of a Desperate Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schwert des Kampfes auf Leben und Tod</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée de feu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Mortali lame da combattimento</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คมดาบแห่งสมรภูมิเลือด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou no Yaiba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41179" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">究極のゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Game</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das letzte Spiel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin de la partie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La fine del gioco</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ฝ่าวิกฤตเกมเสี่ยงตาย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukyoku no Game</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41600" update="2011-01-13">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der letzte Wunsch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ultime vœu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`ultimo desiderio</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความปรารถนาอันสูงสุด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Negai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47733" recap="true" update="2006-03-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<title xml:lang="en">New Year Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120788" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120789" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
