<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2744" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>1983-10-10</startdate>
<enddate>1984-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fushigi no Kuni no Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Alice`s Adventures In Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Alicja w Krainie Czarów</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Alice Harikalar Diyarında</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ふしぎの国のアリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Alice in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Alice im Wunderland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Alice au pays des merveilles</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Alice nel Paese delle Meraviglie</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Alicia en el País de las Maravillas</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">أليس في بلاد العجائب</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Alice no País das Maravilhas</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Liisa Ihmemaassa</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Η Αλίκη στην Χώρα των Θαυμάτων</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">עליסה בארץ הפלאות</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Alisa - Stebuklų Šalyje</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Alice în ţara minunilor</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Аліса в Країні Чудес</title>
<title xml:lang="is" type="official">Lísa í Undralandi</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7787" type="Other">Hello Kitty no Fushigi no Kuni no Alice</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2530" approval="2" total="6">Little Nemo</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/fushiginokunino_alice.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3842" type="Direction">Sugiyama Taku</name>
<name id="4330" type="Music">Koroku Reijirou</name>
<name id="10144" type="Original Work">Lewis Carroll</name>
<name id="6202" type="Animation Character Design">Miwa Takateru</name>
<name id="6071" type="Character Design">Kumada Isamu</name>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the famous children`s novel by http://anidb.net/cr10144 [Lewis Carroll].
Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland is a rich and wonderful journey into a land of the imagination. One day on a trip to London with her mother, seven-year-old http://anidb.net/ch29855 [Alice] finds an old top-hat in a second-hand shop that is the start of her fantastic adventures.
Out of the top-hat bounds Benny Bunny, who introduces Alice to his uncle, the White Rabbit, royal herald to the Court of the Queen of Hearts. Tailing the White Rabbit across her garden, Alice finds a strange rabbit-hole into which the White Rabbit has seemingly disappeared.
With little hesitation, she jumps in after him, and finds herself falling through the tunnel that leads to the magical world of Wonderland. There, she finds unusual and illogical things, including talking flowers, a story-telling mouse, growth-inducing tea and cake, a Humpty-Dumpty in a perilous situation, a mad March Hare, a wise blue caterpillar, and a bossy Queen of Hearts. Nothing but bizarre and unpredictable things happen in Wonderland and Alice finds herself learning to handle the strange and magical events that are the everyday in this world.
Source: AnimeNfo
Note: There were 26 episodes produced for the Japanese market, however 2 episodes were not televised. Another 26 episodes were produced only for the Overseas market.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="126">3.71</permanent>
<temporary count="127">5.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>12529.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>476</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2572</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>995</identifier>
<identifier>uwbary</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nippon-animation.co.jp/work/1438/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fushigi_no_Kuni_no_Alice</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ふしぎの国のアリス_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1164</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1983/alice</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3457" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-17">
<name>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland</name>
<description>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland (often shortened to Alice in Wonderland,) is an 1865 novel written by English author Charles Lutwidge Dodgson under the pseudonym Lewis Carroll. It tells of a girl named Alice falling through a rabbit hole into a fantasy world populated by peculiar, anthropomorphic creatures. The tale plays with logic, giving the story lasting popularity with adults as well as with children. It is considered to be one of the best examples of the literary nonsense genre. Its narrative course and structure, characters and imagery have been enormously influential in both popular culture and literature, especially in the fantasy genre.
The anime or an episode features important elements of the novel. This could mean that the main character is portrayed as Alice (with another name), accompanied by somebody portraying the white rabbit (possibly as a human). While the world can be a Wonderland, it does not have to be.</description>
<picurl>169452.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29855" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3701" picture="25016.jpg">Tarako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="40884" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリスとベニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alice and Benny</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Kaninchen aus dem Hut</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lapin sorti du chapeau</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alice to Benny</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40885" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラビットホール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rabbit Hole</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Fall ins Kaninchenloch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chute dans le terrier du lapin blanc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rabbit Hole</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40886" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙の海のアリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alice in a Sea of Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tränensee</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un océan de larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida no Umi no Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40887" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コーカス・レース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Caucus-Race</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Klüngelrennen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La course de la clique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caucus-Race</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40888" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">でっかいアリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Haus des weißen Kaninchens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La maison du lapin blanc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dekkai Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40889" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハンプティダンプティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Humpty Dumpty</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Ei auf der Mauer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`œuf sur le mur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Humpty Dumpty</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40890" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きな仔犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Enormous Puppy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das große Hundebaby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le gros bébé chien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooki na Koinu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40891" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名なしの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nameless Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Wald ohne Namen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La soupe magique du lièvre de Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanashi no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40892" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41088" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カラスの海賊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crow Pirate</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die räuberischen Krähen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les corneilles de la forêt sans nom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karasu no Kaizoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41089" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャタピラの忠告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Advice From a Caterpillar</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Rat der blauen Raupe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le conseil de la chenille bleue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caterpillar no Chuukoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41126" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノッポのアリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bald Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wo sind die Taubeneier?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Où sont les œufs de pigeon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Dove Sono le Uova?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noppo no Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41134" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">びっくりベイビー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Shocking Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schweinepfeffer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un cochonnet pas comme les autres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bikkuri Baby</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41221" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディーとダムの大決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tweedledee and Tweedledum`s Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tweedledee und Tweedledum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tweedidee et Tweediediur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Twee to Dum no Daikettou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41320" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライオンVSユニコーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lion vs. the Unicorn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Löwe und das Einhorn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lion et le cicorne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lion vs Unicorn</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41679" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クイーンのクローケー大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Queen`s Croquet Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Fest der Herzkönigin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête chez la reine de cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Queen no Croquet Taikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41694" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チェシャキャット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cheshire Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Grinsekatze</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chat ricanant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cheshire Cat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41695" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カキたちの大脱走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dash of the Snails</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Befreiung der Austern</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La libération des huitres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaki-tachi no Daidassou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41696" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エビのカドリール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lobster-quadrille</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Hummertanz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La danse du homard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ebi no Quadrille</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41743" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかしなティーパーティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mad Tea-party</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Teegesellschaft des Hutmachers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un thé extravagant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashi na Tea Party</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41744" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきなサーカスランド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lovely Circus Land</title>
<title xml:lang="de">So ein Zirkus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quel cirque !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki na Circus Land</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41745" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">くいしんぼうジャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jack the Gourmand</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer hat die Törtchen gestohlen?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qui a volé les petits gâteaux ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kui Shinbou Jack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41746" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">泣きむしまがい亀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mock Turtle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die falsche Suppenschildkröte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fausse tortue à soupe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakimushi Magaikame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41817" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さか立ち大行進</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Handstand Race</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ebbe in der Schlosskasse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Disette au château</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saka-tachi Daikoushin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41818" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたベニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Benny`s Disappearance</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Benny Bunny ist verschwunden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Benny Bunny a disparu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Benny</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41819" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">グリーンランドの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Greenland</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das beleidigte Gemüse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un légume fait la moue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Greenland no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41820" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡のアリスと鏡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alice and the Looking-Glass</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Haus hinter dem Spiegel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La maison derrière le miroir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagami no Alice to Kagami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43222" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Weather Man and Weather Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wettermann und Wetterfrau</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alice et la météo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43223" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Exursion of the Heart Queen</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Ausflug der Herzkönigin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pique-nique de la dame de cœur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43224" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Many Colored Candles</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Viele bunte Bonbons</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des bonbons de toutes les couleurs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43225" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Angry Kangaroos</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die verärgerten Kängurus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La malheureuse maman kangourou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43226" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unpleasant Guest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein unangenehmer Gast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Humpty Dumpty n`est pas content</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43227" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Bill has Fallen In Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Little Bill hat sich verliebt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Little Bill est amoureux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43228" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The White Rabbit Moves</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das weiße Kaninchen zieht aus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand lapin blanc déménage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43229" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Clouds Country</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Wolkenland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des nuages</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43230" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Queen Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Königin Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La reine Alice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43231" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Sheep</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Traumschaf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mouton noir</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43232" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pearl of Wisdom</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Perle der Weisheit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La perle du savoir</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43233" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Honey Elephants</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Honigelefanten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alice et les éléphants à miel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43234" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Just the Dawsons</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ausgerechnet die Dawsons</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alice et les jumeaux terribles</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43235" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Non-Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Nicht-Geburtstag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le non-anniversaire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43236" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Washing Day</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der große Waschtag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour de la grande lessive</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43237" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Chimpanzee`s Child</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schimpansenkind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le petit chimpanzé</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43238" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic Drink</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Zaubertrunk</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le filtre d`amour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43239" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shy Duck</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das schüchterne Entlein</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La petite canne timide</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43240" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Strange Tour Operator</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine merkwürdige Reisegesellschaft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">D`étranges compagnons de vollages</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43241" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Small Flutist</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der kleine Flötenspieler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le petit joueur de flûte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43242" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Family Photo</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Familienfoto</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La photo de famille</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43243" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Balloon Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Ballonfahrt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le voyage en ballon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43244" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Benny and the Screw Mouse</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Benny und die Schraubmäuse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Benny Bunny et les souris à vis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43245" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of the Knights</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Kampf der Ritter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tournoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43246" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Wichtelmann für alle Fälle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un petit lutin à tout faire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43247" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vanished Light Fairy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die verschwundene Lichterfee</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La petite fée de lumière</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67320" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85807" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120259" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120260" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Portuguese Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120261" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">German Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
