<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2764" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-16</startdate>
<enddate>2005-04-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eiga Futari wa Precure Max Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">映画 ふたりはプリキュア Max Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Precure Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">映画 ふたりはプリキュア ー マックスハート</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">¿El final de las Pretty Cure?</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3566" type="Sequel">Eiga Futari wa Precure Max Heart 2: Yukizora no Tomodachi</anime>
<anime id="2765" type="Parent Story">Futari wa Precure Max Heart</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/movie/2008_precure5gogo/kako_movie1.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2170" type="Character Design">Tamegai Katsumi</name>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
<name id="2804" type="Direction">Shimizu Junji</name>
<name id="5778" type="Character Design">Inagami Akira</name>
<name id="4131" type="Music">Satou Naoki</name>
</creators>
<description>The Courageous Warriors of the Garden of Hope have summoned Nagisa, Honoka, and Hikari to protect their kingdom from a witch who plans to steal the Diamond Line, which is a set of jewelry the queen of the Garden of Hope wears to a ceremony every year to replenish the water of the kingdom. The witch plans to resurrect the Dark Lord and if she does so, not only will the Garden of Hope be destroyed, but other kingdoms in the galaxies, including the Garden of Rainbows and the Garden of Light.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="167">4.39</permanent>
<temporary count="171">6.21</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>28901.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2042</identifier>
<identifier>zobgir</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/movie/2005_precure/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>映画_ふたりはプリキュア_Max_Heart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2775</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321909</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7332</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6157" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="46">7.21</rating>
<name>Misumi Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misumi Nagisa is the ace of her school`s lacrosse team. Her alter ego Cure Black is the strong fighter of the Pretty Cure duo. She is quite girly, image conscious, and has a large collection of stuffed animals. Nagisa is weak in academics but makes up for it with pure spirit and energy. She also has a large appetite and loves to eat chocolate and, according to Honoka, foods with the word "yaki" in the name. She likes shopping but tends to squander her money and ends up having none when she needs it most. Nagisa has a crush on Honoka`s friend, Fujimura-senpai, also known as Fuji-pi, gets flustered whenever he is around. To her dismay, Nagisa is more popular with the girls than the boys. She has a younger brother, Ryouta, who seems to be very fond of Honoka. Aside from Honoka, Nagisa`s best friends are Shiho and Rina.</description>
<picture>23357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6158" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="47">7.63</rating>
<name>Yukishiro Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukishiro Honoka is the quiet and reserved one, but that does not keep her from having her own friends and following. She can be quite strict and domineering when the situation calls for it. Her alter ego is Cure White. Honoka is very poised and intelligent and enjoys reading. Her specialty is the science club, where she is looked up to by the others. Honoka hasn`t had many friends, but the few she has seem to be really close to her. It has also been noted that she`s relatively popular with the boys, though she seems to have little interest in them.</description>
<picture>23358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6159" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="14">2.28</rating>
<name>Mepple</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mepple is the chosen protector of the Princess of Hope. Because of this, he and Mipple have a "lovey-dovey" relationship. He tends to be a little more agitating, constantly making fun of Nagisa as they get into arguments. He is also mildly jealous of Porun and wishes Porun would act less selfish at times. However, Mepple is just as selfish, constantly eating or whining about being hungry and noting to himself that Nagisa is easy to manipulate. He resides with Nagisa and ends his sentences with "mepo". Both Mipple and Mepple can only stay in their Garden of Light forms for a short time before growing tired, so they generally take energy-saving forms resembling cellphones.</description>
<picture>23359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6160" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="8">2.03</rating>
<name>Mipple</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mipple is the Princess of Hope from the Garden of Light. She, like Honoka, is generally more reserved than her male counterpart. She`s always sticking up for Porun, though, once he comes on the scene, and that tends to cause problems between her and Mepple. She resides predominantly with Honoka and ends all her sentences with the word "mipo".</description>
<picture>23360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6161" type="main character in" update="2010-02-01">
<rating votes="57">7.23</rating>
<name>Cure Black</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2143.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6162" type="main character in" update="2010-02-01">
<rating votes="65">6.10</rating>
<name>Cure White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2144.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6304" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Fujimura Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7068" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6306" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-19">
<rating votes="9">8.49</rating>
<name>Fujita Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2979">Fujita Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7621" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="29">5.59</rating>
<name>Kujou Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujou Hikari has no fighting strength, but she can enhance the power of Cure Black and Cure White when she transforms into Shiny Luminous. She is the "Life of the Queen", having lost all of her abilities and memories from being Queen and is living as a passive human girl. She makes friends with Nagisa and Honoka.</description>
<picture>3012.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14634" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="3">7.54</rating>
<name>Porun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Porun is the Prince of the Garden of Light. He is sent to Earth after Pretty Cure gather all the prism stones. The Queen gives a cryptic statement about his powers aiding Pretty Cure. Later, when Wisdom is in trouble, Wisdom places the power of the Rainbow Stones into Porun without his knowledge. This gives him the ability to remain in his regular form as well as the ability to communicate with various people from the Garden of Light. When communicating with members of the Garden of Light, he turns into what looks like a gaming console and everyone can hear what is said and communicate openly. He also grants Pretty Cure the power of light which gives them their Rainbow Bracelets. He tends to be extremely selfish and think only of himself. He is quite childish and has a lot of energy. He can get a little annoying at times and definitely annoys Mepple. He lives predominantly with Natalie in Pretty Cure and with Hikari in Max Heart. He tends to end his sentences with "popo". He enjoys getting between Mipple and Mepple.</description>
<picture>2951.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="394" picture="17239.jpg">Ikezawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14695" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Kibou no Kuni no Joou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12577" picture="42359.jpg">Kudou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14696" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Round</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3004.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14697" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Square</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3005.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14698" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Marquis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3006.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14699" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Oval</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3007.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14700" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Heart</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3008.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="12578" picture="42363.jpg">Akae Tamao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14701" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Pear</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3009.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="431" picture="23201.jpg">Nakayama Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14702" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Triliant</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3010.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14703" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Kibou no Kuni no Ouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7068" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14704" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Hitsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14705" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-02">
<name>Yami no Sekai no Majo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14706" type="main character in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="36">5.47</rating>
<name>Shiny Luminous</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujou Hikari has no fighting strength, but she can enhance the power of Cure Black and Cure White when she transforms into Shiny Luminous. She is the "Life of the Queen", having lost all of her abilities and memories from being Queen and is living as a passive human girl. She makes friends with Nagisa and Honoka.</description>
<picture>2142.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="44727" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2005-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189197" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Theater Test Screening Event</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
