<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2775" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-05-25</startdate>
<enddate>2005-10-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">UFO Princess Valkyrie: Seireisetsu no Hanayome</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">UFO Princess Walküre 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">UFO Princess Valkyrie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">UFO Princess Walkure 3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">圆盘皇女 星灵节的新娘</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">UFO3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">円盤皇女ワるきゅーレ 星霊節の花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">UFO Ultramaiden Valkyrie 3: Bride of Celestial Souls` Day</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4375" type="Sequel">UFO Princess Valkyrie: Toki to Yume to Ginga no Utage</anime>
<anime id="1111" type="Prequel">UFO Princess Valkyrie: Juunigatsu no Yasoukyoku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tokinoyu.net/market/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="6445" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagisawa Tetsuya</name>
<name id="6242" type="Character Design">Fujii Maki</name>
<name id="1904" type="Series Composition">Tsukimura Ryoue</name>
<name id="1536" type="Direction">Takamoto Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="6517" type="Original Work">Kaishaku</name>
</creators>
<description>Raine and http://anidb.net/ch35266 [Chorus] get a house on Earth, the last three Valhalla princesses each have a story to tell, and finally when http://anidb.net/ch35247 [Kazuto] and http://anidb.net/ch35246 [Valkyrie] manage to stay in their adult form, they try to marry again.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="482">5.04</permanent>
<temporary count="486">6.95</temporary>
<review count="1">3.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>3791.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4570</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1514</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1709</identifier>
<identifier>mayjwx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tokinoyu.net/market/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>UFO_Ultramaiden_Valkyrie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>円盤皇女ワるきゅーレ_星霊節の花嫁#.E5.86.86.E7.9B.A4.E7.9A.87.E5.A5.B3.E3.83.AF.E3.82.8B.E3.81.8D.E3.82.85.E3.83.BC.E3.83.AC_.E6.98.9F.E9.9C.8A.E7.AF.80.E3.81.AE.E8.8A.B1.E5.AB.81</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322295</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7408</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3062" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-02">
<name>unidentified flying object</name>
<description>An unidentified flying object, or UFO, is in its strictest definition any apparent object in the sky that is not identifiable as a known object or phenomenon. However, the term is widely used in popular culture to refer more specifically to supposed observations of craft of extraterrestrial origin.
Most UFOs are later identified as conventional objects or phenomena (e.g., aircraft, weather balloons, clouds). Some of them are not identified, either because of lack of evidence or because no conventional explanation can be found despite extensive evidence. Some people consider the latter cases as possible observations of extraterrestrial space craft.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3679" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>engaged to an alien</name>
<description>The human protagonist in this show is engaged to an alien for some strange reason. Comedy element used to create many strange situations and misunderstandings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35246" type="main character in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="12">4.77</rating>
<name>Valkyrie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4462.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35247" type="main character in" update="2011-08-06">
<name>Tokino Kazuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4463.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35251" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4464.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35252" type="appears in" update="2011-08-06">
<name>Maru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35254" type="main character in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="4">6.08</rating>
<name>Valkyrie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4465.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35256" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="8">5.54</rating>
<name>Nanamura Akina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4466.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35260" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="7">5.46</rating>
<name>Hydra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35262" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="7">3.70</rating>
<name>Tokino Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4469.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35263" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="8">5.54</rating>
<name>Sanada-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4470.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35264" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="8">5.54</rating>
<name>Layne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2138" picture="21613.jpg">Iizuka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35265" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="8">3.93</rating>
<name>Mayim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35266" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="3">6.08</rating>
<name>Chorus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35268" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<name>Fam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35269" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<name>Inarba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35270" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Nekomimizukin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35271" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<name>Nesuthi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="37455" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女と眼鏡の関係について</title>
<title xml:lang="en">About the Relationship Between Girls and Glasses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome to Megane no Kankei ni Tsuite</title>
<summary>A mysterious new teacher just crash landed on the school, and she’s got an unusual fetish: she wants all the female students to start wearing glasses!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37456" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裁きの女神 イナルバ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inarba, the Goddess of Judgment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaki no Megami Inarva</title>
<summary>Inarba, the Princess of Judgment, arrives on the scene to punish anyone who breaks the royal rules of Valhalla. Violators beware, incurring the wrath of Inarba is your worst nightmare!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40327" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猫耳頭巾参上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Caped Catgirl Is Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nekomimizukin Sanjou</title>
<summary>Inarba and Kazuto set out in search of eleven magical stones with the power to grant them a long and happy marriage, but they better watch out for those pesky demons!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="41199" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライネ・ライネ・ライネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raine Raine Raine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raine Raine Raine</title>
<summary>Laine’s trip to the hair salon turns into a time-travelling adventure when a new massage technique brings her face to face with a younger version of herself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="41709" update="2005-09-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41801" update="2005-10-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42165" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家出皇女ワルキューレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway Princess Valkyrie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iede Oujo Warukyure</title>
<summary>Princess Valkyrie runs away from home when she’s given boring old sweet potatoes as a snack instead of delicious cake. Later in the day, an enchanting kiss leads to something big!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44799" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空閣結婚式城の攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of the Wedding Chapel in the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkuukaku Kekkonshikijou no Koubou</title>
<summary>Nesty recovers the Mural of the Legendary Princess in honor of Valkyrie’s wedding, but the ceremony is disrupted when space pirates try to steal the priceless artifact!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80224" update="2007-07-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Tv Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
