<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2780" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1981-08-22</startdate>
<enddate>1983-08-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Daicon III &amp; IV Opening Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Daicon Opening Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Daikon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Daicon</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DAICON III &amp; IV OPENING ANIMATION</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="130" type="Other">Otaku no Video</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325320">Amazing piece of moving picture..... this is all about anime really is, randomness, happiness and unlimited imagination, just brilliant!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="41949">Both of these kick MAJOR ASS, in different ways. Absolutely brilliant. Anyone who hasn`t seen them simply must. 

As [b]azaghal666[/b] said (it bears repeating!):

`Amazing piece of moving picture..... this is all about anime really is, randomness, happiness and unlimited imagination, just brilliant!`</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/daicon/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3584" type="Direction">Yamaga Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>"It`s either real, or it`s a dream, there`s nothing that is in between."
There are many ways one can describe the Daicon III and IV videos, but when someone pointed out to me the quote above (which is a lyric to the song in the Daicon IV video), it made me realize something: these short videos represent the dreams of science fiction and animation fans the world over -- the dreams of the otaku. It`s what a fan might subconsciously envision after watching 12+ hours of anime, having played six or more hours of video games, ingested liters worth of Coke Classic, and having used just a little too much wasabi with the sushi. We are treated to wild and crazy visions of cool, cute, and powerful bunny girls, cities being destroyed and rebuilt, sakura blossoms... just a mish-mash of everything you`ve ever seen in a way that only makes sense when you`re dreaming -- Macross Valkyries with Gundam beam sabers, flying swords performing the "Itano Circus", Darth Vader vs. our hero as Imperial stormtroopers cheer on, a huge white radish firing its main cannon to repopulate the world with trees, all kinds of special effects shots, and reference after reference to the shows and movies which have inspired us, continue to inspire us, and capture our imagination as fans.
The Daicon (note: a daikon is a Japanese white radish) videos are cool to watch just for the sake of watching them, but they`re important for other reasons, too. Without the Daicon videos, the studio known as Gainax might never have come into being. Daicon III, held in Osaka in 1981, was the 20th Japan Science Fiction Convention. The volunteer staff of mostly college kids created the short (music video length) opening animation for the convention`s opening ceremonies. This is the "Daicon III video". Although it was an amateur production using relatively low technology, fans loved it, and the use of opening animations at conventions would become a long-lasting tradition.
By Lawrence Eng, full version at:
http://www.cjas.org/~echen/articles/spring99/05_08g.html
Additional Links:
http://www.ask.ne.jp/~akashi/daicon.html
http://www.gainax.co.jp/sf2001/report/40nen/20.html
http://www.gainax.co.jp/sf2001/report/40nen/22.html</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1036">7.34</permanent>
<temporary count="1042">7.27</temporary>
<review count="2">8.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>212807.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>817</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/daicon/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DAICON_III_and_IV_Opening_Animations</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DAICON_FILM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8456" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-08-14">
<rating votes="868">7.63</rating>
<name>Doraemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doraemon is the titular robotic cat sent back in time by Sewashi to aid Nobita. He possesses a fourth-dimensional pocket from which he can acquire various kinds of futuristic tools, gadgets, and playthings from a future department store. Doraemon originally had ears but they were bitten off by a robotic mouse in the 22nd century. As a result, he developed a morbid fear of mice despite being a robotic cat. He also has the tendency to panic during emergencies, characterized by him frantically trying to pull out a very much-needed tool from his pocket, only to produce a huge assortment of unrelated household items.
Doraemon`s physical appearance changed as the manga progressed. At first, he was predominantly blue, with a blue tail, a white stomach, and flesh-coloured hands and feet. He also stooped, and had a body much larger than his head. In later issues, he sported a smaller body, white hands and feet, and a red tail--the appearance most identify him with today.
In "The Doraemons" story arc, it is revealed that Doraemon`s original paint color was yellow. After getting his ears gnawed off by a robot mouse, he slipped into depression on top of a tower, where he drank a potion labeled "sadness". As he wept, the yellow color washed off and his voice changed due to the potion.
Doraemon weighs 129.3 kg (285 lbs) and measures at 129.3 cm (4`3") tall. He is able to run at 129.3 km/h (80.3 mph) when scared and jump 129.3 m (424.2 ft) when threatened. His maximum power is 129.3 bhp. His wrist, head, and chest circumference are all 129.3 cm. His feet is 129.3 mm in diameter. He is manufactured on September 3, 2112 (12/9/3), at the Matsushiba Robot Factory. Doraemon is considered a substandard product because many of his robotic features (ie. radar whiskers and cat-calling bell) malfunctioned after production. One can turn off Doraemon by pulling his balloon tail.
Doraemon`s favourite food is dorayaki, a Japanese treat filled with red bean paste. Speculations led to dorayaki being the origin of his name. However, it was revealed in one of the manga chapters that his name originates from the Japanese word nora neko for "stray cat", and the -emon ending which is part of traditional Japanese names, as seen also in, for example, Ishikawa Goemon.
In the 2007 birthday episode, `MS-903` is used to call Doraemon by the factory owner where Doraemon is produced.
Doraemon usually uses the phrase "nanoda".</description>
<picture>2237.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="9099" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="550">8.23</rating>
<name>Lum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum (also referred to in some Western versions as Lamu - since her name in Japanese is technically pronounced "Ramu") is the second main protagonist of the series. She is a beautiful Oni alien who is capable of flying and generating electrical shocks and even lightning. She is extremely popular and is famous for ending her sentences with ~daccha (loosely translated as "yes?" or "you know?"). Except when in her school girl`s uniform, she usually wears a sexy outfit consisting of a tiger-striped bikini and knee-high go-go boots. While generally good-natured, sweet, faithful, and innocent, Lum also has a very hot temper and she is extremely jealous. Her dream in life is to live in a "Sweet Home with Darling" in which she keeps house and raises babies while Ataru, her "Darling," works a job. Unfortunately, Lum`s idea of "cooking" is to take very spicy ingredients like jalapenos, cayenne peppers and Tabasco sauce and irradiate them with an alien energy bazooka until they carbonize into inedible, crystallized nuggets. As an alien she has access to many bizarre gadgets whose use she really doesn`t understand all that well, leading to comic results. Differences between human and "Invader" physiology also drive many stories, like the time Lum`s horns begin to grow larger after she is bitten by a cow, or the time she becomes drunk by eating pickled plums.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10986" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="9">8.30</rating>
<name>RX-78-2 Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam is one of three prototype mobile suits secretly developed by the embattled Earth Federation. After suffering tremendous losses to Zeon`s mobile suits earlier in the war, the Federation set out to create its own, using the very latest advanced technology. The Gundam is the most successful of these prototypes, a close-combat mobile suit protected by tough Luna Titanium armour, and armed with both lethal beam sabers and a devastating beam rifle as powerful as a battleship cannon. It`s also equipped with an advanced computer which learns from its pilot, ultimately enabling it to operate the Gundam automatically. In the hands of accidental pilot Amuro Ray, this one prototype mobile suit proves to be the equal of any Zeon weapon.</description>
<picture>32757.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11095" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<name>Zaku II Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This high-performance version of the Zaku II is designed exclusively for squadron commanders and veteran pilots. Although it has more powerful thrusters and a greater propellant supply than the standard Zaku II, the only external difference is the communications antenna on its forehead. Lieutenant Commander Char Aznable - the famous "Red Comet" - pilots this commander`s version of the Zaku II, painted in his trademark colors.</description>
<picture>32993.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12068" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="45">9.32</rating>
<name>Yamato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>After the defeat of the Earth`s space fleet by the Gamilas Empire in the year 2199, the inhabitants of Earth secretly convert the ruins of the Japanese battleship Yamato into a massive spaceship, the Space Battleship Yamato. Using blueprints they attain from Queen Starsha of the planet Iscandar, they equip their new ship with a space warp drive, called the "wave motion engine", and a new, incredibly powerful weapon called the "wave motion gun" which fires from the bow.</description>
<picture>36555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31936" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Darth Vader</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132568.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44913" type="main character in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="2">9.65</rating>
<name>Daicon IV no Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First featured in Daicon III Opening animation in 1981, the Daicon Girl appears again in Daicon IV Opening animation in 1983. This time, as a grown up girl wearing a bunny suit and surfing on Stormbringer sword. The illegal use of Playboy bunny suit and Electric Light Orchestra`s Prologue / Twilight songs prevented the video to be commercially released until now.
The character is mostly remembered for her memorable fight against Eastern and Western SF characters, villains, heroes, famous starships and monsters. This short animation introduced fandom aspects now considered staples of Japanese animation. Among them, the bunny girl theme and Gainax Breast Bounce (yure mune).
For years, Daicon Girl and Daicon opening animations were and are still considered as symbol of otaku culture. In this respect, the character itself is often referenced in other Gainax projects. It also inspired other characters including Noriko (Gunbuster), Misty May (Otaku no Video) and Mina Tsukuda (Getsumen to Heiki Mina and Densha Otoko opening). Haruka (FLCL) and Hatsune Miku both portrayed the character at some point.
There has been much speculation between Daicon fans about the character`s real name. Annie May (pronounced as Anime) has been proposed, which would be referenced in Otaku no Video fictious Misty May character. However, it should be noted that all official products, figures, books and videos released by Daicon Film, Gainax and General Products always used Daicon IVの女の子 (Daicon IV Girl).</description>
<picture>88023.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75528" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-06-01">
<name>Batman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174074.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="26781" update="2014-08-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>1981-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Daicon III</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26782" update="2014-08-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>1983-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">9.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Daicon IV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26783" update="2020-01-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<rating votes="3">9.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Daicon Medley</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168767" update="2015-06-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">DAICON IV Extra</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
