<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="279" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-25</startdate>
<enddate>1998-10-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seishoujo Kantai Virgin Fleet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">VF</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">VFleet</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖少女艦隊バージンフリート</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Virgin Fleet</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10365" approval="2" total="2">Fuuun Ishin Dai Shougun</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/virgin/ova/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="4374" type="Character Design">Kitazume Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="3774" type="Original Work">Hiroi Ouji</name>
<name id="1605" type="Original Work">Imagawa Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="1605" type="Series Composition">Imagawa Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="6392" type="Direction">Hosoda Masahiro</name>
<name id="4374" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kitazume Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="2301" type="Music">Itou Masumi</name>
</creators>
<description>In the pre-WWII era, Nakano Naval Academy`s special school for girls is codenamed "Virgin Fleet". These girls are gifted with a special form of power known as "Virgin Energy". With the fear of another Russo-Japanese war imminent, rookie pilot Shiokaze Umino must hone her powers to save Japan from complete destruction.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="139">2.74</permanent>
<temporary count="139">5.20</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>153268.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>771</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1772</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1093</identifier>
<identifier>tsgiww</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20080622095206/http://www.anime-int.com/works/virgin/ova/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Virgin_Fleet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖少女艦隊バージンフリート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2100</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="3215" update="2005-12-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">初体験</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Experience</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsu Taiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3216" update="2005-12-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">五月の雪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fall of Satsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gogatsu no Yuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3217" update="2005-12-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">初夜桜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wedding</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsu Yozakura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95942" update="2011-08-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
