<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2806" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2005-12-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Transformers: Galaxy Force</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Transformers Cybertron - Robots in disguise</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Transformers: Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">TF:Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">トランスフォーマー ギャラクシーフォース</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Transformers: Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Transformers: Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Transformers Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Transformers: Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Transformers: Cybertron - A new beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Transformers Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">רובוטריקים: סייברטרון</title>
<title xml:lang="hr" type="official">Transformers Cybertron</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1342" type="Prequel">Transformers: SuperLink</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tv-aichi.co.jp/TF/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5735" type="Series Composition">Masaki Hiro</name>
<name id="5055" type="Chief Direction">Kakudou Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="2160" type="Character Design">Kumazen Takashi</name>
<name id="5371" type="Direction">Ono Manabu</name>
<name id="6920" type="Music">Oohashi Megumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Forced to abandon their home planet of Seibertron due to the threat of the Grand Blackhole, http://anidb.net/ch31756 [Galaxy Convoy] prepares to lead his Cybertron warriors to Earth. Just as they are leaving they are confronted by Vector Prime who warns Galaxy Convoy of the threat to the galaxy if the four Planet Force are not gathered. However, Master Megatron has plans of his own for the Planet Force.
Upon the destruction caused by the Grand Black Hole, the cybertron warriors from Planet Seibetron flee to earth in search of the way to stop the Grand Black Hole. They were joined by Vector Prime, an ancient Transformer that were sent by the past to aid and warn them on the dangers of the Grand Black Hole. They were told to gather the legendary planet forces in order to stop the chaos but Master Megatron has his own plans for the planet forces. As they embark on the search, they land on new planets which are inhabited by different Transformer races as well as the Convoys who lead these planets.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="189">4.80</permanent>
<temporary count="194">6.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3867.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4833</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>928</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1675</identifier>
<identifier>accyxb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-aichi.co.jp/TF/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Transformers:_Cybertron</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トランスフォーマー_ギャラクシーフォース</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7077</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="27702" update="2008-05-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖なる故郷 セイバートロン星崩壊!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sacred Birthplace - Planet Cybertron Destroyed!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chutes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinaru Kokyou: Cybertron-sei Houkai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27703" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トランスフォーマーとの遭遇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter with the Transformers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Transformer to no Souguu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28208" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密基地を守れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haven</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un nouveau refuge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu Kichi o Mamore!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28209" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球での暮らし方教えます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hidden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Transformations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu de no Kurashikata Oshiemasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28210" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チップスクエアを探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Landmine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Landmine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chip Square o Sagase!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28211" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚異の惑星スピーディア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui no Wakusei Speedia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28212" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最速の勇者ニトロコンボイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rush</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À toute vitesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisoku no Yuusha Nitro Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29258" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルひみつDVD 「たちあがれ! 新司令官ギャラクシーコンボイ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Secret DVD "Rise! New Commander Galaxy Convoy"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Himitsu DVD: Tachiagare! Shinshireikan Galaxy Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30267" update="2005-02-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! スタースクリーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Speed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confrontations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Starscream</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30531" update="2005-03-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間の街を救え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collapse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Effondrement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen no Machi o Sukue!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="32545" update="2005-03-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベクタープライムの決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Arrêt du temps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vector Prime no Ketsudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="32546" update="2005-03-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔獣惑星アニマトロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vaines recherches</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majuu Wakusei Animatros</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33846" update="2005-04-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪竜王フレイムコンボイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`océan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kai Ryuuou Flame Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34151" update="2005-04-04">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトランティスの攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vaisseau</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atlantis no Koubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34152" update="2005-04-08">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グレートレース開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le héros</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Great Race Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35044" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">トランスフォーマー・ギャラクシーフォースひみつファイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Secret DVD 2 "Transformers - Galaxy Force! Secret File!"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Transformers: Galaxy Force Himitsu File</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35871" update="2005-04-16">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バドとホップの都会旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Race</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La finale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bud to Hop no Tokai Ryokou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35971" update="2005-04-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">野獣転生! ライガージャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Detour</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le détour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yajuu Tensei! Ligerjack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36288" update="2005-04-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リンクアップ! ライガーコンボイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Savage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Féroce</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Link Up! Liger Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36289" update="2005-05-07">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼熱のデッドヒート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épreuve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakunetsu no Dead Heat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36507" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">栄光のプラネットカップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Champions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les champions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikou no Planet Cup</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36610" update="2005-06-02">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーロラの彼方の死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révélations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aurora no Kanata no Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37512" update="2005-06-02">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦え! ライガージャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Honor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`honneur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakae! Ligerjack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37513" update="2005-06-04">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ローリ 魔獣の星へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Primal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le point essentiel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lori Majuu no Hoshi e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37688" update="2005-06-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! アニマトロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La confiance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Animatros</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37725" update="2005-06-16">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪物たちの復活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le guet-apens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaibutsu-tachi no Fukkatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38366" update="2005-06-29">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球の守護神ライブコンボイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Shugoshin Live Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38367" update="2005-07-09">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3つ目のプラネットフォース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Retreat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Séparations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsume no Planet Force</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38613" update="2005-07-09">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙滅亡へのカウントダウン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revelation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un combat sans merci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Metsubou e no Countdown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38614" update="2005-07-15">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">転生! バンガードチーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Critical</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un moment critique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensei! Vanguard Team</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38851" update="2005-07-23">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙から来たスゴい奴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`affrontement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu kara Kita Sugoi Yatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39187" update="2005-07-27">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">野望の王 邪心全開</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starscream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Starscream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yabou no Ou, Jashin Zenkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39479" update="2005-08-02">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">高速機動合体ソニックコンボイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">United</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tous unis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousoku Kidou Gattai Sonic Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39800" update="2005-08-12">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超絶変形! 解放される力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cybertron</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chouzetsu Henkei! Kaihousareru Chikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40318" update="2005-08-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえった巨大神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Balance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un équilibre délicat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaetta Kyodai Shin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40319" update="2005-08-24">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗黒からの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ankoku kara no Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40915" update="2005-09-02">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトランティスの迷路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lavage de cerveau</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atlantis no Meiro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40937" update="2019-04-28">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">疾風のライオコンボイ登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Secret DVD 3 "Enter, Lio Convoy Typhoon"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shippuu no Lio Convoy Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41122" update="2005-09-07">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それゆけ脱出大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un demi fiasco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soreyuke Dasshutsu Daisakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41377" update="2005-09-15">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, 旅立ちの時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le départ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite, Tabidachi no Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41669" update="2005-09-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 砕け散る野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Titans</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les titans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Kudakechiru Yabou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41704" update="2005-09-24">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超時空トンネル突破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warp</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le passage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujikuu Tunnel Toppa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41815" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギガロニアのメガロコンボイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Giant</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gigantisme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gigalonia no Megalo Convoy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42009" update="2005-10-17">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マスターガルバトロン降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fury</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La colère</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Master Galvatron Kourin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42354" update="2005-10-24">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下世界へGO!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Sekai e Go!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42521" update="2005-10-23">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! ローリVSクロミア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ambush</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`embuscade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Lori VS Chromia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42591" update="2005-10-24">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プラネットXの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Planet X no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43003" update="2005-11-05">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きな星の小さな町</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scourge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choix de Scourge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookina Hoshi no Chiisana Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44637" update="2005-11-13">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後のプラネットフォース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Optimus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand combat d`Optimus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Planet Force</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44638" update="2005-11-13">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大いなる野望の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La terrible déception</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooinaru Yabou no Hate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44639" update="2005-11-13">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の時空監視者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ultime gardien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Jikuu Kanshisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44928" update="2006-04-19">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイバトロン大集結</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Planètes en détresse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cybertron Dai Shuuketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44929" update="2005-12-02">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終末の時, 希望の光を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuumatsu no Toki, Kibou no Hikari o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45365" update="2005-12-22">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャラクシーコンボイVSマスターガルバトロン 最終決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unfinished</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce n`est jamais fini</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Galaxy Convoy VS Master Galvatron Saishuu Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45437" update="2005-12-27">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éternel recommencement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127855" update="2011-01-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127856" update="2011-01-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127857" update="2011-01-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127858" update="2011-01-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
