<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2810" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-29</startdate>
<enddate>2005-10-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">ترينيتي بلود</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Kızıl Kan</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">圣魔之血</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">T-Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">T Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">trinity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">TB</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">トリニティ・ブラッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Trinity Blood (Кровь Триединства)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">트리니티 블러드</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Trinity Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Vér és kereszt</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3296" approval="112" total="163">Hellsing (2006)</anime>
<anime id="53" approval="79" total="113">Trigun</anime>
<anime id="1052" approval="63" total="81">Chrno Crusade</anime>
<anime id="32" approval="62" total="88">Hellsing</anime>
<anime id="4072" approval="2" total="6">Strait Jacket</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="558725">I honestly started watching this anime because i have seen a lot of cospalyers portraying at least one character from it year after year and wanted to see what was it about. The story started out great, but it loses potential. The designs, however, are amazing. So if you`re looking for an anime with a visual impact you should watch this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="61229">the art work is .....awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="438022">One of the best vampire series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="521116">A great anime, it caught me, right after the first 5 minutes. The protagonist seems like a goof, but he is very strong. Nice story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="165754">Epic must see anime, even after years I have fond memories to the series. Even the soundtrack is top notch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kadokawa.co.jp/toribla/index.php</url>
<creators>
<name id="3902" type="Music">Eguchi Takahito</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="1419" type="Character Design">Nakajima Atsuko</name>
<name id="31925" type="Series Composition">Kadokawa Sneaker Bunko Henshuubu</name>
<name id="10828" type="Original Work">Thores Shibamoto</name>
<name id="10829" type="Original Work">Yoshida Sunao</name>
<name id="3688" type="Series Composition">Tomioka Atsuhiro</name>
<name id="5510" type="Series Composition">Hirata Tomohiro</name>
<name id="5510" type="Direction">Hirata Tomohiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a series of light novels written by http://anidb.net/cr10829 [Yoshida Sunao] with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr10828 [Thores Shibamoto], originally serialised in http://anidb.net/cr32162 [The Sneaker].
In the distant future, after the destruction brought about by Armageddon, the war between the vampires and the humans persists. In order to protect the humans from the vampires, the Vatican has to rely on unusual allies to control the situation. A priest called http://anidb.net/ch7249 [Abel Nightroad], travels the countries as a representative of the Vatican. However, he is also part of http://anidb.net/ch7310 [AX], a special operations group controlled by Cardinal http://anidb.net/ch7316 [Caterina Sforza]. His encounter with a young girl named http://anidb.net/ch24638 [Esther Blanchett] will determine the struggle between the human race and the vampires.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5377">5.72</permanent>
<temporary count="5482">7.48</temporary>
<review count="19">6.82</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148342.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4874</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1725</identifier>
<identifier>lnbwug</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.kadokawa.co.jp/toribla/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/toribla/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Trinity_Blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トリニティ・ブラッド</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>599</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7229</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2005/trinity_blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2131" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-19">
<name>psychotic</name>
<description>People suffering from psychosis can be described as having lost their contact with reality and deteriorated their social functioning to the point of becoming deranged. Sometimes, these people will try to achieve some absurd goal through trampling on other people, and that`s the point they become villains. Usually, psychotic villains will not show themselves to suffer from mental disorders at first, and will seem like completely normal people; however, as their story unfolds and the show progresses towards its climax, it is usual to have psychotic villains become more and more deranged, to the point of being best described by "batshit insane".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3513" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>special bullet</name>
<description>Custom made bullets that have special effects (and often shapes, too), which take action when hitting the enemy/ally.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4586" parentid="2834" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-30">
<name>Turkey</name>
<description>Turkey, officially the Republic of Turkey, is a transcontinental parliamentary republic in Eurasia, mainly on the Anatolian peninsula in Western Asia, with a smaller portion on the Balkan peninsula in Southeast Europe. Turkey is a democratic, secular, unitary, constitutional republic with a diverse cultural heritage.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192048.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5147" parentid="4586" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Istanbul</name>
<description>Istanbul, historically known as Constantinople and Byzantium, is the most populous city in Turkey and the country`s economic, cultural, and historic center. Istanbul is a transcontinental city in Eurasia, straddling the Bosphorus strait (which separates Europe and Asia) between the Sea of Marmara and the Black Sea. Its commercial and historical center lies on the European side and about a third of its population lives on the Asian side.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214382.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7249" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="35">7.39</rating>
<name>Abel Nightroad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>On the surface, Abel appears to be a clumsy, absent-minded Catholic priest who has bad luck with money and is always hungry. In reality, he is a Crusnik, a vampire with extraordinary powers that can feed on other vampires. Nearly a millennium in age, Abel was created in 2088 A.D. as one of four test tube babies whose bodies were infused with Crusnik nanomachines by the Mars human colonists. Abel once had a hatred for humanity and joined the Methuselah in the war against humans after the Armageddon. During the war between the humans and Methuselah, Abel Nightroad killed seven million humans. Lilith`s death during the war caused him to abandon his hatred. He spent 900 years weeping and mourning in Lilith`s crypt at the Vatican, until a young Caterina Sforza fled there to escape Methuselah assassins. Abel, realizing that it was his task to continue Lilith`s work and defend the humans, saved the young Caterina and chose to live on. He joined the AX at its foundation in May, 3055 A.D.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>25626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7310" type="appears in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="3">4.24</rating>
<name>Kyoukouchou Kokumu Seishou Tokumu Bunshitsu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>AX, short for Arcanum Cella Ex Dono Dei (Latin for Papal State Affairs Special Operations Section), serves as the special division of the Ministry of Holy Affairs. The agents are all elite priests and nuns, trained in different arts of combat, many of whom have special abilities granted to them by lost technologies. The members of the AX unit serve under http://anidb.net/ch7316 [Cardinal Caterina Sforza], and are often referred to as deputy enforcers. They are often sent to investigate issues relating to or involving vampires.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>25763.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7316" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="15">6.07</rating>
<name>Caterina Sforza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cardinal Caterina Sforza, the Duchess of Milan, is a strong willed, determined woman who shows no fear and has a strong resolve in anything she believes in. She is the head of the Ministry of Holy Affairs and leads the department`s special operations group, the AX Agency.
Caterina first met Abel Nightroad when he saved her from a group of vampires who attempted to kill her by order of the Contra Mundi. After she was safe, he promised that he would always protect humans. They have been close friends ever since. Caterina greatly loves her brother Alessandro, the current Pope, and has shown herself to be willing to die to protect him. Caterina frequently clashes with her other brother, Cardinal Francesco, who abhors the idea of peace with vampires and has little regard for the life of Alessandro.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>25768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12713" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="11">6.49</rating>
<name>Tres Iqus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The battle android, Tres Iqus (HC-IIIX), is the third of the ten android models known as the "Killing Dolls".
AX code name: Gunslinger.</description>
<picture>147904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24638" type="main character in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="16">5.06</rating>
<name>Esther Blanchett</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born as the legitimate granddaughter of the queen of Albion, she was brought to Istvan shortly after her birth in order to save her from assassins. She is the daughter of the late Prince Gilbert who was assassinated just after she was born. She was saved by Edward White, who was going by the alias Edward Blanchett, who took her to an orphanage in Istvan where she was raised to be a nun by Bishop Laura Vitez, who loved Esther like her own daughter.
Esther meets Abel during an attack on Count Gyula`s City Military Police as the leader of a band of rebels called the Partisans who worked to oust Count Gyula`s tyranny over Istavan.</description>
<picture>147910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62688" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Mainz Haku Alfred</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62689" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Francesco di Medici</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Duke of Florence, Duke of Tuscany, and a Cardinal of the Vatican, Francesco is a tall and intimidating man. As he is a bastard son, he could not be elected Pope and may harbor some bitterness over it. Using intimidation and loud vocal displays, he frequently attempts to pressure his younger brother to bend to his way of thinking. Harboring a strong hatred for vampires, he frequently clashes with his younger sister, Cardinal Caterina, in her pursuits for negotiation and diplomacy. As the head of the Department of Inquisition, Francesco does not believe in compromise, preferring to respond to situations with militarism, violence and force. He has no compunctions about making decisions that might kill innocent bystanders claiming his actions are done "in the name of God", and would gladly sacrifice his brother to further his own cause.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>147893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62690" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Jessica Lange</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62691" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Kate Scott</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Originally from Albion, Sister Kate is the holographic captain of the AX battleship the Iron Maiden. Kate also oversees most of the AX missions from within the ship, coordinating the agents moves and relaying information via the earpieces all of the agents wear. Kate is also skilled in making herbal tea blends which are well loved by the AX agents and Cardinal Caterina.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>147895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62692" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="1">1.21</rating>
<name>Alessandro XVIII</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His Holiness, Alessandro XVIII, is the 399th Pope of Rome, and the son of the former pope, Gregorio XXX. After the death of his father, Alessandro`s siblings made sure he was given the title of Pope over his uncle, Archbishop Alfonso d`Este. Alessandro did not choose the position himself, and is a nervous and easily frightened teenager who lacks conviction and confidence in himself. He cannot handle shouting, especially when it is directed towards him. Despite his holding the highest position in the Vatican, Alessandro is a puppet ruler who feels unable to make decisions on his own, usually deferring to his older brother`s views in important matters.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>147896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62693" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Mireille Manson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1431" picture="25110.jpg">Kosuge Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62694" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="2">5.57</rating>
<name>Cain Nightroad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62695" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Ellis Wazmaia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62696" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>William Walter Wordsworth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62697" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Dietrich von Lohengrin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62698" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Hungaria Koushaku Gyula Kadar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62699" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Laura Vitez</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62700" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62701" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Esther Blanchett</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62702" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>10 Nen Mae no Caterina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62703" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Vaclav Havel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62704" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Noelle Bor</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62705" type="appears in" update="2013-12-31">
<name>Eihei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62714" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Karel van der Werff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62715" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Hans Memling</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2065" picture="228616.jpg">Kimura Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62716" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Willem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2207" picture="41549.jpg">Makishima Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62717" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Sister Agnes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62718" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Guy de Granvelle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62719" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Thierry d`Alsace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17527" picture="151728.jpg">Miyata Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62720" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Hugue de Watteau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5299" picture="29408.jpg">Kitade Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62721" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Kangofu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147937.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62722" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Biedel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62723" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Wendy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62724" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Carly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62725" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Peter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62726" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<name>Leon Garcia de Asturias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62727" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Sen`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62728" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="1">4.26</rating>
<name>Isaak Fernand von Kampfer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62729" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62732" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>Brother Peter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62733" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Alfonso d`Este Daishikyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3363" picture="24393.jpg">Taniguchi Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62736" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="5">4.82</rating>
<name>Seth Nightroad</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62737" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<name>Endre Kouza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62738" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<name>Astharoshe Asran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62741" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="2">1.91</rating>
<name>Ion Fortuna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62742" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Sister Paula Souwauski</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62743" type="appears in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Radu Barvon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62754" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Mirka Fortuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62755" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Mimar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62756" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Khartoum Danshaku Baibars</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62757" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Candarli</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62758" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Tigris-kou Suleyman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2233" picture="21784.jpg">Takewaka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62760" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Virgil Walsh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62761" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Vanessa Walsh</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62762" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Mary Spencer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62763" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Angelica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62764" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Ginny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62765" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Tom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62766" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="1">2.54</rating>
<name>Abel (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62767" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<name>Seth Nightroad</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62768" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Cain (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62769" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Lilith Sahl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1881" picture="20979.jpg">Kobayashi Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="35249" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="33">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Flight Night</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flight Night</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ночной полёт</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Flight Night</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Skrydžio naktis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flight Night</title>
<summary>The airship Tristan is hijacked by a member of the Fleurs du Mal who demands the release of his comrades held in Vatican captivity. But one passenger stands in his way - Abel Nightroad.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35721" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Witch Hunt</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Witch Hunt</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Охота на ведьм</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Witch Hunt</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Raganos medžioklė</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Witch Hunt</title>
<summary>Nightroad encounters a girl with abilities both strange and deadly. When she attempts to flee, Abel must turn against his own in order to save her life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36275" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">1.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36277" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="16">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Star Of Sorrow I. City Of Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Star of Sorrow I. City of Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Звезда Скорби I. Город крови</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Star Of Sorrow I: City Of Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Liūdesio Žvaigždė (I. Kraujo Miestas)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Star Of Sorrow I. City Of Blood</title>
<summary>Abel’s search for the “star” has tangled him in the web of war. Sister Esther seeks vengeance for the death of her mentor and has gone to great lengths in her quest to eliminate the one ultimately responsible.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36278" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Star Of Sorrow II. Hunters` Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Star of Sorrow II. Hunter`s Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Звезда Скорби II. Пир охотников</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Star of Sorrow II: Hunter`s Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Liūdesio Žvaigždė (II. Medžiotojų Puota)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Star Of Sorrow II. Hunters` Banquet</title>
<summary>The Rosen Kreuz has surfaced again. Fueling the personal revenge of others for their own evil ends, the nefarious order could plunge both races back into the dark days of Armageddon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36279" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Yesterday, Today And Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вчера, Сегодня, Завтра</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Yesterday, Today And Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Vakar, Šiandien ir Rytoj</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yesterday, Today And Tomorrow</title>
<summary>After returning to Rome and joining AX, Sister Esther encounters a crying boy on the vast grounds. Following her attempts at comforting him, she learns that he is none other than Pope Alessandro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36415" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Sword Dancer</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword Dancer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Танцующий с мечом</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Sword Dancer</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Šokėjas su kardais</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sword Dancer</title>
<summary>The murder of clergy in Amsterdam, their bodies drained of blood, draws Lady Caterina’s attention. The local vampires, fearing Vatican retribution, seek out those responsible as Father Hugue investigates.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36417" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Never Land</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never Land</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Нетландия</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Never Land</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Niekieno žemė</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Never Land</title>
<summary>A string of freighter attacks seems to be the work of unusual vampiric faeries. On an island meant to be a retreat for the orphaned, Abel and former AX agent Leon investigate the mystery.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36418" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Silent Noise</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silent Noise</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Беззвучный шум</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Silent Noise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Silent Noise</title>
<summary>Nightroad and Sister Noelle travel to Barcelona to sift through the ruins of the collapsed National Palace. True feelings surface against such a beautiful backdrop - but so does the face of the enemy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36419" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Overcount I. The Belfry Of Downfall</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overcount I. The Belfry of Downfall</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Последний отсчёт. Часть 1. Колокольня, несущая смерть</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Overcount I. The Belfry Of Downfall</title>
<summary>AX scrambles to prevent Rosen Kreuz from destroying Rome with the Silent Noise device, but they may have to act without Abel. Driven by despair, Nightroad considers turning in his gun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37275" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Overcount II. Lucifer`s Choice</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overcount II. Lucifer`s Choice</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Последний отсчёт. Часть 2. Выбор Люцифера</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Overcount II. Lucifer`s Choice</title>
<summary>Under house arrest, Lady Caterina finds herself face to face with a manipulative enemy. Abel’s efforts to save her result in an encounter with a dangerous new foe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37276" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">From The Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From the Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Из Империи</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">From The Empire</title>
<summary>To hunt a mass murderer in Venice, Nightroad works with Asta, who holds a great deal of contempt for all things human.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37277" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Ibelis I. Evening Visitors</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ibelis I. Evening Visitors</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Иблис. Часть 1. Вечерние гости</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Ibelis I. Evening Visitors</title>
<summary>Whispers of an assassination attempt on the Lady Caterina turn agents of the Vatican against each other. Abel seeks a safe path through the hostilities harbored by both sides, and Esther must be the guide.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37278" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Ibelis II. Betrayal Blaze</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ibelis II. Betrayal Blaze</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Иблис. Часть 2. Пламя предательства</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Ibelis II. Betrayal Blaze</title>
<summary>Abel and Esther must protect the messenger from the Empire, Ion Fortuna. And as Cartago undergoes martial law, hope rests on the small group of refugees, alone and outnumbered, forced underground.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38550" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Ibelis III. A Mark Of Sinner</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ibelis III. A Mark of Sinner</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Иблис. Часть 3. Печать грешника</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Ibelis III. A Mark Of Sinner</title>
<summary>As the Puppet Master, a face from Esther’s past, creates chaos, the Rosen Kreuz formulates a murderous plan to inflame the hatred between the two races.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38551" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Night Lords I. The Return Of Envoy</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Lords I. The Return of the Envoy</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Повелители ночи. Часть 1. Возвращение посланника</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Night Lords I. The Return Of Envoy</title>
<summary>The Puppet Master has turned Ion’s childhood home into a carnival of carnage, and with the young vampire blamed for the atrocities, Abel must seek help from the only other vampire he’s ever let live.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38552" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Night Lords II. Twilight Of The Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Lords II. Twilight of the Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Повелители ночи. Часть 2. Сумерки столицы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Night Lords II. Twilight Of The Capital</title>
<summary>Abel and Asta plan to plead Ion’s case to the Imperial Council, and Ion and Esther search the city for answers. But when their trail leads to further intrigue, betrayal comes from beyond the grave.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38553" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Night Lords III. The Island Of Her Darling Children</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Lords III. The Island of Her Darling Children</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Повелители ночи. Часть 3. Остров её любимых детей</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Night Lords III. The Island Of Her Darling Children</title>
<summary>While Esther recovers from her injuries with the help of the enigmatic child Seth, Ion is stunned to find himself face to face with Radu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39374" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Night Lords IV. The Palace Of Jade</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Lords IV. The Palace of Jade</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Повелители ночи. Часть 4. Нефритовый дворец</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Night Lords IV. The Palace Of Jade</title>
<summary>Ion and Esther find themselves unwitting pawns in an elaborate plot to murder the Empress. As treachery emerges from shadow, so does a ghost from Ester’s past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39375" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Night Lords V. A Start Of Pilgrimage</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Lords V. A Start of Pilgrimage</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Повелители ночи. Часть 5. Начало странствия</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Night Lords V. A Start Of Pilgrimage</title>
<summary>Esther and Ion are freed from prison, and the true identity of the Empress is revealed. When she joins Abel in battle against Dietrich, secrets of the past come to light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39376" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Throne of Roses I. Kingdom of The North</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Throne of Roses I. Kingdom of the North</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Трон из роз. Часть 1. Северное королевство</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Throne of Roses I. Kingdom of The North</title>
<summary>While in Londinium for the Queen of Albion’s funeral, Esther and Pope Alessandro are taken hostage by vampires. The AX must rescue them before Cardinal Medici makes a martyr of the Pope.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40842" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Throne Of Roses II. The Refuge</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Throne of Roses II. The Refuge</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Трон из роз. Часть 2. Пристанище</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Throne Of Roses II. The Refuge</title>
<summary>The AX, the Inquisitorial Department, and the rebel terrorists each race to find Pope Alessandro first. Meanwhile, the Rosen Kreuz prepares to exploit the crisis for its own sinister purpose.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40843" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Throne Of Roses III. Load Of Abyss</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Throne of Roses III. Lord of Abyss</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Трон из роз. Часть 3. Князь бездны</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Throne Of Roses III. Load Of Abyss</title>
<summary>Rosen Kreuz soldiers slaughter the underground populace, while Petro battles to guide the Pope to safety. Abel’s confrontation with Dietrich leads to a foe of even greater power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40844" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Crown Thorns I. City In The Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crown of Thorns I. City in the Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Терновый венец. Часть 1. Город в тумане</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Crown Thorns I. City In The Mist</title>
<summary>Cain and Von Kampfer begin the first phase of their quest to destroy the people of the world, both human and vampire. Meanwhile, a startling revelation awaits Esther, one that will forever reshape her destiny.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40845" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Crown Thorns II. The Load Of Oath</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crown of Thorns II. The Lord of Oath</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Терновый венец. Часть 2. Клятва</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Crown Thorns II. The Load Of Oath</title>
<summary>Allies and enemies, both human and vampire, work together against the enemy of the world - the Contra Mundi. Resurrected from the grave, not even death can keep Abel Nightroad from his fate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120699" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120700" update="2015-01-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
