<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2812" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-02-09</startdate>
<enddate>2002-02-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Turn A Gundam II: Gekkou Chou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">∀ガンダムII 月光蝶</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">∀Gundam II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ターンエーガンダムII 月光蝶</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Turn A Gundam II: Moonlight Butterfly</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2813" type="Prequel">Turn A Gundam I: Chikyuukou</anime>
<anime id="916" type="Full Story">Turn A Gundam</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="3412" type="Character Design">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="3412" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
</creators>
<description>Second compilation movie for Turn A Gundam.
Following the events of the first movie, the Militia finishes restoration work on its excavated spaceship and travels to the moon to deal with Gym Ghingnham and Agrippa Maintainer, who along with Dianna Soreil form a governing triumvirate over the Moonrace. On the moon, the political situation rapidly evolves as new deals are made, setting the stage for a decisive final battle to determine the relationship between the people of Earth and the technologically advanced Moonrace.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="150">5.37</permanent>
<temporary count="154">6.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>83861.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2944</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2398</identifier>
<identifier>rmgxfg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>851</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236144</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6663</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6477" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="32">8.23</rating>
<name>Loran Cehack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in the positive calendar November 2, 2328, Loran is a 17 years old boy belonging to the Moonrace and the main character of the series and the pilot of the eponymous mobile suit, WD-M01 ∀ Gundam. Loran and his friends Keith and Fran are secretly sent to Earth by Dianna Soreil in advance of her main colonial force, to ensure that Moonrace settlers can still survive there. The three of them separate upon landing and integrate themselves into the Terran population.</description>
<picture>23992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6479" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="37">7.80</rating>
<name>Kihel Heim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kihel Heim is the oldest daughter of the Heim family. Though Kihel is a wealthy heiress, she chooses to look for work and gain real-world experience rather than attend university. She sticks close to Guin Lineford during Dianna Counter`s first attack and uses the opportunity to become his assistant. Her new position brings her to the attention of the leaders of the Moonrace.
Kihel bears a striking resemblance to Dianna Soreil, which allows her to become the Queen`s double. She takes Dianna`s place at the Queen`s behest and, due to events beyond their control, ends up having to impersonate Dianna and lead the Dianna Counter on a long-term basis. The two go on to switch names and roles several times. Kihel and Dianna share many qualities beyond appearance and their ideals are so aligned that for a time they consider themselves a single person. Even so, Kihel has much more energy than Dianna, and does not share Dianna`s longing for an ordinary life. She is very good at masking her insecurity over whether or not she can live up to Dianna`s example.</description>
<picture>2015.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6480" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="25">6.58</rating>
<name>Sochie Heim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sochie Heim is the second daughter of the Heim family. Sochie is a spoiled, headstrong tomboy who is continually overshadowed by her sister Kihel. She was determined to join the Inglessa Militia even before Dianna Counter`s attack, and is among the first to pilot one of Sid Munzer`s excavated mobile suits. Eventually Sochie becomes a well-respected soldier, though her AMX-109 Kapool is one of the weakest mobile suits in the series.
The death of Sochie`s father causes her to hate the Moonrace and she feels betrayed when she discovers that her crush Loran is from the Moon. It takes a long time for her to grow up and soften her views. While Sochie suffers a great deal of loss over the course of the series, her trials make her a stronger person, and she never loses her fighting spirit.</description>
<picture>2016.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3087" picture="23993.jpg">Murata Akino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6481" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="53">8.39</rating>
<name>Diana Soriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Queen of the Moon, Dianna Soreil is the hereditary ruler of the Moonrace. Now that the Earth has regenerated from the destruction wrought by the Dark History, she believes that it is time for her subjects to return to Earth. Dianna lands a colonial force on the Earth in the hopes that they will be allowed to live in America`s sparsely-populated sunbelt area. Unfortunately, she fails to take Terran resistance to the migration into account, and does not anticipate that her more ambitious subjects might turn against her in her absence. Events quickly spiral out of her control.
Dianna has lived for centuries using the Moonrace`s cryogenic techniques. Her desire to live on Earth is a product of her weariness with her unchanging life on the Moon. She is an intelligent and commanding leader, but she lacks the drive of her young double, Kihel Heim. Dianna is overjoyed when assuming Kihel`s identity allows her to lead a simple life with Loran. She only returns to the Moon in order to correct the mistakes she made in her rash rush towards repatriation.</description>
<picture>2019.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6482" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="21">5.67</rating>
<name>Harry Ord</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harry Ord is the head of Dianna`s Royal Guard, and reports directly to the Queen herself. He pilots a distinctive gold-plated MRC-F20 SUMO and is easily one of the most skilled fighters in the series. An accomplished military strategist, Harry judges situations with a cool and rational demeanor. He is the only person who is readily able to distinguish between Kihel Heim and Dianna Soreil.
Harry remains loyal to Dianna throughout the series. Though he falls in love with Kihel, his duty to the throne always comes first. He uses a large pair of red sunglasses to mask his true feelings.</description>
<picture>2020.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6483" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="7">2.04</rating>
<name>Guin Sard Rhineford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guin Sard Rhineford is a charming young nobleman who rules the principality of Inglessa. He seems dedicated to brokering a peaceful agreement between the Terrans and the Moonrace, and to building up the Earth Militia in case those talks fall through. After his base of power Nocis City is destroyed he masterminds the Terrans` journey into space to confront the Moonrace. He uses his relationship with the Luziannan princess Lily Borjarno to retain his influence after the fall of Inglessa.</description>
<picture>2021.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3090" picture="23995.jpg">Aoba Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6484" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="13">6.50</rating>
<name>Lily Borjarno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest child of Lord Borjarno, who rules over the Luzianna territory. Lily initially appears to be little more than a spoiled dilettante. She behaves pettily towards the disguised Diana Soreil, she claims to work for the Militia out of boredom, and it seems like she`s willing to allow Guin to use her as a pawn so long as he indulges her infatuation.
As the series progresses, it becomes clear that Lily is in fact an insightful and astute politician. She knows the importance of gathering powerful friends and allies, and has no qualms about ditching Guin once he becomes a liability instead of an asset. Lily negotiates with Agrippa Maintainer on the Earth`s behalf and takes control of the Willgame after Guin`s fall from grace.</description>
<picture>2022.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3092" picture="23997.jpg">Kobayashi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6485" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Sid Munzer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An elderly archeologist searching for remnants of the Earth`s "dark history". He works on the excavation of mobile suits which are used by the the Earth Militias to fight the Moonrace.</description>
<picture>2023.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6486" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="2">5.39</rating>
<name>Gym Ghingham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the armed forces of the Moon. Gym is a forceful, swaggering man who carries a katana as an affectation. He believes that humanity can only live up to its true potential during times of war, and seeks to use the Turn X Gundam to sow strife and re-kindle the brutal conflicts that raged throughout the Dark History
Both Agrippa Maintainer and Guin Sard Lineford think that they can use Gym to their own ends, but they fail to understand his lust for battle. Neither politician is able to control him.</description>
<picture>2025.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6487" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Yanny Oviess</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sergeant in the Inglessa Militia, later promoted to second lieutenant. He has a stubborn personality and works against Dianna with Michael Gern.</description>
<picture>2026.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6488" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Michael Gern</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A colonel in the Inglessa Militia. Michael Gern is a proud and straightlaced man who follows orders until they are completed. He has a wife and young son.</description>
<picture>2027.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6489" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="3">1.13</rating>
<name>Joseph Yaht</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Inglessa Militia`s Jalopy Squad. Joseph comes from an ethnic minority that is persecuted in Adeska. He left his homeland to assist Sid Munzer and only departs the excavation team once he is needed to pilot the Militia`s FLAT-LO6D FLAT. Joseph is a brave man with a good heart. He quickly forms a romantic relationship with Fran Doll in spite of his brusque, taciturn personality.</description>
<picture>2028.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2786" picture="211228.jpg">Satou Setsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6490" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="3">1.13</rating>
<name>Miashei Kune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ladderrum`s daughter, and one of the Inglessa Militia`s top pilots. Miashei is Sochie`s best friend and the one who taught her how to operate machines. She is a bright, sensible girl, and is often called upon to act as a voice of reason when Sochie is being too hot-headed.</description>
<picture>2029.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3095" picture="23998.jpg">Kitou Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6492" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="6">3.01</rating>
<name>Bruno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially one of Nander`s subordinates and a member of the Dianna Counter forces, he later joins the Earth Militia. Bruno is an MS Gozzo pilot and Jacop`s partner.</description>
<picture>2033.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6493" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="6">4.49</rating>
<name>Jacop</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially one of Nander`s subordinates and a member of the Dianna Counter forces, he later joins the Earth Militia. Jacop is an MS Gozzo pilot and Bruno`s partner.</description>
<picture>2034.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6494" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-28">
<rating votes="1">6.13</rating>
<name>Horace Niven</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Horace Niven is an engineer from the Moon who defects to the Earth Militias when it becomes clear that Dianna Counter can`t provide for all of the civilian settlers. Without him the Terrans would not be able to use a great deal of their recovered technology.</description>
<picture>172721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12682" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<rating votes="3">3.52</rating>
<name>WD-M01 Turn A Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The WD-M01 Turn A Gundam is a mecha from the Correct Century (正暦 Seireki) calendar system in the anime Turn A Gundam. It is mainly piloted by the hero of the series, and acted as the symbol of the earth militia forces against the superior moonrace.
∀ Gundam is designed by Syd Mead, for the series Turn A Gundam. The original design of the mecha was rejected by Yoshiyuki Tomino due to its exotic appearance and Tomino decided that he wanted a figure that is closer to the previous Gundam designs. The old design was renamed and used for the Mobile Suit Sumo instead. The design is still exotic to Gundam anime fans, however, Syd Mead designed ∀ Gundam using real world industrial design aspects, which was aimed to make it look simple and realistic. The shield was designed by Syd Mead with little constraint form the production team, it needs to be big enough so that the suit can hide behind it, making it easier for the anime production staff to draw. Syd Mead imagined it to be like a clam shell and finally settled with a design that looked like MS-14 Gelgoog`s shield.
The System-∀99 (WD-M01) ∀ Gundam (also known as "Turn A") first appeared in the show when the Moonrace`s Diana Counter army arrived on Earth and attacked the city of Nocis; which at the time was holding a Coming of Age ceremony for Loran Cehack and Sochie Heim, who danced and offered prayers in front of the "White Doll" statue. When the Moonrace forces attack, the "White Doll" statue crumbled, revealing the Turn A. Loran and Sochie take shelter inside the cockpit, which activates and automatically fires at the unaware Moonrace forces. After several battles with the Moonrace, the Turn A became the symbol of the struggle to resist the Moonrace`s attempts at colonizing Earth.</description>
<picture>231941.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="27354" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>130</length>
<airdate>2002-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
