<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2814" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1977-08-06</startdate>
<enddate>1977-08-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchuu Senkan Yamato (1977)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Cruiser: Guardian of the Galaxy</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Cruiser</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Cruiser Yamato</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Star Blazers: The Quest for Iscandar (movie)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Yamato, le cuirassé de l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宇宙戦艦ヤマト (1977)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Space Battleship Yamato: The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La Corazzata spaziale Yamato</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Crucero Espacial Yamato: La Película</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="648" type="Full Story">Uchuu Senkan Yamato</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109064">First anime i ever watched, a VHS UK release of this film.
It was heavily edited back then but still amazing even in its dubbed state!  (i was like 7 or 8)
Since rewatched in HD and subbed, as usual has more detail, depth and other aspects in its original form.
Classic space epic.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/yamato/data/1_yamato.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="7761" type="Character Design">Tsukima Hachirou</name>
<name id="151" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishiguro Noboru</name>
<name id="4232" type="Character Design">Okaseko Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="3327" type="Original Plan">Yamamoto Eiichi</name>
<name id="5288" type="Direction">Masuda Toshio</name>
<name id="5423" type="Music">Miyagawa Hiroshi</name>
<name id="5221" type="Original Plan">Nishizaki Yoshinobu</name>
</creators>
<description>A summary of the first tv series, the quest for Iscandar is a story about the war between the human race and the Gamilon. Constant bombardment of radioactive asteroids has rendered the Earth`s atmosphere uninhabitable. As a means of relief aid, Queen Starsha of the planet Iscandar offers the Earth Forces a device that can completely neutralize the radiation on the planet. For this task, the space battleship Yamato is launched from the remains of its World War II ancestor on a 148,000 light-year journey. However, the crew of the Yamato has only one Earth year to travel to Iscandar and back, or the human race will come to an end.
Source: ANN, modified by Ryuuroden</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="167">5.93</permanent>
<temporary count="168">6.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>153032.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>711</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2474</identifier>
<identifier>hbrixa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/yamato/data/1_yamato.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1822</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90208</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m071</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3234" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-31">
<name>space is an ocean</name>
<description>The difference between space and ocean is marginal. In fact the two are completely interchangeable. Spacecraft are usually called ships and space forces use naval ranks. Movement in space is two-dimensional. There is friction. And not to forget space pirates are roaming through the galaxy and just so often you will encounter space whales.
Some titles take this even a step further by actually displaying the space as a sort of gigantic liquid mass.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12068" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="45">9.32</rating>
<name>Yamato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>After the defeat of the Earth`s space fleet by the Gamilas Empire in the year 2199, the inhabitants of Earth secretly convert the ruins of the Japanese battleship Yamato into a massive spaceship, the Space Battleship Yamato. Using blueprints they attain from Queen Starsha of the planet Iscandar, they equip their new ship with a space warp drive, called the "wave motion engine", and a new, incredibly powerful weapon called the "wave motion gun" which fires from the bow.</description>
<picture>36555.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="48969" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>140</length>
<airdate>1977-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65397" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>70</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65398" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>70</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
