<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2830" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2005-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sousei no Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Holy Genesis Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Genesis of Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Акварион</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">창성의 아쿠에리온</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Święta Geneza Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">أكواريون</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sna</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">創聖のアクエリオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Aquarion</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อควอเรี่ยน สงครามหุ่นศักดิ์สิทธิ์</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8299" type="Sequel">Aquarion Evol</anime>
<anime id="4600" type="Alternative Setting">Sousei no Aquarion (2007)</anime>
<anime id="11151" type="Side Story">Sousei no Aquarion Evol</anime>
<anime id="11150" type="Other">Aquarion Logos</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14" approval="31" total="41">RahXephon</anime>
<anime id="22" approval="27" total="56">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="4931" approval="4" total="8">Kiss Dum: Engage Planet</anime>
<anime id="2826" approval="4" total="6">Koukyoushihen: Eureka Seven</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="115911">It was a good experience watching Aquarion. Although the Plot was so-so and there were practically no character development in the series. it was still a good watch, give it a try and I`m sure you`ll like it as well.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.aquarion.info/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="1043" type="Original Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="2711" type="Series Composition">Oonogi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="152" type="Series Composition">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="152" type="Original Work">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="152" type="Direction">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="2748" type="Music">Hogari Hisaaki</name>
<name id="19131" type="Character Design">Utsunomiya Satoru</name>
<name id="5731" type="Character Design">Fujikawa Futoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>In Holy Genesis Era, in the year 0011, mankind has lost 2/3 of its population. The Great Catastrophe, which ruined the planet 11 years ago, caused the ice of Antarctica to melt.
In Atlantia, believed to have been destroyed long ago, the winged race of Shadow Angels awakens from a 12,000-year slumber. They send their bio-mechanical mythical beasts to harvest the life energy of humans, Plana, attacking the few remaining cities.
Humanity was fighting a losing battle when the Godspeed Magician http://anidb.net/ch35588 [Fudo Gen] excavates the so-called Vectors in the sea near Crete. These three legendary machines, Mars, Luna and Sol, are now piloted by gifted youths possessing the Element to activate them, and to unite as the legendary Mechanical Angel Aquarion... but only if their heart, body, and soul can synchronize.
Source: official site, adapted by mahou (edited)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2528">4.94</permanent>
<temporary count="2571">7.12</temporary>
<review count="9">6.55</review>
</ratings>
<picture>73052.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4796</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>478</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1672</identifier>
<identifier>mrcohd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.aquarion.info/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Genesis_of_Aquarion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>創聖のアクエリオン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322360</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7313</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0017X3H3Q</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3121" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-05">
<name>twisted ending</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3771" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>recycled animation -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag overlaps recaps, http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks], and http://anidb.net/t3671 [footage reuse]. For that reason, it is set to be split. If you can, please apply the correct tag to the anime that have it, and remove this one from them; guidance on how to use each of those tags can be found in their description. If what the anime contains is a mere recap, please don`t apply any tag at all, and remove this tag from it instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4379" parentid="6090" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>Yggdrasil</name>
<description>In Norse mythology, Yggdrasil (/ˈɪɡdrəsɪl/ or /ˈɪɡdrəzɪl/; from Old Norse Yggdrasill, pronounced [ˈyɡːˌdrasilː]) is an immense tree that is central in Norse cosmology, in connection to which the nine worlds exist.
This anime contains a system or other-worldly existence, based on Norse mythology, called Yggdrasil.</description>
<picurl>169458.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5763" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>rock-paper-scissors</name>
<description>Whenever a decision has to be made in anime, the Japanese protagonists seem to be awfully fond of playing rock-paper-scissors (or jan-ken-pon) to determine the outcome.</description>
<picurl>62869.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5910" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>diet</name>
<description>One or more of the characters in this anime go on a diet, to lose some weight. Typically a female character will be extremely distressed that her clothes no longer fit, or that her ideal weight has been exceeded. Ironically, normal growth is often the explanation.
Since diets do not work, this ends up as a comedy element, with many ridiculous attempts to get slim quickly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6090" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Norse mythology</name>
<description>Norse mythology, or Scandinavian mythology, is the body of mythology of the North Germanic people stemming from Norse paganism and continuing after the Christianization of Scandinavia and into the Scandinavian folklore of the modern period. The Norse mythology consists of tales of various deities, beings, and heroes derived from numerous sources from both before and after the pagan period, including medieval manuscripts, archaeological representations, and folk tradition. [...]
Most of the surviving mythology centres on the plights of the gods and their interaction with various other beings, such as humanity and the jötnar, beings who may be friends, lovers, foes and/or family members of the gods. The cosmos in Norse mythology consist of Nine Worlds that flank a central cosmological tree, Yggdrasil. Units of time and elements of the cosmology are personified as deities or beings. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35584" type="main character in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="16">7.52</rating>
<name>Apollo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1203.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35585" type="main character in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="41">6.07</rating>
<name>Silvia de Alisia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1205.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35586" type="main character in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="11">2.35</rating>
<name>Sirius de Alisia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1212.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35587" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="1">2.29</rating>
<name>Jean Jerome Jorge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1215.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35588" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="14">8.50</rating>
<name>Fudou Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1216.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35589" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="6">5.15</rating>
<name>Sophia Belin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1219.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35590" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="5">6.55</rating>
<name>Pierre Vieira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1221.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35591" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="9">5.06</rating>
<name>Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1222.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35592" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="4">3.13</rating>
<name>Jun Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1224.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35593" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="4">5.55</rating>
<name>Tsugumi Rosenmeier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1225.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5011" picture="68997.jpg">Higasayama Tsugumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35594" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="14">5.96</rating>
<name>Rena Rune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1226.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5940" picture="29893.jpg">Satou Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35595" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Glen Anderson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="310" picture="17147.jpg">Kazama Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35596" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="4">4.06</rating>
<name>Kurt Klick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1227.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35597" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="4">6.69</rating>
<name>Chloe Klick</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1227.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35598" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Toma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1228.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35599" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-09">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Johannes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1229.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="609" picture="1835.gif">Aomori Shin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35600" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="2">3.45</rating>
<name>Otoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1230.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2184" picture="49347.jpg">Hyoudou Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35601" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Moroha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35602" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-19">
<rating votes="3">4.39</rating>
<name>Futaba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35603" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Lensi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35604" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Shilha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35605" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-14">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Goushi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44875.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="34082" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35248" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天翅の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of Heavenly Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I ricordi dell`angelo</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Niebiańskie skrzydła</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความทรงจำของเทพยดา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Kioku</title>
<summary>When the Shadow Angels invade after 12,000 years of slumber, one young man - Apollo - could be the prophesized missing piece that finally completes Aquarion.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35621" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beast of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Bestia ciemności</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สัตว์ร้ายแห่งความมืด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Kemono</title>
<summary>The Elements lose their edge, their souls unraveling in battle. Aquarion is torn asunder and the situation looks grim - until Apollo joins the fight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35713" update="2010-11-10">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35752" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エレメントスクール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Element School</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Szkolenie podstawowe</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เอเลเมนต์สคูล</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Element School</title>
<summary>Apollo reports for duty with the new Elements, making some of the more experienced pilots touchy. When an alien harvesting team appears in the city, veteran and rookie alike are pushed to the limits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35753" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裸足の戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Barefoot Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Bosonogi wojownik</title>
<title xml:lang="th">นักรบเท้าเปล่า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hadashi no Senshi</title>
<summary>The recruits undergo a strange training exercise at the will of Gen Fudo, their new commander. Paying attention to the odd lesson could mean surviving versus perishing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36308" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下迷宮の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of the Underground Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Król podziemnego labiryntu</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ราชันย์แห่งเขาวงกตใต้ดิน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Meikyuu no Ou</title>
<summary>Apollo goes AWOL and the team is sent out to find him. His motivations for vanishing are personal, and his vendetta puts the whole team at risk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36442" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想い彼方へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Other Side of Emotions</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ku Odległej Stronie Myśli</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความคิดคำนึงแแสนไกล</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi Kanata e</title>
<summary>Apollo and the other recruits begin work on their telekinetic abilities, enhancing the powers of their imaginations and spirits. The new techniques create a connection easily transferred into fighting strategy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36516" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真紅の薔薇の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knight of the Crimson Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Rycerz Szkarłatnej Róży</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อัศวินกุหลาบแดง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinku no Bara no Kishi</title>
<summary>As the pressure for perfect unity mounts, the recruits’ feelings are getting ragged. If victory is to be assured, the Vector pilots must embrace their darkness. Only in their weakness will true strength be found.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36517" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての合体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Merge</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pierwsze Zjednoczenie</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การรวมร่างครั้งแรก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Gattai</title>
<summary>When you’re one of the few recruits that haven’t experienced a merge, it’s easy to get the wrong idea about it. If you get too excited, things can get explosive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36518" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢のかよひじ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Path to Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ścieżka Snów</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เส้นทางแห่งความฝัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Kayoiji</title>
<summary>A Harvest Beast has opened the door to human dreams and the Shadow Angels seem to be plucking children from their sleep. The fighters take an amazing risk to save them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36661" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空に星, 地に花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stars in the Sky, Flowers on the Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Gwiazdy na niebie, kwiaty na Ziemi</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดวงดาวพราวนภา บุปผาพร่างปฐพี</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora ni Hoshi, Chi ni Hana</title>
<summary>The Shadow Angels unleash a dreadful new weapon, designed to be guided by their most powerful warrior. Elements are seriously injured and must heal while the Vectors are repaired in the field.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36662" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水底のしあわせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happiness Is at the Bottom of the Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Szczęście na dnie jeziora</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความสุขที่ก้นสายน้ำ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suitei no Shiawase</title>
<summary>A crisis of confidence has shaken Reika to the core, forcing the depressed pilot to leave the program and her partners behind.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36663" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">琥珀の時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Time of Amber</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Bursztyn Czasu</title>
<title xml:lang="th">กาลเวลาของอำพัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kohaku no Toki</title>
<summary>An artifact from a holy scripture unleashes a flood of recollection, igniting the souls of Apollo and Silvia. Toma himself visits the Earth in a war machine - and Apollo is in the crosshairs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37148" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一万二千年のラブレター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A 12,000-Year-Old Love Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Miłość sprzed 12 tysięcy lat</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จดหมายรักหมื่นสองพันปี</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichi Man Nisen Nen no Love Letter</title>
<summary>Apollo may be a beast, but Toma knows his weakness: the loyalty that will allow the Shadow Angel access to the relic.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37928" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光る影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Shadows</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Cień</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เงาที่ส่องแสง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikaru Kage</title>
<summary>The Shadow Angels are depending on the Solar Wing to deliver them unto a new world - but who is the true Solar Wing? Silvia struggles to make sense of past lives and present frustrations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37929" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初恋のアクエリオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aquarion`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pierwsza miłość</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รักแรกของอควอเรี่ยน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsukoi no Aquarion</title>
<summary>Pierre has grown addicted to merging, and there’s a real chance his mind will slip into madness if he ever does it again. When the Shadow Angels attack his hometown, Pierre must choose his fate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38243" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い鏡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Mroczne zwierciadło</title>
<title xml:lang="th">กระจกสีดำ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Kagami</title>
<summary>The recruits grow uneasy when one among them is suspected of being a vampire. As rumors float through the base, mysterious sicknesses and strange encounters within the team have Silvia intrigued.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38244" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食べたくて合体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Merge to Eat</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Głodówka</title>
<title xml:lang="th">รวมร่างหิวโหย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabetakute Gattai</title>
<summary>The Shadow Angels are disgusted by the gluttonous dreams of humanity. Exploiting the ultimate weakness as punishment, the Earth’s food supply begins to vanish and the populace is soon starving.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38672" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">けがれなき悪戯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischief Without Malice</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Niewinny żart</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การกลั่นแกล้งที่ไร้เดียงสา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegarenaki Itazura</title>
<summary>As the pilots wander in a strange land of twisted dreams, Aquarion lays broken - and Apollo and the others struggle to stay sane.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38673" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天翅の翅音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sound of an Angel`s Feather</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dźwięk skrzydeł</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เสียงปีกของแองเจิิล</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten no Hane Oto</title>
<summary>A young Shadow Angel is captured and the creature is poked and prodded in a cold laboratory. The horrible result of the torture leaves two species boiling in anger
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="38856" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂のコスプレイヤー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cosplay of the Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Przebierańcy</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คอสเพลย์ด้วยวิญญาณ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii no Cosplayer</title>
<summary>To become intimately familiar with their partners, the Aquarion recruits are commanded to dress and act like their counterparts. Some will have their feelings hurt before the lessons of the exercise become clear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39349" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅い道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crimson Path</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Szkarłatna ścieżka</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เส้นทางสายสีแดง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurenai Michi</title>
<summary>The Shadow Angels lust for revenge after the loss of one of their own. The line between good and evil begins to blur as secrets are revealed and bonds tested.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="39350" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見えない翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wings Unseen</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Niewidoczne skrzydła</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปีกที่มองไม่เห็น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mienai Tsubasa</title>
<summary>Ex-comrades meet on the battlegrounds of a new war. Element will fight Element, the dead will rise to fight their own, and the true Solar Wing will be revealed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40482" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翼, 儚く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fleeting Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ulotne skrzydła</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปีกที่ไม่สมหวัง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa, Hakanaku</title>
<summary>A next generation Aquarion appears and joins the fight, piloted by a victim of the unending war. As tradition and dreams clash, one girl takes a stand.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40483" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空のゲート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heaven`s Gate</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wrota Niebios</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ประตูสวรรค์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkuu no Gate</title>
<summary>The Shadow Angels have gained the upper hand now that Sirius has joined them. Apollo must open the gates to Heaven and undertake a dangerous rescue mission - though it may already be too late.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40484" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦!! アトランティス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle! Atlandia</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Bitwa o Atlantydę</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ศึกตัดสิน!! แอทแลนเดีย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen!! Atlantis</title>
<summary>The remaining members of the Aquarion team have broken through to Atlandia! Sirius and Apollo meet in combat, heading toward their final destiny.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="40629" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界のはじまりの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day the World Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Dzień Narodzin Świata</title>
<title xml:lang="th">วันกำเนิดโลก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Hajimari no Hi</title>
<summary>The secrets of the Solar Wing have been revealed, and Aquarion may be forced to make the final sacrifice in order to save the souls of every sentient being.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126230" update="2010-12-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126231" update="2010-12-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126232" update="2010-12-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
