<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2833" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2005-06-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Izumo: Takeki Tsurugi no Senki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">イズモ -たけきつるぎのせんき-</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">出云战记</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Izumo TTnS</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Izumo2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">IZUMO -猛き剣の閃記-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Izumo: Flash of a Brave Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Izumo</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1987" type="Prequel">Izumo (2003)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="151117">well most of characters and stories copied from other anime but still watchable.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://trinet.cata.jp/izumo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="906" type="Original Work">Studio e.go!</name>
<name id="966" type="Animation Work">Studio Kyuuma</name>
<name id="967" type="Animation Work">Trinet Entertainment</name>
<name id="4534" type="Character Design">Kobayashi Takashi</name>
<name id="3499" type="Direction">Tominaga Tsuneo</name>
<name id="18385" type="Series Composition">Kawakami Osamu</name>
<name id="4534" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the H-RPG by http://anidb.net/cr906 [Studio e.go!].
Yagi Takeru is a student who goes to the Izumo Academy. He lost his parents when he was little, but he got adopted by Touma Rokusuke, who is like a grandfather to him.
Takeru spends his days by getting kendo training from his grandfather and being with his friends like his kendo rival Yamato Takeshi, his childhood friend Shiratori Kotono and her sister Asuka.
Because Takeshi isn`t chosen as the representative for the kendo tournament, he takes it out on Kotono, but starts to argue with Takeru instead when Takeru and the others arrives.
While they are arguing, mysterious light and woman appears which suddenlly causes phase shifting and blinding blue light to be emitted from Takeshi hands then body while he screams in pain. Later they wake up scattered all through the school. The school is covered in vegetation and infested with insect monsters and the town is gone.
After finding each other they gather in the schoolyard and while they are trying to figure things out, six big men in suspicious outfits appear and move towards them. They locate Takeshi and once again the mysterious woman appears. She uses teleportation magic to kidnap Takeshi and Kotono. Then armed men on horses appear and attack the suspicious men.
What does the future hold for Takeru and the others in this strange world?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="612">3.12</permanent>
<temporary count="618">6.17</temporary>
<review count="1">2.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>205296.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5092</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2523</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1696</identifier>
<identifier>gyqjjb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://trinet.cata.jp/izumo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Izumo:_Takeki_Tsurugi_no_Senki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>IZUMO_-猛き剣の閃記-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>582</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322722</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7311</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="35487" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の呼び声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Voice Calling From Within a Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Yobigoe</title>
<summary>In Takeru`s dreams, he hears a girl call out to him, saying she needs his strength to save the world. In the waking world, a new transfer student, yet also a familiar face, joins Takeru`s class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788358</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35488" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">分かたれた友</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Separated Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakatareta Tomo</title>
<summary>In the midst of a chaotic battle, Takeru must protect his friends. The group meets the village chief, Amaterasu, whom teaches them the nature of the world they find themselves in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788362</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35489" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Foreign World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikai</title>
<summary>When Takeru comes to, he finds himself in what appears to be their school, but it`s completely destroyed and overrun with greenery. After meeting with the others, they begin to investigate what has happened to them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788360</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35490" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この世の姿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way This World Is</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Yo no Sugata</title>
<summary>A weakened soldier returns to the base, and Takeru learns that Takeshi may have sided with the evil spirits. Takeru asks Kagutsuchi for permission to meet with the person who may have seen Takeshi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788364</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35543" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuugeki</title>
<summary>Mai still hasn`t returned. When Seri and Sakuya go out looking for her, they find her collapsed in the middle of nowhere. On their way back to the village they make a startling discovery.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788365</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35628" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35754" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四聖獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four Heavenly Beasts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiseijuu</title>
<summary>They group learns that Sakuya may have the power to return everyone to their original world. In order to help her use the anti-spirit technique they need, they seek out the help of the four sacred beasts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788368</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35919" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決の砦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fortress of the Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu no Toride</title>
<summary>Takeru goes berserk when Asuka and Mai are taken by the enemy. The four sacred beasts help Takeru and his friends in their rescue mission as they set out for the evil spirit`s fortress.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788371</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36176" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やすらかな時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Peaceful Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasuraka na Toki</title>
<summary>Takeru`s group has returned to their original world with Sakuya in tow. They enjoy showing her the differences between the two worlds, but Sakuya can`t help worrying about the state of affairs back in Nenokuni.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788372</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36545" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二つの魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Tamashii</title>
<summary>Takeru reaches Himiko`s shrine, but more ordeals stand in his way. Thus begins the race against time to bring Takeshi to his senses and stop Himiko.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788380</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36546" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛る命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Raging Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takeru Inochi</title>
<summary>Takeshi has learned the truth behind Susano-Oh`s spirit. It`s time for he and Takeru to settle the score between them once and for all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788378</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36547" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄泉比良坂(ヨモツヒラサカ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yomotsuhirasaka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomotsuhirasaka</title>
<summary>Takeru and company arrive in Yomotsu-Hirasaka, the land where spirits of the dead dwell.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788376</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36548" update="2019-09-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守るべきもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Things I ought to protect</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamorubeki Mono</title>
<summary>Himiko attacks the second Takeru`s group returns to Nenokuni. Kotono attempts to protect Takeru, but her spirit is blown away in the process. With the four sacred beast`s help, they set out to retrieve her spirit before it`s too late.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>788374</identifier>
<identifier>izumo-flash-of-a-brave-sword</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128019" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128020" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
