<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2835" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2005-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hachimitsu to Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Honey &amp; Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Мёд и клевер</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Miód i koniczyna</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">W poszukiwaniu czterolistnej koniczyny</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Mel e Trevo</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="synonym">Μέλι και Τριφύλλι</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">דבש ותלתן</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Bal Ve Yonca</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Мед и Детелина</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hachimitsu &amp; Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hachimitsu to Kuroba</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Мед з конюшиною</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Мед і клевер І</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">عسل و شبدر</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">h&amp;c</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HachiKuro</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハチミツとクローバー</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">蜂蜜与四叶草</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Honey and Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Honey &amp; Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Honey &amp; Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Honey &amp; Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Med a Čtyřlístek</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Méz és lóhere</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">หวานใจกับใบโคลเวอร์</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Honey &amp; Clover</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Хъни и Кловър</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4422" type="Sequel">Hachimitsu to Clover II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4691" approval="113" total="153">Nodame Cantabile</anime>
<anime id="8181" approval="59" total="110">Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</anime>
<anime id="4143" approval="54" total="87">Nana</anime>
<anime id="9153" approval="29" total="54">Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo</anime>
<anime id="11606" approval="24" total="29">Sangatsu no Lion</anime>
<anime id="9771" approval="11" total="19">Golden Time</anime>
<anime id="6238" approval="8" total="28">Higashi no Eden</anime>
<anime id="1783" approval="5" total="21">Genshiken</anime>
<anime id="10288" approval="3" total="13">Bokura wa Minna Kawai-sou</anime>
<anime id="1648" approval="1" total="15">Aishiteru ze Baby</anime>
<anime id="5584" approval="1" total="13">Special A</anime>
<anime id="3215" approval="1" total="12">Canvas 2: Niji-iro no Sketch</anime>
<anime id="2443" approval="1" total="11">Mahoraba: Heartful Days</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="29">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="321621">It should pull your heartstrings in one way or another... I know I`ve been crying every other episode or so. :(</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="51579">YOU MUST WATCH THIS SERIES. The reasons are vast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you like art, well... you got it. This series is perfectly planned. Even the houses have their inside design planned by the staff. Moreover, the background art is really a good one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you like character development, you got it. You have mainly 4 characters and all of them have an adequate place in your heart, even if you do not identify yourself with them all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you like comedy, you got Morita-san. He will make sure to keep you entertained.&lt;br /&gt;And if you like drama, you got it too! But if drama is all you are after, check the second season `cause it`s way more dramatic. It also focuses on human problems, which resembles to those movies like Crash, Scent of a Woman, Magnolia and so on.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372636">VERY slowpaced drama with many depths that leaves a warm feeling in the stomach. Carefully drawn portraits of people with layers that makes them very loveable. I was impressed by very innovative ways of drawing - poses, expressions, angles that aren`t very usual and made this anime come alive in a way that`s quite unique. I started off quite blasé but actually fell for it pretty hard.&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="66705">Mielestäni tosi söpö anime, jonka hahmot on hyvin pidettäviä. Mutta yksi niistä tosiaan näyttää pikkutytöltä...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="33925">I`ve never seen an anime that I liked better than Honey and Clover. The slapstick humor, the drama, the music; it`s all so brilliantly put together than once you start watching, there`s not really any way of turning back. A must- see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="364222">Superb. Intellectual romantic and humorous. Gives you something to think about instead of just making random jokes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="76529">This is a must see for anyone who loves heartfelt, funny in the right places, serious when it needs to be, overall awesome characters and anime.
One of the best I`ve seen!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="290186">A rarely seen character devellopment combined with a moving storyline. Not only a drama but nevertheless a comedy, which doesn`t take itself too serious, a very nice mixture. This is an anime for everyone, who is into compelling stories.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="281953">Personlly I think this is the best anime of all I`ve seen. Must see. Nothing to add here.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="120720">The absolute best slice-of-life anime I`ve ever seen. Good pacing and great character development drive the series. It never got old. Same for the sequel.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="554983">The character development is outstanding, and the mix of drama and comedy is really pleasing. I love laughing over comedy elements while being deeply moved by the characters feelings.

The last picture of the show demonstrates what a well-thought piece of art Honey and Clover is.

On my way to watching the second season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="531127">This is one of the best anime I`ve watched. Enjoyable, Awesome, Realistic, Wonderful, I never known other like this. Great characters design, music, visual art, EVERYTHING IS GREAT. You must to see, recommended 100%!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="237158">One of the best slapstick anime I know. Pulls you in, you stay in until the end :))</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="332307">This is a must see for all anime lovers. ESpecially who are stressed and trapped between the same and repetative scripts and novels. Make a difference and watch Honey and Clover. Totally worth the time spent.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.hachikuro.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2187" type="Character Design">Shimamura Hidekazu</name>
<name id="3031" type="Original Work">Umino Chika</name>
<name id="654" type="Direction">Kasai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="4163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshida Takahiko</name>
<name id="5670" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuzou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr3031 [Umino Chika].
http://anidb.net/ch7794 [Takemoto Yuuta], http://anidb.net/ch7800 [Mayama Takumi] and http://anidb.net/ch7796 [Morita Shinobu] are three art school students, friends and flat-mates. Yuuta, the freshman, lives in terror of Shinobu, a very erratic sculptor.
Their routine is disrupted when their teacher, http://anidb.net/ch10225 [Hanamoto Shuuji], introduces them to his cousin`s daughter, http://anidb.net/ch7798 [Hanamoto Hagumi]. Even though she has already entered college, she still looks like a middle school student. Yet despite her appearance, she is a talented sculptor and painter with several gallery showings already in her portfolio. Naturally, all the men around her fall in love with her...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6902">8.19</permanent>
<temporary count="7014">8.41</temporary>
<review count="17">8.98</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133493.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4975</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1688</identifier>
<identifier>isjecv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hachikuro.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.viz.com/anime/streaming/honey-and-clover</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Honey_and_Clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ハチミツとクローバー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>592</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322362</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7248</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2005/hachikuro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="601" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>bicycle</name>
<description>A bicycle, often called a bike or cycle, is a human-powered, pedal-driven, single-track vehicle, having two wheels attached to a frame, one behind the other. A bicycle rider is called a cyclist, or bicyclist.
Souce: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>172772.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2666" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>art school</name>
<description>The education in art plays an important part in this anime.
Art school is a general term for any educational institution with a primary focus on the visual arts, especially illustration, painting, photography, sculpture, and graphic design. The term applies to institutions with elementary, secondary, post-secondary or undergraduate, or graduate or postgraduate programs in these areas. They are distinguished from larger institutions which also may offer majors or degrees in the visual arts, but only as one part of a broad-based range of programs (such as the liberal arts and sciences). France`s École des Beaux-Arts is, perhaps, the first model for such organized instruction, breaking with a tradition of master and apprentice instruction when it was formed.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4344" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-26">
<name>motivational anime</name>
<description>The anime motivates doing something which is shown in the show (for example club activity, sports, choosing a job, a hobby etc).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5944" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-28">
<name>i got a crush on you</name>
<description>It happens when a person develops an interest in someone that seems mysterious, smart, sexy, cute, fun, etc. Basically just someone you would like to spend more time with. Crushes are usually one sided and they happen more frequently among middle and high school students.
A person with a crush usually has a hard time expressing or conveying his/her feelings to that other person. That other person is usually clueless of the situation. Sometimes that person knows about the crush, but feels annoyed or embarrassed by it for some reason.
Having a crush on someone does not mean you are in love with that person, at least not yet. Depending on the situation crushes could develop differently (for better or worse):
1) Larger scale interactions (love).
2) Dating relationships.
3) Scary obsession or stalker type situations.
4) Disappear over time or distance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7794" type="main character in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="82">7.20</rating>
<name>Takemoto Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takemoto Yuuta is a second-year art student, age 19 at the start of the series, living in the same apartment complex as Mayama and Morita. Takemoto is the primary point-of-view of the series, and often acts as narrator of episodes. He is depicted as the most mellow of the main characters. He falls in love with Hagu immediately after being introduced by his professor but keeps his feelings to himself through most of the series. Because of his inability to act upon his feelings as freely as Morita, Takemoto decides to act as a brother-figure to Hagu, giving her friendly support when needed, for example, building her sophisticated dollhouses at her request. Later in the series, as a result of his conflicted emotions, Takemoto develops a stomach ulcer, forcing him to repeat a year of school. Early in the series, he questions his vocation as an artist, but over the series he becomes comfortable with himself. After a bicycle trip to Cape Souya, the northernmost point in Japan, Takemoto gains the confidence to tell Hagu how he really feels. Although Hagu does not accept him, Takemoto admits that just meeting her and the time they spend together has influenced him.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7796" type="main character in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="143">8.38</rating>
<name>Morita Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morita Shinobu is a sixth-year art student, age 24 at the start of the series, in the same apartment complex as Takemoto and Mayama. Morita is depicted as a perpetual student, unable to graduate because of persistent absenteeism. This is mainly due to his work, which forces him to go missing for several days, after which he sleeps for at least 48 hours. Morita is considered mysterious by the other students, prone to bizarre behavior such as creating a version of Twister with too many colors. He is a perceptive person who cares for his friends Takemoto and Mayama but often expressing himself tactlessly, and who is not generous with his money and food. He also expresses his desire for Hagu in quirky ways, such as forcing her to dress up as a mouse because he likes cute things. Later in the series, he departs for a year in America, and eventually the others learn he has been moonlighting as an award-winning CGI artist.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7798" type="main character in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="68">3.85</rating>
<name>Hanamoto Hagumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanamoto Hagumi is usually called Hagu by her friends, she is an 18-year-old first-year art student at the start of the series. She is depicted as appearing and acting several years younger than her true age. Despite her appearance, she is a gifted artist and her work is highly praised by art professionals. She is shy and very nervous when interacting with people, to the point of becoming physically ill from stress, with the result that other art students think she is strange. She was raised by her grandmother in a sheltered environment, where she learned to draw sketching the ever-changing view from her porch. When Morita and Takemoto first meet Hagu, they both immediately fall in love with her, although they express it in different ways. Hagu spends most of the series unaware of their feelings for her, seeing them as friends. After Takemoto confesses his feelings for her, she begins avoiding him, and at the end of the series she admits she loves Morita. However, she returns to Shuuji because she cannot imagine a life without drawing.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="257" picture="17078.jpg">Kudou Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7800" type="main character in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="51">6.12</rating>
<name>Mayama Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayama Takumi is a fourth-year art student, age 22 at the start of the series, in the same apartment complex as Takemoto and Morita. He acts as a senpai (senior) to Takemoto and tries to help Morita get up for early morning classes. Early in the series, Mayama helps Rika Harada out with various errands at her design firm, Harada Design, during which time he develops feelings for Rika. The series initially leaves unclear whether Mayama takes advantage of Rika`s disability to fulfill his desires, but it is later shown that Rika reciprocates his feelings. At her urging, Mayama begins working for a different design firm, but after it breaks up, near the end of the series, he returns to work for Rika. Despite Yamada`s throwing herself at him, Mayama considers her only as his close friend, but he becomes protective of her when a colleague with a reputation for playing girls develops an interest in her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7802" type="main character in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="85">7.79</rating>
<name>Yamada Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamada Ayumi is a third-year art student, age 21 at the start of the series, specializing in ceramic arts. She is well-known by other students for her pottery and her nickname Tetsujin Iron Lady for running 6 km to school every morning to help her dog lose weight. She is depicted as a beautiful young woman, who catches the attention of her male friends and coworkers. Yamada is deeply in love with Mayama, but he does not return her feelings and repeatedly encourages her to find someone else. Later in the series, she is angered by Mayama`s sudden protectiveness when he tries to shield her from his former boss, Nomiya. Yamada is close friends with Hagu, who addresses her by first name. At the end of the series, Yamada continues as a graduate student in art, while making pottery for Harada Design.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>26832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10225" type="main character in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="35">6.67</rating>
<name>Hanamoto Shuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanamoto Shuuji is a professor at the college that Morita, Mayama, Takemoto, Yamada, and Hagu attend, serving as the father figure for the group. He is also Hagu`s relative (he is father`s cousin) and the person that Hagu is really closest to, and gets very overprotective of her at times. Shuuji is a close friend of Rika and her late husband, who had been his roommate until Rika and her husband married. Unlike his friends, Shuuji`s artistic talent was not remarkably impressive, but found he was good at explaining things like art history and anatomy (subjects which Harada and Rika shruggled with) and eventually decided to become a teacher as a result.
When Rika`s husband died in a traffic accident, he took care of Rika so that she wouldn`t try and join her husband in death, but Shuuji begins to wonder if Rika would`ve been happier if she died alongside her husband. Because of this, Shuuji recommends Mayama as Rika`s new assistant; he believed Mayama`s companionship would be a healthy change for Rika.</description>
<picture>30665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10228" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="37">6.98</rating>
<name>Harada Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harada Rika is the founder and manager of Harada Design. She also ran it with her husband until he died in a car accident that happened on the opening night of one of the stores they designed. This accident also left her badly scarred on her back, and has damaged her legs so she is unable to walk for long periods without the help of a cane and medicine. During college, Egami Rika had been known for being a talented artist, but also very cold and aloof. Harada, Rika`s eventual husband, befriended her and she began to live in the apartment Harada and Shuuji shared. The three were very close friends and continued to live together until Harada and Rika got married and founded Harada Design. She is from the city of Otaru in Hokkaidou.
When Professor Hanamoto believes that his presence will hinder Rika`s recovery, he sends Mayama to help her, believing that Mayama would be the least likely to intrude on other people`s business. However, as Mayama tends to Rika`s injuries, he develops feelings for her. Rika knows that Mayama likes her, but pushes Mayama away because she doesn`t want to hurt him. It was unclear whether Rika reciprocates the feelings that Mayama has for her, but later chapters of the manga and the first episodes of the second series seem to imply that she does. Later in the series, it appears that Rika finally opens her heart to Mayama after a shock ending sequence where Mayama`s feelings finally flood out.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10229" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="4">5.19</rating>
<name>Aida Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aida Mitsuko is Takemoto`s mother. Works as a nurse. She remarried when Takemoto finished junior high school.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10230" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="3">6.40</rating>
<name>Aida Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aida Kazuo is Takemoto`s stepfather. He is an affable and loud man, but Takemoto has difficulty getting used to him because of how different Kazuo is from his father. Kazuo often means well, but is not terribly articulate and usually tries to use his actions to express what he means. He and his family accept both Takemoto and his mother as part of their family, though Takemoto still feels as though he does not belong.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10231" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="2">5.53</rating>
<name>Shouda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shouda is another elderly teacher at the art institute that every attends, Shouda is Yamada`s supervising instructor and an extremely avid admirer of her work, along with her Iron Lady fans. He is especially impressed with Yamada`s graduation project, a beautifully thrown and large bowl, to point of weeping tears of joy and expresses the same reaction when she creates a similar and equally large bowl post-graduation. After Yamada graduates, she decides to continue studying with Shouda as a post-graduate student until she can find a job.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10232" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-07">
<rating votes="3">6.43</rating>
<name>Tokudaiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10233" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="6">6.33</rating>
<name>Tange</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tange is a teacher and the professor emeritus of sculpture at the art institute everyone attends, elderly Tange-sensei is a long suffering supervisor to Morita. Recognizing Morita`s genius, Tange makes the mistake of taking Morita seriously and constantly finds himself stressed out while trying to control Morita. Tange`s greatest desire is to get Morita to finish his graduation project (and with Morita`s talent, it means refusing to accept unfinished works) so that he may retire in peace. When Morita is finally completes his graduation project, Tange expresses bittersweet sentiments towards the role of teacher. Despite constantly upsetting Tange, Morita greatly appreciates and respects Tange for all that he has done for Morita in their eight years together. After Morita graduates and then re-enrolls as a third year student, Morita transfers his attention to Nakamori Okina, the professor emeritus of Classical Japanese painting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10234" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="8">5.74</rating>
<name>Morita Kaoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morita Kaoru is Morita Shinobu`s older brother who seems to have a mysterious agenda in earning ridiculously large amounts of money.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2233" picture="21784.jpg">Takewaka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10235" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="14">4.17</rating>
<name>Nomiya Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nomiya Takumi, along with Yamazaki and Miwako, is first introduced on episode 14 of season 1. Nomiya is the type of guy who could throw a cellphone in the sea full of women`s numbers, without caring at all as said by Mayama. Mayama is somewhat adverse to him, partially because he sees Nomiya as the ideal professional he wants to become and dislikes the comparison and also because of Nomiya`s interest in Yamada.
Nomiya is Mayama`s former boss at Fujiwara Design. He is decribed as handsome, intelligent and somewhat workaholic. Though he`s deemed by Mayama as a playboy, and is actually quite experienced with women, he falls in love with Yamada. He tries to visit her whenever he can, although he is aware of Yamada`s feelings for Mayama. Mayama tries to act as the middleman as much as he can in order to protect Yamada, as he doubts the sincerity of Nomiya`s feelings. However, Mayama finally gives in, realizing that Nomiya isn`t as evil as he thought. There are hints of this couple at the end of the series.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10236" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="13">5.69</rating>
<name>Teshigawara Miwako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teshigawara Miwako is another employee at Fujiwara Design along with Nomiya and Yamazaki. She owns a dog named Leader. She enjoys teasing her co-workers to an extreme extent and has been described as someone who takes advantage of others like an old woman would. Miwako is a big fan of Rika`s work and also enjoys going to the health spa to relax.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10237" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="7">4.48</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Kazushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamazaki Kazushi is an employee at Fujiwara Design along with Nomiya and Miwako. He is romantically interested in his co-worker Miwako, but so far his love is unrequited. Yamazaki is somewhat shy around women, since he attended an all-boys high school and did not have the opportunity to meet many female students while he studying engineering in college.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="34829" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35865" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="51">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじまりの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day It All Began</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A szerelem első pillanata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Hi</title>
<summary>Takemoto Yuuta, a second-year student at an art school, desperate tries to wake up sixth-year student, Morita Shinobu, for school, in order to prevent Morita from repeating yet another school year. Later on, Takemoto and Mayama Takumi, a fourth-year student, are introduced to Hanamoto "Hagu" Hagumi by Hanamoto Shuuji, her father`s cousin. However, Morita also meets Hagu, causing him to constantly take pictures of her.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784224</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="35866" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2つの恋が回り出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Affections Start to Turn</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az első lépések</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Koi ga Mawari-dasu</title>
<summary>Takemoto and Mayama soon discover Hagu`s artistic talents. They, as well as Hagu, discover Morita`s website which contains a collection of pictures featuring Hagu. Hagu gets upset and throws random objects at Morita, which included her wish list. Meanwhile, Takemoto plans to throw a teppanyaki party. Later, after his job, Morita spots one of the items from Hagu`s list, a pair of patent pink mules, in a store and buys it as a present for Hagu. Morita arrives back in a drowsy state and gives two bags of meat for Takemoto`s party, as well as the mules for Hagu. Hagu is delighted and Morita faints from exhaustion from his job. Takemoto offers to carry him home and suddenly notices his feelings towards Hagu on the way back.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784225</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36276" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="28">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは2つの片思い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">These Were Two Unrequited Loves</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Két szerelem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Futatsu no Kataomoi</title>
<summary>It is late summer. Takemoto, Mayama, and Morita are coming back from an evening bath when Takemoto receives a phone call from Hagu inviting them all over for dinner the next evening. Mayama and Morita decide not to go, leaving Takemoto to have dinner with Hagu and Professor Hanamoto. Meanwhile, Mayama has developed feelings for Rika Harada, an older woman who is good friends with Professor Hanamoto, and is also Mayama`s boss. Ayumi Yamada, a friend of Mayama who has a crush on him, finds out about this and publicly chastises him for it. Later, Yamada approaches Mayama and asks why he works for Rika without mentioning his feelings for Rika. However, Mayama coldly tells Yamada that she should find another guy. Yamada is deeply hurt and cries about it to Morita.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784226</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36387" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼と彼女が揺れ動く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy and Girl Are Swayed</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Egy bizonytalan tánc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kare to Kanojo ga Yure-ugoku</title>
<summary>Mayama continues to battle over his feelings for Rika and his feelings for Yamada. Meanwhile, Hagu is overwhelmed by other people`s expectations of her artistic ability. The next day, Morita invites Takemoto, Mayama, Hagu, Professor Hanamoto, and Yamada to a Christmas party. Takemoto and Hagu go Christmas shopping, and it is revealed that Takemoto does not really like Christmas. Mayama visits Rika and learns that she is going out with Professor Hanamoto. The night of the Christmas party comes, and everyone has a good time. Mayama arrives late, and the party has become a little crazy. Mayama steps out to meet Professor Hanamoto, and asks where Rika is. Professor Hanamoto replies that she is at her husband`s, meaning that Rika is visiting the grave of her husband. Hagu interrupts their conversation, and Mayama and Professor Hanamoto join the party. At the end of the party, Mayama stays to clean up, and Professor Hanamoto takes everyone else home. Mayama stands by the window and thinks wistfully of Rika, and then Yamada. Morita startles Mayama out of his reverie, and the two drink. Takemoto is asleep, dreaming of a happy Christmas with himself and Hagu.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784227</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36601" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">故郷の母を想う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Think of My Mother in My Hometown</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Anyámra gondolok</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokyou no Haha o Omou</title>
<summary>Takemoto goes home to visit Mitsuko Aida, his mother, for the first time in a while. Takemoto`s father died years before, and Takemoto does not like Kazuo Aida, his mother`s love interest. While visiting, Takemoto realizes that Kazuo is not a replacement for his father, but someone to care for Mitsuko. He finds a respect for Kazuo. Later, Professor Hanamoto takes Takemoto, Hagu, Morita, and Yamada on a trip. Mayama is invited as well, but comes later.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784229</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="36720" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去と涙と告白と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Past, the Tears, the Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A múlt és egy vallomás</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako to Namida to Kokuhaku to</title>
<summary>Takemoto, Hagu, Morita, Mayama, Yamada, and Professor Hanamoto go to the zoo. Professor Hanamoto talks to Mayama and tells him about Rika`s husband. Professor Hanamoto lived with Rika her husband, and was very close to both of them. When Rika`s husband died in an accident, Professor Hanamoto took care of Rika, as she suffered major injuries in the accident. Professor Hanamoto also tells Mayama that Rika is hiring someone to replace Mayama. This is because Rika believes Mayama will get the job he applied for, but it is also because she has feelings for him, and it is too painful to have him around her. Later, Yamada decides to stay at the school as a graduate student. Mayama is notified that he has received a job at the place he applied to. Takemoto, Hagu, Morita, Mayama, Yamada, and Professor Hanamoto have a party to celebrate. Mayama carries a drunken Yamada home on his back and tells her that he thought she would leave if he turned her down. Yamada begins crying and tells him she loves him.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784230</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37280" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちは奇跡を探す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Look for a Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Keressük a csodát</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku-tachi wa Kiseki o Sagasu</title>
<summary>Professor Hanamoto is offered to travel with his old teacher for one year to gather research and survey material for a new book, and offers to bring Hagu along for the trip. Hagu refuses, stating she won`t be lonely because she now has friends, which is a stark contrast to Professor Hanamoto`s recollection of Hagu`s life prior to coming to the art school. Meanwhile, Mayama bids Rika farewell when she learns he has been hired and started working at the Fujiwara Design Office, promising he would return some day. Before Professor Hanamoto`s farewell party, Hagu tries to find a four-leaf clover to give Professor Hanamoto as a good luck charm, to which everyone coincidentally passes by and helps out to find. Ultimately, they are unsuccessful, although Professor Hanamoto`s appreciates the effort and Takemoto cherishes the memory of that day.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784231</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37544" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キミを放っておけなくて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because I Can`t Leave You Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Nem tudlak elengedni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi o Houtte Okenakute</title>
<summary>Yamada has moved in with Hagu, and the two invite Takemoto, Morita, and Mayama over for a strange dinner. It`s shown to humorous effect that Hagu and Professor Hanamoto greatly miss each other. After dinner, Mayama asks why they are gathered together, and no one seems to know. Takemoto replies that it`s his birthday, and everyone is very embarrassed. They all attempt to make up for it. Morita makes a Twister mat and cards with too many colors, and he and Takemoto become hopelessly entangled in it. Morita makes a joke about Mayama`s stalking, and Mayama leaves. Yamada sees him off. After Mayama has left, Yamada looks up at the sky and wonders how to give up on Mayama, and whether it`s worth it. Mayama, meanwhile, sits and stares at Rika`s window. The next day, Yamada has to leave Hagu alone in the apartment for a night. Takemoto remembers that he made it through his first night alone because of his friends, so he goes to visit Hagu. The two sit and talk late into the night.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784232</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37858" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そのブローチが重たくて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Brooch Was So Heavy</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A madaras kitűző</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Brooch ga Omotakute</title>
<summary>Morita makes and discreetly gives Hagu a brooch she wanted, while Takemoto fights feelings of jealousy and whether or not to tell Hagu who gave the brooch to her. Yamada also thanks Morita for bailing her out of a situation where she awkwardly tried to casually say that she loves Mayama. Christmas arrives, and Hagu begins her first part-time job by helping Yamada in the local shopping district. Takemoto is asked to help with decorations when Hagu and the shopping district try to win back business from a competing supermarket chain, and Takemoto has a change of heart over how he feels about Christmas. He also attempts to tell Hagu about the brooch during the ensuing Christmas party, but is interrupted by Morita who tells Hagu herself that there`s no deep meaning to it.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784235</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38238" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちは空を横切る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Fly Across the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Átússzuk az eget</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi wa Sora o Yokogiru</title>
<summary>After the school festival and Christmas passes by, the entire group goes on an outing by going on a water taxi ride along the Sumida River. On there, Mayama reveals to Takemoto he knows about Takemoto`s feelings toward Hagu and tells him to not give up. Their day continues when they arrive at the Kasai Seaside Park, only to find it largely deserted due to the season. They ride the Ferris wheel there, but end up in awkward seating arrangements due to Morita`s antics. On the water taxi ride back, Takemoto ponders about the group`s situation and how the new year will be like.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784237</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38473" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋に振り回されて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Pushes Us Around</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A szerelem az orrunknál fogva vezet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi ni Furimawasarete</title>
<summary>Takemoto and Yamada talk about Mayama`s future and how Hagu has grown before they are interrupted by Professor Hanamoto`s sudden and early return from his trip to Mongolia. Everyone then gathers at night to hear about Professor Hanamoto and his teacher`s trip. The next day, Hagu goes out shopping with Morita for art supplies due to everyone else being busy. Hagu wrests with her feelings for Morita as he treats her coldly the entire day. Eventually, Hagu returns and cries to Professor Hanamoto, nearly regressing to the past where she only trusts Professor Hanamoto.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784238</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38671" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突然のキス, 唐突な別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sudden Kiss, the Unexpected Parting</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Egy váratlan csók</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsuzen no Kiss, Toutotsu na Wakare</title>
<summary>It is spring again. The whole group attends the annual school festival. Some of them tell stories about what happened recently to them, while others think of their loved ones. Later on the next day, Hagu is still in an uncomfortable mood. She went out to buy tobacco for Professor Hanamoto and took a look of cherry blossoms for a while. Morita suddenly appears in his eccentric behavior, giving her his scarf and kissing her unconsciously. He ran away the moment he realized what he had just done. Hagu was quite shocked after that and she got a fever which, according to Professor Hanamoto, is often caused to her by stress. Professor Hanamoto told Takemoto about Hagu`s uncomfortable feelings while going out with Morita last time, and he said she did not realize that was because she liked him. Takemoto, feeling depressed, comes back home, finding the person responsible for summoning Morita to work, who is seen breaking into Morita`s overly secured room. The room shockingly resembled that of a master control room. This mysterious person then finds Morita`s passport, in order to be delivered to the airport. He then tells Takemoto that Morita is about to go to Los Angeles for six months for a job. Takemoto jumps into the car with him to go to airport but he could not make it in time to bid Morita farewell. The person is later revealed to be Morita`s older brother, Kaoru Morita, who also portrays eccentricity. Takemoto asks Kaoru whether Morita will return or not. In turn, Kaoru asks Takemoto whether or not he wants Morita to return.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784241</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39067" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そのたったひと言がききたくて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All I Wanted to Hear Was That Little Thing</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A várva várt szó</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Tatta Hitokoto ga Kikitakute</title>
<summary>Takemoto later announced the news about Morita leaving to Los Angeles to Hagu and the rest. Later, they all went to Morita`s room, since the door was destroyed by Kaoru. Takemoto asked Hagu whether or not she wants Morita to return, but her stern and straightforward answer before was really hurting him. The story mainly talked about Yamada and her feelings later on. To save money, Mayama asked Yamada to help making some artwork for his firm`s project. Takemoto, seeing Hagu all fired up creating her latest work, reminded him of Morita`s dedication in his work. Yamada invites Hagu along with the gang to the fireworks display that will be taking place that evening. Both Hagu and Yamada choose their yukatas for the event. Later that evening, Yamada, being conscious with her look, revealed that she just wanted Mayama to compliment her on her yukata. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784242</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39068" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の中で彼女に触れた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Touched Her in My Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Álmomban láttalak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Naka de Kanojo ni Fureta</title>
<summary>Mayama dreams of Rika. One of his co-workers, Miwako Teshigawara, says that when one dreams of another, it is because the person in the dream wants them to meet so much that the soul escapes the body and comes to the dream. Mayama was in doubt about that, but on the way back home from a meeting, he and his other co-workers, Takumi Nomiya and Kazushi Yamazaki, passed by a park where Rika was just behind a fountain watching him passing by. Mayama didn`t notice until later on. However, when he ran back to the fountain, she was not there anymore. Later, everyone at Mayama`s workplace began talking about Rika`s deceased husband, seemingly making Mayama realize that he was the only one who did not know Rika`s husband personally. Nomiya mentions Yamada, implying that he wants to meet her. Mayama then leaves the office, only to go to the festival with Takemoto, Hagu, Yamada, and Professor Hanamoto. He was followed later by Nomiya, Yamazaki, and Miwako, much to his chagrin. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784243</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39069" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卑怯な僕が走り出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Cowardly Self Starts Running</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Egy gyáva tett</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikyou na Boku ga Hashiridasu</title>
<summary>Mayama`s work is going well with his co-workers. Miwako noticed how well Mayama and Nomiya potted bowls. But this leads to Mayama discussing to his co-workers about his feelings toward Yamada. Yet he still misses Rika. Mayama and Nomiya head over to Yamada`s room, after they had finished their work for the day. They start gathering Yamada`s pottery to display at an art exhibition. However, Miwako calls Mayama to urgently come back to the office, concerning a scale model for a meeting the next day, as it has been accidentally broken. After noticing that Mayama left his coat at her place, Yamada reminisces with her time with Mayama. Nomiya comes in, as Yamada is in deep thought, which, in turn, startles her. Nomiya takes Yamada out in the evening to eat. Furious, Mayama develops jealousy, as he finds out that Nomiya went out with her last night. Yet Yamada becomes frustrated for his jealousy. Mayama converses with Professor Hanamoto about Rika, but Mayama ends up walking back home, disappointed. He starts to reminisce about Rika again, when suddenly he gets a call that Asai, Rika`s current assistant, suddenly has health problems and needs to stay in the hospital. Mayama meets Asai in the hospital, and he finds out that Rika is also in the hospital. He asks her if he can come back to him, but she rejects him. However, Mayama reluctantly offers her a ride home. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784245</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39396" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">が彼女を呼んでいる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moon Is Calling Her</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A Hold hívása</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki wa Kanojo o Yondeiru</title>
<summary>Nomiya tells Miwako that the firm will split into two locations. One will stay in Tokyo, while the other will move to Tottori. Nomiya intentionally wants Mayama to go to the firm in Tottori. At the same time, Asai is still in the hospital and Rika hasn`t been able to find a replacement for him. Hence, Mayama decides to leave the firm and comes back to work with Rika at the Harada Design Office, without much of asking for her permission. Yamada was acknowledged about this two weeks later through Nomiya, resulting in her depression. Later on, Yamada tells the others that four guys, who were childhood friends of hers, proposed to her at a shopping district, but she chose to run away from them. Professor Hanamoto later on explained to Yamada that her situation with Mayama was similar than that of the four guys who proposed to her. Professor Hanamoto tells her that in the case of one loving someone who doesn`t love another, people could just choose either to try or give up. He advises her to tell the four guys her true feelings. When Yamada leaves, Professor Hanamoto`s thoughts reveal a third choice, but he would never say it aloud. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784246</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39853" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自分の気持ちもわからない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Even Know How I Feel</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Nem tudom, mit érzek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jibun no Kimochi mo Wakaranai</title>
<summary>Having lost Mayama from the Fujiwara Design Office, Miwako expresses her depression by buying a massage chair for their new office. Yamada, who was brooding over the proposal of her childhood friends, confronts them and turns them down properly, later wishing for their own happiness while selling cakes with Hagu. Meanwhile, Takemoto is being depressed from the fact that he has not realized yet what his goal in life really is, giving him trouble on his job applications. He then took down the artwork he made for the art exhibition, much to a surprise for the others. His depression made the opening of their Christmas party a little dull, but Professor Hanamoto`s antics made things lively. Rebuilding another artwork for his graduation art project, Takemoto suddenly collapses and is brought to the hospital to be diagnosed for an ulcer. Visited by Mitsuko and Kazuo, he decides to stay and study for another year. Takemoto was about to confess his feelings to Hagu when they were interrupted by Professor Hanamoto, who has brought him a handheld television. What they saw on television totally surprises them. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784248</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39854" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの人が帰ってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He Came Back</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Morita hazatér</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Hito ga Kaette Kita</title>
<summary>Morita, airing on television in a startling appearance, is given an Academy Award. After making a ruckus on the hospital ward, they were shocked to see Morita on the bed right beside Takemoto. The next day, they return to the hospital, only to see Morita well. After Professor Hanamoto drags Morita away for his thesis, Yamada asks Mayama about his work, realizing that she herself is being hurt from the fact that only Mayama and Rika are working together. Later, Morita was given a heavy lecture by Professor Tange, but still ends up graduating due to his graduation thesis being finished and submitted in time, being that his work was a self-portrayed hand-made sculpture made of gold. But he returns later, enrolled as a third-year student in the Japanese painting department. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784250</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39855" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">止まった時間が動き出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Begins to Move Again</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az idő ismét mozgásba lendül</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomatta Jikan ga Ugokidasu</title>
<summary>Mayama arrives at the Fujiwara Design Office, only to found out that Yamada is there. After she leaves abruptly, Mayama mistakes Nomiya`s business interest with Yamada for his love interest. Mayama then goes to the apartment to meet up with Takemoto and Morita. When the three gather to eat dinner prepared by Morita, Takemoto reminisces over the time when Morita departed to America. The following night, Mayama meets up with Takemoto, Morita, Yamada, Professor Hanamoto, Yamazaki, and Miwako at the annual school festival. Later after the festival, Yamada agrees to go with Nomiya, after she had an argument with Mayama. However, Yamada begins to have second thoughts about going out with Nomiya, as she faces the truth about her relationship with Mayama told by Nomiya. Meanwhile, at the Fujiwara Design Office, Yamazaki and Miwako talk with Morita and Mayama about Nomiya. Miwako explains to Mayama that he and Nomiya are alike in personality, which makes Mayama frustrated. Nomiya and Yamada bought food at a pastry shop. Nomiya brings her to the sight of a Ferris wheel at his place, while Yamada reminisces over her time with Mayama in the Ferris wheel. Yamada then admits that Nomiya was right about her relationship with Mayama, causing her to cry. The next morning, Yamada is shocked to have slept overnight with Nomiya, but Nomiya calms her down by offering her a ride on the Ferris wheel. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784253</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39856" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜空に浮かぶ月に祈る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Pray to the Moon Hovering in the Night Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Imádság a Holdhoz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozora ni Ukabu Tsuki ni Inoru</title>
<summary>Nomiya calls Yamazaki and Miwako to the office early in the morning to assist a drunken Yamada to her father`s house. Later on, Morita meets up with Mayama, and Morita tells Mayama that he wants to visit the office again sometime. Mayama views pictures of Ferris wheels taken by Nomiya, noticing how much Ferris wheels meant to Nomiya. Morita finds Yamada, having great concern over her. Morita then walks her to her house. The next day, Professor Hanamoto explains to Takemoto how he became a teacher. Takemoto then tells Professor Hanamoto that everyone except him has their future planned out, including Hagu. Morita becomes surprised that Hagu doesn`t want her paintings to be displayed and shown in museums and art galleries. Professor Hanamoto tells Morita that it is up to Hagu to do what she wants with her art, but Professor Hanamoto questions himself if that is the right thing to do. At the office, Yamazaki and Miwako accuses Nomiya of having a perverted personality. However, Nomiya recalls that he was trying to change his ways until Mayama started working at the office, since Mayama had the same personality as him. Yamada is seen by Professor Shōda, making pottery. She had made too much pottery, which Professor Shōda realized that something was troubling her. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784254</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39857" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕は, いつも怖かった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Always Been Scared</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Teljesen üres...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa, Itsumo Kowakatta</title>
<summary>Takemoto meets with Professor Hanamoto and a businessman. The businessman offers Takemoto a job, and Takemoto quickly accepts the job. Takemoto celebrates this occasion with Morita, Mayama, Hagu, Professor Hanamoto, and Yamada. However, the businessman had declared bankruptcy. Meanwhile, the Tottori firm joins back with the Tokyo firm, resulting in some unfinished work in the Fujiwara Design Office. Yamada catches Nomiya before he walks out, dropping off some pottery at the office. Miwako tells Yamada that Nomiya is headed over to the Tottori firm, which surprises Yamada. Takemoto disappears and hasn`t returned to the apartment in a few days, causing the others to be worried. Professor Hanamoto concludes that Takemoto wanted to be away for a while to find himself and that he will return within a few days. It is revealed that he went away for a while to find himself in the past, ending up at a beach. He begins to worry about the others. Morita, Mayama, and Professor Hanamoto set out to look for Takemoto. Takemoto seems to fear what his future will turn out to be. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784256</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="41314" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨に濡れた花のように</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like a Flower Getting Wet in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Mint egy virág az esőben</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame ni Nureta Hana no You ni</title>
<summary>Takemoto travels to many houses to get water to drink. Miwako text messages for Yamada to Nomiya, as she wonders how he is doing. Hagu believes that she is selfish for not displaying her paintings. Takemoto is uncertain to return to the apartment. Unfortunately, his bicycle breaks down when he passes by a temple. He meets with carpenters who restore temples and shrines. He decides to help them until he is able to buy a new bicycle. Professor Hanamoto reveals to Hagu that Takemoto reminds him when he was younger. Yamada meets Rika for the first time, and she eventually starts to feel sorry for Rika. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784258</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="41315" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, 僕は走り出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And So, I Begin to Run</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Ismét útra kelek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite, Boku wa Hashiridasu</title>
<summary>Takemoto cooks for the carpenter, and they seem to like the food he prepares. Takemoto calculates that he will work for ten days until he is able to buy a new bicycle. Meanwhile at the Fujiwara Design Office, Rika ask if Yamada could work with her, since she takes an interest in Yamada`s pottery. Mayama becomes worried when he hears the news. Takemoto reluctantly wants to stay with the carpenters, since they love his cooking. He gradually starts finding himself after bonding with the carpenters. One of the carpenters lends Takemoto his bicycle as well as a map, giving Takemoto quite a surprise. The carpenters say farewell to Takemoto, as he leaves to finish the rest of his journey. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784262</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="41316" update="2017-03-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="26">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちは, 回り続ける観覧車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re a Continuously Spinning Ferris Wheel</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Én</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi wa, Mawari Tsuzukeru Ganransha</title>
<summary>Takemoto views the map the night before he starts traveling the next morning. He comes across a store near a school, and ends up eating sweet rolls. The store owner talks to him about her time in America, offering him some corn for the trip afterward. Takemoto reminisces about the time he wished he could go to America with his father. Not paying attention, he falls off his bicycle, but manages to get back on and continues on his journey back to the apartment. When he arrives home, he goes to see Hagu. Professor Hanamoto goes to see Hagu shortly after, but finds out that both Takemoto and Hagu are asleep. Takemoto wakes up the next morning and receives a warm welcome from everyone. Takemoto explains to them that he was simply trying to go on a journey, meeting people along the way. It is revealed that Takemoto has been away for two months. Everyone goes to a harvest festival, and they all see the fireworks. After realizing that what he leaves behind can mean so much to him, Takemoto admits his love for Hagu. As Takemoto spends the night with all friends in the apartment, a four-leaf clover is secretly shown next to his bicycle. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784263</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="45432" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter L</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az L-akták</title>
<summary>Takemoto, Morita, Mayama, and Professor Hanamoto all reminisce about Lohmeyer, a friend of theirs. In a flashback, it is revealed that he is a large, bulky guy, and known for his generosity and his kindness. He brings tons of meat to them, as the four happily ask for more. Until one day, Lohmeyer disappears, leaving the four in major depression and sorrow. In the present, Takemoto and Mayama go to an amusement park. Mayama explains the history and design of the amusement park as well as its mascot, leaving Takemoto in total shock. The suit of the mascot, ironically, was worn by Lohmeyer at the time. Mayama says that Lohmeyer as the mascot attracted many of the adults more than the children, because of his personality. Takemoto then wonders about Lohmeyer as the mascot of the amusement park. However, Takemoto, Hagu, Mayama, and Yamada are surprised to discover that Morita is the new wearer of the suit of the mascot. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784266</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="46119" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter F</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az F-akták</title>
<summary>Before Mayama starting working at the Fujiwara Design Office, Miwako becomes upset to see Yamazaki in a fashion magazine. It is explained that Miwako bought a shirt for Yamazaki as a practical joke device. However, the shirt seems to suit him well. Each day, Miwako attempts to give Yamazaki another shirt as a practical joke device, but she again fails to humiliate him, seeing him displayed the same fashion magazine. After Morita returned from America, Mayama plays shogi with Professor Hanamoto. When Takemoto and Hagu arrive, they all converse about Yamada in parties. It is explained that Yamada is the most attractive girl in every party, but she experiences love sickness after becoming drunk. Moreover, Mayama becomes responsible for caring for Yamada after every party. They then talk about Mayama time in the office. It is explained that Yamazaki was invited to a party. Miwako still becomes obsessed in trying to humiliate Yamazaki, only for him to be invited to many parties due to his popularity. Mayama and Professor Hanamoto, not realizing that Takemoto and Hagu both departed, ended up calling it a night, only to see Morita right in front of them. 
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784446</identifier>
<identifier>honey-and-clover</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="80222" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128522" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">First episode parody subs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130625" update="2011-05-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130626" update="2011-05-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130627" update="2011-05-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130903" update="2011-06-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144481" update="2012-10-05">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Midori-chan`s Unaired Version</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
