<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2855" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>102</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2007-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">MAR Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">MÄR Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">MÄR</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">メルヘヴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">MAR Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">МЕР Рай</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Marchen Awakens Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Maruhebun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">メル</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">MÄR メルヘヴン MÄRCHEN AWAKENS ROMANCE</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Märchen Awakens Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">메르헤븐</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อิทธิฤทธิ์พิชิตมายา</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="571" approval="20" total="23">Rekka no Honoo</anime>
<anime id="2921" approval="12" total="12">Ueki no Housoku</anime>
<anime id="1540" approval="1" total="8">Tenjou Tenge</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="190362">Everything about this Shonen anime is passable. Characters are plentiful and varied for both protagonists and antagonists, while the BG music is appropriate when played. I also found it unique that power levels were expressed as chess pieces and appreciated the lack of drawn out battles. However seasoned Shonen fans may find little that`s extraordinary about this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="597887">I think this Anime was pretty good, though a few parts just make it seem repetitive. I give this a 7.9/10.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://marheaven.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="6061" type="Character Design">Komaru Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="3634" type="Series Composition">Takegami Junki</name>
<name id="3483" type="Direction">Okuwaki Masaharu</name>
<name id="6061" type="Chief Animation Direction">Komaru Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="4051" type="Music">Ikeda Daisuke</name>
<name id="8521" type="Original Work">Anzai Nobuyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Toramizu Ginta is a young boy always dreaming of a magical world out of his reach. But his dream isn`t too far off, as Ginta one day is given the chance to enter the magical world. Entering the new place, he almost immediately finds out the existance of ÄRMS, weapons that the people of this world use. Ginta`s life changes forever as he journeys through this new world, meeting new companions and gaining fighting abilities. This land Ginta has always dreamed of isn`t some joyful place however, as he soon begins to witness first hand the harshness of the land he has found himself in.
Source: Baka-Updates Manga</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1074">4.52</permanent>
<temporary count="1136">7.07</temporary>
<review count="3">6.55</review>
</ratings>
<picture>45678.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>738</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1700</identifier>
<identifier>jdrxga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shopro.co.jp/tv/marheaven/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>MÄR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>MÄR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322688</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7279</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6442" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-09">
<name>Weekly Shounen Sunday</name>
<description>Weekly Shounen Sunday is a weekly shounen manga magazine published in Japan by Shogakukan since 1959. Contrary to its title, Weekly Shounen Sunday issues are released on Wednesdays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>175276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8714" type="main character in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="1">7.38</rating>
<name>Toramizu Ginta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8715" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="3">3.34</rating>
<name>Snow</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8716" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="12">8.51</rating>
<name>Dorothy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14356" type="appears in" update="2010-01-25">
<rating votes="3">6.95</rating>
<name>Chaton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1283.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19712" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-18">
<name>Nanashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanashi is one of the more mysterious characters in MÄR. He was found lying alone in the middle of nowhere with a nasty wound to his stomach by Galian. After he was revived by him and taken to the bandit village of Luberia, it was revealed that he has no memory of his past or even his name, and thus Galian named him Nanashi, or "nameless." Galian would later betray Nanashi, joining the Chess Pieces and leaving him in charge of Luberia after erasing his memory of him. Nanashi`s main goal is to track down the Chess Piece responsible for wiping out Luberia (Peta) and avenge his slain allies. Like Ginta, he has the scent and incredible strength of someone who came to MÄR-Heaven from another world. Early on, Dorothy noticed that he had great physical strength, just like Ginta. Nanashi uses lightning ÄRM.</description>
<picture>92603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19713" type="main character in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Babbo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The legendary ÄRM in the first two MÄR-Heaven war, wielded by captain of MÄR, Ginta. Ever since the 2nd war concluded, he`s been traveling around searching for Ginta, and ended up sleeping in a lake until Kai wakes him up. Babbo has no magic stone inserted, so it can not transform into his previous versions. However, Babbo has new versions.</description>
<picture>156788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19715" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jack is the son of Jake, a member of the Cross Guard who was killed by the Chess Piece Weasel.
Loud-mouthed and clumsy, Jack is the weakest of Team MÄR, however not by any means the least resolute, if not the most, and having the least experience. He never misses a chance on training to get stronger. He also has a hopeless crush on every cute girl he can lay his eyes on, especially Snow and Dorothy, despite how cruelly they treat him.
Jack is the one who meets Ginta Toramizu early in his adventure when he and Babbo stumble upon his garden. After Jack helps him beat the Rugelu Brothers (a pair of werewolves that were terrorizing Jack`s home to claim the farm`s vegetables), he and Ginta becomes best friends and joins Ginta on his journey.</description>
<picture>156792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19716" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-18">
<name>Alan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hardened (smoking) warrior, the powerful human who participated in the previous MÄR-Heaven War against the Chess Piece, known as the 2nd man, Danna`s partner in the Cross Guard. His power level is said to be equivalent to a Knight in the method of power ranking used by the Chess Pieces, and once fought to a draw with the Knight`s second in command, the one ranked directly under the No.1 Knight Phantom, Halloween. However, because of a curse set by Halloween`s Darkness ÄRM, Igneil, in the same fight, Alan was sealed inside the court guardian and custodian dog of princess Snow, Edward. In order to change back into Alan, Ed has to sleep three times, often forcibly knocking himself out, which is too risky and inconvenient for most situations. If Alan sleeps once, he becomes Ed again. After the visit from Phantom and his Zodiac Knights, Alan and Ed are split apart into two beings by Ginta, using Babbo`s Alice transformation. Ironically, due to his time inside Edward, Alan has developed a fear of cats. In the end of the anime, Alan lives with Chaton, Babbo, and the baby Loco. His ÄRMs include:</description>
<picture>92605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19717" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-18">
<rating votes="3">7.79</rating>
<name>Alviss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The cold figure of MÄR, Alviss is the one who brought Ginta into MÄR-Heaven. He joined the Cross Guard in the 1st War Game and grew fondness toward their leader, Danna, with whom he shared the very same goal for which they put their lives at risk, to fight the Chess and protect MÄR-Heaven. This pure courage, however, got Alviss further than he could ever have expected even in his wildest dream: Phantom also chose him as one who would reside in the dreary future of MÄR-Heaven... in the form of a Zombie-tattooed undead. For years Alviss lives under the looming shadow of this most unwanted tomorrow, and recluses from opening his heart for others. However after meeting with Ginta, Alviss starts to change and finally, stands up facing destiny in full height in order to realize his lifelong wish, the banishment of his hated enemy Phantom, riddance of the curse Tattoo, and peace attained for MÄR-Heaven. A Darkness ÄRM user. He is loyal and protect for everyone that he thinks as his `friend`.</description>
<picture>92604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19718" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Belle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tiny fairy seen most of the times at Alviss` side. Belle befriended Alviss in his earlier years while he was training under Gaira`s supervision and from then on has cherished a passion for him, which borders on monopolising crush: she cares for him a great deal, and gets jealous of whomever Alviss so much as behaves intimately to (which ranges from girls to friends, e.g. Alan). Belle and Edward host extras at the end of each episode that sums up the plot of each episode and lists the ÄRM Chess Pieces use in that episode. In the end of the anime, Alviss and Belle live together. Named for Tinkerbell from Peter Pan.</description>
<picture>51411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19719" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-17">
<name>Edward</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19720" type="appears in" update="2010-07-17">
<rating votes="2">5.86</rating>
<name>Candice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sadomasochistic woman who relishes physical pains in a fight as pleasures, before joining the Chess, Candice was a mercenary officer, and was feared by many for her violent and abusing personality. After a defeat to Phantom, however, Candice fell in love with Phantom and followed him. Though this remains largely an unreciprocal passion, Candice still endeavours to undertake many demanding tasks (e.g. taking on powerful enemies) to get Phantom`s commends, and is resolute to obliterate whoever obstructs his way.
Candice first appeared during Phantom`s revival and informed him that Queen Diana summoned him. During the Chess Pieces` war campaign, Candice single-handedly defeats the soldiers at Castle Geirelulu using Gorgon to turn them into stone. Candice reappeared during the 5th Round of the War Games and fought to a draw with Jack. After Phantom`s defeat, Candice accompanies Phantom to Lestava`s castle, and in the manga witnesses his death while he rests on his throne. In the anime Candice tries to help him escape from the pursuit by Team MÄR in the end of the Ghost Chess attack. Though this ends unsuccessfully, it deeply touches Phantom and partly lets him die in peace, knowing he after all isn`t so hated. Her last appearance is with the revived Rolan, visiting Phantom`s grave.</description>
<picture>51416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19721" type="appears in" update="2010-07-17">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Gido</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gido is Ian`s girlfriend and the only Pawn of the Chess Pieces to have an individual identity. She accompanied Ian in his first battle against Ginta. When Ian is taken down, she holds her ground against the others until she is knocked down by Jack`s attack. Due to Ian`s loss to Ginta, Halloween had Ian punished by ordering Chimera to transform Gido into a creature with her body fused with tentacles, unable to of speak as she transforms slowly into the hidieous creature.
Eventually she is returned to her human form by Chimera`s death and the couple leaves the Chess Pieces. however In the anime, they meet up with Ash, who they quickly befriend, Ash dies protecting Ian and Gido from King, who return the favor by taking care of Ash`s friends. Once Ash is revived, she and Ian continue to live with Ash and his kids</description>
<picture>51418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19722" type="appears in" update="2010-07-17">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Ginta no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An author who writes fantasy stories (which her missing husband and son are extremely interested in), Ginta`s mother is a strong drinker and smoker, and also apparently has an interest in cooking unusual foods, once trying to make "pizza curry". In spite of her occupation, she stands a very practical viewpoint in matters regarding fantasied subjects, therefore tends to make light of her husband`s, and later son`s, passion for such. After Ginta`s disappearance, however, she rues this dearly, thinking it was her fault her family`s gone and as Koyuki narrates Ginta`s journey in MÄR-Heaven, starts seeing fantasy in a different light.</description>
<picture>51420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2945" picture="177565.jpg">Ishizuka Sayori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19723" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Koyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginta`s friend in his own world, who has often taken care of him. She has a strong connection to Princess Snow. Not only does she look just like her, the two of them often see the other`s world through their eyes in their dreams. She uses this to keep track of how Ginta is doing, and tells Ginta`s mother what`s going on. She also collects his schoolbooks and homework, and plans to make Ginta study hard to catch up when he gets back. At the end of the series Koyuki begins to grow feelings for Ginta.</description>
<picture>156793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19724" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<name>Mokku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19725" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<name>Chappu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3954" picture="173079.jpg">Motoi Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19726" type="appears in" update="2010-07-18">
<name>Jack no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wife of the Cross Guard soldier Jake and mother of Jack, she resides on a small farm with her son and later, when he`s away, a pair of werewolves who once attacked their farm. Jack is very close to her heart, especially after Jake was killed by the knight Vizel in the first War Games, and she at first discourages him to get in any fights with any opponent who may try to kill him, even if facing them is the right thing to do (when the werewolves were terrorizing their farm, she happily tolerated their cruel gorging for fear that Jack would get hurt if they tried to stand up for themselves). However, after Jack`s triumph over the werewolves, and later during Jack`s first match in the War Games she realizes that the time has come for Jack to become a man and that she should support him in this. One of her regrets is that while she taught Jack everything she knew about farming, she never taught him the proper way to treat a lady, and Jack is thus a little bit of a pervert. Jack`s mother also takes Pano in hand and considers her like a daughter, (or more like a daughter-in-law, as a wife for her son).</description>
<picture>51430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2355" picture="223496.jpg">Tachibana Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19766" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="1">7.72</rating>
<name>Peta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Very little is known about Peta`s early background. At some point he would befriend Phantom, a Kaldean outlaw and eventually the strongest Knight, some point before Phantom received the Zombie Tattoo. hortly before that Peta witnessed the breakup of Phantom and his lover, the Vestrian Alma. At some point, apparently after Alviss, Peta would receive Phantom`s Zombie Tattoo, wishing to walk the path of destruction together for all eternity. After the formation of the Chess Piece army, Peta quickly gained Knighthood and became the Knights` strategic officer. Peta, however, did not fight in the previous War Games, choosing instead to broadcast the battles throughout MÄR-Heaven.</description>
<picture>156797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19767" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Stanley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19768" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Garo Rogelu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Is a vegetarian wolf brothers who used to steal the vegetables grown in Jack`s garden. He threatened to kill Jack and his mother at first, but after the fight between them and Jack + Ginta, which they lost... The Rogelu Brothers turned out helping with the farming and earned their food(vegetables)from Jack`s mother.</description>
<picture>51510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19769" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Ruga Rogelu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Is a vegetarian wolf brothers who used to steal the vegetables grown in Jack`s garden. He threatened to kill Jack and his mother at first, but after the fight between them and Jack + Ginta, which they lost... The Rogelu Brothers turned out helping with the farming and earned their food(vegetables)from Jack`s mother.</description>
<picture>51511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19789" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Emokis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emokis is a Level 1 Bishop of the Chess Pieces. She is very foolish and carries a sword named Dandarshia, which she treats unfairly, Emokis` personality can be described as stubborn.</description>
<picture>51540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19790" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<name>Phantom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The commander-in-chief of Chess Piece army`s combat force and the strongest warrior of the Knight class (aka the Zodiac Knights). Phantom is a callous, sadistic individual who revels in bloodshed and destruction and, with his body rendered unkillable by the immortalizing power of the Zombie Tattoo, is one of the most fearsome beings to ever walked MÄR-Heaven. His overwhelming power and charisma makes him the object of fear and respect, in some cases even love, of many Chess Piece members.</description>
<picture>51541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19793" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<name>Halloween</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Halloween is the second strongest Knight and the third in command, losing out to Peta only for the latter`s intelligence. Halloween was abandoned as a child by his parents, who gave him the name of Pump, and was often bullied by other children in his town. During his childhood, Pump also developed a penchant for dismembering small animals, such as dogs. Despite this and the town`s disliking towards him, Pump`s childhood friends, Alan, still remained friends with him. One day, however, Alan showed Pump an ÄRM that creates flames. Attracted to it, Pump thieved the ÄRM, murdered the children who bullied him, and left the village, but not before telling Alan they would always be different people. At some point, Pump joined the Chess Pieces, and, taking on the title of Halloween and chaining himself to a cross ÄRM, would eventually rise to the rank of Knight. As fate would have it, Halloween would fight Alan, who had joined the Cross Guard, and the fight ended in a draw. Even to today Halloween still holds a deep hatred for Alan inside of his crippled heart.</description>
<picture>51555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19794" type="appears in" update="2010-08-24">
<name>Chimera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chimera`s appearance, masked or unmasked, is generally anomalous for her gender. She usually dons a ghastly skeletal mask with a green wig attached to it, concealing her blonde hair color (the green color is possibly exclusive to only the anime, however, as the cover of volume 13 shows a blonde-haired masked Chimera). Since her enlisting for the Chess Pieces she`s fashioned her hair spiky, a mode far more commonly styled for males, and (exclusively for the anime) builds up her stature into a more masculine form, misleading people about her actual gender. In addition to these extraordinary outward features, Chimera`s facial appearance carries hideously unique traits: she wears a grotesque mass of eyeballs on the left side of her face, stitches a horizontal black line on the scar across her nose`s bridge, and seasons the overall gruesome sight by piercing her Knight insignia earring on the tip of her tongue.
When she was getting married to Marco, some villagers came and took Marco away by force since he was once part of the Chess Pieces. Though the 1st War Game was over they were insistent on finding the refugees. When Marco won`t say anything they ended up killing him and took Chimera next. After a few hellish months she managed to escape with her face looking wrong. Soon after that Peta came and persuaded her to join the Chess Pieces. She`s a Ghost ARM user.
After the war game with Dorothy (in which she lost) Ian chases her due to the fact that it was her who made Gido look like a bug and lost speech. In the end her real name was revealed as Eileen. She appears to lost all hope in life, but she was carrying the marriage rings of her and Marco.</description>
<picture>51556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="309" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19795" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<name>Rolan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At some point early in Rolan`s childhood, Rolan`s parents died to unknown circumstances, leaving a poor and starving Rolan to live on the streets. Rolan was always ignored by the others, and Rolan himself would have died under such a living eventually. At one point, a number of kids stealing food bumped into Rolan and left a large amount of food around him, leaving the owner of the stolen food to blame Rolan and severely abuse him, putting Rolan in an even worse state than before. Just after this, Rolan was found by Phantom, the leader of the Chess Pieces. Phantom became the only one to treat Rolan with kindness, giving him food to survive.
Just before Phantom left, he asked Rolan if he would follow him, which was followed by Rolan taking Phantom`s hand and the two walking out of Rolan`s home village together. Rolan, having a wish to serve Phantom, would join the Chess Pieces. According to Alan, Rolan fought in the first War Games as a Rook or Bishop which he is now a Knight. He battled Alviss 3 times two of which he lost. He`s a stone manipulator. He lives for Phantom and shares a zombie tattoo like Alviss.
The reason behind his following Phantom so desperately lies in that he doesn`t want to have the pain of having someone leave him like his parents did that left him in such a state. Even though Phantom haven`t really shown love towards him, Rolan still fights for the sake of eternity and Phantom.</description>
<picture>156796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19796" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Weasel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Weasel is the oldest of the Knights (84 years old), but nevertheless a nimble fighter. He is easily distinguished due to his eccentric appearance with a tree growing out of his head containing all his magic power, and always seen holding a wood cane inside which he hides all his ÄRMs. As a Chess Piece he`s wicked, but is overall an amicable figure to his Chess fellows, and is civil enough towards his opponents.
In the 1st War Games, Weasel fought Jack`s father, Jake and grasped victory using his Guardian Bird of Rotten Wood, leaving Jake fatally wounded (and dying at his home shortly thereafter, which was unknown to Weasel). He plays little to no role in the 2nd War, save for once in the War campaign when he took over an unnamed castle by his trees, and like most of the Chess Pieces spends the War Games observing the fights. He takes special notice of Jack since his debut of victory, for the boy also masters his wood element and uses Jake`s memento scoop. He fights Jack in the final round of the 2nd War Games and is defeated by him, who used Kikazoku Fire to burn the tree on his head, eliminating the source of his power. Weasel compliments Jack by telling him that he has surpassed his father, and after the War Games ends, receives no more lines for the rest of the series. Weasel is a plant Guardian ÄRM user.</description>
<picture>51558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19797" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-19">
<rating votes="1">7.72</rating>
<name>Ian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>On the surface, Ian appears to be a laid-back, jovial young man who (even when he was still a low-ranked Rook) is one of the few Chess Pieces to have the daring to be blunt and disrespectful towards his superiors. This ranges from addressing the senior Loco "-chan" in spite of her insistence on their age gap, to talking back to Halloween who is one of the highest-ranked Knights, and in his quest for vengeance later on, challenging even the Knights. Ian`s amiable manners, however, belies the lethal, battle-thrilled fighter he can be in the battlefield. Once driven by determination he is relentless in his pursuit, be it a simple case of getting the fight he enjoys or the venture to eliminate a superior sworn enemy. Ian`s tenacity is prone to lead him go against his orders, and Ian admits because of it, he is always mentally prepared for death penalty.</description>
<picture>51559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19798" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Magical Roe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magical Roe is a clown who was Snow`s babysitter when she was younger by order of Diana. While being Snow`s caretaker, he quickly became Snow`s best friend, and the two grew very close to each other. Years later, Magical Roe was sent into the War Games in order to kidnap Snow. During this round, he tells Snow that he didn`t join the Chess Pieces, he was with them from the start. After Snow used Undine to destroy Magical Roe`s Nightmare, he successfully made off with Snow during the 6th Round, much to his reluctancy. Thus, Magical Roe won by default. While Team MÄR stormed Lestava Castle, Magical Roe fought off Nanashi, Alan, and Gaira to prevent them from reaching Snow. In the anime adaption, instead he fought Alan and Ginta Toramizu, and after defeat, Magical Roe regained his senses, and sacrificed his life in order to save Snow from the Queen`s Darkness ÄRM, attoning for his wrongdoings towards the princess.Little is known about Magical Roe`s personality, besides that he cares deeply for Princess Snow.</description>
<picture>51560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19799" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Galian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Galian is the former leader of the notorious thief guild Luberia, founding it as a sanctuary for the lowest of the world. As a leader he was an amicable figure and well-loved by his subordinate thieves, and led Luberia in a peaceful reign - until the 1st War started. The birth of a homicidal Chess Pieces army begot disasters and destructions all over MÄR-Heaven, which, while seen as a bad thing for `business` by many Luberians, set Galian on constant agitation, eager to test his power. His first encounter with the Chess was inside a havoc-wrought castle they occupied, and after defeating many Pawns, Galian faced the strategist Knight Peta. Although Galian was easily worsted, Peta still acknowledged his great potentials and let him go after provocatively advising him to invest his power in a worthier place.
The 1st War Games concluded with the Chess` defeat, however that did little to help Galian`s already triggered infatuation with their immense power. Predicting the Chess` inevitable return, he resolved to abandon Luberia and joined the Chess. During that time he found and saved a wounded man with no memory of his past life, but nevertheless endowed with latent might, whom he named Nanashi. Turning a deaf ear to his thieves` suspicion and cool reception towards Nanashi, Galian took Nanashi under his wings. To help him win Luberia`s heart Galian sent a monster to the guild`s fortress, which Nanashi outfought and earned him the respect of many, just like Galian wished. After that he trained Nanashi and when he was strong enough, he left his throne and the Electric Eyes ÄRMs, symbols of Luberia`s leader to Nanashi, erased all memories regarding him and went to Peta to accept his previous offer. Over the years, his name also faded from Luberia`s memories itself as the thieves recognized Nanashi as their true leader.
Although Galian severed all his ties to Luberia when he gave up on it, the news of Luberia`s extermination (along with its ragged flag), brought to him by the perpetrator Peta himself, comes as a great personal blow, though he denies it by setting fire to the flag. Knowing Nanashi`s nature and his reaction to this homicide, Galian anticipated the man`s participation in the 2nd War Games and entered it thus, to prove he had chosen the right path. With Phantom`s approval, he revealed himself to Nanashi in the 5th round after Ash`s defeat and the two battled, Nanashi`s memories of him gradually returning. He`s defeated by Nanashi and compliments him for having become a fine leader, admitting his envy. At the end of the series, Nanashi and Galian rule Luberia together. Like Nanashi, he fights with lightning-themed ÄRMs:</description>
<picture>51561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19800" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Ash</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash is easily distinguished by his mask: a grim reaper skull with its tongue sticking out. Ash joined the Chess Pieces in the hopes on using their immense power to conquer the world, ending all other wars countries might bring up, preventing the deaths of the children he loves. Ash`s personality is rather unusual on Chess Piece standards, being both playful and fun-loving. Ash prefers to solve matters without fighting, urging the other knights during a meeting not to deal with Rapunzel`s insolence. Phantom himself, who is one of the Knights` more sadistic members, states that he could never hate Ash, as he is "just that sort of person". Ash is almost always seen enjoyably playing with children, usually Defu, Ko, and Benni, three children he rescued from the war, when not fighting a battle. Ash is also very willing to take punishment, sometimes volunteering to be punished when he felt he did something wrong. Galian also states that Ash is usually not one to give up in battle. Ash`s original design had little differences from his original one, the most notable being having a regular mask rather than a skull one.</description>
<picture>51562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19801" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Pinocchio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>12th strongest Knight and the smallest of the Knights, Pinocchio was once a marionnette made by Diana for her little sister Dorothy when Dorothy was a child, and was apparently animated to life upon joining the Chess Pieces. In the 6th round, he was ordered to defeat Dorothy if he wished to become human. Like his namesake, his nose grows when he lies, but it transforms into a cannon after about three lies and can be used to shoot his opponents. In the War Games at the Mushroom Field, he is ripped apart by Dorothy`s ÄRM Toto, his remains salvaged by Chaton by the end of the 6th Round. In a filler episode, he was rebuilt with wagon wheels. Alongside Kouga and Girom, they ambushed Dorothy, Ginta and Alviss where Pinocchio destroyed Dorothy`s Andarta at the time when Babbo gets cracked. After being repelled, Diana then sent them to capture Caldia`s Grand Elder only to be defeated by Dorothy and Ginta. Also in the anime, they were last seen riding Kouga`s Kung Fu Frog somewhere. A Weapon ÄRM user.</description>
<picture>51563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2460" picture="22350.jpg">Nagasawa Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19802" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Rapunzel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rapunzel is the older sister of Girom. Their father died early of an illness, after which their mother became deranged and physically abused the siblings on a daily basis. Gradually driven to their limits, one day Rapunzel and her brother finally broke down and chopped their mother to death, then ran away. The scar of this matricide survives into her adulthood: Rapunzel grows up to be bloodthirsty, arrogant and riotous (to the irritation and exasperation of many Knights), and appears to share with her brother Girom (notably the only one she holds dear and is gentle with) a love for killing women. Despite being quite far from most visions of beauty herself, Rapunzel is shown to be helplessly narcissistic and looks down on everyone, men or women, as obnoxiously ugly.
Rapunzel was present at Phantom`s revival, and in the campaign of the 2nd War Games, she was responsible for the siege of Reginrave castle. Besides being with Girom watching the match between Ginta and Garon, Rapunzel was only seen outside once with the rest of the Knights after the 3rd Round. She persuaded Phantom to let her and Girom fight in the 4th Round. When someone on her team loses to Team MÄR, she challenges the loser of her team to a game of Rock-Paper-Scissors and ends up decapitating them if they lose. After Ginta defeated Girom, Rapunzel wanted to fight Ginta only for Dorothy to step in. She loses to Dorothy in the 4th round of the War Game, but it was not after the 5th Round of the War Games that the deserving retribution was delivered: as punishment for slaying her comrades, Phantom has the Rook Ian battle and kill her (by decapitation in the manga, and incineration in the anime) in battle in front of Girom`s eyes and usurp her Knighthood.</description>
<picture>51564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5073" picture="33047.jpg">Sasaki Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19803" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<name>Kouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The weakest Knight and the largest of the Knights. Kouga is sensitive about his ugliness, due to which as a child he was always treated miserably. He`s extremely arrogant and dense, and hates anyone with good looks (e.g. Alviss, as he claimed in their fight) as he thinks people with good appearances carry dark hearts. Although his magical powers and ÄRM strength are more along Bishop class, Kouga rose to Knight Class due to his vast amount of strength and a sturdy stamina which takes in unusually low damage from the most destructive of attacks.
Kouga appears cloaked throughout most of the series until War Games` 6th round, wherein he fights Alviss and loses. In a filler episode of the anime, he teams up with Pinocchio and Girom to attack Dorothy, Ginta, and Alviss. After being repelled, Diana then sent them on a mission to kidnap the Caldian Grand Elder, and is later defeated by Dorothy and Ginta. He is last seen (in the anime only) somewhere with Pinocchio and Girom, riding Kung Fu frog. A user of ninja-themed Weapon ÄRMs</description>
<picture>51565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19804" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Girom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Girom, or Gillom in the game, is a psychotic boy about Ginta`s age who enjoys killing, particularly women, much like his maniac older sister, the Knight Rapunzel. This is largely due, however, to the tremendous stress from their childhood abuse from their mother, whom they later killed. He was present at Phantom`s revival, along with the Knights and several other Chess Pieces. He and Orco attacked Vestry during the Chess Piece`s war campaign, under the order to search for a certain ÄRM. While searching the boat at the cave`s end, he quickly meets up with and fights Ginta, who defeats him using Gargoyle.
Girom was seen with Rapunzel observing the fight between Ginta and Garon. Girom then showed up in the 4th Round of the War Games, where he killed Aqua after her tie with Nanashi. As he wanted, Girom had a rematch with Ginta, and Girom almost won, due to Ginta`s anger of him killing Aqua. Babbo later calmed Ginta down, however, and Ginta defeated Girom with Gargoyle, to which Girom also survived. He later witnessed his sister killed by Ian in battle as punishment for her killing of her teammates in the 4th Round. In a filler episode of the anime, he alongside with Kouga and Pinocchio attacked Ginta, Dorothy, and Alviss at the time Babbo was cracked. Ginta barely survived his battle with him. After being repelled, Diana sent them to kidnap the Kaldea Elder, to which Ginta and Dorothy come to rescue him. He is last seen (also in the anime only) with the two somewhere riding Kung Fu Frog. A user of ice-based Nature ÄRMs.</description>
<picture>51567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19805" type="appears in" update="2010-07-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Loco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Loco is the strongest Rook and one of the first Chess Pieces introduced. Loco`s name means a patron of healers in the religion of Voodoo, a reference to her ÄRM Straw Doll (Spikes and Hammer). Loco was born 32 years before the main part of the series. At age 26, Loco, at that point a Pawn, the lowest Chess Piece rank, was given the order to participate in the attacking of a, unknown, town. While fighting, Loco`s only ÄRM the Weapon ÄRM Ring Dagger, was broken, leaving Loco defenseless. While stumbling throughout the battling village, Loco crossed paths with a midget-like cloaked figure carrying a large suitcase. The cloaked person asked Loco if she wanted strength, to which she answered that she only wanted power to fight with. The cloaked person then gave Loco the suitcase, telling her it was full of seven Darkness ÄRMs, the cost of using being reversed aging, and the mysterious figure died from the ARM`s effects. Using the Darkness ÄRMs, Loco eventually increased in the ranking system to the strongest of the Rooks. The Darkness ÄRMs affects had damaged her, however, as her body had been transformed into a young child`s by the series` beginning.</description>
<picture>51566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19851" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Carl</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19852" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Lilith</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who was once in the Cross Guard during the first war.</description>
<picture>51611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19853" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Diana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diana is a former citizen of Caldia, the island nation of witches and wizards off the Southern Continent of MÄR-Heaven. Very little is known about her time in Caldia, though from what is known Diana, and her sister Dorothy, belonged to an aristocratic wizarding family. It was Diana who trained Dorothy to use the ÄRM Zephyrus Broom, as indicated by a flashback in the anime, and it is also possible she was its original wielder. It is also known that she made dolls for Dorothy and repaired them when they were broken, one of which she later was the later Chess Pieces Knight Pinocchio. While to Caldian and her little sister she was a caring figure and a well-liked citizen, Dorothy says that Diana insatiably covet nearly everything since a young age.</description>
<picture>51612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19854" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="2">8.43</rating>
<name>Aqua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aqua is a pretty girl wearing a sea-themed ball dress. Despite being a Chess Piece, the happy and rather unpredictable Aqua always keeps a smile on her face, much to the surprise of Team MÄR. Aqua refers to everyone with honorific suffixes in the Japanese version, while in the English dub puts either "Mr." or "Miss" in front of everyone`s names, including herself.
Aqua appears in the 3rd round of the 4th Battle. After witnessing several examples of how Rapunzel kills any losing Chess Pieces, Nanashi and Aqua fight each other, where Nanashi defeats Aqua with his Electric Eye. Nanashi, however, pretends that attack removed all of his energy in order to make the fight a draw and save Aqua. Although Rapunzel isn`t happy about this, Aqua wins Rock-Paper-Scissors against her and Rapunzel doesn`t kill her, but has her brother Girom do it in her stead. Her final words were an apology to Nanashi. After Rapunzel was defeated by Dorothy, Nanashi floats her body into the water as a burial. Her character is based on The Little Mermaid. she uses sea-themed ÄRM.</description>
<picture>51613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19855" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Jack no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father of Jack and a disciple of Gaira. In the previous War, heeding Gaira`s summon, Jake left his family and went join the Cross Guard.</description>
<picture>51614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19856" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Alma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dead Vestrian female sailor whose ghost haunts Vestry`s underground cave with her fellow crew, and also the only one among them to actually possess the ability of materialization into a ghostly human form. Around 4 years before the 1st MÄR-Heaven war, Alma became Phantom`s sweetheart until Phantom took on the Zombie Tattoo from his Queen, Diana. An argument soon broke out between the two, and as Alma realized she (and her viewpoint of life and humankind in general) couldn`t shake his steadfast belief in the magnificence of immortality in the least, she bade Phantom farewell, never again met him . Alma and the crew of her ship died in the 1st War and, by the King of Chess Pieces himself, cursed to be wandering ghosts sealed inside the underground cave (in which approximately 2 years before she`d departed with Phantom) along with the Holy ÄRM Purific Ave it hid. 6 years later, at the prelude of the 2nd War Game, Ginta &amp; co. arrived at Vestry and ventured into the cave to defeat the two Chess Bishops responsible for rampaging Vestry, Orco and Girom. Heeding their beg for freedom, after defeating Girom, Ginta cleared the blocked end of the cave, opening the way for the ship to depart. As a token of gratitude (and also in a hope to stop Phantom, Alma gave him one magic stone and the Purific Ave and ascended to heaven. Alma made a reappearance exclusive to the anime in the Ghost Chess attack, transporting Ginta and Dorothy back to Phantom`s fortress after they were expelled out of there to her cave by the Ghost Chess. After the attack, she also appeared before Phantom and by assuring him he was not at all unloved, helped his soul achieve salvation before he died.</description>
<picture>51615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19857" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Gaira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 3rd man who fought in the 1st War Game 6 years ago alongside Danna and Alan, earning the Cross Guard their victory. He, however, loses to the Knight Chimera in the preliminary of the 2nd, and since then aids MÄR by training its inexperienced members. At the end of the anime, he was last seen attending the wedding of the Princess of Reginrave and Carl.</description>
<picture>51616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19858" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Pozun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "judge" of the War Games, in charge of rule explanation and fight announcement. He is a servant of the Chess Pieces, as seen when he takes orders from Halloween (upon Alan appearing before the third round). After the War Games are over, Ginta takes Pozun`s Andata so they can go to Lestava Castle in the manga, while in the anime they have him take them to Lestava Castle, and he grows rather attached to Team MÄR. At the end of the anime, he is seen playing with the rest of his kind in a hot spring.</description>
<picture>51617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19859" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Alibaba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alibaba is a rather arrogant Rook. He strongly believes rank doesn`t symbolize strength, and thinks his is on par with the Knights. Alibaba is largely Arabian themed.Alibaba first appears during the 3rd Round of the War Games. He is the first to go up when Alan wants to go first, claiming the other Chess Pieces there are too weak to fight him and that victory will make him a Knight.</description>
<picture>51619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19860" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Mr. Hook</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pirate-like member of the Chess Pieces. Bishop class. His characteristics are based off of Captain Hook from Peter Pan.
He made his appearance in the third battle, Volcanic Mountain Range.</description>
<picture>51620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19861" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Kannochi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19862" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Fuugi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuugi is a very Happy type of person he does not appear to be angry in some curcumstances but isn`t too happy like Chaton. Fuugi is a wind wielder and is always seen with a Mask.</description>
<picture>51622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19863" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Maira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the anime, it is revealed that Maira, a former Pawn, became a Bishop by gaining the ÄRM Vaqua. He is not given a backround in the manga. Maira is a black-cloaked masked man who takes pleasure in engulfing and digesting people with Vaqua. Vaqua is a resemblance to a yugioh card that marik uses called "revival jam". Maira is first seen watching the War Game battle between Ginta Toramizu and Garon. During the second round of the War Games, Maira reappears as a fighter for the Chess Pieces. He has the last of the battles in that round, and goes up against Dorothy.</description>
<picture>51623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19864" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Merilo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pendant Guardian ÄRM in the form of a polite, slender girl with a cat tail and ears, used to help people the Training Gate train, and to navigate for them. She`s referred to as `the cute one`. Although she does have cat attributes, Alan doesn`t fear her because she is an ÄRM .</description>
<picture>51624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19865" type="appears in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Bumolu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Guardian ÄRM in the form of a rude, fat woman with a bear tail and ears, used to help people the Training Gate train, and to navigate for them. She`s referred to as `the ugly one.`</description>
<picture>156801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19866" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Marco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marco is featured in Chimera`s very sad past, from the flashback in episode 72.
Chimera`s actual name is Eileen. Years prior to the 2nd War, she met and saved Marco, a man of the then-dispersed Chess Pieces. The two eventually fell in love with each other and one day, held their wedding in a small church. However, in the middle of the ceremony tragedy befell: when Eileen and Marco finished exchanging wedding vows and rings and were about to kiss, they were interrupted by a hostile group of villagers. The mob, who were Chess victims still living in vestiges of the war, were on a witch-hunt for the Chess and knowing Marco`s former affiliation, took him captive. For she loved him despite this, Eileen desperately beseeched for her fiancé`s life, protesting Marco had already defected from his organization, and that the war was already over. In response, a representative man of the group told her as long as a Chess was still alive, the war would not end.</description>
<picture>51627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19867" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Hamelin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hamelin is a member of the Chess Pieces and he is currently at the top of Bishop class.
Hamelin is over confident and is unaware of what other people can do. He is however very clever.</description>
<picture>51628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19868" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Saturn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A twisted man who enjoys seeing others in pain.</description>
<picture>51630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19869" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Jupiter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51632.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19870" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Venus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19871" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Mars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18300" picture="48477.jpg">Tomisaka Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19872" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Mercury</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19873" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Uranus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A women who appears to be the leader of her two sisters, Pluto and Neptune.</description>
<picture>51636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1659" picture="223004.jpg">Katsuragi Nanaho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19874" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Neptune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19875" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Pluto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4860" picture="211311.jpg">Sasajima Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19876" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>John Peach</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>John Peach is a boy who fancies himself as the future great hero of MÄR, quite ignorant of his dim-witted and cowardly nature. John Peach is followed by three gelatinous creatures called Burube, Torobe, and Garobe, who care very much for his safety. He has a backpack of ÄRMs that are either too hard for him to use, very weak or do not work right. Hearing about the Chess raid in Vestry, he appeared there just after Ginta defeated Girom and challenged the boy for Team MÄR`s leadership, which he lost miserably (as during each contest, just about every ÄRM he used backfired on him). When a group of thieves he had defeated (which was due to sheer dumb luck, since the Demon Tarantula ÄRM they used turned on them instead of him) appeared to take revenge on John Peach, he activated Demon Tarantula, only to had himself and his three friends nearly devoured by it, had it not been for Ginta`s help. John Peach left before the Second War Games begun, and returned for once to cheer for MÄR in the Final Battles. He`s seen at the end of the anime training with his three friends as he meditates under a waterfall.</description>
<picture>51639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19877" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Princess Reginleif</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Princess Reginleif is the princess that helped hold the war games for her people.</description>
<picture>51640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2945" picture="177565.jpg">Ishizuka Sayori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19878" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Garon Rodokin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Garon Rodokin is the Chess Piece who fought Ginta in the first round of the War Games and the father of Leno and Pano. He is an honorable man, and Ginta ends up sparing him (partly due to intervention by Pano) after Babbo`s Gargoyle form broke his ÄRM. He was killed by King but was revived when King was defeated. He uses Nature ÄRM.</description>
<picture>51641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19879" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Leno Rodokin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leno Rodokin is the son of Garon and Pano`s brother, and the first enemy fought in the war games. He fought against Alviss, who easily beat him. He was killed by King (which left behind his mask) and revived at the end, watching Pano and Jack from afar with his father. A Nature ÄRM user.</description>
<picture>51642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19880" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Pano Rodokin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pano Rodokin is the sister of Leno and the daughter of Garon. Pano`s most notable trait is her relationship with Jack, who she falls in love with during the series. She defeats him in the first round of the War Games, though loses to him during their rematch in the third. In both of her battles with Jack, at some point Jack is comically hit in the groin by Pano. Using Jack`s mushrooms, it`s discovered she`s scared of bats, being immobilized, leeches, and likes pretty flowers and butterflies.</description>
<picture>51643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="137" picture="214428.jpg">Sasamoto Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19881" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<name>Toramizu Danna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Danna-san ("Boss" in the English translation) was the leader of the Cross Guard that defeated the Chess Pieces in the war six years before Ginta`s arrival to Mar Heaven. Even though he came from another world, the world Ginta came from, he loved Mar Heaven, and was more than willing to fight to protect it. He died in battle against Phantom, the immortal military leader of the Chess Pieces.
It`s later revealed that Danna-san was actually Ginta`s father, who disappeared six years prior. Apparently, he acted the exact same way Ginta does, which makes a lot of people have high expectations of Ginta.</description>
<picture>51644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19910" type="appears in" update="2010-07-22">
<name>Orca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19978" type="appears in" update="2010-07-24">
<name>Korekkio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19979" type="appears in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Avrutuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17183" picture="46461.jpg">Matsubayashi Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20850" type="appears in" update="2010-08-15">
<name>Torobe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20851" type="appears in" update="2010-08-15">
<name>Jing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20852" type="appears in" update="2010-08-15">
<name>Pumon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20853" type="appears in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Ben</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20854" type="appears in" update="2010-08-15">
<name>Toto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20855" type="appears in" update="2010-08-15">
<name>Pirun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4710" picture="27532.jpg">Nasu Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20862" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Undine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20863" type="appears in" update="2014-06-17">
<name>Benny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2384" picture="44878.jpg">Kouzuki Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20864" type="appears in" update="2010-08-16">
<name>Luke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="7049" picture="32044.jpg">Sakai Keikou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20865" type="appears in" update="2010-08-16">
<name>Rondo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="17183" picture="46461.jpg">Matsubayashi Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20905" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<name>Nagagutsu o Haita Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20906" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-17">
<name>Yami no Orb</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20907" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<name>Minako</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="35350" update="2005-04-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">2.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開け! 異世界の扉!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Open! Door to Another World!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La porte vers un autre monde</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La porta per l`altro mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hirake! Isekai no Tobira!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35351" update="2005-04-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説のアーム! バッボ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Babbo: The Legendary ARM!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Babbo, l`Ärm de légende</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Babbo: L`Ärm leggendario</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no ARM! Babbo!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35751" update="2005-04-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャック! バトルスコップ発動!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jack`s Battle Shovel in Action!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jack et la pelle de combat</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Jack in azione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jack! Battle Scoop Hatsudou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35877" update="2005-04-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギンタ! バッボを取り返せ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost and Found Babbo!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ginta ! Ramène Babbo !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Perduto e ritrovato</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginta! Babbo o Torikaese!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35878" update="2005-04-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の美少年, アルヴィス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alviss, The Mysterious Young Man!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alviss, un mystérieux jeune homme !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un giovane misteriosoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Bishounen, Alviss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35879" update="2005-04-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の中の少女, スノウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow: The Young Girl Inside the Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Snow, prisonnière des glaces !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Neve, la ragazza che vive nel ghiaccio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Naka no Shoujo, Snow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36538" update="2005-06-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めよ! もう一人のエド!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awaken: Meet the Other Ed!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le réveil de l`autre Edo</title>
<title xml:lang="it">All`interno di Ed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame yo! Mou Hitori no Ed!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36624" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活のナイト・ファントム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom, The Undead Knight!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fantôme, le cavalier d`outre-tombe !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Phantom, il non morto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu no Night Phantom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36625" update="2005-05-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修練の門, メリロとブモル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Training Gate - Merilo and Bumoru</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La porte de l`entraînement, Merilo et Bumolle</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La porta della disciplina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuren no Mon, Merilo to Bumoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36626" update="2005-12-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二次メルヘヴン大戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Great War Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La 2e grande guerre de Mär Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Seconda Grande Guerra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dainiji MAR Heaven Taisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37660" update="2005-06-07">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見せてやる! バッボ・バージョン②!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Babbo: Version 2!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attention les yeux ! Babbo version 2 !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Seconda Versione Di Babbo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misete Yaru! Babbo Version 2!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37697" update="2005-08-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルベリアのボス, ナナシ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanashi, Chief of Luberia!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nanashi, le boss de Luberia !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Nanashi: Il Capo Di Rubelia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Luberia no Boss, Nanashi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38067" update="2005-08-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底湖の戦い! ナナシVSオルコ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanashi vs. Orco at the Underground Lake!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille dans le lac souterrain ! Nanashi vs. Olk !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Orco nel lago sotterraneo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiteiko no Tatakai! Nanashi VS Orco!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38068" update="2005-08-12">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バッボ・バージョン③! 出て来いガーゴイル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Babbo Version Three: Gargoyle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Babbo Version3 ! La Gargouille !!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Babbo Version 3! Detekoi Gargoyle!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38520" update="2005-10-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7人目の仲間? ジョン・ピーチ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">John Peach, The Seventh Team Member?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">John Peach, le 7e compagnon ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-ninme no Nakama? John Peach!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38886" update="2005-07-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォーゲーム開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War Games Commence!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Que le War Game commence !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">War Game Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38976" update="2005-07-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1STバトル1! アルヴィスVSレノ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Battle: Alviss vs. Leno!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">1e bataille, Round 1 : Alviss VS Leno !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1st Battle 1! Alviss VS Leno!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38977" update="2005-07-22">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1STバトル2! ジャックVSパノ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Battle: Part 2, Jack vs. Pano!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">1e bataille, Round 2 : Jack VS Pano !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1st Battle 2! Jack VS Pano!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38978" update="2005-08-02">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャプテン・ギンタ! ガーゴイルVSガロン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captain Ginta and Gargoyle vs. Garon!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille des capitaines : Ginta VS Garon !!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Captain Ginta! Gargoyle VS Garon!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39596" update="2005-11-03">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修練の門再び! ケンカのやり方教えます!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back to the Training Gate! Learn How to Really Fight!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour à la porte d`entraînement !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuren no Mon Futatabi! Kenka no Yarikata Oshiemasu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39894" update="2005-08-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠フィールド! 闘うお姫様!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Desert Field and the Fighting Princess!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille du désert: Snow entre ne scène !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku Field! Tatakau Ohime-sama!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39895" update="2005-08-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナナシVSロコ! 呪いのワラ人形!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanashi vs. Loco and the Straw Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nanashi vs Loco: l`épouvantail maudit !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanashi VS Loco! Noroi no Wara Ningyou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39896" update="2005-08-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐るべき魔女! ドロシー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dorothy: A Witch to be Feared!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dorothy, une redoutable sorcière !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osorubeki Majo! Dorothy!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41281" update="2005-09-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントムの密やかな楽しみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom`s Hidden Joy!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La joie secrète du fantôme !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom no Hisoyaka na Tanoshimi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41289" update="2005-09-12">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遅れて来た男! アラン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alan: The Man Who Came Late!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alan, l`homme en retard !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okurete Kita Otoko! Alan!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41380" update="2006-01-17">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">男を見せるぜジャック! 魔法のキノコ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Show Your Stuff, Jack: Funky Fungi!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jack, un homme, un vrai !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko o Miseru ze Jack! Mahou no Kinoko!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41703" update="2005-09-24">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, 負けないよ! 火山群のスノウ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow at the Volcano Mountain Range Field</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi, Makenai yo! Kazangun no Snow!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41803" update="2005-10-02">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪いのロウソク! ギンタVSカノッチ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Accursed Candle! Ginta vs. Kannochi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroi no Rousoku! Ginta VS Kannochi!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42079" update="2005-10-09">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうひとつのゾンビタトゥー! アルヴィスVSロラン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Zombie Tatto! Alviss vs. Rolan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Hitotsu no Zombie Tatoo! Alviss VS Rolan!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42305" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄! ファントムとゾディアックのナイト!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom and the Zodiac Knights</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu! Phantom to Zodiac no Knight!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42306" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャドーバトル! ガーゴイルVSブラックガーゴイル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow Battles! Gargoyle Vs. the Dark Gargoyle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shadow Battle! Gargoyle VS Black Gargoyle!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42307" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静かなる闘志... アルヴィスの力...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Quiet Fighting Spirit... Alviss` Power!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizuka Naru Toushi... Alviss no Chikara...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43040" update="2005-11-06">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どうなるジャック! どうするドロシー!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Team MAR on the Ropes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dou Naru Jack! Dou Suru Dorothy!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44449" update="2005-11-11">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アクアとアッコちゃんとナナシ流!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aqua, Akko and the Nanashi Method</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aqua to Akko-chan to Nanashi Ryuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44640" update="2005-11-13">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲のギロム! エゴラVSガーゴイル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girom Counterattacks! Egola Vs. Gargoyle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu no Gillom! Egora vs Gargoyle!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44641" update="2005-11-13">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドロシーVSラプンツェル, 唄え. クレイジーキルト!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sing, Crazy Quilt, Sing! Dorothy Vs. Rapunzel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorothy VS Rapunzel, Utae. Crazy Quilt!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45395" update="2006-05-13">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法の国, カルデアへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Caldia, the Land of Witches</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou no Kuni, Kaldea e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45396" update="2006-06-17">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵略者ファントム・ギンタ激闘の果てに...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom Vs. Ginta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinryakusha Phamtom - Ginta Gekitou no Hate ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45702" update="2006-06-22">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">こども大好きナイト, アッシュ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ash, the Knight Who Protects Children</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodomo Daisuki Knight, Ash!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45920" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界一ブサイク決定戦!?スノウVSエモキス!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World`s Ugliest Match! Snow Vs. Eemokis!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekaiichi Busaiku Ketteisen!? Snow VS Emokis!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46037" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪われた魔力! アルヴィスの危機!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aalviss` Crisis: Stolen Magical Power!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ubawareta Maryoku! Alviss no Kiki!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46038" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">快感! 石使いのナイト, キャンディス!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensation! The Knight Candice, Stone User!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaikan! Ishi Tsukai no Knight, Candice!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46244" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の戦場! サイコスペース!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Field of Death! The Psycho Space!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Senjou! Psycho Space!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46245" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の死闘! ナナシVSガリアン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fateful Mortal Combat! Nanashi Vs. Galian!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Shitou! Nanashi VS Garian!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46917" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒りのドロシー! 砂漠の塔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dorothy`s Anger! The Desert Tower!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikari no Dorothy! Sabaku no Tou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46918" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新生ナイト, 復讐のイアン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Knight Reborn! Ian`s Revenge!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei Knight, Fukushuu no Ian!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46919" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷撃×雷撃! ナナシ, よみがえる記憶!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lightning Vs. Lightning! Nanashi`s Memory Returns!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raigeki x Raigeki! Nanashi, Yomigaeru Kioku!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46920" update="2006-09-12">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷だらけのアルヴィス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alviss` Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizu Darake no Alviss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48641" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾンネンズ! 狙われた修練の門!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Zonnens Infiltrate the Training Gate!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zonnens! Nerawareta Shuuren no Mon!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48642" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルヴィス×ナナシ! 禁断のラビリンス!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alviss Vs. Nanashi! Forbidden Labyrinth!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alviss X Nanashi! Kindan no Labyrinth!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48643" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドロシー×スノウ! 誘惑のルージュ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dorothy Vs. Snow! The Allure of Lippenstift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorothy X Snow! Yuuwaku no Rouge!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49835" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届け! 希望のシックスセンス!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Concentrate! The Power of the Sixth Sense!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoke! Kibou no Sixth Sense!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49836" recap="true" update="2008-05-10">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントムを倒す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ll beat Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom o Taosu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49837" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アランのサブイボ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alan`s Goosebumps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alan no Sabuibo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49838" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルヴィスが許せない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unforgiving Alviss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alviss ga Yurusenai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49839" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドロシーが食べられた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dorothy Gets Swallowed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorothy ga Taberareta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49840" update="2006-06-27">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スノウが笑った</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow`s Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Snow ga Waratta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50463" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イアンが怒る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ian`s Anger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ian ga Okoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50464" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギンタ東京へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ginta Returns to Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginta Tokyo e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50465" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナナシの暴走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanashi`s Reckless Move</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanashi no Bousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50466" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">深窓のドロシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep Depths of Dorothy`s Mind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsou no Doroshii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50467" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アランの名探偵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alan the Famous Detective</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alan no Meitantei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50468" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルヴィスと少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alviss and Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alviss to Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50469" update="2006-05-30">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小雪の仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koyuki`s Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koyuki no Kamen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51327" update="2006-09-23">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の国のリリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lilis of the Strange Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi no Kuni no Lilis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52155" update="2006-07-16">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レギンレイヴ姫の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess Reginre`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reginleif Hime no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52156" update="2006-07-16">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロコと呪いの新ÄRM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New ARM of Loco and Curse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loco to Noroi no Shin ARM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52321" update="2006-07-23">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストバトル始まるッ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginning of the Last Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Battle Hajimaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52322" update="2006-07-23">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャックと炎のガーディアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jack and the Fire Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jack to Honoo no Guardian</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52323" update="2006-07-23">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再戦 アルヴィス対ロラン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rematch: Alviss vs. Rolan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisen Alviss Tai Rolan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57868" update="2006-08-10">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の刹那</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Setsuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62449" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみの花嫁[キメラ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bride of Sorrow (Chimera)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Chimera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62450" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アランの古傷[トラウマ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alan`s Old Wound (Trauma)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alan no Trauma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62451" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば旧友[ハロウィン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Old Friend (Halloween)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Halloween</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62452" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルベリアの誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruberia`s Oath</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ruberia no Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62453" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真紅の爪[ガーネットクロウ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scarlet Claw (Garnet Crow)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garnet Crow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62454" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギンタ対ファントム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ginta vs. Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginta Tai Phantom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62455" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最凶猫ガーディアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Most Evil Cat Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sai Kyou Neko Guardian</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62456" update="2006-09-11">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着ッ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64205" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわいい来客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cute Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaii Raikyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64206" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バッボ割れる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Splitting Babbo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Babbo Wareru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64207" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活の咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Roar of Revival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu no Houkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64208" update="2006-10-14">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イアンと花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ian and Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ian to Hanayome</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65160" update="2006-11-13">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スノウ奪還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rescue Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Snow Dakkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65161" update="2007-01-04">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の嵐ゼピュロスブルーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stormy Zephyroth Broom of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Arashi Zephyroth Broom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65229" update="2006-11-19">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時間の輪舞[ロンド]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Round Dance of Time (Rondo)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikan no Rondo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65365" update="2006-11-27">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">城塞都市パルトガイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fortress City Pultgayin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jousai Toshi Pultgayin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65506" update="2007-01-04">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントムの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65570" update="2007-01-04">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒のゾンビタトゥ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awakening the Zombie Tattoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei no Zombie Tattoo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65587" update="2007-01-04">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘却のクラヴィーア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cravea of Forgetfulness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boukyaku no Cravea</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65588" update="2007-01-04">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルヴィスよ瞑[ねむ]れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alviss Closes His Eyes (Name)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alviss yo Nemure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66494" update="2007-01-07">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミスティ キャッスル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misty Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misty Castle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66692" update="2007-01-10">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冥界のアナリーゼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Analyst of the Dark World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meikai no Analyse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66693" update="2007-01-10">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薔薇は散りてなお染まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scattered and Dyed Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara wa Chirite Nao Somari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66694" update="2007-01-10">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スノウの真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow`s Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Snow no Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67317" update="2007-02-05">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽りの平和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deceitful Peace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari no Heiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67409" update="2007-02-11">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎に散り 水に眠る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disperses in Flame, Sleeps in Water</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo ni Chiri Mizu ni Nemuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67410" update="2007-02-11">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば 心優しきチェス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Tender-Hearted Chess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Kokoro Yasashiki Chess</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67411" update="2007-02-11">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルヴィスの光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light of Alviss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alviss no Hikari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68347" update="2007-03-12">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀の嵐ゼビュロスブルーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stormy Zephyroth Broom of Pity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Arashi Zephyroth Broom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68348" update="2007-03-12">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギンタ対ダンナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ginta vs. Danna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginta Tai Danna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68349" update="2007-03-12">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワクワクは止まらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Excitement That Never Stops</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakuwaku wa Tomaranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128027" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128028" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128029" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128030" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128031" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128032" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128033" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128034" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128035" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128036" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128037" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128038" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
