<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2858" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Solty Rei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">SoltyRei</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">曙光少女</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">solty</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソルティレイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Solty Rei</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Solty Rei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Solty Rei</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">الصياد</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Solty Rei</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11345" approval="15" total="15">Dimension W</anime>
<anime id="14574" approval="5" total="5">Cop Craft</anime>
<anime id="412" approval="3" total="3">Z.O.E Dolores,i</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="270639">Just awsome, too bad is so underrated.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="301144">Freaking Great Anime, A should see soon-type.&lt;br /&gt;</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="132226">A must-see for everyone who likes bounty-hunter settings like Cowboy Beebop or Outlaw Star. And if you like Zone of the Enders too, you`d be crazy to miss it. ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="89596">awsome anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="625307">rather than excelling at a single part, this show tries to be good through the board. and most of the time they succeed.
every emotional challenge gets a cathartic solution. world building and character development work in sync. animation and sound keep the same quality throughout the show. the plot stays on course while fulfilling tropes.
everyone who likes their Drama dressed up as a Sci-Fi and sprinkled with Action, will love this show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="363244">Awsome anime, this is one of "must see" anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="533655">Generally good story. Predictable, but still good. There are some extremely annoying characters, but it gets better. Nice sci-fi cyberpunk atmosphere, touching story and bounty hunters!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296097">great anime. definitely a `must watch` anime!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.solty.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="2161" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shuujirou Ha</name>
<name id="2161" type="Character Design">Shuujirou Ha</name>
<name id="2161" type="Original Plan">Shuujirou Ha</name>
<name id="735" type="Original Plan">Gonzo</name>
<name id="2149" type="Direction">Hiraike Yoshimasa</name>
<name id="116" type="Music">Oomori Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Countless were killed in the unexplained Blast Fall, and those left maimed - the Resembles - had their bodies rebuilt with high-tech prosthetic devices. Bounty hunter http://anidb.net/ch10617 [Roy Revant] was sure he`d seen everything the broken city had to offer - until the day a strange little girl named http://anidb.net/ch10616 [Solty] fell from the sky. Roy and Solty may seek different things, but who wants to search for truth alone?
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1573">6.13</permanent>
<temporary count="1594">7.45</temporary>
<review count="6">7.30</review>
</ratings>
<picture>84008.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5051</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3138</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2399</identifier>
<identifier>scnjsl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.solty.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>SoltyRei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ソルティレイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322664</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7745</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="807" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>prosthesis</name>
<description>A prosthesis (prosthetic) (from Ancient Greek πρόσθεσις, "addition, application, attachment") is a device that replaces a missing body part.</description>
<picurl>223944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1616" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-07">
<name>crippled</name>
<description>A person that is partially or totally unable to use one or more limbs, for example a lame.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3431" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>retro</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4577" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-19">
<name>family values</name>
<description>Family values are traditional or cultural values, generally conservative in nature, that pertain to the family`s structure, function, roles, beliefs, attitudes, and ideals. They encompass a set of beliefs, the most common of which is the classical "traditional family" involving a middle-class family with a breadwinner father and a homemaker mother, raising their biological children.
According to Merriam-Webster, family values are "values especially of a traditional or conservative kind which are held to promote the sound functioning of the family and to strengthen the fabric of society."
Source: English Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6066" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>improvised weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be split and deleted. Please apply any applicable http://anidb.net/tag/?parentid=7405&amp;reltb=chartb [weaponized object tags] to the relevant characters, or create new tags if necessary, and delete this tag from the anime/character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10616" type="main character in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="14">6.29</rating>
<name>Solty Revant</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the series` main protagonists, she is first seen battling RUC`s special forces. She accidentaly meets Roy Revant, whom she gets attached too. After saving Roy`s life she ends upo staying in his house. Her cheerful, helpful and naive personality is the object of patronizing feeling of people surrounding Roy, and eventually Roy himself, who gives her the name Solty (which comes from one of the old records at Roy`s home). It is up to her acquaintances and friends to discover Solty`s real identity.</description>
<picture>31675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10617" type="main character in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="7">5.75</rating>
<name>Roy Revant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the main protagonists of the series`, Roy lives with only one aim - to find his daughter, which had been lost after a catastrophy also known as Blast Fall (which also took his wife`s life). Roy usually tries to appear gruff and standoffish, however, he presents more parental features in Solty`s presence. He works as a bounty hunter at "Maverick Hunters" agency, and simultaneously has the duty of being Miranda Maverick`s (who happens to be the head of the agency) bodyguard.</description>
<picture>31677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28107" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-05">
<rating votes="7">6.30</rating>
<name>Rose Anderson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A vain, attention-seeking bandit who calls herself "The Blue Comet". She is honest, yet unyielding, proud, and selfish. Although she and her brothers donate their spoils to the Unregistered Citizens clustered in the city`s underground and outskirts, they often cause large amounts of public damage in the process. She is armed with a laser-based hand pistol, and she rides a large motorcycle with three spherical wheels in front, driving wheels behind, and a cannon hidden in the frame. She occasionally hums the song "Return to love (Jazz version)" to calm herself.It is later revealed that she is actually Roy`s daughter Rita Revant. Her hair and eye colour had changed due to exposure to nanomachines from the Blast Fall. Having been adopted by Larry and Andy`s father with no memory of who she was, she initially resisted the idea that she was Roy`s daughter until later. She was supposedly killed in the collapse of a clock tower, but later, she was shown to be alive and working for Ashley Lynx, in order to follow their common dream of equality among residents. She was given a red and black Proceed suit. It also includes a jet pack, which allows her to fly. Solty eventually wore the suit in the final episode when she went into space. Eventually, she overcame Ashley`s brainwashing to see the limitations and problems of her attitudes and dream. During the "Five Years Later" epilogue, she is referred to as "Representative Rita Revant" by a radio broadcast, indicating she attains a position of political power.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28108" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="5">7.16</rating>
<name>Miranda Maverick</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roy`s employer and Kasha`s foster mother. She runs the "Maverick Hunters", an independent bounty hunting agency. She is normally a very kind and laid-back person, but can be aggressive when necessary. Her husband was killed in the Blast Fall.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28110" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="6">2.85</rating>
<name>Kasha Maverick</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miranda`s adopted daughter. She is pragmatic and slightly distrustful of others, but latches onto Solty and (eventually) Rose. Kasha forms an awkward friendship with Sylvia when they both stalk Rose and Ashley on their date.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28112" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Yuuto K. Steel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Resemble specialist in the city hospital. It is through his analysis that Solty`s gynoid nature is first revealed. After being fired due to an accident during the diagnosis, he is hired by Miranda and moves into Roy and Solty`s building. A stereotypical geek, his fascination with Solty annoys Roy and Kasha to no end.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28113" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">1.60</rating>
<name>Ashley Lynx</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ashley Lynx is a white haired, high-ranking member of the R.U.C. His original name is Locke. The left side of his face and torso, his left arm, and possibly more of his body are Resemble. He is one of the few surviving first-generation immigrants, and once supervised the construction of the underground city. While he is charming superficially, he holds ulterior motives for those who work for him, and ultimately has little regard for his subordinates.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>64896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28114" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">4.99</rating>
<name>Integra Martel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dark-haired leader of R.U.C. Special Security Division (PROCEED Team). Integra is responsible and level-headed. Her PROCEED suit is pink and can increase her speed to superhuman levels, but it taxes her to do this more than three times successively.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>64897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28115" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">5.02</rating>
<name>Sylvia Ban</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hot-tempered blonde who has romantic feelings for Ashley. Her PROCEED suit is blue and increases her strength.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28116" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="5">2.96</rating>
<name>Celica Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tanned, carefree sniper who works as long range support for the PROCEED Team. She is quite a laid back person who is very close to Sylvia and often teases Accela. Despite working for the R.U.C., she was an Unregistered Citizen in her youth until she was adopted by Kasha`s uncle and aunt and raised as their own. Her PROCEED suit is orange, and contains multiple laser ports on the shoulders and arms. It also aids her sight, which is good in her position as a sniper. She has a penchant for slacking off and playing video games, but she does her job well as long as she gets paid.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28117" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="6">3.46</rating>
<name>Accela Warrick</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A redheaded, shy, information specialist of the PROCEED Team. Accela is a good cook. She takes care of Solty temporarily after Roy scolds her. Her PROCEED suit is white and allows her greater computer network access.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28118" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Larry Anderson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The older of the two Anderson Brothers and Rose`s elder foster brother. He has noticeably dark pink hair. He is the leader of the bandit group.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28119" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="3">1.60</rating>
<name>Andy Anderson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The younger, hot-tempered Anderson Brother. He has spiky brown hair. He is an expert in computer network and computer hacking.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28120" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="1">3.38</rating>
<name>Rita Revant (Greco)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A New Rights Child who`s living with Vincent Greco in the outskirts of the city. She`s blind and crippled from the waist-down, disabilities she acquired from the Blast Fall.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28121" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>John Kimberley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A murderer who killed Rose`s best friend`s family when she was a child. Rose eventually finds him and confronts him, but he proves to be more than she can handle, largely due to the laser deflector blades in his arms.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28122" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<name>Vincent Greco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Unregistered Citizen who becomes one of Roy`s bounty targets. Vincent stole P-1O crystals to sell on the black market in order to earn money for his daughter`s Resemble operation. Vincent told his daughter, Rita, that he is her uncle, for fear that his status would take away her rights as a Registered Citizen.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28123" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<name>Dewey Black</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Administrator of a hospital. He hires Roy for guarding the transport of a suitcase.</description>
<picture>64907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28124" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Jack McLean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Condemned Prisoner no. 11467, Test Subject no. 4385. A 78% Resemble, which was achieved with the most state-of-the-art technology. McLean escaped from the research facility and was being hunted by the PROCEED Team.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3264" picture="24262.jpg">Dan Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28125" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Meryl Tyler</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Solty`s first friend, whom she met while shopping. Later, after seeing Solty`s powers, she shuns her out of fear.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28126" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<name>Dale Boyd</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bounty hunter mark and Gray Walker`s partner in crime.</description>
<picture>64910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37018" picture="49379.jpg">Hirao Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28127" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<name>Gray Walker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dale Boyd`s partner in crime. Both of his arms are Resemble that can extend at great lengths.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30151" picture="79475.jpg">Tsuji Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28129" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Natalie Roman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A secretary to the hospital director Dewey Black.</description>
<picture>64912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3398" picture="224826.jpg">Kingetsu Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28130" type="appears in" update="2011-02-01">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Kelly Jones</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A criminal who offers jobs to Vincent Greco to gather the money for the operation of Vincent`s daughter.</description>
<picture>64913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3264" picture="24262.jpg">Dan Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28131" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">1.57</rating>
<name>Hou Chuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A psychotic genius of explosive technology. He holds a grudge against Roy for intentionally destroying his right arm more than a decade ago, when Roy was still a police officer and mentally unstable due to his daughter Rita`s disappearance.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>64915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28143" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">1.66</rating>
<name>Jeremy Kolbel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young female researcher and friend of Yuuto`s. Jeremy was performing an experiment in search of new forms of energy, in defiance of the R.U.C. monopoly.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="433" picture="17312.jpg">Nagata Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28145" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-02">
<rating votes="2">8.11</rating>
<name>Will</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young orphan and Blast Fall survivor who is living with Joseph beyond the outskirts of the city.</description>
<picture>64937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28146" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">3.56</rating>
<name>Joseph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first-generation immigrant and former senior member of the R.U.C. who knows Solty`s workings well. He had a dispute with Ashley Lynx in the past and become a passive observer of the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>64938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28147" type="appears in" update="2011-02-02">
<name>Jeff Miyamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bounty hunter mark. Jeff is a former bank employee who embezzled money.</description>
<picture>64941.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28151" type="appears in" update="2011-02-02">
<rating votes="2">7.59</rating>
<name>Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young girl who steals fruits from Votre`s food stall. She is an Unregistered Citizen and her parents died in the Blast Fall. Her hair is done to resemble Nekomimi.
-Wikipedia-</description>
<picture>64956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28152" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">7.59</rating>
<name>Votre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Registered Citizen who runs a fruit stand. He later befriends Mii after she stole from him. His wife and daughter died in the Blast Fall.</description>
<picture>64957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28153" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Illumina Kisch</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend and co-worker of Locke (later known as Ashley) aboard the colonization ship. She was the overseer of the construction of the underground city and the terra-formation on the planet from the ship.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>64959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2227" picture="73301.jpg">Inamura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41433" update="2005-09-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42140" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい朝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Dawn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein neuer Morgen</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Un nuevo amanecer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Asa</title>
<summary>The mystery of Solty’s origins grows when the RUC Elite Squad comes knocking. Roy’s starting to care about Solty in spite of himself, but nothing’s going to change the fact that something isn’t right about her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42141" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーロラの降る街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The City Where the Aurora Falls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Stadt, in der Aurora fiel</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La ciudad donde cae la aurora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aurora no Furu Machi</title>
<summary>Roy Revant spends his days with one eye looking down the barrel of a gun and the other scanning for clues about his vanished family. He’s in a rut with no future - until a little girl falls from the sky.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42501" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl in Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Mädchen in Blau</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La chica de azul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao no Shoujo</title>
<summary>Solty unleashes a shocking display of strange abilities when thieves try to steal a package placed in Roy’s care. After a scan at the hospital, it’s quickly becoming apparent that Solty is something special.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42696" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">微笑む猫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freundin</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Amiga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hohoemu Neko</title>
<summary>Science may call Solty a machine, but her emotions are as human as they come. After a clash with a dangerous Resemble in the sewer, Solty explores some new human traits: the pangs of loss and loneliness.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42951" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォーターサイド・パニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waterside Panic</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Panik am Wasser</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Pánico en el agua</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waterside Panic</title>
<summary>Roy’s and his crew head to the pool! But when news of a stolen jewel gets out, and the bathing beauties include a thief and RUC Security Force members, it’s not likely anyone will be able to relax.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42952" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛娘(まなむすめ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beloved Daughter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geliebte Tochter</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Amada hija</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manamusume</title>
<summary>When Roy and Solty confront a thief with a previously clean record, it may prove easier to sympathize than condemn one caught in such a desperate situation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44387" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小悪魔の訪問</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Little Blue Demon Comes to Visit</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Besuch von einem kleinen Teufel</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Un pequeño demonio en casa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koakuma no Houmon</title>
<summary>Rose crashes with Roy and quickly becomes a thorn in his side. But the circumstances surrounding some stolen medical shipments prove that many desperate people view her in a whole different light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44388" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リベンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rache</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Venganza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Revenge</title>
<summary>Rose’s hope of turning Solty into a thief is causing friction with Roy, but he may be the only person who can help when a face from Rose’s past pushes her to the brink of murder.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44656" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女達の休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Day Off</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Feiertag des Mädchens</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Día libre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome-tachi no Kyuujitsu</title>
<summary>Roy could use a little comfort food, so Solty spends her day trying to improve her culinary skills. Meanwhile, Rose is cooking something up with a mysterious RUC official who talks a good game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44658" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレジャー&amp;レスキュー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasure and Rescue</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schatzsuche und Rettung</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Tesoro y rescate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Treasure &amp; Rescue</title>
<summary>Solty and Rose find themselves trapped in the crumbling underground city, and even with the help of the Resemble Rescue Squad, the situation looks exceedingly bleak.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="45399" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バースデーゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birthday Game</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geburtstags-Spiel</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Fiesta de cumpleaños</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Birthday Game</title>
<summary>Just in time for Roy’s birthday, a homicidal mastermind from his past starts leaving explosive gifts around town. Revant isn’t the only target - everyone he cares about is in danger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46084" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着の果てに-na-mi-da-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tears: After the Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Ende der Entscheidung - Tränen</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Lágrimas después del enfrentamiento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku no Hate ni: Namida</title>
<summary>As Roy fights to free Rose from the bomber’s clutches, he learns his daughter is alive and closer than expected. Revant risks life and limb for his little girl as the world explodes around him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46120" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distance</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Distanz</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Distancia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigai</title>
<summary>Roy cherishes the memory of his daughter, but living with her is a handful. Rose finds herself torn between two identities, desperate to learn who she really is.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46188" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心覆う闇のために...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heavy Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Für die Dunkelheit, die das Herz erfüllt</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Corazones fuertes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro Oou Yami no Tame ni...</title>
<summary>Alone once more, Roy turns inward, facing destiny at the bottom of a bottle. But Solty needs him now more than ever. As she wanders the streets alone, Roy must decide to gather his strength or suffer forever.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46568" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たどり着いた場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Safe Haven</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Ort, an dem ich angekommen bin</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Paraiso seguro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadori Tsuita Basho</title>
<summary>Solty’s feeling down and ventures into the desert, stumbling upon an old man and a kid named Will. In the city, Roy continues to wallow in a dark funk - until Miranda decides to beat him out of it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46738" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冗談です, 半分</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Half Kidding</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das war ein halber Witz</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Mitad en broma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joudan Desu, Hanbun</title>
<summary>While Solty deals with tragedy in the desert, strange tests are being run inside RUC headquarters. Ashley introduces the new leader of the Security Force, shaking the squad to its core.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47039" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LADY(レディー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La dama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lady</title>
<summary>Solty returns home just as Roy ventures into the desert to find her. Meanwhile, Rose is back and in a position of power in the RUC. And when Ashley reveals his true colors, the primary shade is blood red.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47064" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかえりなさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Home</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schön, dass du wieder zu Hause bist</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Bienvenida</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaerinasai</title>
<summary>Treason and murder have the RUC girls scrambling to survive. Not the types to take betrayal lightly, they begin a personal war. Meanwhile, the brothers Anderson learn of Rose’s return.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47289" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全員集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Together</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alle kommen zusammen</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Todos juntos!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zen`in Shuugou</title>
<summary>Roy confronts Ashley, taking a stand against the seeming corruption of his daughter. As the Aurora Shell shimmers over a crippled metropolis, an observer from the desert decides to take action.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47424" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">訪レル災い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Catastrophe Calls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Unfall, der dich besucht</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Llega la desgracia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otozureru Wazawai</title>
<summary>An encounter with Ashley leaves Solty catatonic. Meanwhile, the desert hermit reveals information about the Aurora Shell’s impact on little girls - and one of the little girls decides to fight back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47699" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実の刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Time for Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Zeit der Wahrheit</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La hora de la verdad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjitsu no Toki</title>
<summary>The dark reality of Resemble technology is revealed along with insight into Eunomia; the super-computer steering the destiny of all who live beneath the incandescent heavens. Deconstruction is imminent.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48036" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしと彼女と, 少女の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three Girls, Three Intentions</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Meine, ihre und des Mädchens Gefühle</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Tres chicas, tres intenciones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi to Kanojo to, Shoujo no Omoi</title>
<summary>Humanity is in the crossfire as Solty takes her first steps toward her incredible fate. First, she must face Rose in the smoke above the burning city. A better world awaits, but by whose design shall it arise?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48037" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後のコトバ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Message</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die letzte Nachricht</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Mensaje final</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kotoba</title>
<summary>Two hundred years of pain bring Ashley to the cusp of apocalypse, and humanity’s undoing looms just beneath the stars. A time for great sacrifice has arrived.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48038" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Future</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Zeit ab jetzt</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El futuro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Korekara</title>
<summary>Armed with an appreciation for life, death, and love, Solty rises to confront civilization’s final threat that drifts silently through the stars. She is humanity’s only hope.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65169" update="2017-08-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2006-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違うキモチで, 想い合うココロで.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opportunities Missed and Love Shared</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Oportunidades perdidas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigau Kimochi de, Omoi Au Kokoro de.</title>
<summary>This is a two part story that happened after Rose moved into Roy`s apartment. During the preparations for Appreciation Day, Solty watches people in the city going about and preparing for the celebration and is confronted with a thought: what is true happiness? While trying to understand happiness and the complexity of human emotions, a young girl who has had a falling out with her mother confronts Solty and Rose asking for their help.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
