<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="287" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>1997-12-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shoujo Kakumei Utena</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Revolutionary Girl Utena TV</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Rewolucjonistka Utena</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shoujo Kakumei Utena TV</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">少女革命</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Utena TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">rgu</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="short">Utena</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Utena</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">少女革命ウテナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Revolutionary Girl Utena</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Utena - La fillette révolutionnaire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Utena la fillette révolutionnaire</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La rivoluzione di Utena</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Юная революционерка Утэна</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="256" type="Alternative Setting">Shoujo Kakumei Utena: Adolescence Mokushiroku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8421" approval="83" total="109">Mawaru Penguindrum</anime>
<anime id="7591" approval="45" total="75">Star Driver: Kagayaki no Takuto</anime>
<anime id="516" approval="41" total="53">Princess Tutu</anime>
<anime id="10811" approval="18" total="19">Yurikuma Arashi</anime>
<anime id="181" approval="14" total="27">Versailles no Bara</anime>
<anime id="8069" approval="10" total="24">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
<anime id="1551" approval="10" total="17">Boukyaku no Senritsu</anime>
<anime id="131" approval="4" total="13">Ayashi no Ceres</anime>
<anime id="10046" approval="3" total="10">Hanamonogatari: Suruga Devil</anime>
<anime id="6820" approval="2" total="12">Black Rock Shooter</anime>
<anime id="9875" approval="2" total="6">Kill la Kill</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="744069">A good series, but overrated.
The story is decent, while the anime production is cheap.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292982">Superb analog visuals and more CLAMP than CLAMP</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="3391" type="Character Design">Hasegawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="3392" type="Series Composition">Enokido Youji</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="5629" type="Original Plan">Saitou Chiho</name>
<name id="5628" type="Original Work">Be-Papas</name>
<name id="3569" type="Music">Mitsumune Shinkichi</name>
<name id="3648" type="Original Plan">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
<name id="3648" type="Direction">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Tenjou Utena]`s parents died when she was a little girl. At that time, a prince appeared to her and gave her a signet ring with a rose crest. He told Utena to keep the ring and promised that they would meet again someday. Utena was so impressed by him that she decided to become a prince herself! Utena is all grown up now. She studies at the Ootori Academy and wears her own version of the boys` uniform. She still looks forward to finding her prince, but in the meantime, it`s up to Utena to save damsels in distress and cross swords with Ootori Academy`s top duellists. When Utena unwittingly wins the "Rose Bride" in one such duel, she finds herself in the middle of something else... something that just may lead her to her prince.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2040">7.29</permanent>
<temporary count="2069">7.57</temporary>
<review count="9">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>50314.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>207</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>440</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>308</identifier>
<identifier>pqjjon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Revolutionary_Girl_Utena</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>少女革命ウテナ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88909</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1916</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B008M36GQE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3047" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>feminism</name>
<description>Women or girls fighting against the social stereotyping of females.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3849" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-01">
<name>it`s time to duel</name>
<description>Individual characters frequently face each other head-on, usually for a prize.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4337" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-03-11">
<name>you`re my hidden weapon!</name>
<description>One or more characters (females usually) turn into weapons or release them from their body to be used by their teammate or partner in times of need.
Examples: Himemiya Anthy from Shoujo Kakumei Utena, Soul from Soul Eater, Kureha from Shining x Tears Wind, and Yuzuriha Inori from Guilty Crown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6847" type="main character in" update="2012-01-14">
<rating votes="55">8.65</rating>
<name>Tenjou Utena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Utena is a tomboyish, courageous and naïve character who lives to emulate the idealised prince figure from her childhood. She is forthright, honest, and friendly. Nearly all the girls in school idolise her. She both subverts and conforms to the stereotypes she embodies as a noble warrior and a naive magical girl in danger of becoming a damsel in distress. The series chronicles her journey to protect her friend http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy] and become a truly noble Prince. Her Duelling Rose is white.
In the anime, the initial story the anime presents is almost identical to that of the manga, except with darker detail. Flashbacks show the young Utena climbing into a coffin upon her parents` deaths, seeing no point in living if all humans eventually perish. She is "saved" by Prince http://anidb.net/ch8696 [Dios], who instils in her a drive to become a Prince herself. Up until the end of the series, Utena believes that her thirst for selfless nobility springs from her desire to meet her Prince again.
In both the anime and manga, Utena accidentally becomes a Duellist and wins Anthy as the Rose Bride. Though critical of the Duels for objectifying Anthy, her desires to protect Anthy as well as a drive to act like a Prince lead her to become the Duels most prominent Champion. As the series passes, her nobility is continuously tested, until she is finally forced to confront her own hypocrisy.
In the anime`s finale, http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio] tries to convince Utena to become his princess, and despite being reminded of her own failings and her feelings for him, Utena goes against him in the duel called Revolution. Her revived dedication to become a prince shocks Akio, and causes the destruction of the illusionary castle above the arena, where Utena gets the upper hand- only to get stabbed in the back by Anthy. Her sword taken from her, Utena is forced to watch Anthy being impaled by the swords of hatred while Akio tries to open the Rose Gate with her sword. But, after being goaded by Dios, Utena drags herself to the Rose Gate and pulls it open with her bare hands. Behind the Gate is Anthy, inside a coffin, and pleads for Utena to not try to save her. Utena doesn`t listen and begs Anthy to take her hand. Upon doing so, the coffin breaks off of the arena and falls towards Earth and Utena is pierced by the swords in Anthy`s place, which then destroy the arena. Some time after, people are starting to forget that Utena was ever at the academy, with Akio commenting that she became "another side leftover to be pitied". But, Utena did indeed get her wish, and managed to free Anthy from her bonds to the school and Akio. The anime ends with Anthy leaving the academy to find Utena.</description>
<picture>79967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6889" type="main character in" update="2012-01-09">
<rating votes="28">7.46</rating>
<name>Himemiya Anthy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious, shy girl whose vapid expression and superficial politeness mask a complex, darker persona. She is said to have no thoughts or desires besides that of what her master expect of her. Because of her "doormat" behaviour, other characters tend to project their wants or desires onto her, and she`s always the target of their eventual rage. Her past and current personality are simultaneously tragic and sinister, and her personality sifts between selfless love, passive-aggressive revenge, cruelty, and learned helplessness. Like http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena], Anthy also subverts and conforms to the stereotypes she embodies as both a damsel in distress and a witch.
Anthy appears to house the Sword of Dios within her own body. At the beginning of a duel, she slips into a trance and the Sword manifests, protruding from her chest so that her champion may draw it from her. This Sword is said to be a key to reaching the goal of Revolution, and Anthy, in her position as the Rose Bride, is supposed to be the key to obtaining it.
Anthy exhibits other unusual abilities as well, including magically embellishing Utena`s uniform before the duel. She seems to be able to completely alter her appearance, or at least induce others to see her for someone other than who she really is. Likewise, there is some indication that she has the ability to transform others as well (as in the episode "The Cowbell of Happiness").
In the anime, she appears to be servile and obedient to all, especially her current victor, whose every wishes she must cater to. Because of this, many Duellists believe that she lacks a personality and thoughts of her own, and she is treated badly by them. However, Anthy only pretends to be so in order to keep them in the Duels, and often enjoys subtly taking revenge on those around her.
According to the Adolescence of Utena manga, Anthy is in fact responsible for the duelling of which she is the prize. When her Prince http://anidb.net/ch8696 [Dios] (or http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio]) died, she became reborn as the Rose Bride. When she took this role, the Duelling Arena appeared and the "game" was set in motion so another "Prince" could take Akio`s place. In the anime series, the duels are a strategic game set in motion to restore Akio`s former powers and open the Gate of Revolution. In both of the film and manga (and sometimes in the anime), Anthy tries to make sexual advances towards Utena, but then she realizes that she`s her real prince and that she loves her.
In the anime, Dios is an actual prince who saves the girls in the world on a daily basis. The work eventually weakens him to the point of death, but the world still demands his services. Anthy ends up facing an angry mob alone in order to protect him, and is stabbed by a million swords. The swords quickly take a life of their own, eternally thirsting for a prince`s blood. To combat the pain, Anthy splits herself in two, and seals the part of her containing the swords beyond the Rose Gate, becoming the Rose Bride. This incident shatters Dios` faith in the world, and he is also split in two. One part of him becomes an altruistic but powerless ghost, while the other part becomes selfish and manipulative Akio. No longer a prince, Akio loses most of his power, so he establishes the Duelling Game to regain it. Anthy accepts her role as the Rose Bride, despite the suffering it inflicts on her, because she does not want to live in a world which had tortured her and her brother.</description>
<picture>3453.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7002" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-08">
<rating votes="19">8.50</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Juri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the academy`s fencing team, Juri is one of Ootori`s most highly respected students, and even the teachers appear to be in awe of her. Her aloof, intimidating manner belies a dark secret. Of the http://anidb.net/ch9171 [Student Council] Duellists, she is thought to be the most noble, and thus the one with the most potential to become a Prince, but her nobility and the strength that comes with it are constantly undermined by her desires and despair. Her Duelling Rose is orange.</description>
<picture>79656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7003" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="9">6.28</rating>
<name>Kaoru Miki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An ingenuous and polite seventh grader who befriends http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena], despite their role as possible opponents in the duels. He is especially known for his skill with the piano. In spite (or because of) his genius, he is lonely, sheltered, and insecure, and seeks a person who is just as pure and talented as him. His Rose Crest is light blue.
A piano player par excellence, Miki has fond memories of playing songs with his twin sister http://anidb.net/ch7312 [Kozue] in his childhood, but her refusal to play with him in the present — the symbol of a much deeper rift — gives Miki a sense of loss. His crush on http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy] in the anime (but on Utena in the manga) develops when he realises that they remind him of his estranged sister. In both adaptations, his drive to duel stems from a desire to find something to replace Kozue in his affections. All the females of the school, even older ones, idolise him, but Kozue threatens any girls who attempt to get too close to him. Likewise he is very protective of her, and so she tries to make him jealous by dating as many boys as possible. Letters sent to Miki from his parents hint at the fact that his parents are divorced.
He is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch9171 [Student Council], his position appearing to be the council secretary. He frequently appears with a stopwatch in hand. Miki is also a member of the fencing club.</description>
<picture>25769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7004" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="8">6.42</rating>
<name>Kiryuu Touga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>President of the http://anidb.net/ch9171 [Student Council] and Ootori`s resident playboy, Touga is an arrogant and handsome young man whose desire to be powerful drives him to cruel and unscrupulous deeds. He is the only regular Council Member who deliberately involves himself in http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio]`s plans. Despite his talent and intelligence, Touga eventually realizes that he`s nowhere near as influential as Akio or strong as http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena], and this causes him to change his ways as he tries to discover a new method to gain power. His Duelling Rose is red.
Although he says that he wishes to be noble, he has little empathy towards anyone, and his powers of manipulation are second only to Akio. He also shares his playboy attitude and has many female conquests. He is a childhood friend of Saionji, although their relationship took a turn for the worse at a point in their childhood that is the centrepiece of their respective personal journeys.
Toward the end of the series, however, Touga`s façade of chivalry is replaced with an apparently truer concern for Utena, to the extent that he very subtly attempts to substitute his head for hers on Akio`s chopping block. Arguably, this is also an example of Touga`s inability to see Utena as who she really is, rather than in a stereotypical feminine role.</description>
<picture>28721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7005" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-20">
<rating votes="6">4.96</rating>
<name>Saionji Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice-president of the Student Council and captain of the kendo team. He is temperamental, egotistic, prone to angry rages, and often cruel. His lack of self-control stems from insecurity, a lifelong rivalry against Touga from which he is always at the losing end, and the fear that everyone and everything he knows will eventually die. He is obsessed with Anthy because he views the Rose Bride as a mindless doll who will never disobey him, and thus be with him forever. His Duelling Rose is green.</description>
<picture>25266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7006" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-14">
<rating votes="9">5.21</rating>
<name>Shinohara Wakaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most outwardly cheerful person in the series and is http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena]`s best friend, but she feels surrounded by "special" people and doesn`t know how to become special herself. She is a co-dependent person who`s only happy when she takes care of people because she doesn`t feel like she has any other talents.</description>
<picture>79966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7007" type="appears in" update="2012-01-14">
<rating votes="2">5.35</rating>
<name>Chuchu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy]`s pet (whom she will only refer to as friend, but may be more properly described as a familiar). He is a small marmoset who acts as comedic relief. However, he also acts as an omen of bad fortune in certain episodes. He dresses similar to http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio], with a yellow-striped red tie and a single gold earring because Anthy appears to be enthralled by Akio and Chuchu wants to please Anthy.</description>
<picture>3495.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7082" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="10">6.09</rating>
<name>Kiryuu Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7004 [Touga]`s dramatic little sister, often used as comic relief throughout the series. Her love for her brother borders on obsession and incest, and she is often seen using devious scenes to punish the people who take her brother`s attentions away from her. Though her motivations are considered the simplest and least ambitious out of all the Duellists, they are no less real to her, and she suffers just as much as all the other http://anidb.net/ch9171 [Student Council] members throughout the series. Her Duelling Rose is yellow.
She is very fond of Touga to the point of their relationship having semi-incestuous edge, at least on her part. Nanami often makes various malicious attacks on students she deems inferior (or worse, those she suspects Touga is paying attention to).
After Touga is wounded in a duel with http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena], she temporarily takes over as Student Council President, adopting a bright yellow uniform. In duels, Nanami uses a style of dual blade fencing.</description>
<picture>25382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7312" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kaoru Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7003 [Miki]`s twin sister, Kozue feels shadowed by her brother`s talents and reacts by sleeping with many different men. She`s extremely possessive of Miki to the point where she physically hurts anyone who tries to hurt or "steal" him. She feels overshadowed by his talent and dirtied by comparison with him. Kozue resents Miki`s affection for http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Himemiya Anthy] and is prone to "acting out" to grab her brother`s attention, most notably by exercising loose sexual morals. Like http://anidb.net/ch7082 [Nanami], Kozue also seems to have an extreme brother complex. She is very protective of Miki and is the reason that he does not have a girlfriend (despite the affection of many of his schoolmates).</description>
<picture>25765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7322" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Wakiya Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="488" picture="138714.jpg">Takano Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7323" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Sonoda Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keiko is one of http://anidb.net/ch7082 [Nanami]`s sidekicks, who follow her only because she has a crush on http://anidb.net/ch7004 [Touga]. Her jealousy, though as simple as Nanami`s is strong enough for Mikage to take advantage of her mind.
Keiko is Nanami`s best friend. Like many other girls at the school, she has a secret obsession with Touga. Keiko is in love with him and wishes only to be with him. She is also very insecure and has low self-esteem. However, she knows that Nanami`s clout and Touga`s rank makes it impossible to even approach him.
She is tossed out of Nanami`s circle after she shares an umbrella with Touga, and becomes a Black Rose Duellist. Later on, she becomes one of Touga`s many girlfriends upon learning that he and Nanami are not actually related, so she lets Nanami know exactly what she thinks of her. Later, Nanami beats up Keiko, http://anidb.net/ch7322 [Aiko], and http://anidb.net/ch7324 [Yuuko], and they are seen following her once again. In the series finale, all three are seen together again without Nanami.</description>
<picture>25778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3955" picture="71111.jpg">Nakagawa Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7324" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="1">6.30</rating>
<name>Oose Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3954" picture="173079.jpg">Motoi Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7325" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Tsuwabuki Mitsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7082 [Nanami]`s most devoted lackey, a boy in fourth grade. He is obsessed with serving Nanami and wishes to be her adored "brother". He is extremely confused about love, sex, and adulthood in general. His fruitless attempts to experiment makes him a Black Rose Duellist.</description>
<picture>25779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7327" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7328" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2342" picture="22096.jpg">Ishizuka Katashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7329" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7352" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The catalyst for http://anidb.net/ch7002 [Juri]`s current broken state of mind. She simultaneously idolises Juri for her brilliance and despises her for it. Her extreme lack of self-worth is the reason for the rocky relationship between the two, and it reaches a breaking point when http://anidb.net/ch9206 [Ruka] re-enters Ootori academy.
Juri`s childhood friend. http://anidb.net/ch7352 [Shiori] left the school after stealing the man she believed to be Juri`s boyfriend in order to feel more powerful than her, leaving Juri devastated (contrary to Shiori`s initial beliefs, however, Juri is hurt because of her love for Shiori). Shiori is in many ways an innocent character, in denial of her true feelings of admiration for Juri. Due to her inferiority complex, her attitude towards Juri is often downright sadistic (as her schemes are often designed to hurt Juri for no reason other than to see her suffer) and at the same time masochistic (as Shiori hurts herself every time she hurts Juri). Upon discovering Juri`s love for her, Shiori becomes a Black Rose Duellist and pulls her duelling sword from Juri.</description>
<picture>25857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8696" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="5">5.59</rating>
<name>Dios</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The enigmatic "prince" from http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena]`s childhood. Dios` name, which means "Godlike" in Greek, as well as his presentation in the anime, suggest that he is to be considered Utena`s guardian angel. During most of the duels, it is shown that his spirit enters Utena`s body and aids her. This is an indication that Dios may have been a skilled swordsman before his imprisonment.
Despite his limited screen time, Dios is a central figure in the anime and is at the centre of the plot. Dios was created when http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy] imprisoned the Prince, splitting him into two parts (the other of which is http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio]). However, it is not known whether it was a physical separation or if Dios exists only as a spirit.
During the anime, Dios is seen repeatedly providing assistance to Utena; whether this is part of Akio`s plans or Dios` own will is uncertain.</description>
<picture>28888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8697" type="main character in" update="2012-01-08">
<rating votes="23">7.58</rating>
<name>Ootori Akio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy]`s older Indian brother, the acting chairman of the academy, and the closest character to a main antagonist the series has.
In his youth, Akio and http://anidb.net/ch8696 [Dios] were apparently one and the same, but he became corrupted and lost his purpose as a "prince". Given the origin of his name and his role in the story, Akio may be compared to a fallen angel.
In order to regain the power he lost when he lost his nobility, he creates the Duelling Game in order to create a Duellist with a sword noble and powerful enough to break the Rose Gate sealing his lost power. In the film, "Dios" is merely an illusion created by Anthy to hide her brother`s flaws so she can have a hero to believe in.</description>
<picture>3434.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8699" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Ootori Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio]`s fiancée, daughter of the school`s Trustee Chairman. She is unnerved by http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy], who deliberately distances herself from Kanae. When Kanae enters the Black Rose interview, she reveals that she finds Anthy to be creepy and intolerable. Her distrust for Anthy drives Kanae`s hatred during her Black Rose duel with http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena], starting the cycle of the Black Rose duels.</description>
<picture>27999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8700" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="3">3.49</rating>
<name>Mikage Souji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The pink-haired head of the popular http://anidb.net/ch9170 [Mikage Seminar] at http://anidb.net/ch9224 [Ootori Academy]. He wishes to kill http://anidb.net/ch9170 [Anthy] and install a gravely ill boy, http://anidb.net/ch8710 [Mamiya], as the Rose Bride is order to save him from terminal illness. Mikage uses manipulation and psychology to control students close to the Council members in order to create a Duellist who can beat http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Utena]. Mamiya is the ill brother of a woman named http://anidb.net/ch9018 [Tokiko], and Mikage believes that he can save Mamiya if he wins the duels. His sabre is reminiscent of the Sword of Dios.
The Mikage Seminar is held in Nemuro Memorial Hall, a building famous for a giant fire in which 100 boys died. Their coffins appear to be stored in the basement, and Mamiya harvests the roses to create his own Black Rose duellists.
When students are upset, they come to him for counselling and reveal their inner turmoil to him as they ride down to the basement in an elevator resembling a confessional. He gives each duellist one of the rose crest rings from the coffins, now black after the boys` deaths, while Mamiya stabs the duellist with the stem of the black rose. The duellist pulls a sword out of the body of the Student Council member he or she is most closely connected to (the only exception being Ootori Kanae) and confronts Utena. After being defeated, the Black Rose duellist has no memory of the experience.
Mikage fights Utena as the final Black Rose duellist. Upon his loss, Akio reveals that Mikage`s memories had been tampered with and used as a tool to push the duels to their next level. Mamiya had actually died years ago. Anthy had just used magic to disguise herself as Mamiya. Long ago, Mikage was called Nemuro, a professor at Ootori Academy working a project to "obtain eternity". Emotionless and uncaring, he learned to feel when he fell in love with Tokiko, and threw himself into his research in order to save her ailing brother and preserve their family forever. His dreams were dashed when Akio seduced Tokiko, causing him to burn down Nemuro Hall because he believed it to be the last step to opening the gate to "revolutionise the world". Mikage leaves the school and the timeline returns to its normal flow, all the events of the arc wiped from everyone`s minds.</description>
<picture>28000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8710" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<name>Chida Mamiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Indian boy who Mikage wants to replace http://anidb.net/ch6889 [Anthy] with. His pale purple hair and dark skin resemble that of Anthy, http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Akio], and http://anidb.net/ch8696 [Dios]. Mamiya is the younger brother of http://anidb.net/ch9018 [Chida Tokiko], a woman employed by the Ootori Academy board, whom Mikage had become infatuated with back when he was Professor Nemuro. Mamiya was born with a mysterious, life-threatening illness, to which Tokiko hoped that the mysterious project Nemuro and the one hundred boys were working on could cure. Mikage became more driven to complete the project, also hoping that it could cure Mamiya.
At first, it was believed that Mamiya was the one who set fire to Nemuro Memorial Hall so the gates to the Duelling Arena could open, and years later Mamiya and Mikage would start sending out the Black Rose Duellists to challenge http://anidb.net/ch6847 [Tenjou Utena]. During that time, Mikage was the only one whom Mamiya ever had contact with besides the Duellists, who bare no memory of the meeting once their black rose was destroyed, so his existence was not acknowledged by anyone else on campus besides Akio and Tokiko. Once the final black rose had been given to Mikage, it was revealed that Mamiya had actually died years ago, and that the Mikage Mamiya had been living with for all these years was an illusion Akio created, and that it was Mikage himself that set fire to the Hall, so he could give eternity to Mamiya. Once Mikage disappeared, it was revealed that the fake Mamiya might have possibly been Anthy.</description>
<picture>28032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8871" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<name>Hozumi Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of http://anidb.net/ch7325 [Mitsuru] who tries to act as his common sense. She seems slightly jealous of his attentions to http://anidb.net/ch7082 [Nanami] — and interestingly, vice versa.</description>
<picture>28246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8872" type="appears in" update="2009-06-09">
<name>Kazami Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A childhood friend of Wakaba`s. When they were little, she recruited him as her "Onion Prince" to protect her from the taunts of her classmates. As he`s grown older, he`s come to regard Wakaba with affection, but she has since turned her attentions to her new "Prince", Saionji. Tatsuya is the only character who goes through Mikage`s confessional and is rejected as a duellist because his heart is "too pure" to be converted.</description>
<picture>28249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9018" type="appears in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="2">3.87</rating>
<name>Chida Tokiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman employed by the Ootori Academy board, whom Mikage had become infatuated with back when he was Professor Nemuro.</description>
<picture>28496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9170" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Mikage Seminar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>28665.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9171" type="appears in" update="2017-10-16">
<name>Ootori Gakuen Seitokai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Ootori Gakuen Seitokai (Ohtori Academy`s Student Council) play a vital role in the series. Moved by his or her own personal interests, their great objective is to bring "World Revolution" and in order to obtain it, a true champion must rise from their battles to obtain possession of the Rose Bride. Instructed by letters sent from an entity called "End of the World", each of them possesses a rose signet ring similar to the one Utena received from her prince, allowing them to participate in the duels. Some view Utena only as a threat to their plans, while others develop some sympathy for her. During the duels, they place on their chests a single rose that matches the colour of their hair or clothing.
"If the egg`s shell does not break, the chick will die without being born. We are the chick; the egg is the world. If the world`s shell does not break, we will die without being born. Break the world`s shell! For the sake of revolutionising the world!" - Ootori Gakuen Seitokai oath (paraphrased from Hermann Hesse`s Demian).</description>
<picture>28667.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9172" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<name>Chida Mamiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28669.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9206" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Tsuchiya Ruka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A master swordsman, Ruka is the former captain of the fencing team and a former member of the Student Council. His cunning, manipulative behaviour belies a hidden desperation to live, and his influence on Juri becomes one of the major turning points for her character.
It is not clear whether or not Ruka was a Duellist before he returns. When he returns, he takes Shiori as his girlfriend, though it`s made clear that he was simply manipulating her. He duels Utena once with Shiori as his Rose Bride and loses. He then dumps Shiori and begins to court Juri. From him we learn that it was Juri who told him, "If you believe in miracles they will occur." Ruka says he is in love with Juri and kisses her during a fencing match; he states that he believes she was in love with him before he disappeared. As in the manga, it is due to his feelings for her that he wants her to claim the power of Dios and defeat Utena in order to save her from her burdens. Juri denies she was ever in love with him. Ruka subsequently appears as Juri`s Rose Bride in her final duel, after which he leaves the school. His "death" is reported by the Shadow Girls, though unlike the manga, the reality of his death is debatable.</description>
<picture>28720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9213" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ootori-fujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8699 [Ootori Kanae]`s mother and one of http://anidb.net/ch8697 [Ootori Akio]`s many conquests.</description>
<picture>28726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9215" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Kyoutou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5074" picture="156840.jpg">Kitagawa Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9217" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<name>Josei Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5076">Takemasa Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9224" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Ootori Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>28734.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9245" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kagee Shoujo A-ko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of three girls, seen only in silhouette, who spend about thirty seconds per episode energetically commentating on its events in symbolic allegory. Their antics provide both comic relief and insight into the show`s plot. While they function much like a Greek chorus, their primary influence is shadow puppetry.
In episode 34, it is suggested that they are members of the school`s drama club as well. In that episode, A-Ko and B-Ko act out a version of the story behind the series, suggesting that they may know about the nature of Akio and Anthy and their reason for the duels.</description>
<picture>28762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9246" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kagee Shoujo B-ko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of three girls, seen only in silhouette, who spend about thirty seconds per episode energetically commentating on its events in symbolic allegory. Their antics provide both comic relief and insight into the show`s plot. While they function much like a Greek chorus, their primary influence is shadow puppetry.
In episode 34, it is suggested that they are members of the school`s drama club as well. In that episode, A-Ko and B-Ko act out a version of the story behind the series, suggesting that they may know about the nature of Akio and Anthy and their reason for the duels.</description>
<picture>28763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9247" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kagee Shoujo C-ko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of three girls, seen only in silhouette, who spend about thirty seconds per episode energetically commentating on its events in symbolic allegory. Their antics provide both comic relief and insight into the show`s plot. While they function much like a Greek chorus, their primary influence is shadow puppetry.</description>
<picture>28764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9360" type="appears in" update="2009-06-14">
<name>Gekidan Kagee Kashira</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>28887.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3604" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞踏会の夜に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On the Night of the Ball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nuit du bal</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La notte del ballo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Происшествие на балу</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butokai no Yoru ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3605" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰がために薔薇は微笑む</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Whom the Rose Smiles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour qui sourit la Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Per chi sorride la rosa</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кому улыбнётся Невеста-Роза</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taga Tame ni Bara wa Hohoemu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3606" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薔薇の花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rose Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fiancée de la Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La sposa della rosa</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Невеста-Роза</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara no Hanayome</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3770" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光さす庭・プレリュード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sunlit Garden: Prelude</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jardin d`été : Prélude</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il giardino di luce: preludio</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Залитый солнцем сад: Прелюдия</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikarisasu Niwa: Prelude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4111" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠(えいえん)があるという城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Castle Said to Hold Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le château de l`éternité</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il castello che nasconde l`eternità</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Замок, где живёт вечность</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien ga Aru to Iu Shiro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4112" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カレーなるハイトリップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curried High Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand trip du riz au curry</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il magnifico scherzo del curry</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Путешествие за карри</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Curry-naru High Trip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4113" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見果てぬ樹璃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unfulfilled Jury</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La déception de Juri</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I sogni spezzati di Juri</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Чудес не бывает?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mihatenu Juri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4114" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七美様御用心!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Care, Miss Nanami!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attention, Lady Nanami !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Attenta, Nanami!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Будь осторожна, Нанами!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanami-sama, Goyoujin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4115" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七実の大切なもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanami`s Precious Thing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il preferito di Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Счастье Нанами</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanami no Taisetsu na Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4116" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光さす庭・フィナーレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sunlit Garden: Finale</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jardin d`été : Final</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il giardino di luce: finale</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Залитый солнцем сад: Финал</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikarisasu Niwa: Finale</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4360" update="2009-09-28">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">描かれる軌跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tracing a Path</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le repérage des lieux</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Costruzione di un miracolo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">В поисках пути</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Egakareru Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4361" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たぶん友情のために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Friendship, Perhaps</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Par amitié, peut-être...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Forse per amicizia</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Во имя дружбы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabun Yuujou no Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4362" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優雅に冷酷・その花を摘む者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gracefully Cruel: The One Who Picks That Flower</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Élégant et impitoyable, celui qui cueille la fleur</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Bello e senza scrupoli, chi coglie questo fiore</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Тот, кто может сорвать этот цветок</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuga ni Reikoku: Sono Hana o Tsumu Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4784" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その梢が指す風景</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landscape Framed by Kozue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le paysage imaginé par Kozue</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Как смотрит на жизнь Козуэ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Kozue ga Sasu Fuukei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4785" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒薔薇の少年たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boys of the Black Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ceux de la Rose Noire</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I ragazzi della rosa nera</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Юноши Чёрной розы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro Bara no Shounen-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5045" update="2010-02-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の棘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Thorns of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les épines de la Mort</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Смертельные шипы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Toge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5046" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せのカウベル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cowbell of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cloche de vache du bonheur</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Колокольчик счастья</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Cowbell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5870" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜を走る王子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince Who Runs Though The Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le prince qui court dans la nuit</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il principe che corre nella notte</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Принц, мчащийся сквозь ночь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru o Hashiru Ouji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5871" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今は亡き王国の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Song for a Kingdom Now Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chant du royaume déchu</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Песня пропавшего королевства</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima wa Naki Oukoku no Uta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5872" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">踊る彼女たちの恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Romance of the Dancing Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La romance de danseuses</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Любовь танцующих девушек</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odoru Kanojo-tachi no Koi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5873" update="2010-02-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みつるもどかしさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mitsuru`s Impatience</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La douleur de Mitsuru</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Нетерпение Мицуру</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsuru Modokashisa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5874" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の悲劇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Tragedy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tragédie</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Её трагедия</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Higeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5875" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裸足の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Barefoot Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille aux pieds nus</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Босоногая девушка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hadashi no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5876" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空より淡き瑠璃色の</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Azure Paler Than the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un azur plus bleu que le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Бледнее небесной лазури</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora yori Awaki Ruriiro no</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5877" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇に囁く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whispers in the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chuchotement dans les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sussurrando nel buio</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Шёпот в темноте</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami ni Sasayaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5878" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七実の卵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanami`s Egg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`œuf de Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`uovo di Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Яйцо Нанами</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanami no Tamago</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5879" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幹の巣箱(光さす庭・アレンジ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miki`s Nest Box</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nid de Kosue (Jardin d`été, arrangement)</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il nido di Miki (il giardino di luce: variazione)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Гнездо для Мики (Залитый солнцем сад: Аранжировка)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miki no Subako (Hikarisasu Niwa: Arrange)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5880" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりの永遠黙示録</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Eternal Apocalypse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apocalypse éternelle pour deux</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La nostra eterna apocalisse</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вечный Апокалипсис</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Eien Mokushiroku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5881" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七実様秘密日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Nanami Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal secret de Nanami</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Тайный дневник Нанами</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanami-sama Himitsu Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5882" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デュエリストの条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Terms of a Duelist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le talent d’un duelliste</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Кодекс Дуэлянта</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Duelist no Jouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5883" update="2005-12-23">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつか一緒に輝いて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Someday, Together, We`ll Shine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Soleil se lève aussi</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un giorno risplenderemo insieme</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Когда-нибудь мы будем сиять вместе</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuka Issho ni Kagayaite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5884" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">根室記念館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nemuro Memorial Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mémorial de Nemuro</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il padiglione di Nemuro</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мемориальный зал Немуро</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemuro Kinenkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5885" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">End of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les fins du monde</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il confine del mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Край света</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Hate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5886" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪い虫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vermin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Insectes nuisibles</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Insetti fastidiosi</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вредители</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warui Mushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5887" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界を革命する者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One Who Brings the World Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celle qui révolutionnera le monde</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Тот, кто принесёт в мир революцию</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai o Kakumei Suru Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5888" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若葉繁れる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wakaba Flourishing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La métamorphose de Wakaba</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Цветение Вакабы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaba Shigereru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5889" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして夜の扉が開く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Thus Opens the Doorway of Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et les portes de la nuit s’ouvrirent</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Si aprono le porte della notte</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">И открылись врата ночи</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Yoru no Tobira ga Hiraku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5890" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬のころ 芽ばえた愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Love That Blossomed in Wintertime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un amour en hiver</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un amore fiorito in inverno</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Любовь, цветущая зимой</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Iro Mebaeta Ai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5891" update="2005-05-26">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薔薇の刻印</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rose Crest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sceau de la Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il sigillo della rosa</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Печать розы</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara no Kokuin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="28155" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Characters song special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46145" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46146" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103937" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103938" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103939" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
