<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2881" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-05-07</startdate>
<enddate>2005-07-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shinshaku Sengoku Eiyuu Densetsu Sanada Juu Yuushi The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Legend of the Heroes of the Warring Nations - The Ten Sanada Brave Soldiers Sanada 10 TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新釈 戦国英雄伝説 眞田十勇士 The Animation</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1835" type="Prequel">Shinshaku Sengoku Eiyuu Densetsu Sanada Juu Yuushi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8571" approval="6" total="7">Brave 10</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="6302" type="Original Work">Kawanaka Shimao</name>
<name id="4506" type="Direction">Shimizu Keizou</name>
<name id="6029" type="Music">Nakajima Yuuki</name>
<name id="774" type="Animation Work">Group Tac</name>
<name id="4506" type="Character Design">Shimizu Keizou</name>
<name id="6523" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shishikura Toshi</name>
<name id="810" type="Animation Work">G&amp;G Entertainment</name>
</creators>
<description>In the Fifth Year of the Keicho era, the Tokugawa clan sought to solidify their control of Japan. Tokugawa Hidetada has come to the doorsteps of Ueda Castle with the intentions of having the Sanada clan open its doors to him. But the Sanada and their retainers have other plans...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="35">4.40</permanent>
<temporary count="39">6.50</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>246705.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3771</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>988</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1711</identifier>
<identifier>xlibzv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新釈_眞田十勇士</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>558</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322745</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7319</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="36666" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">関ヶ原の戦い (前篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Sekigahara (Front Chapter)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36667" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">関ヶ原の戦い (中篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Sekigahara (Middle Chapter)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36668" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">関ヶ原の戦い (後篇)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Sekigahara (Rear Chapter)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36669" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">流転生死</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reversing Life and Death</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36670" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36671" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇士の旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warrior`s Journey</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36672" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧隠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kirigakure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36673" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">関白秀次の女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Daughter of Kanpaku Hidetsugu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39576" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">家康暗殺計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Plot to Assassinate Ieyasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39577" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">厭離穢土 欣求浄土</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Onriedo Gongujodo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39578" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">九度山の客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guest from Kudoyama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39579" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Covert Operation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128230" update="2011-02-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128231" update="2011-02-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
