<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2889" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-04-22</startdate>
<enddate>1993-04-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sousei Kishi Gaiarth</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Genesis Surviver Gaiarth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sosei Kishi Gaiarth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gaiarth</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">創世機士ガイアース</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Genesis Survivor Gaiarth</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2891" type="Character">Scramble Wars: Tsuppashire! Genom Trophy Rally</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="486811">Another classic anime that makes use of that blur between fantasy and sci-fi, which became pretty much a trademark of japanese animation back in the 80`s-90`s. 
A chivalric saga with traditional elements such as,a journey, knights, swords, dragons, damsels in distress, all view through cyberpunk eyes.
A great watch.

A++++</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.aicanime.com/products/gaiarth/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="781" type="Work">Artmic</name>
<name id="150" type="Original Plan">Aramaki Shinji</name>
<name id="22836" type="Music">Ashizawa Kazunori</name>
<name id="4374" type="Character Design">Kitazume Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4374" type="Direction">Kitazume Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="6315" type="Direction">Ooba Hideaki</name>
<name id="6199" type="Direction">Ooseki Masayuki</name>
<name id="150" type="Direction">Aramaki Shinji</name>
<name id="993" type="Animation Work">Big Bang</name>
<name id="966" type="Animation Work">Studio Kyuuma</name>
</creators>
<description>Gaiarth - a world devastated by a cataclysmic war, where pockets of humanity struggle to survive amidst the wreckage of technologies made magical by ignorance.
Gaiarth - a world where artificially intelligent machines doggedly pursue their programmed imperatives: to protect, or destroy, humanity.
Gaiarth - a world in which an old and terrible evil has reawakened, threatening to once again bring forth Armageddon!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="221">4.95</permanent>
<temporary count="223">6.43</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>129518.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2068</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>428</identifier>
<identifier>fzyvcm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.aicanime.com/products/gaiarth/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Genesis_Survivor_Gaiarth</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>創世機士ガイアース</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88418</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2603</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29909" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Zaxon</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29910" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Sahari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29911" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Ital Del Labard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="37766" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1992-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37767" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1992-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37768" update="2006-01-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1993-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
