<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2907" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2004</startdate>
<enddate>2005</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Shen Diao Xia Lu II: Xiang Yang Feng Yun</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">Shen Diao Xia Lu II: Xie Dan Qi Jing</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">ch2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">loch2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Condor Hero II</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">神鵰俠侶 II 襄陽風雲</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Legend of the Condor Hero II</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6376" type="Sequel">Shen Diao Xia Lu III: Xiangyue Shiliu Nian</anime>
<anime id="148" type="Prequel">Shin Chou Kyou Ryo: Condor Hero</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://tvcity.tvb.com/special/condor_hero/main/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1100" type="Animation Production">Jade Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>Continuation of Legend of the condor hero, a chinese production running on TVB.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="307">5.99</permanent>
<temporary count="318">7.36</temporary>
<review count="2">6.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4166.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>960</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tvcity.tvb.com/special/condor_hero/main/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Legend_of_Condor_Hero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神鵰侠侶_コンドルヒーロー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神鵰俠侶_(動畫)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3771" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>recycled animation -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag overlaps recaps, http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks], and http://anidb.net/t3671 [footage reuse]. For that reason, it is set to be split. If you can, please apply the correct tag to the anime that have it, and remove this one from them; guidance on how to use each of those tags can be found in their description. If what the anime contains is a mere recap, please don`t apply any tag at all, and remove this tag from it instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6707" parentid="2282" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-11">
<name>wuxia</name>
<description>Wuxia, which literally means "martial hero", is a genre of Chinese fiction concerning the adventures of martial artists in ancient China or pre-modern China. A typical wuxia story features a young male protagonist who experiences a tragedy, such as the loss of his loved ones, and goes on to undertake several trials and tribulations to learn several forms of martial arts from various fighters. At the end of the story, he emerges as a powerful fighter whom few can equal.
The heroes in wuxia fiction typically do not serve a lord, wield military power or belong to the aristocratic class. They often originate from the lower social classes of ancient Chinese society. A code of chivalry usually requires wuxia heroes to right and redress wrongs, fight for righteousness, remove oppressors, and bring retribution for past misdeeds. Chinese xia traditions can be compared to martial codes from other cultures such as the Japanese bushidou tradition.
Source: English Wikipedia
Note: Pre-modern China is generally accepted as the period from the 1890s dying days of the Qing dynasty to the early 1930s before the Sino-Japanese Wars.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12207" type="main character in" update="2010-06-21">
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<name>Yang Guo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youka (Yang Guo or Yang Gor) is small boy without parents who lives with his surrogate uncle Guo Jing. He whishes two things - find truth about death of his father and learn kung fu.
Noone wanted to help him so he decided to leave them, and started to live in cave with his master of kung fu - young girl Xiao Long Nu (Dragon Lady).</description>
<picture>50122.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19075" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="2">5.02</rating>
<name>Xiao Long Nu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She lives in a huge underground imperial tomb as the heiress of Old Tomb School`s Kung-Fu. She is very beautiful, but never shows her feelings because Old Tomb School`s Kung-Fu fighters aren`t allowed to let their feelings show.</description>
<picture>50131.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="28353" update="2005-01-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">父仇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father`s Avenge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29043" update="2005-02-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">血染襄陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood-stained Shang Yang</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29889" update="2005-02-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">俠中之俠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hero Amongst Heroes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30181" update="2005-02-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">捨身一戰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sacrifice for One Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30447" update="2005-02-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">深入虎穴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep into the Tiger`s Lair</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31265" update="2005-03-08">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">超越恩仇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surpassing Kindness and Vengeance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="33715" update="2005-03-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">身命終結之際</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the End of Life</title>
</episode>
<episode id="34171" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">戰火之子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Child in the midst of battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35491" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">惡夢重現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare reappears</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35763" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">神雕谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sacred condor valley</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35918" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">黎明的決戰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fierce battle of the dawn</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36231" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">憂傷的小龍女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Depressed and Hurt Shooriyojou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36567" update="2005-05-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">命運多劫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robbing of Fortune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36721" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">身負重傷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reinventing to Make Up for Loss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37345" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">不說話的師父</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Master who doesn`t talk</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38357" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">神雕重劍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The heavy and important sword of the sacred condor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38571" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">遙遠的夢想</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Faraway Dream</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38891" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">女傑決鬥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fierce Battle of Female Fighters</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39301" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">終南山烏雲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Clouds of Mount Chongnan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39383" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">血色的再會</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood-colour Reunion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39891" update="2006-04-24">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">洞房花燭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wedding</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41138" update="2005-09-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">寒玉床的秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Chilling Jade Bed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41715" update="2005-09-24">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hope</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42149" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">危機逼近</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger pressing close</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42678" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="zh">劫難重重</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragedy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62099" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="zh">雪中送炭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unexpected Encounter in the Snow</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
