<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2921" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ueki no Housoku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Law of Ueki</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Законът на Уеки</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">TLoU</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ueki tv</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">UnH</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ueki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">うえきの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Law of Ueki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">La loi d`Ueki</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">La ley de Ueki</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Закон Уэки</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">A Lei do Ueki</title>
<title xml:lang="ca" type="official">La llei de Ueki</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="92" approval="23" total="26">Shaman King</anime>
<anime id="4596" approval="21" total="43">Shijou Saikyou no Deshi Ken`ichi</anime>
<anime id="638" approval="20" total="21">Konjiki no Gash Bell!!</anime>
<anime id="2855" approval="12" total="12">MAR Heaven</anime>
<anime id="571" approval="4" total="7">Rekka no Honoo</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="242315">Very nice.  One of the best shonen anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177218">Frankly speaking it was an interesting anime &amp; I did enjoyed watching it. But one most annoying fact is, I don`t really like Mori Ai, gosh she`s so damn annoying &amp; useless to the MAX!! Well that`s my opinion anyways~ Other than that is the repetitive explaination through out the combat on each fighting skill lol...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="738147">Love the concept and idea behind the anime. A good mix of action and comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="280899">A very good shounen anime.&lt;br /&gt;MUST SEE if you like shounen!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/ueki/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="734" type="Unknown Relation">Shogakukan Productions</name>
<name id="3580" type="Series Composition">Kawase Toshifumi</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
<name id="2744" type="Direction">Watanabe Hiroshi</name>
<name id="9892" type="Chief Animation Direction">Horikoshi Kumiko</name>
<name id="22893" type="Original Work">Fukuchi Tsubasa</name>
<name id="6734" type="Character Design">Tagashira Shinobu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr22893 [Fukuchi Tsubasa].
God is not a position for life, and the current God`s term in office is almost up. Switching things up, he decides to chose the next God through a series of battle games and tournaments. The tournament is not actually fought between the God Candidates, but between junior high school students chosen by the various God Candidates and granted a special power and talents called zai. The winning student receives a blank zai as a reward, to write in whatever ability or talent they want, while their God Candidate becomes the next God.
http://anidb.net/ch3910 [Ueki Kousuke] is one such junior high school student, chosen by http://anidb.net/ch3912 [Kobayashi] and bestowed with the peculiar power to change trash into trees. Neither Kobayashi and Ueki are particularly interested in the tournament, but in order to protect himself and his friends from other chosen students, Ueki is forced to participate. Driven by his image of justice, helped by the guidance and worry of the people who gather around him, Ueki is drawn deeper into the tournament, finding reasons to fight with the intent to win, instead of just to survive.
— written by Quaenorde</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2074">6.08</permanent>
<temporary count="2107">7.53</temporary>
<review count="6">6.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4320.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5063</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>479</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1683</identifier>
<identifier>hbyswr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/ueki/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/ueki/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Law_of_Ueki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>うえきの法則</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7312</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3833" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>there can be only one</name>
<description>The long-term plot of the program revolves around a group of characters whose numbers are being slowly whittled away by one means or another, usually by killing each other. In the case of some reality shows, this is a process of elimination intended to result in a single winner. In other shows, this is a dramatic device, designed to generate tension and conflict with which to drive the overall plot of an episode or Story Arc (if any); in these cases it is sometimes combined with Anyone Can Die to especially heighten the resulting excitement, even when the apparent main character may be protected by Contractual Immortality. Compare Gotta Kill Them All.
Named for one of the catchphrases that came out of the Highlander franchise.
Source: TVTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3910" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="8">8.36</rating>
<name>Ueki Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ueki Kousuke is the main character in the series. He is in Class 1-C at Hinokuni Junior High School. Ueki`s ability is given to him by Kobayashi (a.k.a. Mr. K), who is also Ueki`s homeroom teacher. He is also seen wearing pinkish-red shoes during his first fight with Robert Haydn.
Ueki is an unusually calm individual, and doesn`t care about what happens to him. He can be found snoozing in class, letting children use him as a target for shooting soccer balls (or in one case, a surfboard),and also calling the police without panicking when he faces a gang of rowdy teenagers. However, he cares for people around them, even going as far as saving Robert Haydn from falling debris in the Dogura Mansion. He also seems have a strong battle sense, as he often finds his opponent`s weak points, or unique strategies to defeat them
According to a short profile of the main characters of The Law of Ueki (published in the end of manga vol. 16 by the author), Ueki`s hobbies include cleaning up his town. In the first volume of the manga, Ueki is seen planting trees in the town park.
Ueki is a genuinely kind person who is always trying to help people. Ueki is actually a heavenly being sent to Earth by his father in order to take part in this tournament. Being a heavenly being allows him powers beyond his tree-making skills.
Taken from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>25732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3911" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="11">6.38</rating>
<name>Mori Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mori Ai is one of Ueki`s classmates at Hinokuni Junior High School. When in a casual mood, Ai is usually upbeat and friendly, although she is often shown with a very shallow side, initially believing that all power-users (with the exception of Ueki) are dangerous enemies that can`t be trusted. Still, Ai cares deeply for her friends, especially Ueki. She discovers Ueki`s power early on, coming to a rather unusual conclusion and at first believing him to be an alien. Upon learning of the competition Ueki is in, she decides to back him up, to keep him from losing all his talents and disappearing because of it.
She is strict with Ueki at times, especially when he looks like he is about to do something rash. Ai continuously tries to be his voice of reason, although her shallow antics and outspoken personality often annoys him. Later on in the series, she is given an ability by the King of the Celestial World Candidate, Wanko, during Ueki`s fight with Sano. However, her power`s condition is that her opponent must perform a goody-two-shoes pose (raising the right leg backwards while putting both of the fists close to the mouth region). Once this power is activated, her opponent falls totally in love with Ai`s glasses and will do anything to keep them from harm, even defeat themselves. Also, they will not attack because they may accidentally break the glasses, and will do anything to prevent Ai breaking them.
The food she cooks tends to look rather odd and off-putting (usually with squirming octopus tentacles), but it still tastes good.
Taken from wikipedia</description>
<picture>25742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3912" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="3">8.69</rating>
<name>Kobayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kobayashi, nicknamed as Mr. K (Kobasen in the Japanese versions), is a teacher at Hinokuni Junior High School. Mr. K is also a King of the Celestial World Candidate who gives Ueki his power. He is Ueki`s homeroom teacher and had been carefully studying him in order to judge his worth for the tournament.
Kobayashi is usually a laid-back, forgetful, and friendly man, although he can be quite serious, depending on the situation. He has a very strong sense of justice, actually inspiring Ueki long ago when he saved him from falling off a building, and acts as both his mentor and role model. He is sent to Hell for saving (and thus helping) Ueki in his first fight against Robert Haydn. He then become Mori`s god candidate.
It is mentioned in the show that Kobayashi`s least favourite food is fried crickets in soy.</description>
<picture>70713.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1816" picture="20691.jpg">Mori Katsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3913" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<name>Sano Seiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change towels into iron
* Ability Level 2: Make his steel towels into powerful magnets.
Sano can change towels into iron by holding his breath, however sharp-eyed fans can see that sometimes it appears to be voice-activated instead. But after he gives the commands, he is sometimes left with a second or two to stop breathing in.
Sano, a 9th grader at Inaho Junior High School, was known as the Genius of Robert`s Ten while he was part of it. But he had joined because the leader of Robert`s Ten (Karlpaccho) had placed a Death Pentagon on Sano`s King of the Celestial World Candidate Inumaru that would kill him by removing all his blood unless he listened to Robert.
Sano can be creative with his power, creating shields, springboards (spring) and even boomerangs which he calls "boomerang cutter".
He has a burn over his left eye which was caused during an accident with a hot spring. Still, he does love those hot springs and hopes to get the blank talent to obtain the talent of discovery in order to find a hot spring of his own.
His Level 2 makes his steel towels into powerful magnets. Seems to possess a ridiculous amount of his necessary towels, pulling them out of his robe in rapid succession. Sano is seen teaming up with Rinko in various episodes. It seems he has a crush on Rinko.</description>
<picture>25807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3914" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Inumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The King of the Celestial World Candidate who gave Sano his powers. The two officially pair up for the tournament when Sano risks his life to save a child from a burning building, and Inumaru does likewise despite Sano`s threats.
Inumaru`s credo is that he can not ignore people in danger regardless of the reason, which prompts Sano to join, and to think of Inumaru as his friend rather than his Candidate. In Dogura Mansion, after being told that Sano joined Robert`s Ten to save him from the Death Pentagon (a small black bug that Karlpacchio attaches to Wanko`s neck, that would suck all of Wanko`s blood out of him on command, thus killing him), he contrives to destroy himself, so that Sano can be freed from his obligation.
He gives Mori his power, thus breaking the most important rule of the tournament, in order to force himself to go to Hell so that the others would be saved from certain circumstances that threaten the rest of the Ueki Team. He is the one who gave Mori her power.
Was chosen as God at the end of the series.</description>
<picture>64157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3915" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="8">6.11</rating>
<name>Rinko Jerrard</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change beads into bombs
She creates special accessories in order to use her beads in more constructive ways such as:
* Rinko Rocket - Made of a special alloy and then filled with beads. She uses this to blast herself up into the air
* Beads Cannon - Special metal tubes that are filled with beads and then go over her fingers so that she can detonate one bead and send the rest of them rapidly at her opponents.
* Her recent accessory is a special glove with beads hidden inside when used with her power, producing a force impact that claims to be as great as a close-contact weapon.
She comes from a rich family and in the past many people had pretended to be her friend so that she would buy them things. Disillusioned with the seeming coldheartedness of the world, she succumbs to Robert`s hypnotic charisma and joins the Ten. Initially, Rinko has a crush on Robert since he treats her as a real friend, but she eventually sees Robert for what he really is and joins up with Ueki, indeed becoming his guardian and constant caretaker.
Rinko`s Celestial King Candidate is a man named Nikay, one of Margarette`s followers whom she hasn`t seen since the battle began.
She loves all animals, taking an immediate liking to Tenko (whom she calls "Tenko-chan"), but her weakness for cute things makes her vulnerable to Ban`s power.
Note that it is wise not to insult her no matter what, for she has a side to her that makes her incredibly unhealthy for the person who insults her.
She doesn`t seem to realise that she has this "evil" side and fortunately for her that she forgets whatever her "evil" side says or does. This "evil" side seems to be activated whenever someone insults her.
The only example of this is when Ban calls her an `insect` which causes her to become furious and unlock her "evil" side. This "evil" side has no love for animals,as shown when she remorselessly swats away Ban`s cute, living Pick with her special glove, then beats Ban by slapping him with the glove relentlessly. In another instance at the end of the manga series, she confesses her love to Robert, but Robert insults her (although he doesn`t really meant to) by calling her "small fry". Robert becomes her second victim and has to be hospitalized for a fortnight.
In the epilogue at the last episode of the anime, Ai says that Rinko and Robert only dated once but Rinko dumped Robert because she suddenly felt a strange feeling about Sano.
She is seen teaming up with Sano in various episodes.</description>
<picture>25803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3916" type="main character in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Souya Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn voices into portraits
His ability to turn voices into portraits can make voices come out of them. The condition is that he needs to bend his fingers or toes.
He is a power user that Ueki and Mori meet. He is prone to deception, using various novelty gags and tricks in a fight such as soy sauce bomber. He looks out for a group of kids at a place called the Sun House.
His first King of the Celestial World Candidate, Nero, was a kind heavenly being that did not want to become the King of the Celestial World; he simply wanted to help out humans which he did at the Sun House. Soya offered to become gifted so that Nero could stay longer on Earth. Unfortunately, he helped Soya during a fight and was sent to Hell.
Then, Soya received a new King of the Celestial World Candidate, Zack, whom he hates for turning out to be a jerk and wanting him to join forces with a nasty bunch of power users. He agrees to help Ueki when he hears that they can save Nero. Although sometimes cowardly and weak when Soya performs his sneak attacks in conjunction with his power he can be a formidable foe.
In one occasion, he put his portraits on Sano`s towels, then turned them back to voices in order to launch a sonic attack on Team Marylin. In addition, his ability to use his opponent voices as well work with his tricks making it easier to deceive his foes.
At the end of the series, Ai refers him as the useless member of Team Ueki. In anime, Ai refers to him as the secret savior because he gave ueki one last zai before Ueki disappeared when he was hit by Ueki`s Kurogane.</description>
<picture>64167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3917" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="2">7.58</rating>
<name>Tenko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A large tailess yellow fox-like creature with a duiker-like horns on his head, ten blue beady eyes (with the main pair three to six times larger than the other pairs), black bat-like wings, brown stripes on his limbs and with no visible ears that helps Ueki awaken his celestial powers.
He can also change his shape to fit onto Ueki`s wrist like an arm protector used by goaltenders in ice hockey to give him advice, and seems to be able to communicate with Ueki telepathically. He is a Heavenly Beast who is something of a mutation among his kind (he is born as an ancient version of Heavenly Beast, which is a ferocious-looking Godzilla-sized fox-like creature instead of an adorable cat-sized genetically-engineered house pet).
He is treated very poorly by Heavenly Beings and Ueki is the first to actually treat him with some kindness and respect. He is able to detect the power level of Heavenly Beings and because of his mutations has a bigger version of what is called the "awakening organ" that can awaken the hidden powers within Ueki.</description>
<picture>25795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3918" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Anon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanon in the English dub. He is from a race known as the Hellions, who come from the Protector clan. Anon can swallow and absorb people within himself, thus making their bodies his, as well as gaining whatever abilities they have such as Robert`s power to make the ideal thing and his sacred treasures.
With a surprisingly humble nature, he has a hard time understanding humans and tends to experiment on them with reckless curiosity. Although it appears that Margarette is his father it is actually a Hellion who swallowed Margarette using his appearance.
Later in the series, he swallows King of the Celestial World who is "God" and changes up the rules of round 4. He first told Ueki that his dream is to destroy everything, but in fact, his real dream is to have someone who can beat him.</description>
<picture>39272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3919" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-07">
<rating votes="2">3.66</rating>
<name>Robert Haydn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn ideas into reality
* Ability Level 2: Blow gravity-changing bubbles
Robert Haydn (Arnun Vanichyanukroh) is a frightening person with an equally frightening power. His power may seem weak, but it caused Ueki to fall several meters below in their first battle. Before such, Ueki wasted a lot of trees to Robert`s power, causing things to be either heavier or lighter.
Like Ueki, he is a Heavenly Being, but didn`t reveal it until after Ueki discovered he was one himself. Ueki decided to battle Robert, who decided to not use powers beyond level 6. He proved to be the strongest among anything Ueki had ever battled, probably because of his power to turn ideas into reality, which could do anything, from making his sacred treasures indestructible or super accurate no matter what circumstance, The condition to this was that he would lose one year of his life.
His Kurogane resembled a spiky purple ball. His Masshu was something that was like a painting on the ground, moving around fast with the same effect as Robert`s bubbles and the regular Masshu. His Pick was a drill, which caused many harm.
To get rid of the other power users he created Robert`s Ten. They act as his brawn, doing the fighting for him in order to save those precious years. He is a fairly nasty character, not caring who he harms and how badly they are harmed.
But unlike Ueki, however, Robert has been training in his power for quite a long time. Robert has an unfortunate past in which he was treated as a monster by the people of his town. After being betrayed by his friends, he starts to hate humanity and destroys the entire village where he lived (1/3 in the manga).
After his battle with Ueki in the Dogura Mansion, Robert was beginning to grow doubts due to Ueki`s strong sense of justice, therefore forcing Margarette to feed him to Anon.
At the end of the series, he becomes a nice person like his childhood self, having been touched by Ueki and his friends.</description>
<picture>32658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3920" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Margarette</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Robert`s father and the King of the Celestial World Candidate who gives him his power. Margarette sends his own son to Earth as a child so that he could choose him for the tournament. He is not above sneaky tactics to ensure his son`s victory.
Later, his body is possessed by a Hellion with the intention of taking over Heaven. In this new form, he puts Ueki in his awakening organ (It turns out that his clan had eaten a lot of ancient Heavenly Beasts), and advances Ueki to his 9 and 10 star treasures.</description>
<picture>70717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3921" type="appears in" update="2009-02-26">
<name>Kuroki Kageo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change his shadows into clay men
He can create more than one clay man - even altering their appearance - which can confuse the enemy and thus keep them from finding the real Black Shadow. His favorite technique though is to create a giant clay man. If the sun disappears, so does his power.
He was the captain of his school basketball team, but because of an unfair ruling that disqualified his team from entering a tournament, he became the unemotional person who joined ranks with Robert.
During his fight with Ueki, he was defeated by a fellow member of Robert`s Ten. Ueki luckily got through to him (with the help of Kuroki`s little brother) and even though he was knocked unconscious he becomes good again.</description>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3922" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Oni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change bamboo swords into scissors
Oni wears an all black outfit with horns and a forehead protector which is actually a form of chain mail. He doesn`t say much, but he is able to defeat most opponents quickly. He is shown defeating an unnamed opponent (Kagura in the anime) with the power to change leaves into blades, but because he defeated him so quickly, it is unknown if he used his sword or his scissors. Usually seen with Becky. Ueki defeats him with Ranma.</description>
<picture>64164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3923" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-07">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Myoujin Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Abilities: Change his whistle (the sound, not the object) into a laser, change fans/cards/disks (menko) into buzzsaws.
The buzzsaw can only be avoided by jumping. Dodging it will only result in it following the target. This is used in combination with the laser so that when they jump from the buzzsaw, they are easy targets for the laser.
He was given powers by two King of the Celestial World Candidates who were in cahoots with each other, but changed their minds after seeing Robert in action.
In the Japanese version, he has a speech impediment that often causes him to elongate his pronunciation of the consonant "s," but in the American dub he instead appends "like" to nearly each sentence he utters. Neither of these carries over into the English translation of the manga.
Myojin fits the same personality type as most of the other Ten members, seeing friendship as weakness and showing no mercy. This makes for a very hard character shift from his goofy simpleton looks. Myojin was the one who recruited Ueki to join Robert`s Ten. Ueki retires him with Masshu.</description>
<picture>85442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="170535.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3924" type="appears in" update="2010-12-22">
<name>Yunpao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change electricity into sugar
A rotund youth with "the power to change eletricity to sugar" when he opens his eyes open very wide. A replacement member of Robert`s Ten. Utilises his limiting condition, as when he revert his eyes to normal size, the sugar turns back into electricity which can make for a devastating attack.
Also, Yunpao uses strange poses to distract his enemies from his large eyes and appears to be quite acrobatic as well. Loves sweets. Ueki retires him with a Pick. Yunpao seems unsuited to being in Robert`s Ten, seemingly possessing no evil. He does, however, become very annoyed when he is interrupted while eating.</description>
<picture>61218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3925" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Kabara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change cloaks into wings
He is a replacement member of Robert`s Ten. He can also shoot out the feathers on his wings as he turns them into wing shurikens. He is an expert hunter (assassin in the English manga) and is able to shoot pachinko balls with as much power as a rifle bullet (In the manga, he throws kunais instead of pachinko balls).
He is very fond of showing off his marksmanship skills, even to the point where he will shoot any target in front of him. Due to an exploding cossack hat during his battle with Ai at the Dogura Mansion, he is bald the second time he appears (In manga, he shaved his head bald for unable to win the battle). Kabara fits with most of the Robert`s Ten because of his cold hunter nature.
He felt no qualms about letting Ai suffocate during the Cossack Dance Battle, and believes that friendship is weakness. Rinko retires him with a combination of her powers with her new made weapons. Due to the nature of his match with Rinko, he develops a fear of cats.</description>
<picture>64158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3926" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Marilyn Carrey</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn one second into ten seconds for herself
* Ability Level 2: Double her attack power
She uses this power to make her look like she`s using super speed. Her Level 2 is the ability to double her attack power, but it`s only limited to 10 minutes. When she activates it, a gauge appears on her neck and she will collapse after the gauge empties. Reason of her defeat is her level 2.
Marylin, along with the rest of her team, grew up in a war zone in an unnamed country, so they spent their lives in training. Once the war was over, her family joined the upper class. She claims to be proud of her upbringing and how she only feels truly alive when she is fighting, but this is a facade. She holds onto a childhood promise to her dead war buddies that forces her to keep fighting, despite her actual distaste for the act.</description>
<picture>62997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3927" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Memory</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn her plans into reality
She uses her power with Putting`s to make a combination attack. This, however, was taken out temporarily by Hideyoshi blocking her sketch pad with one of his portraits, and the loss of Pudding earlier so she has no materials. In her fight with Ai, Memory is forced to fall back on hand-to-hand combat. She is the first "victim" of Mori`s power. A very competent field leader who acts as a spotter from higher ground.
She is also the smartest and the strictest of the team.</description>
<picture>64162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3928" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Matthew</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Triple his pair of hands
His power is the ability to triple his pair of hands, making him have six arms. When used with his military weapons, he can hold either six guns or two guns and two bazookas. Matthew is something of a flirt when it comes to ladies and thought Sano`s dream was pointless if it didn`t include women. Like all the members of the Marilyn team, he just wants to see Marilyn smile. Wears an eyepatch. Defeated by Sano`s level 2.</description>
<picture>64161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3929" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-20">
<name>Baron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Able to move to wherever his knife is when he throws it
* 2nd Ability: After he moves, everything within 10 meters is stuck to the ground, including himself.
Baron is a knife user. He has the ability to move to wherever his knife is when he throws it. His level two is to immobilize himself and his opponent to the ground if he teleports within one meter of the person.
An honest and naive fellow and he always refers to himself in the third person in the Japanese version. This is toned down alittle but still existent in the Gainax dub. Baron is very loyal to Marilyn and can be quite gullible due to the fact that he is tricked by Ueki repeatedly. After a long fight in which Ueki discovers his own unique fighting style, Ueki temporarily takes him out with Masshu.</description>
<picture>61120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="95" picture="16702.jpg">Horanai Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3930" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Pudding</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Changing his mouth into a dimensional portal
He uses his power with Memori`s to transport materials above the enemy, while she uses her power to change them into traps. He also uses his portal to hold smaller weapons such as grenades. Temporarily taken out by running into one of Memory`s traps in the smoke, when she thought he was Soya, because Sano had blocked his mouth portal with a gag which also stopped him from speaking. Soya then put his portrait on Pudding`s back, and then spoke to make it appear it was him.</description>
<picture>64168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3931" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Barou Escarotte</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn past visions into reality
He used this power in conjunction with his Sacred Treasures to create endless attacks. Largely concerned with achieving his goals, throwing aside anything that gets in the way of said objective. Notably, he cannot use any Sacred Treasures other than Kurogane, Masshu, and Galiper with his power, as all the other Sacred Treasures are attached to the body,and using his power with them would recreate his past selves, and defeating one of his past selves would defeat him.
He has a very sad past because he accidentally used Kurogane on his adoptive mother when he mistakes her as a burglar breaking into their home. She fell into a coma for several years and wakes up terrified when he actually does use his Kurogane on several burglars.
At that point, he ran out of their house thinking that he is a monster and joined Robert along with the rest of the team. He is a talented artist.</description>
<picture>70721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3932" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Ban Dicoot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: To animate and make things come alive
He has the ability to animate and make things come alive, usually with adorable faces attached to them. Likes to use the phrase To the max a lot.
He sports a green ducktail hairdo. Like Rinko, he adores all things cute, but he is the first person to fall victim to Rinko`s "evil" side for calling her an insect and a small fry. He resembles Inuyama as a Rez-Boa-Dogz team leader in Air Gear as well as Boukuto no Ryu in Shaman King.</description>
<picture>64155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3933" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Diegostar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn all things invisible and colorless
He has the ability to turn all things invisible and colorless. He is prone to talks of manliness and wisdom.</description>
<picture>64156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3934" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Kilnorton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Unknown
He has an I.Q. of 179, but strangely, even though he has a high I.Q., he is constantly outsmarted by Ai. He also has the talent of calculating. He named his glasses Bianca, after falling in love with them during his fight with Ai.
Mori suspects he is a pervert, but he denies these claims and states that he has an I.Q of 179 as a counter.
Mori defeated Kilnorton using her I.Q. Kilnorton`s ability was not revealed during the series. At the end of the anime,he still falls in love with his glasses without Ai using her power on him, and mutters "Glasses...glasses...glasses...", creeping Ai out.</description>
<picture>64160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3935" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the current King of the Celestial World who sets up this whole tournament. As shown in the anime, God is a pervert who likes women and drinking. In a flashback, he was inspired to start the tournament, due to the actions of Ueki`s adoptive mother, Haruko Ueki, who at the time was a high school student just before she was deceased.
He started the tournament to give all beings, whether human or heavenly being, a chance to create their own futures. Although his front is a mindless idiot who likes to slack off, he actually very wise and powerful. According to a text box in the English manga, he lives in a skyscraper in the USA.
He`s considered the best King of the Celestial World in history, which is a fact that he is very proud of.
Although he was pierced by Anon`s Ranma, he survived and was later shown in hospital, and also managed to restore some of the years to Robert`s life that Anon had used up.</description>
<picture>64159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3936" type="appears in" update="2011-04-06">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Yodogawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yodogawa replaces Kobayashi as Ueki`s King of the Celestial World candidate. Yo-chan had a deal with another more promising King of the Celestial World Candidate, Margarette, to get Ueki to lose as soon as possible in order to take a cushy job as his assistant advisor.
He does his best to persuade Ueki to quit the tournament, but never succeeds. He rejoins to help Ueki later and apologizes for his previous behavior when Ueki is forming his team. He is at least a level 6 Heavenly Being, since in one episode, he used Raika to transport the rest of Ueki`s team to stop Tenko`s deadly final training. For the rest of the series, he is seen either helping Team Ueki or ingratiating himself with Kobayashi and Inumaru.</description>
<picture>64170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10626" picture="38527.jpg">Toriumi Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3937" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Pag</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A heavenly being who sent his son, Kosuke, to Earth as a baby with the same selfish intents as Margarette; to choose his son for the tournament so that he himself could benefit.
Unfortunately for him, he was not chosen as a King of the Celestial World Candidate, as Margarette was. He does, however, seem to express regret when he meets up with Ueki and company later in the anime, not revealing his true identity to Ueki due to his shame.
Pag also teaches Ueki a way to advance to his Level 2 power stating that it would be "the first and last time" he would aid Ueki. It is to be known in a later episode that he is Ueki`s real father.</description>
<picture>64166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3938" type="appears in" update="2009-02-26">
<name>Lafferty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The King of the Celestial World Candidate who gave Taira his powers. She tried to cheat during a fight by giving Taira more water and was sent to Hell for it.</description>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3939" type="appears in" update="2009-02-26">
<name>Ganju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The King of the Celestial World Candidate who gave Li Ho his powers. He is also Li Ho`s coach, and Li Ho wears a hat that looks like his but with different colors.
Not even Ganju himself has seen Li Ho use his powers before.</description>
<seiyuu id="23437" picture="63755.jpg">Imai Akinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3940" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Taira Maruo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change water that he gargles in his mouth into fire
Usually likes to just blast fire, but he can manipulate it by gargling, sometimes making it into an explosive fireball. He wants the talent of manipulation if he wins. He was Ueki`s first fight, and he lost after being hit by one tree.</description>
<picture>70727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3941" type="appears in" update="2015-07-23">
<rating votes="1">2.54</rating>
<name>Adachi Hayao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change cotton into stakes
Adachi wants to obtain the talent of running because he absolutely loves track but he is not a very good runner. He loses when he meets Ueki, who Adachi is envious of for his talent to run, but promises to keep running and maybe even beat him someday.
He is the parody of Kazuma Azuma in the anime Yakitate!! Japan.</description>
<picture>175731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="565" picture="171984.jpg">Takagi Motoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3942" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-21">
<name>Oniyama Monjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change soil into cannonballs
He believes in fair and square fights. He has a tendency to shorten words and phrases, and he has 299 talents.
He loves his home village and wants the village building talent if he wins in order to build his own village back up.
He teaches Ueki some basic fighting techniques to help win the fight against the Black Shadow, (Kurokage) the first person Ueki meets of Robert`s 10.</description>
<picture>64163.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3943" type="appears in" update="2011-01-21">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Ueki Gengoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ueki`s adoptive father. He is a writer and likes anything weird or unusual. Rather than being shocked or scared at peculiar things, he shouts in excitement, especially when he saw Tenko for the first time ever. He went nuts, as Ueki had predicted, over Tenko, squeezing and stretching his face. He also enjoys sports very much. Extremely energetic. He often says, Reality is Stranger than Fiction!</description>
<picture>64169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3944" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="2">6.75</rating>
<name>Ueki Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ueki`s stunningly beautiful adoptive sister, she is a student in a nursing school. She is extremely protective of Ueki, and when she first hears that he has taken part in the battle game, she reacts by complaining about all the bruises and scraped knees he will get, and that she could not bare the thought of him getting hurt.
In the series, she likes to play video games, owning a myriad of games along with the PlayStation 2, a Dreamcast and a GameCube consoles. She is very enthusiastic about playing video games with Ai.</description>
<picture>70728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29938" picture="223212.jpg">Kosaka Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3945" type="appears in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="2">5.29</rating>
<name>Ueki Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ueki`s adoptive mother. She died in a car accident the same day in which Ueki arrived on Earth. She is the first person God meets while on a trip on Earth twenty years before when he is a newly elected god, when she was a high school student.
Oddly enough, her maiden surname is Ueki and she mentions that she has a boyfriend who is a writer, which is also Gengoro`s occupation. This could mean that either she`s related to her husband, that they have the same surname by coincidence, that she lied and they were already married, or that Gengoro took on her surname after their marriage, which is not all that uncommon in Japan. . Her daughter is her spitting image with the exception that Haruko wears her hair in a ponytail.</description>
<picture>32021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3946" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Li Ho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change his fighting will into power (never used)
Li Ho considers Ueki his rival and wants to become a strong fighter in honor of his father, who fell victim to the plague. Originally, he fights Ueki using a move he calls the Secret of the Count of Monte Cristo (秘鍵巌窟王, hiken gankutsuou) but succumbs to its weakness when Ueki grabs hold of his shoulders. He covers this weakness in Round 4 by rotating his arms and shoulders, but his technique fails once again when Anon grips onto his head to stop his movement.
During the third round, Li Ho displays a distinct growth in power, utilizing his inner power to perform powerful attacks. Channeling his power into his feet, for instance, allows him rapid movement.
Li Ho has developed a defense called Tai Chi Chuan which is a circular strike used to repel any attack. Ueki battles him before facing Marylin, and learns new ways to use his powers and skills in battle.</description>
<picture>70725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3947" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<name>Baba Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Change coins into whirlwinds
B.J. loves hip-hop music. He has a tendency to lie a lot, particularly about who he is when fighting other power users.
When we first meet him he convinces another power user that he is Robert Haydn. His defeat at the real Robert Haydn`s hands spurs Ueki to challenge him the first time.
He is somewhat a pervert especially towards Ai. During Ueki`s first battle with him, he maximizes the speed of his whirlwinds to see her underwear and during their second meeting, he rubbed her body which resulted with a punch his face.</description>
<picture>70723.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3948" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Bolo T</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>* Ability: Turn his forehead into diamond whenever he puts his hands in his pockets
He tends to just headbutt his opponents. Has many talents which he uses quite skillfully in battle. He often incorporates the word "jyan" at the end of his sentences. This is changed to "man" in the English anime.</description>
<picture>70720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31675" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Karl P. Accho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karl, Robert`s second in command, has the power to copy another person`s power. The condition is that he has to spend 24 hours within 10 meters of them. He used this to acquire the powers of all of the other members of Robert`s Ten.
He has two powers from outside the Ten which are the power to change the opponent`s thoughts to a cell phone Text-message and the power to reverse one`s position with the opponent`s.
He uses all of these powers in combat and may actually have had more, but it is unknown as he was knocked out by Ueki`s Masshu. Karl is a very sneaky (yet ironically loud) type who isn`t above underhanded tactics to get what he or Robert wants.
In the manga, he is portrayed as somewhat girl-crazy, and even in the anime he says Robert`s Ten should have more girls in it.</description>
<picture>70714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31676" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Mario</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He likes to give his attacks English names that sound absolutely absurd, such as calling his billiard attack Super Dynamic Elegant Ball (this may refer to Mario, the video game character, due to the game`s use of the word super, as in Super Mario. They also have the same name). This is because the anime states that English is his best subject.</description>
<picture>70715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31677" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Nico</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He likes to attack from the ground where he can surprise people. One of the gifted that is trying to get Soya to join up with them.
He is very vain, especially when it comes to his hair, and also tends to use the word beautiful in his sentences. He looks more like a beautiful girl rather than a boy and has a tendency to wear girlish clothes. During the Battle Game, though, in the last few minutes of Ueki Team against Marilynn Team, Nico can be more mature than he was before.</description>
<picture>70716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31678" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Nero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hideyoshi`s god candidate.</description>
<picture>70718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31679" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Zack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Soya`s current King of the Celestial World Candidate who is actually a malicious individual who wants Soya to join his newly formed group to win the tournament.</description>
<picture>70719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3227" picture="24207.jpg">Ichikawa Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31680" type="appears in" update="2011-05-06">
<name>Hugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the power users that is trying to get soya to join up with them. He is quite gullible and constantly falls for Soya`s tricks, even though he claims he won`t be fooled. Soya defeats him by stuffing nattou soybeans down his shirt and squirting wasabi sauce up his nose.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>70722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31681" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Caption</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of Capucho Team. He has a level two power which is a red gas that freezes things and makes them easily shattered by his attack alone. He wants Hideyoshi to join his group so that he could use his own power to send his freezing voice from multiple directions. Tends to get impatient and repeat certain words and phrases. His name is also written as Kapucho and Caption.</description>
<picture>70724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31682" type="appears in" update="2011-05-01">
<name>Kamui Rosso</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamui has little respect for anyone, adhering to the motto "I don`t need any robots that won`t listen to me." After knocking Kageo, his fellow teammate out, Ueki knocks him out of the tournament with some cunning tree manipulation.</description>
<picture>70726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31689" type="appears in" update="2013-07-12">
<name>Suzuki Sakura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60859.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31690" type="appears in" update="2013-07-12">
<name>Kuroiwa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60860.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31691" type="appears in" update="2011-04-29">
<name>Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="209">Ootake Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="35036" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">植木耕助・正義の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ueki Kousuke, Law of Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ueki Kousuke, Seigi no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35037" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">才の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Zai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zai no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35038" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトル開始!! の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of "Start of Battle!!"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Battle Kaishi!! no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35334" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35530" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">体術の男・李崩の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Man of Martial Arts! The Law of Rihou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taijutsu no Otoko, Rihou no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35804" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強能力者ロベルト・ハイドンの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Ability-Holder, Law of Robert Haydn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Nouryokusha Robert Haydn no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35805" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Goodbye</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35922" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コバセンの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Kobasen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kobasen no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36174" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正々堂々!男鬼紋の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fair and Square! The Law of Onimon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seisei Doudou! Onimon no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36175" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼紋の特訓の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Onimon`s Training</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onimon no Tokkun no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37658" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">むくわれぬ正義の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Justice That Never Comes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukuwarenu Seigi no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37659" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ロベルト十団』の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Robert`s Ten</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Robert Juudan" no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37702" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天界人の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Heavenly Beings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkaijin no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38072" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天界獣の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Heavenly Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkaijuu no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38073" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒臓器の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Awakening Viscera</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei Zouki no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38358" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鈴子の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Rinko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinko no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38359" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新天界人[ネオ]の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Neo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neo no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38360" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二つの能力の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Two Powers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Chikara no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38751" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄! ドグラマンションの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tremble! The Law of Dogura Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu! Dogura Mansion no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コサックダンスの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Cossack Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cossack Dance no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39352" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネコとねずみの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Cat and Mouse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neko to Nezumi no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39353" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">佐野清一郎の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Sano Seiichiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sano Seiichiro no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39354" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬丸の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Inumaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inumaru no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40653" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">植木VS十団の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Ueki VS The 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ueki VS Juudan no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40654" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年ロベルトの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Young Robert Hayden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen Robert no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40655" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活! コバセンの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revival! The Law of Kobasen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu! Kobasen no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40656" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖! アノンの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror! The Law of Anon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu! Anon no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41685" update="2005-09-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41784" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒデヨシの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Hideyoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hideyoshi no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41785" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たいようの家の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Sun House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyou no Ie no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42220" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死なないでテンコの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Die! Tenko`s Law</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinanaide Tenko no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42221" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三次選考の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Third Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanji Senkou no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42222" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強タッグの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Ultimate Tag Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Tag no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42223" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の強さ! の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Real Strength!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Tsuyosa! no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44441" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 植木VS李崩の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! The Law of Ueki vs Rihou!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Ueki VS Rihou no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44442" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリリンチームの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Marilyn Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marilyn Team no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44898" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はかったなあぁぁああ! の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of YOU TRICKED ME!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakattanaaaaaa! no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44899" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲間の証明の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Proof of Companionship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakama no Shoumei no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44900" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神器の弱点の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Sacred Treasure`s Weak Spots</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinge no Jakuten no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44901" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">佐野・覚醒!! の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Sano`s Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sano, Kakusei!! no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45706" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉ざされた心の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Closed Heart!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tozasareta Kokoro no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45917" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素晴らしい『あい』の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Wonderful Mori Ai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subarashi "Ai" no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45918" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本物と偽者の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Real Thing and the Imposter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honmono to Nisemono no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46066" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バロウチームの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Ballow Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ballow Team no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46067" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶりっ娘ポーズの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Goodie-Two-Shoes Pose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Burikko Pose no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46068" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神と少女と未来の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of God, a Girl and the Future!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami to Shoujo to Mirai no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46069" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去からの攻撃の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Attacks from the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakokara no Koudaki no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46070" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">植木・レベル2! の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Ueki Level 2!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ueki, Level 2! no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46494" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神になったアノンの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Anon Who Became God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami ni Natta Anon no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46495" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第四次選考の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Round Four</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiyonji Senkou no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47103" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十ツ星の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of the Ten Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tootsu Hoshi no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47104" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">植木VSアノンの法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Ueki vs Anon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ueki VS Anon no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47738" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空白の才の法則</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Law of Null Zai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuhaku no Zai no Housoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125944" update="2011-02-23">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125945" update="2011-01-03">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125946" update="2011-01-03">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125947" update="2011-02-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125948" update="2011-02-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125949" update="2011-02-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125950" update="2011-01-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
