<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2926" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2006-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Angel Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">エンジェル・ハート</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сердце ангела</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">قلب ملاك</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Melek Kalpli</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">天使心</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AH</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Angel Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Angel Heart</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1565" type="Alternative Setting">City Hunter `91</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1002" approval="1" total="6">Gunslinger Girl.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="489149">this story is great  and strong  humanity feels ( 1`st class.)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="18949">An hauntingly alternative not to be missed!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ytv.co.jp/angelheart/</url>
<creators>
<name id="862" type="Original Work">Houjou Tsukasa</name>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="3656" type="Series Composition">Uetake Sumio</name>
<name id="1938" type="Direction">Hirano Toshiki</name>
<name id="1414" type="Music">Iwasaki Taku</name>
<name id="5447" type="Character Design">Saijou Takashi</name>
<name id="5447" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saijou Takashi</name>
<name id="7635" type="Chief Animation Direction">Aono Atsushi</name>
<name id="7635" type="Character Design">Aono Atsushi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7970 [Glass Heart] is a female member of the dreaded Suzaku Unit, an elite corps of Taiwanese assassins who have been raised since childhood to be heartless killing machines. At age 14 she is congratulated for her fiftieth successful hit, but she has become painfully disillusioned with her line of work and leaps from the roof of a building. But the Suzaku Unit is not ready to let such a valuable member go so easily, and are willing to take extraordinary measures to save her, including the theft of a transplant-compatible girl`s heart from the streets of Japan. Glass Heart finds herself somehow in contact with the spirit of her heart`s previous owner, and cannot resist the urge to search for this woman`s lover...
Source: MIKOMI</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1089">6.46</permanent>
<temporary count="1112">7.53</temporary>
<review count="3">8.55</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83730.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>282</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1808</identifier>
<identifier>vlhqsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ytv.co.jp/angelheart/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Angel_Heart_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エンジェル・ハート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>601</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323500</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7729</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="155" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-16">
<name>bodyguard</name>
<description>A bodyguard is a type of security guard or government law enforcement officer or soldier who protects a person or people, usually high-ranking public officials or officers, wealthy people, and celebrities, from danger: generally theft, assault, kidnapping, assassination, harassment, loss of confidential information, threats, or other criminal offences.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>213116.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="596" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-12">
<name>crime syndicate</name>
<description>An organization run by criminals for the purpose of illegal activity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2769" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>hyperspace mallet</name>
<description>It comes from nowhere, it strikes without mercy, and disappears again. It`s a mallet the size of a circus sledgehammer, and it`s evidence that anime characters watch too many Bugs Bunny cartoons or Three Stooges shorts. An angry character — usually but not restricted to short-tempered schoolgirls — can often whip out a massive hammer with which to slam the target (and cause) of her ire.
In Fan Fic circles, the notional storage place for mallets when not in use is known as hammerspace or malletspace.
A recent variation is to have the character pull out a http://anidb.net/t1662 [harisen], a huge folded fan made out of paper or metal, a.k.a. the Paper Fan of Doom, and smack them with that. This is usually less painful-looking than the mallet, unless she uses it to deliver a Megaton Punch.
Ironically, this is now a Dead Horse Trope in the West, where it originated; modern Western examples are typically from shows invoking anime, which has added its own touches to the mix, or from homages to Warner Brothers cartoons.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>10253.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4812" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>dark past</name>
<description>Way back when, something horrible happened - like murder, betrayal, rape or cataclysm. It may have happened to a character, or been caused by a character. It may be some powerful evil that was vanquished long ago.
Whatever it was, that past event will echo in the plotline of this story, providing motivation or peril for the protagonists.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5902" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-27">
<name>organ trafficking</name>
<description>Illegal trafficking of human organs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1363" type="main character in" update="2008-12-17">
<rating votes="740">9.14</rating>
<name>Saeba Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>15741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7965" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="178">6.81</rating>
<name>Makimura Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8" picture="171393.jpg">Ikura Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7968" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="88">8.12</rating>
<name>Ijuuin Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7969" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-20">
<rating votes="179">8.70</rating>
<name>Nogami Saeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7970" type="main character in" update="2017-06-17">
<rating votes="7">7.91</rating>
<name>Shan`in Ri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young Taiwanese girl who is the main protagonist of Angel Heart. In reality, she is the daughter of Li Jiang Qiang, the leader of the crime syndicate Zheng Dao Hui. However at the age of two, she and her mother were involved in a car accident when their car plunged off a cliff into a river. Her mother was killed in the accident but Xiang Ying was never found, despite the best efforts of her father and his organization to locate her. In a cruel twist of fate, Xiang Ying was found and taken in by the Zhuque Corps (a section of Zheng Dao Hui which specializes in assassinations) and trained to be an assassin. Because of the accident, she has no memory of her childhood, and as a result does not know her true parentage. This is also why her entry in the Zhuque was never known by her father until it was too late. While in training for the Zhuque Corps, she was referred to as Number 27 but after her training was complete, she was referred to as Glass Heart. After attempting to commit suicide, the heart of Kaori Makimura was transplanted into her, and with it, the overpowering desire to live and to be reunited with Ryo Saeba. As a result, she busts out of the lab she was kept in and travels to Japan where she finally meets Ryo. Ryo, in turn adopts Xiang Ying as their (Ryo and Kaori`s) daughter.
Xiang Ying was only 15 years old at the start of the series, despite looking like she was in her early twenties. By volume 20 of the manga she is already 19 years old, though appearance-wise she has not changed.
Xiang Ying has had very little contact with the outside world, except through her handlers. As a result, any potential situation which she perceives as a threat assessment would meet a harsh response, as evidenced when she nearly kills a man merely trying to pick her up. Not surprisingly, the people around her, Ryo, Saeko, Umibozu, Chin, and even Xin Hong realize they have an upward task in trying to teach her how to function in the outside world.
There are several coincidences between Xiang Ying and Kaori. One, is that the Japanese character for Kaori is pronounced as "Xiang" in Chinese, hence her name "Xiang Ying". Also, her major histocompatibility complex is very similar to Kaori`s as their human leukocyte antigen encodings are virtually identical. Because of this, Xiang Ying does not need to worry about her body rejecting Kaori`s heart as her immune system has been fooled into thinking her heart is the same.
With Kaori`s heart, she remembers all of Kaori`s memories, her residence, favorite coffee, quotes, and emotions. Along with these memories she inherits is also the ability to hammer Ryo with Hammerspace weapons if Ryo gets out of line (much like Kaori did), much to Ryo`s annoyance. She has also gained the penchant for wanton destruction that Kaori has always exhibited when the latter is infuriated, this is in contrast to her previous tendency to execute her previous missions with stealth and finesse.</description>
<picture>44112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4651" picture="27074.jpg">Kawasaki Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15530" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-04">
<name>Liu Xin Hong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Xin Hong is a childhood friend of Xiang Ying and was referred to as Number 36 during training for the Zhuque Corps. He has developed feelings of affection for Xiang Ying, and as a result, the trainers had Xiang Ying and Xin Hong face off in a fight to the death in the final exam. Xiang Ying managed to get the drop on Xin Hong and reluctantly killed her only friend, or so she thought. Somehow, he survived, and was transferred to the Qinglong Corps, another branch of Zheng Dao Hui. In fact, throughout this time, Xin Hong has kept his desire to reunite himself with Xiang Ying as his motivating factor to live. After the Qinglong were killed off by the Xuanwe, he was allowed by Li Jiang Qiang to live a normal life in order to watch over Xiang Ying.
Incidentally, Xin Hong was also the assassin who sniped Li Qian De through his hotel room window. However, Li Jiang Qiang did not hold him responsible for his brother`s death, knowing full well that he was trained to follow orders, and that most soldiers and assassins that work under him do not know who their leaders are.</description>
<picture>44113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15531" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Doc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A doctor who runs the Hanazono clinic, and looks after most of the underworld denizens of Shinjuku. As a result, he does not make much money out of this venture and occasionally doubles as a club harker in order to make ends meet. Despite this, he is a very capable doctor. He is the second person after Umibozu to realize that Kaori has returned in Xiang Ying. In fact, before hiring Tomoko as his nurse, he had previously employed Kaori when she was around Xiang Ying`s age.
It should be noted that this "Doc" is based on the original Doc in the City Hunter manga where he helps Ryo out on a consistent basis. "Doc" did not appear in the City Hunter anime series, so therefore viewers may be confused as to how Ryo is associated with him.</description>
<picture>132274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15532" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-10">
<rating votes="2">8.81</rating>
<name>Yan Fanyui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4193.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15533" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Mochiyama Hideo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A low-level yakuza affiliated with the Zheng Dao Hui. Mochiyama is one of the first to encounter Glass Heart and is later witness to Li Qian De`s death. He is a bit of an incompetent, however, as he cannot participate in a firefight, and has some homosexual tendencies as he displays open affection for Ryo.</description>
<picture>132276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15534" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Li JianQiang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15535" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miki is a young girl who lived in the slums of Shinjuku. Labeled as the "Lucky Little Ghost", those who meet her would fall for her smile, and are somehow befallen with good fortune later on. Previously, she lived in an underground section of Shinjuku Station alone after her mother had passed away several years before. After a hit-and-run accident, she would be adopted by Umibozu and would later on live with him at the Cat`s Eye Cafe.
Miki is unaware of who her father was, though it was revealed later to the other characters that he was the King of an unnamed country. He often visited Japan while on business and fell in love with Miki`s mother who worked in an old bar in a quiet area. Because the political situation in the kingdom was unstable, when she became pregnant, Miki`s mother left her job and disappeared. She raised her daughter all alone in an abandoned underground arcade so no one would be able to find them if they discovered their existence. Miki`s mother would later die in an accident and Saeko would be the first of our heroes to encounter the little girl. Much later after Miki starts living at the Cat`s Eye Cafe, Ryo and Xiang Ying would find out the King had been killed and replaced with a double. All these events are kept from Miki to protect her.
It should be noted that although this Miki shares the same name as Miki in City Hunter, they are not the same character. Like the Miki in Angel Heart, the Miki in City Hunter was also an orphan and raised by Umibozu, though in City Hunter, this Miki is much older. Miki`s hairstyle also appears to be similar to the original Miki in the third and fourth City Hunter series.</description>
<picture>132283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15536" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Max</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15537" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Hayakawa Shunsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15538" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Tanya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15539" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Bandou Sanemichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59829.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15540" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Shoumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15541" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Kawamoto Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15542" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Souchi Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3703" picture="151656.jpg">Ikeda Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15543" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Chen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15544" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15545" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Muto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15547" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Natsume Yoshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15548" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<name>Shimazu Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15549" type="appears in" update="2013-02-17">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Souchin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90000" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Li QianDe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90001" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-18">
<name>Chen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3360" picture="24707.jpg">Yada Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90002" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Joy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3969" picture="48838.jpg">Oomoto Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90003" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90004" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Shachou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90005" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17653" picture="47257.jpg">Yukino Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90006" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90007" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Yume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90008" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Irina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16988" picture="46178.jpg">Kodama Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90009" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Shimazu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90010" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Asakura Tomomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3274" picture="24702.jpg">Yamamoto Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41430" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41848" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガラスの心臓[グラス・ハート]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glass Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Glass no Shinzou [Glass Heart]</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42285" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">香が帰ってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaori Came Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaori ga Kaette Kita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42286" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">XYZの街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">XYZ Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">XYZ no Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42287" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さまようHEART</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Puzzled Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samayou HEART</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42396" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Coundown! Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42894" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永別(さよなら)... カオリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye... Kaori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara... Kaori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42895" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43342" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の愛すべき街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Loveable Street</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Aisubeki Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44661" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実(ホント)の仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honto no Nakama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44664" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">香瑩 ~ 失われた名前 ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Xiang Ying: Her Lost Name</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shan In ~ Ushinawareta Namae ~</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44665" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンジェルスマイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Smile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45293" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父娘(おやこ)の時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Parent and Child`s Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyako no Jikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45337" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">船上の出会いと別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting Onboard and Separation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou no Deai to Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45338" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">李大人からの贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Present from Master Li</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Li-daijin kara no Okurimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45339" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活C.H(シティーハンター)!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revival City Hunter!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu C.H [City Hunter]!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45340" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パパを捜して!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find Papa!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Papa o Sagashite!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45341" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">C.H(シティー・ハンター)としての資格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Qualifications as C.H. (City Hunter)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">C.H (City Hunter) Toshite no Shikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46686" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の中の出会い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting within a Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Naka no Deai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46952" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">親子の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Familial Ties</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyako no Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47290" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陳老人の店</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Old Man Chen`s Place</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chen Roujin no Mise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47291" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命のプレリュード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fated Prelude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Prelude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47449" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しき守護者(ガーディアン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorrowful Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Guardian</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48987" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出発のメロディー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melody of Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuppatsu no Melody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48988" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鼓動と共に...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Beat...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koudou to Tomo ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48989" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不公平な幸せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unfair Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukouhei na Shiawase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48990" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死にたがる依頼者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Client who Wishes to Die</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinitagaru Iraisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48991" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一度あの頃に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Once More at That Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Ichido Ano Koro ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50571" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私, 恋してる!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m in Love?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi, Koishiteru!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50572" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50573" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私の妹...香</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Sister... Kaori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Imouto...Kaori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50618" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この街は私のすべて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Town is My Everything</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Machi wa Watashi no Subete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50619" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の夜に見た奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Night`s Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Yoru ni Mita Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50620" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">組織から来た女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman from the Organization</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshiki kara Kita Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50621" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神から授かりし子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Child, a Gift from God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami kara Sazukarishi Ko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50622" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision of the Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51051" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来へ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Future...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai e...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52266" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せを運ぶ女の子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Who Carries Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase o Hakobu Onnanoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52267" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汚れのない心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unsoiled Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yogore no Nai Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52477" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレの目になってくれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Be My Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Me ni Natte Kure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52478" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">依頼者は大女優</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Client is a Famous Actress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iraisha wa Dai Joyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52479" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミキの隠された秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret You Keep</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Kakusareta Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52480" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自分の居場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Whereabouts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jibun no Ibasho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52481" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人だけのサイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Secret Signal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari Dake no Sign</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52482" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私が生きる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Daily Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ga Ikiru Nichijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52483" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺たちの子供のために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Sake of Our Children</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oretachi no Kodomo no Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52484" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間核弾頭, 楊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Human Nuclear Warhead, Yang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen Yakudantou, Yang</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52485" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マザー・ハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mother Heart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61034" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アカルイミライ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bright Future?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akarui Mirai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62053" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">引き寄せられる運命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drawing in Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikiyoserareru Unmei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62054" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Get My Life</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get My Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Get My Life</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62055" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストプレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Present</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Present</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91766" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91767" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91768" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91769" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91770" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117730" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117731" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117732" update="2010-04-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
