<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2989" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>61</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>1998-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hare Tokidoki Buta</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はれときどきぶた</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tokyo Pig</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8670" type="Other">Hare Tokidoki Buta (1988)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="3734">In which other series can you see Darth Vader, Kimba the lion, a Snowman pissing on the main character, Evangelion Fight, All Pink Sentai Team, and probably lot and lot of other references I didnt recognize, with a great deal of classical Japanese stories revisited pig style. The subs are a bit crappy, but the characters are just great and it`s a lot of fun.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="4538" type="Character Design">Nishino Rie</name>
<name id="4243" type="Series Composition">Urasawa Yoshio</name>
<name id="3963" type="Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="2341" type="Music">Masuda Toshio</name>
<name id="24619" type="Original Work">Yadama Shirou</name>
<name id="774" type="Animation Work">Group Tac</name>
</creators>
<description>Tokyo Pig is the wacky and crazy story of a young boy named Spencer and his magical pet pig named Sunny. This is the wierd adventures of these two wierdos.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="37">3.40</permanent>
<temporary count="38">4.84</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>78516.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2053</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2246</identifier>
<identifier>hchydx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tokyo_Pig</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>はれときどきぶた_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88920</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1056</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="30035" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おやじと野菜とマシンガン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30036" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪だるまのとけない夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pouty Pig: Scourge of the Galaxy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30037" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パパは地獄のコックさん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bitter Fruit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30038" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしは給食が好きです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 48</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30039" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿題シュクシュクかぶと虫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Aliens, Pig Trouble</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30040" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムダな筋肉質</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30041" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">A[アメリカ]-ザリガニの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 55</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30042" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あぁ希望!吸える鼻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30043" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪女・恋の炎でアチチのチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30044" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐竜のおなかの中のええ話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 53</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30045" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天然100%入ってんねん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30046" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真夏の夜の花火だポン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 52</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30047" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">武蔵小金井くんはまずい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion of the Pig Clones</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30048" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルーズソックスとピアス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kite-Flying for Dummies</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30049" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏だ! プールだ!校長だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Incredible Shrinking School</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30050" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おめでたい戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Milk of Amnesia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30051" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">矢玉アナは雷がお好き!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spencer Goes Buggy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30052" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あぁ絶望! 吸えない鼻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30053" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あッ! ぶたママだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 58</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30054" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんはジャングルの王や</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 49</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30055" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はれときどきはらいた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aliens</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30056" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">回転地獄・昔々その武蔵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 50</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30057" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">中華なマダムがヤンヤヤン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Luck of the Draw</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30058" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おれたちは友だちだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bummer Vacation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30059" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">弱虫なよろいかぶと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30060" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べない鯉の物語・純情篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30061" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オーマイ学校どこ行った?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30062" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガイコツのカルシウム不足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 54</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30063" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬のおじさんと春の妖精</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30064" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">外伝・はれときどき大江戸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30065" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">てんやわんやの里帰り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Veggie Power</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30066" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! はれぶたvsクロブタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Auld Lang Swine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30067" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超ゲテモノより愛をこめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oinks from Outer Space</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30068" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔界は今日も雨だった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 47</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30069" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブーブーぶたパニック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When Pigs Fly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bu-Bu-Buta Panic!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30070" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">木枯らしこがらし恋かしら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pooped Out Pig</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30071" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それいけ! 大宇宙ナイター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Trip to the Slopes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30072" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴースト・オブ・トンカツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bones</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30073" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恩返ししてチョー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30074" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブーブーライダーが来た!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trouble in Lightning Land</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30075" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ママのごきげんプリンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lovesick Castaway</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30076" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">玉ちゃんタマゲタかぐや姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lookout! It`s A Cookout</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30077" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">安則君は角頭! って誰?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 56</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30078" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れるガイコツの大統領</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30079" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピザ少女の初恋デリバリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30080" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">平賀きみよでございましょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon Girl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30081" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファイト一発! 涙の運動会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pigs on Ice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30082" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふりむけばブタぶたブタ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samurai Lunch Lady</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30083" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">2・14バレンタイン決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30084" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はれときどき...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 61</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30085" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">できれば結婚したかった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dad is the Worst Cook Ever</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30086" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出太りのダイエット あぁ絶叫! ミュージカル話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 57</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30087" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">結婚してケローッ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 46</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30088" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はれときどきお別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 59</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30089" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">台風だ! ヒッコスで引越す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">20,000 Leagues Beneath a C+</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30090" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙姫さまの学力アップ塾?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pigtoven vs. Principal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30091" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はれときどき旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 60</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30092" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖! ゆでダコの呪い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tickled Pigs Feet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30093" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜だ! 宝だ!UFOだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30094" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えろサマーでザマー見ろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 51</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30095" update="2007-06-24">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">玉ちゃんタマゲタかぐや姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil Lady Next Door</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106444" update="2009-08-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128320" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128321" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128322" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128323" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128324" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128325" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
