<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="2990" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>49</episodecount>
<startdate>1982-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>1983-05-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Patalliro!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ぼくパタリロ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I, Pataliro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Boku, Patariro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Boku Pataliro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Patarillo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">パタリロ!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2278" type="Sequel">Patalliro! Stardust Keikaku</anime>
<anime id="3176" type="Alternative Setting">Patalliro Saiyuuki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/patariro/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="4542" type="Chief Direction">Nishizawa Nobutaka</name>
<name id="5242" type="Chief Designer">Tsuchida Isamu</name>
<name id="5553" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Kin`ichirou</name>
<name id="4808" type="Music">Aoki Nozomi</name>
<name id="10048" type="Original Work">Maya Mineo</name>
</creators>
<description>Patarillo! is set in a society much like ours in most ways, with one decided twist. The manga on which it is based is one of the much-read works produced for adolescent Japanese girls that features a healthy proportion of gay men and beautiful teenagers aka bishounen (beautiful boys). Most of the action takes place in Marinera, the land of eternal spring, located somewhere in the South Seas. The country is a major producer of diamonds; they provide much of the basis of conflict in the anime series. They come from one of the most prolific mines in the world, owned by the king of Marinera, the vertically challenged but horizontally endowed boy-king Patarillo himself. The International Diamond Syndicate - a huge semi- criminal organization/ secret society dedicated to taking over the world`s entire diamond supply- wants that mine and will stop at nothing to get it. In the early episodes they send off a number of bishounen assassins to do in Patarillo, which necessitates his having a bodyguard, the English MI6 agent, Major Jack (`Bishounen-Killer`) Bancoran. Bancoran`s nickname doesn`t mean he shoots bishounen in cold blood. The soubriquet comes from the fact that no male under the age of 17 can resist his sexual fascination. This, to Bancoran`s eternal disgust, includes Patarillo himself. The action switches often from Marinera to MI6 headquarters in London (London seems to be an easy two hour`s flight from the South Seas) or Bancoran`s palatial condo in the suburbs of same. (MI6, be it noted, looks a lot like Fritz Lang`s Metropolis, while Jack`s `apartment` bears a passing resemblance to Randolph Hearst`s spread.) The action also goes into the past and future and out into space. Patarillo evidently gets around.
Source: aestheticism.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="60">6.12</permanent>
<temporary count="62">6.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4683.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1228</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2835</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2005</identifier>
<identifier>ytvuea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/patariro/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Patalliro!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>パタリロ!#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89354</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1096</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="29979" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少年キラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bishounen Killer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29980" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪がやんだら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the snow stopped</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29981" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おちょくり24時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">24 hour escape</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29982" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墓に咲くバラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A rose blooms on his grave</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29983" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧のロンドン・エアポート (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Foggy London Airport 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no London Airport (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29984" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パタリロより 愛をこめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Patarillo with love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29985" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パタリロ異変</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patarillo`s strangeness</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29986" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パタリロ大集合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patarillo`s great gathering</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29987" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニャンコはニャンコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nyanko is nyanko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29988" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイ・ラブ・マライヒ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I love Maraich</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29989" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧の夜に 花が散る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A flower falls on a misty night</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29990" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プラズマの恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plasma`s love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29991" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パタリロ 危うし!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patarillo beware!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29992" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プラズマ・パパ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Papa Plasma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29993" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンコラン死す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bancoran is dead!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29994" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マライヒの季節</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maraich`s season</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29995" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧のロンドン・エアポート (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Foggy London Airport 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no London Airport (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29996" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきた暗殺者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The assassin`s return</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29997" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の天使 マライヒ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maraich the angel of death</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29998" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忠誠の木ものがたり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The legend of the loyalty tree</title>
</episode>
<episode id="29999" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたし待つわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll be waiting</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30000" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プララのお兄さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pulala`s brother</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30001" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ああ, 花の新学期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ahh... new schoolterm amid the flowers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30002" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">やっぱりプララ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Still Pulala</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30003" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30004" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カンフー大あばれ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kung fu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30005" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝けタマネギ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twinkle twinkle, Tamanegi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30006" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月への旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey to the moon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30007" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならアフロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Afro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Afro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30008" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">殺しのライセンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Licence to kill</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30009" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アメリカ乗っ取り!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">American capture</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30010" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパーロボット・プラズマX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super-robot Plasma X</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30011" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">その男 バンコラン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That man Bancoran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30012" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">べらんめえ 桜吹雪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diabolical cherry-blossom storm</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30013" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立てジャック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly away Jack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30014" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイヤモンドの伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary diamond</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30015" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛しのプララ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beloved pulala</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30016" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンコランに死の愛を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True love for Bancoran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30017" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パタリロ8世と10世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patariro 8-sei to 10-sei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30018" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パタリロ7世と8世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patarillo 7th and 8th</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30019" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリンス マライヒ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prince Maraich</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30020" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲルマン城のとりこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gelman castle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30021" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリネラの吸血鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marineran Vampire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30022" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プララの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pulala`s first love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30023" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マライヒ マライヒ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maraich maraich</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30024" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリネラに 降る雪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snowfall in Marinera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30025" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみのエトランジュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Etrange`s grief</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30026" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベルサイユのヒマワリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunflower of Versailles</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30027" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1982-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれた赤い人魚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target: scarlet mermaid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123943" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1982-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123944" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1982-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
