<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="303" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1988-04-16</startdate>
<enddate>1988-04-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tonari no Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">My Neighbour Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Meu Vizinho Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="synonym">Näkymätön ystävä</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Người bạn hàng xóm Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Мій сусід Тоторо</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">TnT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Тоторо</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">となりのトトロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">My Neighbor Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Mein Nachbar Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mon voisin Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il mio vicino Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Mi Vecino Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Мой сосед Тоторо</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">이웃집 토토로</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Mój sąsiad Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Min granne Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">جاري توتورو</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="no" type="official">Min nabo Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Meu Amigo Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Můj soused Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Min nabo Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Naapurini Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Οι περιπέτειες του Τότορο</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">השכן שלי טוטורו</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Totoro - A varázserdő titka</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Mano kaimynas Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โทโทโร่ เพื่อนรัก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Komşum Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Vecinul Meu Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="sl" type="official">Moj sosed Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Моят Съсед Тоторо</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Naaber Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="hr" type="official">Moj Susjed Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">龍貓</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">龙猫</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Mi vecino Totoro</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="official">Миний хөрш Тоторо</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3365" type="Same Setting">Mei to Koneko Bus</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="112" approval="63" total="85">Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi</anime>
<anime id="5107" approval="55" total="65">Gake no Ue no Ponyo</anime>
<anime id="679" approval="31" total="44">Neko no Ongaeshi</anime>
<anime id="8270" approval="22" total="28">Momo e no Tegami</anime>
<anime id="3195" approval="8" total="20">Kamichu!</anime>
<anime id="5297" approval="8" total="13">Miyori no Mori</anime>
<anime id="3365" approval="8" total="9">Mei to Koneko Bus</anime>
<anime id="333" approval="2" total="8">Omoide Poroporo</anime>
<anime id="1218" approval="1" total="16">Howl no Ugoku Shiro</anime>
<anime id="8832" approval="1" total="9">Ookami Kodomo no Ame to Yuki</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="19">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="647482">Ghibli! What else do you need to know</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="27720">Great Anime for all ages with excellent animation.
The animation and mannerisms of the four year old Mei are especially exquisite.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="30442">Great, great, GREAT. Relly a must-watch even for a people who never have liked or seen anime. The ideal family movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516146">A simple story, but one that should resonate with anyone who has an open heart. Truly a classic of children`s anime. Personally, I think the Fox dub is better, not technically, but in capturing the feelings of our heroes. If you are forced to experience the Disney dub, please try to let your inner child prevail.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="721720">This is an awesome anime, and a great introduction for younger anime watchers (your children.) My three year old LOVES it, and my 5 year old and 11 year old still really enjoy it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="40" type="Direction">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="40" type="Original Work">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch2482 [Totoro] is a forest spirit that little http://anidb.net/ch2481 [Mei], and later her older sister http://anidb.net/ch2480 [Satsuki], encounter in a giant camphor tree near their new home in the countryside. Although their father http://anidb.net/ch2479 [Kusakabe Tatsuo], a university professor, is with them when they move, their mother http://anidb.net/ch2478 [Yasuko] is in the hospital, recovering from some unnamed illness. When Mei hears that her mother`s condition may be getting worse, she resolves to visit her all by herself. When everyone realizes she is missing, only Totoro knows how to find her!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7667">8.37</permanent>
<temporary count="7721">8.28</temporary>
<review count="8">8.74</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221542.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>523</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>278</identifier>
<identifier>ahdhkc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nausicaa.net/miyazaki/totoro</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>My_Neighbor_Totoro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>となりのトトロ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2614</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>150435</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/514</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>이웃집_토토로</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>龙猫</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2550</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6350" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Oofuji Noburou Award</name>
<description>The Oofuji Noburou Award is an animation award given to a group or individual at the Mainichi Film Awards to recognise animation excellence. It is named after Japanese animator http://anidb.net/cr5602 [Oofuji Noburou].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2478" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-07">
<rating votes="12">6.85</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Yasuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2479" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="13">8.12</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Tatsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1144.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="549" picture="17783.jpg">Itoi Shigesato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2480" type="main character in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="48">8.71</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2481" type="main character in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="49">8.23</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2482" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="178">8.80</rating>
<name>Totoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="547" picture="17780.jpg">Takagi Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7470" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="59">8.54</rating>
<name>Nekobus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nekobus ("Cat Bus") is the bus used by the main character of Tonari no Totoro (My Neighbour Totoro).</description>
<picture>26106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10034" type="appears in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="35">7.16</rating>
<name>Susuwatari</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Susuwatari (lit. meaning "travelling soot") are the "dust bunnies" or "soot sprites" that appear in two Studio Ghibli anime movies, My Neighbour Totoro (1988) and Spirited Away (2001). They are shy, slightly frightful creatures that live in abandoned buildings such as old houses.</description>
<picture>30239.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17645" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="12">7.97</rating>
<name>Kanta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanta is a boy who lives in the same neighborhood as Mei and Satsuki, and is Satsuki`s classmate. He seems to have a liking to Satsuki in spite of his initially gruff demeanor towards her.</description>
<picture>47980.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17646" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-15">
<rating votes="13">7.85</rating>
<name>Kanta no Baa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanta`s grandmother, whose real name is never mentioned, was caretaker of the house the Kusakabe family lives in. She later becomes good friends to the Kusakabes, and has special love for both Mei and Satsuki.</description>
<picture>47981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18022" picture="47982.jpg">Kitabayashi Tanie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76104" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-28">
<rating votes="3">3.26</rating>
<name>Michiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9800" picture="36489.jpg">Koujiro Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3758" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>1988-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10674" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1988-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15232" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1988-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92679" update="2008-08-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92680" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92681" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92682" update="2008-08-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Microphone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141513" update="2012-08-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2012-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboards</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
