<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3050" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1971-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>1972-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fushigi na Melmo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ふしぎなメルモ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Marvelous Melmo</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">I bon bon magici di Lilly</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7876" type="Character">Ravex in Tezuka World</anime>
<anime id="1553" type="Character">Hi no Tori</anime>
<anime id="8488" type="Other">Tezuka Osamu ga Kieta?! 20 Seiki Saigo no Kaijiken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://en.tezuka.co.jp/anime/sakuhin/ts/ts012.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1195" type="Original Plan">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="1195" type="Series Composition">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="723" type="Work">Tezuka Productions</name>
<name id="5673" type="Chief Direction">Nagaki Bonjin</name>
<name id="4382" type="Music">Uno Seiichirou</name>
</creators>
<description>Lilly looses her mother in a car accident. She is so young and she must look after a younger brother too. Her mother asks god to let her give a last help to her beloved childeren. God gives his permission, so Lilly receives a bottle full of pills with magical powers. There are blue ones and red ones. The red ones make her older and the blue, younger. A combination of them can also transform her in any animal she wants. Her brother swallow a bunch of them by mistake and becomes a frog.
Note: On 06.05.1998, WOWOW broadcast what is known as the Renewal version of the TV series. It featured new voice actors, new music and some new footage. The DVD-box released in 2002 is the Renewal version.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="42">5.48</permanent>
<temporary count="42">5.89</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4322.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1517</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5476</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648</identifier>
<identifier>ulxrpf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://en.tezuka.co.jp/anime/sakuhin/ts/ts012.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/39.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Marvelous_Melmo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ふしぎなメルモ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89578</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>108</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="54811" type="main character in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Watari Melmo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="15692" picture="228933.jpg">Mutou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54812" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Watari Totoo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1677" picture="223670.jpg">Matsumoto Sachi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3286" picture="24711.jpg">Matsushima Minori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="10191" picture="186250.jpg">Hasebe Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54813" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Watari Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30623">Ishii Naoko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="6374" picture="30939.jpg">Kitahama Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54814" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Watari Tatchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25075">Sawada Kazuko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="36631" picture="135048.jpg">Yoshimi Yuuko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="30623">Ishii Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54815" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Waragarasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3284" picture="24296.jpg">Kitamura Kouichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54816" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Tezuka-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3252" picture="24231.jpg">Tomiyama Kei</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="278" picture="44088.jpg">Ootake Hiroshi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="36632" picture="135047.jpg">Itou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54817" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Watari Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30623">Ishii Naoko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="6374" picture="30939.jpg">Kitahama Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54818" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<name>Hi no Tori</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134958.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54819" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-07">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Melmo no Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4204" picture="86092.jpg">Tsunoda Narumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1801" picture="146194.jpg">Asou Miyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54820" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Kuromatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10191" picture="186250.jpg">Hasebe Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54821" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Shiramatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134962.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54822" type="main character in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Melmo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="15692" picture="228933.jpg">Mutou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54823" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Melmo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134964.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54824" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Wakamono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30303" picture="24131.jpg">Takeo Tomoharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54825" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Melmo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134967.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54826" type="appears in" update="2013-04-07">
<name>Burako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10059.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54827" type="appears in" update="2013-04-08">
<name>Zenzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="31032" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミラクルキャンデーをどうぞ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle Candies!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miracle Candy o Douzo!!</title>
<summary>Melmo and two of her younger brothers love their mother very much, but tragedy strikes and they suddenly lose her in a traffic accident. The mother is told in heaven that only one of her wishes may be fulfilled. So, she asks that her children be allowed to grow up soon since it is too difficult for them to go on living as kids. Then, God gives her candies of two different colors. A blue candy adds ten years to a person`s age, while a red candy makes you lose the same 10 years. Appearing in front of Melmo as a ghost, her mother gives her the candies. Encouraging Melmo tenderly but firmly that she will be fine with the candies, Melmo`s mother asks Melmo to take good care of her little brothers, and leaves her.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31033" update="2017-03-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラ子 どこへゆく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where Is Burako Going?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Burakko Doko e Yuku</title>
<summary>A breeder at the zoo tells Melmo that her favorite elephant, named Burako, has moved to a snowy country and is living there in good health. Melmo goes to see Burako, and finds her in low spirits. Having reached puberty, Burako is looking for a boyfriend. Using the magical candies, Melmo grows up and takes a test to be a stewardess. What for? Of course, to take Burako to Africa where she will have many choices for a boyfriend. Melmo gives Burako a red candy to make her regress into a fertilized cell, and heads for Africa.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31034" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">男の子をやっつけろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beating the Boys</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otokonoko o Yattsukero</title>
<summary>Which gender is superior, boys or girls? In Melmo`s class, the boys and girls confront each other over this issue. Melmo asks for advice from her senior girl friend Naname, who is the leader of the girls. Naname insists that girls are undoubtedly superior to boys. Asked for advice from the boys, Shikaku, who is the leader of the boys, proudly proclaims that boys are unquestionably superior to girls. These assertions intensify the confrontation between them.. In the end, they come up with the idea to "decide which is superior by a match."
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31035" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チッチャイナ国のとりこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Captive of Chicchaina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chicchaina Koku no Toriko</title>
<summary>Melmo is abducted by the minister of Chicchaina, who tries to deprive her of the secret medicine of regaining youth. Held captive in the palace of Chicchaina, Melmo is urged to reveal the secret of rejuvenation to Professor Waregarasu, who is in reality a rebel with no intentions of obeying the dictatorial government. Professor Waregarasu persuades her to never reveal the secret, telling her that she would be killed if she does so. Using the power of the candies, Melmo escapes from the palace to save herself and the professor. But their pursuers are drawing near.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31036" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もえる 無人島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Burning Deserted Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeru Mijintou</title>
<summary>The airplane Melmo and Prof. Waregarasu were fleeing on crash lands on a desert island. The pilot shoots a rabbit with a rifle to secure some food. But Melmo and the party immediately find themselves surrounded by all the animals living on the island. Looking closely at the animals, they realize that there is a pair of each kind. The male rabbit is alone because his partner has been killed. Melmo and the party apologize to the animals. Deeply sympathetic with the male rabbit, Melmo takes red and blue candies at the same time, transforms herself into a rabbit, and comforts the male rabbit.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31037" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白雪姫をいじめよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Bully Snow White</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shirayukihime o Ijimeyou</title>
<summary>Melmo is chosen to play the leading role for "Snow White" at the upcoming school festival. Nitako, who is from a very rich family, is also eager to play that role. Although Nitako is eventually cast as the stepmother who bullies Snow White, she works out a scheme with her mother to take the role from Melmo. Even on the very day of the play, Nitako has not yet given up on her idea. She changes her lines as she likes, and persistently bullies Snow White. In the meantime, having stolen Melmo`s candies, Nitako`s mother threatens Melmo that she will not give back the candies unless Melmo surrenders the role of Snow White to Nitako.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31038" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トカゲ館の一夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night at the Mansion of the Lizard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokagekan no Ichiya</title>
<summary>Having taking away the bottle of candies, Melmo`s brother, Totoo, keeps teasing her and won`t give it back. Melmo tries to make him return it, but Totoo won`t give it to her. Melmo decides to teach him how to use the candies to turn into an animal. She plans to get the bottle of candies back while Totoo is in the form of an animal. Totoo then turns into a frog. Melmo is now in trouble, because a frog cannot eat the candy when she wants to turn him back into Totoo. And it can`t even take the water that she could dissolve the candies into. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31039" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ママがかえって来た!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother Is Back!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mama ga Kaette Kita!</title>
<summary>A man named Damon visits Melmo`s house and tells her that he will let her see her mother if she gave him candies. True to his words, Melmo`s mother is back. But Totoo who is now a frog and Touch, who is only a little baby, instinctively understands that the mother is a fake. In fact, the mother who comes back home is a doll that has been implanted with a snake`s soul and is being manipulated by Damon. Melmo runs away from the fake mother, but the mother with a snake`s soul begins to truly love Melmo and her little brothers. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31040" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビリケン まかり通る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Biriken Having His Own Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Biriken Makari Tooru</title>
<summary>A puppy named Biriken is always bullied by grown-up dogs. Feeling sorry for Biriken, Melmo uses candies to make the puppy grow up. Growing bigger than all the other dogs, Biriken starts to punish them, and becomes the boss of all stray mutts. But he becomes a puppy again with a red candy only when he goes back home to his mother and acts like a baby with her. The mother starts to teach the spoiled Biriken how to become strong. But after knowing that he can be strong with the power of the candies, Biriken no longer listens to his mother. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31041" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘソガエルのひみつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Frog with a Navel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hesogaeru no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Because Totoo was originally a human, he has a navel even though he is now a frog. Finding out that a frog with a navel is living on a Southern island, Melmo and the party head there. On the island, a masked woman is giving villagers pollen as a medicine to make them regain their youth. Prof. Waregarasu, who accompanies the party, sees that the pollen contains narcotics. The navel of a frog is proven to be a stomach wart caused by narcotics. Melmo and the party decide to stick stamens to the pistil of a giant flower blooming on the top of the mountain. If they succeed in fertilizing to the seed, the flower will wither. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31042" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの子 を にがすな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Let That Kid Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Ko o Nigasuna!</title>
<summary>The president of a company that used to employ the criminal who hit Melmo`s mother visits Melmo at her house. Feeling deeply sorry for depriving them of their mother, the president offers to adopt Melmo and her little brothers, and Melmo and her brothers decide to accept his offer. It is after they are adopted that they come to know that the president is living with an evil woman and is running a smuggling company. Knowing that the police have started to investigate the hit-and-run case, the president tries to deceive them by drawing attention to their adoption and diverting their eyes from his smuggling business. Growing impatient, Melmo tries to report the case to the police. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31043" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひん死の白鳥さん / 学園広場を守れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dying Swan / Protecting the Schoolyard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hinshi no Shiratori-san / Gakuen Hiroba o Mamore</title>
<summary>Part A: Coming upon a swan about to die from pollution, Melmo decides to make it go back to being an egg with her candies so that she can take it to a northern county. But on her way there, the egg breaks. Although she could somehow revive the swan with the magic of her candies, the swan becomes spotted. She is then bullied by the other swans because of the spots on her body. Nevertheless, the swan takes on a hunter in order to protect the other swans that shut her out. 
Part B: A boy in Melmo`s class named Komori goes to a cram school every day. Being forced to study even at home, he is about to have a nervous breakdown. Melmo offers to take him to a schoolyard because she thinks that he needs some time to play. After playing make-belief war to his heart`s content, Komori regains the lively look on his face. Seeing the change in him, Melmo grows confident, sets up a barricade at school, and demands that children should have more time to play! So begins a battle between children and adults. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31044" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1971-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス・メルモ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Melmo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas Melmo</title>
<summary>One night while she is counting the days to Christmas on her fingers, Melmo finds an abandoned child. She gives a candy to the child to make him grow up to be a boy, and finds out that the child is named Tadao and was abandoned by his parents who had lost their jobs. Melmo then turns the president, who abandoned Tadao`s father, into an old man. The president apologizes in a fit of tears, and he promises that he will by all means find Tadao`s parents and take care of them. In the meantime, Tadao`s parents are heading for a snowy mountain to commit suicide. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31045" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-01-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">身がわりにされちゃった!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Substitutes!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Migawari ni Sarechatta!</title>
<summary>Melmo and Touch, who have turned themselves into adults, are flying a kite on New Year`s Day. They are greeted by a sister and a brother whom they`ve never met before. They ask Melmo and Touch to live in the upscale apartment where they used to live. Melmo and her brothers gladly move into their luxury apartment. But a tempting offer is always deceptive: the sister and brother turn out to be thieves who are sought after by the police. The police break into the apartment, discovers many purses, and try to arrest Melmo and Touch mistaking them for thieves. Melmo and her brothers narrowly escape arrest. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31046" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メルモと魔術師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melmo and a Magician</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Melmo to Majutsushi</title>
<summary>Melmo is brought out to appear in a magic show. But becoming angry at the deception of the magician, she uses the magic of her candies and startles him. Watching Melmo`s excessive use of candies, God decides to punish her a little. Completely unaware, the magician coerces Melmo into teaching him the magic of how to transform. He has already snatched Touch. Melmo succeeds in transforming herself into a dog and rescuing Touch, but she cannot return to being herself because she is being punished by God. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31047" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくは人間だ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Human!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Ningen Da!!</title>
<summary>Totoo, who has turned into a frog, wants to go to grade school. He asks the school principal to accept him. The principal offers that if a frog can pass the test, he will accept him, and Totoo takes the test. But after the test, he scares the principal`s wife in the pool. The wife loses her ring and panics. Totoo leaves his home knowing that he cannot go to school after causing such big trouble. He drops himself into the sewage pipe to die. But in the water, he finds the principal`s wife`s ring. In this episode Totoo is able to return to his original human form. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31048" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりぼっちのジャングル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Alone in the Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no Jungle</title>
<summary>Melmo sneaks into a big garden of a big house with Totoo, who is now in human form, to play. But they are spotted by the surveillance camera, and are scolded by the old man living alone in the house. The next day, the old man visits the school to complain that he is annoyed by children sneaking into his garden. Melmo is in charge of school announcement on that day and transforms with her candies into an old woman in order to sound like one. The voice of the old woman startles the old man because it sounds exactly like his late wife. After coming to know how lonely the old man is, Melmo transforms herself into an old woman, and visits his house.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31049" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">3650日の恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3,650 Days of Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3650 Nichi no Kyoufu</title>
<summary>Brother burglars who have stolen a billion yen`s worth of gold nuggets run away into Melmo`s house and hole up, taking Melmo and her brothers hostage. But their gun suddenly goes off and they faint. The police are in trouble because they won`t wake up and the police cannot get a confession on the whereabouts of the gold nuggets. Melmo takes her candies in order to grow up, and makes the awakened burglars believe that 10 years have passed since the incident. She figures that by making them believe such a long time has lapsed they would rush off to get the gold nuggets. But to her surprise the burglars start to cry over their little sister, thinking that she must be dead for over 10 years now. They were, in fact, committing burglary to get money for an operation for their sick sister. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31050" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メルモの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melmo`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Melmo no Hatsukoi</title>
<summary>The man who helped Melmo when she was being picked on by a student gang on her way to school turns out to be Mr. Nozawa, a new teacher. Melmo instantly falls in love with him. She even dreams about getting married to him. Melmo takes candies to grow up, introduces herself to Mr. Nozawa as Melmo`s elder sister, and asks him out. But on the first date, Mr. Nozawa tells her that he will be getting married soon. On the next day, the broken-hearted Melmo leaves school early. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31051" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すて猫トラちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stray Cat Tora-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteneko Tora-chan</title>
<summary>An imported tiger escapes at the port, and the scared workers shoot it. Melmo talks to the injured tiger and learns that she has just given birth to a baby. Asked by the mother tiger to take care of her baby, Melmo takes the baby tiger to her home. But this mischievous tiger grows up by eating blue candies, rages about in town, and is finally surrounded by police. Melmo runs to go and save the baby tiger. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31052" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉チャンなんか大嫌い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hate My Sister!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ane-chan Nanka Daikirai!</title>
<summary>Melmo thinks of growing up and breast feeding Touch. But she doesn`t have any milk. Prof. Waregarasu explains to her that she cannot have any milk unless she gets pregnant and hormones are properly excreted. He also reminds her not to abuse the candies if she cares about herself at all. So, she goes to parents` day at Totoo`s school as she is. But this upsets Totoo. He runs away from home and gets abducted. Finding a threatening letter from the kidnappers, Melmo asks for Prof. Waregarasu`s help. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31053" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたし求婚されちゃったァ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someone Proposed to Me!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Kyuukon Sarechattaa!!</title>
<summary>Melmo disguises herself as her mother to comfort Totoo, who misses his deceased mother intensely. Shogo, the school gang leader, falls in love with Melmo as her mother at first sight, and asks her to marry him. Asked for advice, Prof. Waregarasu explains to her what marriage is about. His advice makes Melmo prudent about marriage. She makes an unreasonable demand upon Shogo, hoping that he will give up. But to her surprise Shogo grows more enthusiastic. His dedication moves Melmo, and she finally make up her mind to marry him. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31054" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">光りと闇と愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light, Darkness, and Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari to Yami to Ai</title>
<summary>While taking shelter from the rain in a limestone cave, Melmo and Prof. Waregarasu meet a couple named Tsumura and Chiyoko. They are actually hiding in the cave and have apparently have run away from their homes. Then, Chiyoko`s father breaks into the cave and threatens Tsumura at gunpoint to part with his daughter. Her father grows impatient with the unyielding Tsumura, and shoots the gun at the ceiling. The impact of the gunshot causes the ceiling to collapse, and Melmo, Tsumura, and the party is all trapped in the limestone cave. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31055" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋人がいっぱい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Many Boyfriends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koibito ga Ippai</title>
<summary>Three men confess their love to Melmo. The three are named Ichiro, Jiro, and Saburo; and they all happen to be brothers. The three brothers start to fight, each claiming that he is the most suitable boyfriend for Melmo. Totally at a loss, Melmo carelessly tells them that she will date the one who first makes Touch laugh. So Melmo, Touch and the three brothers drive to the sea. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31056" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">豪傑赤チャンに泣く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tough Guy Crying for a Baby Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouketsu Akachan ni Naku</title>
<summary>Eventually, Jiro becomes Melmo`s boy friend. Jiro tells Melmo that he has some knowledge of karate and that he has become physically strong thanks to the master of the dojo he used to learn from. Growing interested in karate Melmo visits the dojo. There she finds the grand master, named Yanagida, who looks tough as can be. But at home things are different, and he feels small surrounded by all women in the family. Yanagida has been praying fervently that his pregnant wife would finally give birth to a baby boy. Professor Waregarasu explains to Melmo the mechanism of pregnancy, and tells her that it is impossible to select the gender. Melmo starts to imagine what kind of a baby she would give birth to. 
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31057" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1972-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さようならメルモ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Melmo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayounara Melmo</title>
<summary>Prof. Waregarasu decides to go back to his home country. He asks Melmo and her brothers to come with him. He is worried about leaving the three children to live by themselves. But Melmo cannot give him any immediate reply. Jiro`s mother asks Melmo if she wants to move into to her home with her little brothers. After much thought, Melmo decides to move to Jiro`s house. Professor Waregarasu asks Jiro to take good care of Melmo and her brothers, and goes back home. Fifteen years later, Melmo and Jiro have a baby girl. One day, the daughter takes blue candies and grows up. The spirit of Melmo`s mother, who longs to see Melmo again, dwells in her body. Melmo meets her mother again, and they spend short but unforgettable moments together. The mother leaves and Melmo finds her little daughter smiling in front of her.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="56146" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88411" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120257" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Italian Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120258" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Italian Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168355" update="2015-05-11">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
