<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3058" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>43</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>1991-02-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Idol Tenshi Youkoso Youko</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Idol Angel Welcome Yoko</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Diventeremo famose</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Las aventuras de Yoko y Saki</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Привет! Звездният ангел Йоко</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アイドル天使 ようこそようこ</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2558" approval="2" total="2">Idol Densetsu Eriko</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w019.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="778" type="Work">Ashi Productions</name>
<name id="4999" type="Direction">Amino Tetsurou</name>
<name id="22594" type="Work">TV Setouchi</name>
<name id="19636" type="Character Design">Chikanaga Sanae</name>
<name id="6598" type="Work">Umehara Masaru</name>
<name id="5112" type="Original Plan">Shudou Takeshi</name>
<name id="5112" type="Series Composition">Shudou Takeshi</name>
<name id="4870" type="Music">Andou Takahiro</name>
<name id="1059" type="Work">Big West</name>
<name id="20801" type="Work">Tsuchida Tamiya</name>
<name id="787" type="Character Design">Studio Live</name>
<name id="22086" type="Character Design">Tominaga Mari</name>
</creators>
<description>Tanaka Youko leaves country life behind to go to Shibuya to fulfill her dream of becoming an idol singer. Traveling with her is her pet flying squirrel Muu. Along the way they meet up with Saki, who has similar plans. They become friends and decide to work together to pursue their dreams of stardom.
Source: animemetro.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="26">4.81</permanent>
<temporary count="26">6.38</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4325.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1779</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4928</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2150</identifier>
<identifier>nzsjyz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/tv_series/w019.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アイドル天使ようこそようこ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89132</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30674" type="main character in" update="2011-04-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Tanaka Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30675" type="main character in" update="2011-04-01">
<name>Yamamori Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30676" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-01">
<name>Muu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30677" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-01">
<name>Hoshihana Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34893" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Tokudaiji Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34894" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Shibuya Chougorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34895" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Yoshiaki Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2055" picture="21393.jpg">Shimazu Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34896" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Yamashita Hideki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34914" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Omo-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34916" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Saku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34917" type="appears in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Richard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34918" type="appears in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Kuroudo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34919" type="appears in" update="2011-07-23">
<name>Takarada Umetarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34920" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Barry Garnin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34921" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Hayami Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34922" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Shibuya no Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34924" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Harada Toshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34925" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Heisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34926" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Ijuuin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34928" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34930" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34931" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<name>Kanako no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4718" picture="27537.jpg">Takizawa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35131" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<name>Mickey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35132" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kano Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35133" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Michael Jackson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38309" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Omawari-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29983">Nagashima Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38310" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Tokudaiji Tetsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38311" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Hayami Namiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38312" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Tokudaiji Matsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38313" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Hayami Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3310" picture="24332.jpg">Mizutori Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38314" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38315" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38316" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Shun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38317" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Rindou Baku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38318" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Yasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38321" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Tenchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38322" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Megu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38323" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38324" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38325" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Ranko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5651" picture="25812.jpg">Ikura Kazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38326" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Sue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38327" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Sue no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="256" picture="188450.jpg">Satou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38328" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Sue no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49297" type="appears in" update="2012-09-24">
<name>Yuki Daruma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49298" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-10-20">
<rating votes="4">8.71</rating>
<name>Tamura Eriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94848.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50841" type="appears in" update="2012-11-26">
<name>Hoshina Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50842" type="appears in" update="2012-11-26">
<name>Kakimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3231" picture="24214.jpg">Sugawara Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="30679" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそin公園通り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Koen-Dori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso in Kouendoori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30680" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌声はバイエルで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bayer Under the Starry Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utagoe wa Bayer de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30681" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おもちゃのロフト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Loft of Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omocha no Loft</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30682" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トマトの朝は歌声で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomato no Asa wa Utagoe de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30683" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真夜中のライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayonaka no Live</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30684" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">響け!心のバイオリン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibike! Kokoro no Violin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30685" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さびしがりやの町のかみさま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabishigariya no Machi no Kamisama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30686" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきなハンズロフト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki na Hands Loft</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30687" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきなカンちがい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki na Kanchigai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30688" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ湯ートピア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Utopia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30689" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペイン坂の雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Spain-zaka no Ame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30690" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔女は月の夜に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majo wa Tsuki no Yoru ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30691" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の交換日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Koukan Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30692" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗記と恋のAtoZ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anki to Koi no A to Z</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30693" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">翼に夢を乗せて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa ni Yume o Nosete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30694" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな星空の奇跡(ミラクル)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Hoshizora no Miracle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30695" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドルへの道Part1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol e no Michi Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30696" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドルへの道Part2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol e no Michi Part 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30697" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ夏の雪ダルマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Natsu no Yukidaruma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30698" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏, 私, 元気です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu, Watashi, Genki Desu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30699" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌え!走れ!グランプリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utae! Hashire! Grand Prix</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30700" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">公園通りの動物園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouendoori no Doubutsuen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30701" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦争は知らない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensou wa Shiranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30702" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グランパの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Grandpa no Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30703" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニュートレンディを探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New Trendy o Sagase!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30704" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スターを探す男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Star o Sagasu Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30705" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそカレー行進曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Curry Koushinkyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30706" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガラスの中のアイドル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Glass no Naka no Idol</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30707" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レッスンアンダーザスカイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lesson Under the Sky</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30708" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌声でタイホして</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utagoe de Taiho Shite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30709" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シネマパニックパラダイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cinema Panic Paradise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30710" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイStar危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Star Kikiippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30711" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋文横丁からの手紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koibumi Yokochou kara no Tegami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30712" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしのジュリエットPART1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Juliet Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30713" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしのジュリエットPART2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Juliet Part 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30714" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猫子ちゃんのユウウツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nekoko-chan no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30715" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドルは知っている</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol wa Shitte Iru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30716" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球の酸素がなくなる日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu no Sanso ga Nakunaru Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30717" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サーカスが来た!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Circus ga Kita!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30718" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レッツシングwithバード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Let`s Sing with Bird</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30719" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪のラビリンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki no Labyrinth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30720" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の街のアリスたちPART1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi no Machi no Alice-tachi Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30721" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の街のアリスたちPART2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi no Machi no Alice-tachi Part 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128407" update="2011-02-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1990-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128408" update="2011-02-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1990-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
