<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="306" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-07-18</startdate>
<enddate>1992-07-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kurenai no Buta</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Crimson Pig</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Scarlet Pig</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Crimson Pig</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">بوركو روسو</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="synonym">Punainen sika</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Порко Россо</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Червоний кабан</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">くれ豚</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">くれぶた</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">PR</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kurebuta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KnB</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">紅の豚</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">紅豬</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Порко Россо</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">붉은 돼지</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Szkarłatny pilot</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Porco Rosso: O Porquinho Voador</title>
<title xml:lang="no" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Porco Rosso: O Último Herói Romântico</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Karmínové prase</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Οι Αερομαχίες του Πόρκο Ρόσσο</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">פורקו רוסו</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Porco Rosso - A mesterpilóta</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Porko Roso</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">พอร์โค รอสโซ สลัดอากาศประจัญบาน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Kızıl Kanatlar</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Порко Россо</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Porco Rosso</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">飛天紅豬俠</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">红猪</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9514" approval="10" total="16">Kaze Tachinu</anime>
<anime id="8256" approval="3" total="9">Ojii-san no Lamp</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="314120">One of my favorites from Ghibli.  Soooo many pig puns...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="371481">While finding the animation slightly below standards of the Studio Ghibli works, the show drawing inspiration from other anime titles has its unique humour with lots of puns, and it delivers pretty well-balanced action, comedy and story aspects. Although development of characters is a little bit messy, and one can easily find himself lost due to lack of additional information moving the plot forward, this film surely shows it was created by Miyazaki - aeronautics, , blood-less action and strong feeling of feminism. It might not be a masterpiece, but it is definitely worth your time!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="230513">A must see classic with all the good in it what a anime needs: good characters (designs), not to deep but good to watch and excitement plot  and a nice heartwarming story with a couple good morals! Please watch you won`t be disappointed!

Dp</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="278370">This film is criminally undervalued and yet for me ranks with [i]Spirited Away[/i] as not only Miyazaki`s best, but also one of the best anime films period. Charming, witty, and with an actual moral for adults and children alike, there is really no reason for anyone to not see this film.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="784472">While the gender politics are remarkably dated at this point, Porco Rosso still has charm and depth in spades. You`d be doing yourself a great disservice to not at least give this a shot. If you like contemplative reflection on war, slapstick comedy and loveably over-the-top supporting cast you can`t go wrong here.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="40" type="Direction">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="40" type="Original Work">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
</creators>
<description>A dashing and brave WWI Pilot is transformed into a pig by a mysterious curse. He is now employed as a paid mercenary/problem solver and sea plane pilot in the Adriatic Sea for the side of good. He is forced to do combat with a band of air pirates who never bathe and call themselves Mama Aiuto (Mothers Helper). Anarchy and war are coming to Italy and the adriatic pilots are being forced to join the Air Force or become fugatives from the law. Our hero Porco is shot down in a dogfight with a self styled air ace called Curtis.
Porco must rebuild his plane, Fight Mama Aiuto, run from the Italian government, engage in a final showdown with Curtis whilst courting the lovely Gina and saving young school girls from the clutches of Mama Aiuto, pay back Papa Piccolo for the renovation of his airplane, win a bet, break the curse, and save himself in the bargain.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4099">7.73</permanent>
<temporary count="4114">7.92</temporary>
<review count="3">8.27</review>
</ratings>
<picture>145634.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>855</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>416</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>298</identifier>
<identifier>gqeaxc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://gkids.com/films/porco-rosso/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nausicaa.net/miyazaki/porco/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Porco_Rosso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>紅の豚</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2530</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>151731</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>451</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>붉은_돼지</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>红猪</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2689" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-02">
<name>1920s</name>
<description>During the 1920s, we had gangsters, Mafia, alcohol, and gambling prohibition.
The Corleones ruled that time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3421" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>aviation</name>
<description>"These magnificant men in their flying machines"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4830" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-03">
<name>flying boats</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13884" type="main character in" update="2016-12-15">
<rating votes="24">7.49</rating>
<name>Fio Piccolo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23539" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-27">
<rating votes="12">6.98</rating>
<name>Madame Gina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The owner of Hotel Adriano in which she also performs.</description>
<picture>58095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6777" picture="82773.jpg">Katou Tokiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23540" type="main character in" update="2010-10-27">
<rating votes="27">8.69</rating>
<name>Marco Pagot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He was a fighter pilot for the Italian Air Force in WWI. A curse has since given him the appearance of a pig, leading to the nickname Porco Rosso. He now operates as a bounty hunter in the Adriatic Sea.</description>
<picture>58096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29468" picture="78588.jpg">Moriyama Shuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23541" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-27">
<rating votes="10">4.17</rating>
<name>Donald Curtis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A confident American pilot, recruited by the Flying Pirates Alliance to take out their enemy Porco Rosso. His goal in life is to become a Hollywood star and President of the United States.</description>
<picture>58097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23542" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-27">
<rating votes="9">6.97</rating>
<name>Master Piccolo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owner of Piccolo S.P.A., builder of seaplanes.</description>
<picture>58098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33104" picture="90263.jpg">Katsura Sanshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23543" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-27">
<rating votes="9">6.85</rating>
<name>Mamma Aiuto Boss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of a gang of flying pirates.</description>
<picture>58099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4843" picture="47884.jpg">Kamijou Tsunehiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4012" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>1992-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6026" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1992-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6027" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1992-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24398" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1992-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24400" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1992-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24401" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1992-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37546" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37547" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37548" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37549" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37550" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the microphone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37551" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
