<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3070" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zoids Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゾイド ジェネシス</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Zoidai</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1382" type="Same Setting">Zoids</anime>
<anime id="1774" type="Same Setting">Zoids Shin Seiki/Zero</anime>
<anime id="1775" type="Same Setting">Zoids Fuzors</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/zoids_g/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7874" type="Direction">Mizuno Kazunori</name>
<name id="3519" type="Character Design">Sakai Kyuuta</name>
<name id="3661" type="Series Composition">Nishizono Satoru</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>Natural disasters have devastated planet Zi, killing off almost all life. A thousand years later humans have gradually re-established civilization, salvaging ancient Zoids through diving and mining efforts. In a village whose most previous item is a giant sword which they worship as a holy symbol. A teenage boy discovers an ancient Liger-type Zoid while on a deep water salvage operation. Suddenly the village is attacked by skeletal Bio-Zoids intent on stealing a powerful generator located in the village. Our teenage hero awakens the Liger and discovers that the town`s sacred sword is the Liger`s weapon, together they fight off the mysterious Bio-Zoids. At least for now...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="356">5.55</permanent>
<temporary count="367">7.29</temporary>
<review count="3">5.94</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10479.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1748</identifier>
<identifier>lscman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/zoids_g/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zoids:_Genesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゾイドジェネシス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7353</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15427" type="main character in" update="2010-03-01">
<rating votes="5">8.39</rating>
<name>Kotona Elegance</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A charming and optimistic mercenary who travels with a white bird (of unknown species) named Kurruku. Kotona is only her alias, and her real name was revealed later. She prefers to use her feminine wiles and diplomatic nature to avoid conflict but still reach her objective. She joins Ruuji in his quest for a Generator mechanic, as a way to repay him for helping defeat a group of Zoid thieves. Later on, Ruuji would ask her to aid him in a campaign against Digald. From clues in later episodes it shows that Kotona stayed with them because she likes Ruuji.
Her hometown, IronRock, is revealed to house a facility that can create the silver armor which Digald uses, and that a secret guild which she was part of would assassinate anyone who was close to uncovering its secret. Kotona left because she was to be the next leader, but to do so, her twin sister would have to be killed. Because she ran, her sister took her position and attempted to kill her. Wounded, Kotona fell into IronRock`s deep lake, but she was rescued by the hitherto-inert RainbowJerk, which was hidden in the watery depths. Since leaving her home she led a freelance life, keeping her identity and past a secret.
She was brought up to be a skilled assassin and has many weapons hidden on her body. It was later revealed that her people are actually part of a surviving group that avoided the "Gods` Fury" event and rebuilt their society at IronRock. Throughout the years, her people began to forget their origins, but a small group of them has kept the secret for generations as custodians of the city and to their sleeping Gil Dragon. She knows various ancient phrases passed down by her mother, and her real name is actually the Gil Dragon`s activation code. No one can know her true name unless it`s her husband.
Ruuji tried to ask her real name anyway for the sake of obtaining Gil Dragon. Kotona revealed her secret without Ruuji marrying her, but still joked about the prospect. She found it ironic that her early painful memories would come to aid the war effort. Kotona and Souta would eventually help pilot Gil Dragon to fly to Sora City to recover the Leeo ammunition for the war against Jiin. It has been seen she was relieved after Ron reported that Seijuurou recovered from his illness back in Sora City.It is unknown if she resolved to return to IronRock as leader as intended.
She pilots the Zoid Rainbow Jerk later the Rainbow Peak.</description>
<picture>43936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35501" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Zairin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35502" type="appears in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Shio Familon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5099" picture="29011.jpg">Takeguchi Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35503" type="main character in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Seijuurou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35504" type="appears in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Faaji Familon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35505" type="appears in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Min Familon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35506" type="main character in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Ra Kan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35507" type="appears in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Raaji Familon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="35508" type="main character in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Ruuji Familon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35509" type="main character in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Ron Mangan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35510" type="main character in" update="2011-08-11">
<name>Raimei no Garaga</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35511" type="main character in" update="2011-08-11">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Re Mie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Re Mie is a pragmatic, energetic, and occasionally cynical traveling companion of Ra-Kan. She is the daughter of Ra-Kan`s younger sister, making her his niece, and shows a great deal of respect for him, often calling him as Oji-sama. She`s the princess of Ra-Kan`s fallen nation and has a crush on Ruuji. She displays her attraction by blushing from time to time and gets jealous when she thought Ruuji was engaged to Kotona. In fact, her attraction is so blatant that merely being physically close to Ruuji prompts blushing and exaggerated reactions out of her insecurity. On the other hand, she has been willing to admit her feelings, at least to herself, as seen in her occasional romantic daydreams, even before their final battle against Jiin. While still crying for the supposed death of Ra-Kan, she finally fell into Ruuji`s embrace as he tried to comfort her, this being their most intimate moment together, despite a lack of confessing her feelings. Also, as she was being crushed by Jiin`s Bio Tyranno, it was thoughts of her that Ruuji was able to revive the fallen Murasame Liger. That aside, she usually criticizes Ruuji for his impulsive behavior as well as his inexperience in piloting Zoids. Despite her size, she is a capable combatant, able to pin down Ruuji with little effort. Ruuji and Garaga complain much about her cooking ability as she only knows how to barbecue. She would eventually become good friends with Souta, the amnesiac former pilot of the Bio Kentro, who was rescued after its destruction, and named him Gin. During her time in the Suppression Army, she was in charge of supply guard detail and led her own Lanstag battalion. In the aftermath of Jiin`s defeat, there was no epilogue to satisfy the subplot of her feelings for Ruuji. It can at least be assumed that she returned to her kingdom with Ra-Kan to rebuild.
She pilots the Lanstag and later on in the series, the Lanstag Break Her Zoid was destroyed in saving Ruuji from Jiin`s Bio-Tyranno.</description>
<picture>1018.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="35835" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35836" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイオゾイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bio Zoid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bio Zoid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36508" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departing on a Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36509" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City of Beginnings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36510" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41870" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">山のアジト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mountain Hideout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yama no Ajito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41871" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘆きの山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mountain of Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nageki no Yama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41872" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下水路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underground Waterway</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Suiro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41873" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉の村</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Spring Village</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen no Mura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41874" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hesitation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41875" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅の仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Travelling Companions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi no Nakama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41876" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41877" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">支配</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Control</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shihai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41878" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dasshutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41879" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">離散</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dispersal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Risan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41880" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再起への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Road to Recovery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiki e no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41881" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハヤテ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hayate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hayate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41882" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰郷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41883" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">驕り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ogori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41884" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出会い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41885" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41886" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">進軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Advance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41887" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41888" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧の河</title>
<title xml:lang="en">River of Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no Kawa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41889" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41890" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41891" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">合流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Union</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41892" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅蓮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crimson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41893" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42144" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔物の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forest of Monsters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamono no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42145" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">残された者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Were Left Behind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokosareta Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44712" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソラノヒト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People of the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora no Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44713" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予兆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Omen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yochou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44882" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44883" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ambush</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45012" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほころび</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Falling Apart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokorobi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45435" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">襲来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuurai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46426" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">入城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entry into a Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyuujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46427" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">密会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clandestine Meeting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46428" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rush</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46429" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">政変</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coup d`Etat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seihen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46430" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイオ粒子砲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bio-Particle Cannon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bio Ryuushihou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46789" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">離陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takeoff</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ririku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46790" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鍵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Key</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46791" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inheritance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48420" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">瓦解</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fatal Flaw</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48421" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決別</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsubetsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48422" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">神の雷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Divine Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami no Kaminari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48423" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48424" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128415" update="2011-02-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128416" update="2011-02-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128417" update="2011-02-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128418" update="2011-02-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
