<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="312" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>112</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-10-10</startdate>
<enddate>1995-01-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yuu Yuu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">幽遊白書</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">幽★遊★白書</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Yu Yu Hakusho - Les aventuriers de l`au-delà</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Yuu Yuu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Yu Yu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">YYH</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">yuyu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">幽☆遊☆白書</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho: Ghost Files</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho - Yu Degli Spettri</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Отчет о буйстве духов</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">يو يو هاكوشو</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho - Velká zkouška</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">יו יו האקושו</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho - A szellemfiú</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">คนเก่งฟ้าประทาน</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Yu Yu Hakusho</title>
<title xml:lang="tl" type="official">Ghost Fighter</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="753" type="Side Story">Yuu Yuu Hakusho: Meikai Shitou Hen - Honoo no Kizuna</anime>
<anime id="1084" type="Side Story">Yuu Yuu Hakusho (1993)</anime>
<anime id="14506" type="Side Story">Yuu Yuu Hakusho Kanzen Shinsaku Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2369" approval="139" total="176">Bleach</anime>
<anime id="132" approval="85" total="97">Hunter x Hunter (1999)</anime>
<anime id="8550" approval="58" total="68">Hunter x Hunter (2011)</anime>
<anime id="1530" approval="54" total="68">Dragon Ball Z</anime>
<anime id="571" approval="40" total="46">Rekka no Honoo</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="18">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="476533">A bit underrated.. possibly due to the sometimes crappy animation.  However, story is good, characters are funny, and the action is pretty decent.  Recommended for any fan of fighting/action shounens.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="89468">The father of all modern action animes. Ive never been so drawn in by an action series like this one did. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="479550">Haha, I remember seeing all 112 eps plus one of the movies [Poltergeist Report, maybe] back in 2006. I was only about 12 at the time, so i can`t say whether this would be good for a mature audience for sure. But, from memory, this was a great series with arc after arc being executed very well. It also had nice closure.
Definitely recommended for those that want a popular fighting manga or anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="759528">One of the great original anime`s of the 1990`s. A must see for all anime fans!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="498732">Shounen super-power never got better than this. Yuu Yuu Hakusho succeeds in telling a good story, creating charismatic chararacters, showing nice battles and bringing comic elements without losing the direction of the series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="320398">Best shounen ever!Battles and more battles!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="359130">Loved this series!  Very old but very good and amazing storyline.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319389">One of the best shounen animes of all time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="43461">This story has such an awesome hook and keeps trucking through the Sensui arc, but gets crippled when things turn to Demon World by power creep where it languishes before coming to a somewhat touching end that leaves you feeling it can continue on. Still a great watch! Also, watch this in English if possible, the ad-lib work for Yusuke done by Justin Cook was quite masterful!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1990/tv_027.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="18672" type="Animation Character Design">Kitayama Mari</name>
<name id="6428" type="Animation Character Design">Oonishi Masaya</name>
<name id="5006" type="Animation Character Design">Yamasawa Minoru</name>
<name id="7075" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="724" type="Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="733" type="Work">Yomiko Advertising</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="874" type="Original Work">Togashi Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="4326" type="Music">Honma Yuusuke</name>
<name id="3717" type="Series Composition">Oohashi Yukiyoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7220 [Urameshi Yuusuke], 14 years of age, is about as troublesome and violent as teenagers come. He is constantly ditching school, causing uproar, and getting into numerous fights everyday. One day however, he does the unexpected: sacrificing himself to save a young child. Such an action was never ever expected, especially coming from someone as troublesome as Yuusuke. The afterlife is not prepared for Yuusuke, as they never thought he would make such a sacrifice. Nowhere to go, and dead, Yuusuke becomes a ghost and must earn his way back into existence.
Yuusuke is "employed" by http://anidb.net/ch25880 [Koenma], who is in charge while his father and ruler of the afterlife, King Enma, is away. Under Koenma`s command, Yuusuke helps to stop menacing demons that threaten the lives of people everywhere - whether by stealing priceless and invaluable items and destructive weapons, or by wreaking havoc on humans.
Throughout Yuusuke`s journey, he is usually joined by his arch-rival, and local bully, http://anidb.net/ch7221 [Kuwabara Kazuma]; he is also joined by two demons named http://anidb.net/ch7224 [Hiei] and http://anidb.net/ch7223 [Kurama], who are ex-convicts of the afterlife that managed to escape from Koenma.
This group of unlikely allies goes on to participate and struggle in battles that have outcomes that determine the fate of humanity!
Yu Yu Hakusho is created by popular mangaka http://anidb.net/cr874 [Togashi Yoshihiro], who is also responsible for creating the acclaimed and much-loved series known as http://anidb.net/a132 [Hunter X Hunter].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3816">7.46</permanent>
<temporary count="3896">8.04</temporary>
<review count="11">8.12</review>
</ratings>
<picture>131089.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>311</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12455</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>392</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6964</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2125</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2126</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324</identifier>
<identifier>zidsxg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1990/tv_027.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>YuYu_Hakusho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>幽☆遊☆白書_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1696</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89083</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06W2HBGVQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="155" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-16">
<name>bodyguard</name>
<description>A bodyguard is a type of security guard or government law enforcement officer or soldier who protects a person or people, usually high-ranking public officials or officers, wealthy people, and celebrities, from danger: generally theft, assault, kidnapping, assassination, harassment, loss of confidential information, threats, or other criminal offences.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>213116.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3884" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-07">
<name>preview before ed</name>
<description>Unlike most productions, where the next episode preview rolls *after* the ending with the production credits, this title does the reverse: preview the next episode *first*, then enjoy the ED (or skip it if you prefer, without missing the juicy preview details).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7220" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="78">7.03</rating>
<name>Urameshi Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urameshi Yuusuke is known to be a stereotypical bad seed; having a spotty attendance record, doing poorly in class, and picking fights with many other students. He also smokes cigarettes and drinks alcohol in the manga.
He dies after saving a small child from being struck by a car, which is something the guardians of the afterlife did not predict. Koenma allows Botan to becoming Yuusuke`s guide for the Ordeal that he must undergo in order to be brought back to life, as well as help show him that he is actually a good person. He is then forced to become a Spirit Detective who protects the human race from demons.</description>
<picture>2120.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7221" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="74">7.03</rating>
<name>Kuwabara Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuma Kuwabara is the second toughest student in Sarayashiki Junior High School and is always trying to usurp Yusuke Urameshi`s position as the toughest. He develops feelings for the ice apparition, Yukina, though it becomes difficult since she remains oblivious of them, mainly from having been raised in a single gendered culture. Kuwabara is fiercely loyal to the the people closest to him, such as his trio of friends, as well as the other members of the Spirit Detectives.</description>
<picture>25593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7223" type="main character in" update="2011-11-14">
<rating votes="74">8.57</rating>
<name>Kurama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurama (蔵馬 warehouse horse) is a demon thief who, after being wounded by a bounty hunter, possesses and fuses with the unborn son of Shiori Minamino. Growing up for fifteen years as Shuichi Minamino (南野 秀一 south field, excellence first), Kurama has learned to embrace his human lifestyle. Kurama is a polite, soft-spoken boy and a dutiful son. He is regarded as a prodigy at his high school, Meiou Shiritsu Gakuen (盟王私立学園 Oath of Kings Private High School).
Calm and analytical, Kurama will go to any lengths to accomplish his goals, even if they endanger his life. He prefers to study the strengths and weaknesses of his opponents before devising a strategy of his own. He has an incredible sense of smell and has picked up many skills over the years, including the ability to read lips[8]. Kurama`s real talent is with plants: He can turn plants into deadly weapons, and has been known to use herbal remedies to treat wounds and other ailments. His favorite weapon is a bara shibenjin (薔薇棘鞭刃 rose thorny whip-blade), commonly called the Rose Whip.</description>
<picture>77117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7224" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="86">8.67</rating>
<name>Hiei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiei (飛影 flying shadow) is a male fire demon born to a race of female ice demons called koorime (氷女 ice maiden). His mother, Hina, is forced to abandon him because koorime prohibit male children. Hiei is taken in by a group of thieves and learns to kill at a very young age.
Throughout his traumatic childhood, his one shred of sanity is a necklace made from his mother`s hiruiseki (氷涙石 ice tear stone). He eventually loses the necklace in the heat of battle. In order to find the lost hirui, Hiei acquires the Jagan (邪眼 Evil Eye). He uses the Jagan to seek out the place of his birth and learns that the grief-stricken Hina committed suicide after losing her son. Hiei also learns that he has a twin sister, Yukina, who has disappeared from the village. He now has another goal, to search for Yukina.</description>
<picture>25597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8533" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="15">3.45</rating>
<name>Yukimura Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukimura Keiko (雪村 螢子) is Yusuke`s childhood friend; nowadays, they are near polar opposites, Keiko being a straight-A student and Yusuke being a juvenile delinquent, but the two are both closer than either like to admit. Keiko`s parents run a ramen restaurant named Yukimura Diner (雪村食堂 Yukimura Shokudou). After Yusuke is killed in a car accident, he is permitted another chance to live should someone, who ends up being Keiko, kiss his corpse. Yusuke tries not to involve her with his spirit detective experiences, though multiple interferences from demons prevent this. After being told an almost unbelievable lie by Botan, Keiko learns the truth when she goes with Botan, Yukina, Shizuru and Atsuko to the Dark Tournament, and continues supporting Yusuke in his further adventures. Towards the end of the series, Yusuke proposes to Keiko, telling her that no matter where life takes them, they will always be together in each others` hearts, even after having to wait three years for him to return to her.
In the English FUNimation anime her name is spelled Kayko.</description>
<picture>27701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15993" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="35">7.48</rating>
<name>Botan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Botan is the grim reaper, or guide to the underworld. She is charged with ferrying souls of the deceased to the underworld to face their final judgment. She also acts as http://anidb.net/ch7220 [Yusuke`s] assistant and trainer as he starts out his tenure as underworld detective.</description>
<picture>44987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6820" picture="151692.jpg">Miyuki Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21776" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-22">
<rating votes="7">7.48</rating>
<name>Sensui Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="599" picture="226547.jpg">Naya Rokurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25856" type="appears in" update="2017-06-02">
<rating votes="6">5.98</rating>
<name>Urameshi Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urameshi Atsuko is Yusuke`s alcoholic mother, who gave birth to him when she was only fourteen. Atsuko wants nothing more than for her son to turn out better than her, but does not succeed. While Yusuke rarely gets along with her, she truly cares about him, which he only sees when he notices her crying at his wake.</description>
<picture>61143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25858" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-20">
<rating votes="11">7.53</rating>
<name>Genkai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teaches Yusuke how to harness his spiritual power.</description>
<picture>61148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25859" type="appears in" update="2010-12-21">
<rating votes="3">4.10</rating>
<name>Randou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yusuke`s major opponent in the battle to become Genkai`s student.</description>
<picture>61150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25876" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">2.11</rating>
<name>Genbu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rock monster who resides in the Labyrinthine Castle. Kurama fights and defeats him.</description>
<picture>61192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2823" picture="83143.jpg">Shimaka Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25877" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="3">2.79</rating>
<name>Byakko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second of the Four Beasts. Kuwabara insists on fighting Byakko solo, which proves to be a long and dangerous fight.</description>
<picture>61193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25878" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">2.79</rating>
<name>Seiryu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fourth beast in the Labyrinthine Castle. He kills Byakko, and is subsequently quickly slain by Hiei. He has power over ice and great speed.</description>
<picture>61194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3125" picture="24097.jpg">Mitsuo Senda</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25879" type="appears in" update="2010-12-21">
<rating votes="3">6.31</rating>
<name>Suzaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fourth Beast.</description>
<picture>61195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25880" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-21">
<rating votes="9">7.78</rating>
<name>Koenma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26035" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">1.90</rating>
<name>Murugu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzaku`s bird companion. Proves to be useless and rather irritating.</description>
<picture>61472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28434" type="appears in" update="2011-02-09">
<rating votes="4">3.63</rating>
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28435" type="appears in" update="2011-02-09">
<rating votes="3">4.34</rating>
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28437" type="appears in" update="2011-02-09">
<rating votes="4">6.48</rating>
<name>Misako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28439" type="appears in" update="2011-02-09">
<rating votes="3">1.90</rating>
<name>Akashi-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4475" picture="26748.jpg">Nishikawa Ikuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28440" type="appears in" update="2011-02-09">
<rating votes="3">2.31</rating>
<name>Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28447" type="appears in" update="2011-02-10">
<rating votes="3">1.90</rating>
<name>Keiko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28448" type="appears in" update="2011-02-10">
<rating votes="3">1.72</rating>
<name>Keiko no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3305" picture="47438.jpg">Arakawa Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28514" type="appears in" update="2019-02-23">
<rating votes="3">2.79</rating>
<name>Kurama no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4718" picture="27537.jpg">Takizawa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28515" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<name>Kuroda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3322" picture="24340.jpg">Shiroyama Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28516" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3305" picture="47438.jpg">Arakawa Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28517" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<name>Kazemaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28518" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="3">3.70</rating>
<name>Kibano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28519" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Oni</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28521" type="appears in" update="2011-06-28">
<rating votes="3">3.81</rating>
<name>Shorin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28524" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="3">2.35</rating>
<name>Iwamoto-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28526" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Hirue</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28527" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Sakashita</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28528" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Gokumonki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2823" picture="83143.jpg">Shimaka Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28529" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Inmaki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="28530" type="appears in" update="2014-10-14">
<rating votes="2">2.27</rating>
<name>Miyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3968" picture="22867.jpg">Mizuhara Rin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28531" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Shidekin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28532" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Senchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="8057">Sasaoka Shigezou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28533" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Dafuya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="28534" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Youkai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28535" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Ken Tahara</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28536" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Ougyoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28537" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Ragubi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3362" picture="69121.jpg">Fukuda Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28538" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Hitotsumegyuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28539" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2144" picture="21622.jpg">Maruyama Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28540" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Mitamura</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2144" picture="21622.jpg">Maruyama Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28541" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<name>Sakigake</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28542" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="2">4.71</rating>
<name>M3 Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28543" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Liang</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3305" picture="47438.jpg">Arakawa Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29859" type="appears in" update="2011-03-11">
<rating votes="3">3.12</rating>
<name>Kuro Momotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="609" picture="1835.gif">Aomori Shin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31160" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="3">1.72</rating>
<name>Chinpou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31161" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Takenaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31162" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="4">2.19</rating>
<name>Gouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31163" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="3">1.72</rating>
<name>Koumori Dukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37748" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="8">7.58</rating>
<name>Koto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37749" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Chuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60151" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<rating votes="2">7.84</rating>
<name>Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60895" type="appears in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="2">9.25</rating>
<name>Karasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karasu is a Quest-class demon. Like Bui, Karasu fought against the Toguro brothers and lost and subsequently became a member of Team Toguro. He is able to use his aura to create bombs undetectable by lower level demons, as well as create bombs within his victims. Karasu displays sadistic tendencies during his fights and delights in torturing and humiliating his opponents. He wears a mask over his mouth which restricts his unstable powers. He is also able to use his entire body as an explosive.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>144992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61816" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-25">
<rating votes="2">8.00</rating>
<name>Jorge Saotome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146374.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65777" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="4">9.87</rating>
<name>Toguro Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger Toguro is a human turned (absolute strength class, rated as a B-class) demon and the main antagonist during the Dark Tournament arc. His signature is the ability to regulate how much of his maximum power he releases, ranging from 0% to 100%. With each increase comes a burst of demon energy and his muscles thicken and enlarge themselves. At full power, his appearance changes drastically, affecting even his skin color, but requires him to feed on souls to maintain such immense power, which leads him to suck out the souls of the weaker creatures in the surrounding area through special appendages on his upper back. He also has the ability to move fast enough to not be seen. Once a great martial arts master and Genkai`s lover, Toguro is psychologically scarred when a demon named Kairin kills all of the students at his dojo. Toguro and Genkai participate in the Dark Tournament and defeat Kairin in the final round. Toguro decides he does not want to age and lose his power, so as his prize for winning he asks to be turned into a demon. 50 years later he returns to the Dark Tournament, challenging Yusuke, hoping he has finally found a fighter worthy of his full 100% power. He dies in their fight and in the afterlife Koenma offers him a lighter sentence for his misdeeds, however, Toguro refuses and requests the harshest sentence there is: 10,000 years of torture in hell for 10,000 cycles, with your soul ceasing to exist afterward (in the English anime dub it is changed to him requesting "limbo"). In the anime television series, Younger Toguro is voiced by Tesshou Genda in Japanese and Dameon Clarke in English.[2] Togashi considers the Toguro brothers to be his favorite villains in the series because they are "fundamentally unrestrained"</description>
<picture>151906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70662" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-18">
<rating votes="4">4.88</rating>
<name>Yukina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70729" type="appears in" update="2014-10-18">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Juri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38808" picture="203413.jpg">Endou Katsuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70730" type="appears in" update="2019-09-29">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Youko Kurama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70747" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Sakyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10353" picture="65354.png">Furuta Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70748" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Bui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70749" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Toguro Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76935" type="appears in" update="2015-08-20">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93515" type="appears in" update="2018-01-30">
<name>Mukuro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mukuro (軀) is one of the three kings of the Makai realm. Early in her childhood, she is sold into slavery to a humanoid demon named Chikou. Her master is continuously cruel to her and used Mukuro as a sex slave. He raped her every year on her birthday. To control her, he implanted a single memory of himself being kind into her mind, which she remembered each time she thought of killing him. When she turned seven years old, she poured acid on herself, hoping that her master would lose interest in her.</description>
<picture>212487.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107185" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<name>Urameshi Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3906" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死んだらオドロいた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surprised to Be Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entre un monde et l`autre</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Morte</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Morte</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Un lucru neaşteptat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shindara Odoroita</title>
<summary>Teen hoodlum Yusuke is having a typical day – until he makes the ultimate sacrifice by diving in front of a speeding car to save a little boy’s life! Is it really time for this brash young man’s existence to come to an end?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3907" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊界のコエンマ! 復活への試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koenma Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Junior, roi des Enfers</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">No Mundo Espiritual - Teste da Ressurreição</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">No Mundo Espiritual - Teste da Ressurreição</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Apariţia lui Koenma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikai no Koenma! Fukkatsu e no Shiren</title>
<summary>After entering the Spirit World, Yusuke meets Koenma, a 700 year-old ruler with the body of a toddler! But there’s no room for laughs, as Koenma gives Yusuke an ordeal to restore his life: hatching a Spirit Beast!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3908" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追いつめられた桑原! 男の誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuwabara: A Promise Between Men</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une amitié à la vie à la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Kuwabara, o promisiune între bărbaţi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oitsumerareta Kuwabara! Otoko no Chikai</title>
<summary>With his rival Yusuke gone, Kuwabara is the new kid to beat, which means he’s making plenty of enemies. Yusuke isn’t fond of this classmate, but if he wants to win back his life, he’ll need to give him a ghostly hand.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3909" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱き炎! 恋人のきずな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Requirements for Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Preuve d`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Dragostea cea mare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsuki Honoo! Koibito no Kizuna</title>
<summary>Spirit World forgot an important question: does anyone even want Yusuke back? And will Yusuke give up the Spirit Beast, his one chance of reviving, when his friends suddenly find themselves in danger?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="3910" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三匹の妖怪! 飛影・蔵馬・剛鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three Monsters</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les trois démons</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Trei monştri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sambiki no Youkai! Hiei, Kurama, Gouki</title>
<summary>Three demon thieves have muscled their way into King Yama’s vault, stealing the three Artifacts of Darkness. Yusuke must recover the artifacts and bring the thieves to justice before they unleash their powers upon the Earth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4101" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蔵馬の秘密?! 母と子のきずな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gouki and Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Gouki si Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurama no Himitsu?! Haha to Ko no Kizuna</title>
<summary>Yusuke’s closing in on Gouki, a monster that’s capturing the souls of children, when the second thief suddenly appears. His name is Kurama, and he asks Yusuke for a surprising favor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4102" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助苦戦! 傷だらけの反撃!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hard Fights for Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une bataille éprouvante</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O luptă grea pentru Yusuke. Un contraatac sângeros</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke Kusen! Kizu Darake no Hangeki</title>
<summary>In his first match of the tournament, Yusuke can’t see a thing in the pitch-black arena, but Kibano is able to follow Urameshi’s every move. If the detective survives Kibano, his next fight – against a ninja – will start immediately!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4103" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">螢子あやうし! 邪眼師・飛影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Eyes of Hiei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Monstre aux Cent Yeux</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Hiei cel cu trei ochi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiko Ayaushi! Jaganshi Hiei</title>
<summary>The ruthless demon Hiei kidnaps Yusuke’s girlfriend, Kayko. Urameshi must retrieve the antidote inside Hiei’s Shadow Sword before Kayko becomes a brainless slave!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4104" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱童あらわる! 桑原無念の敗北</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rando Rises, Kuwabara Falls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La défaite de Kuwabara</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Apariţia lui Rando. Marea înfrângere a lui Kuwabara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rando Arawaru! Kuwabara Munen no Haiboku</title>
<summary>Yusuke, Kuwabara, and Shorin are the only fighters still standing in the Genkai Tournament. Yet Rando has not been found. Could this mean that Shorin is actually Rando? Or is the demon lurking somewhere in the shadows?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4105" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻海の継承者トーナメント開始</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chasse est ouverte !</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Căutarea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genkai no Keishousha Tournament Kaishi</title>
<summary>Aging psychic Genkai is ready to find a student worthy of her Spirit Wave technique, but demonic Rando plans to steal the technique and use it for mass destruction! Yusuke must go undercover and infiltrate Genkai’s compound!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4106" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助VS乱童 乱れとぶ妖術!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke vs. Rando: 99 Attacks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yusuke contre Rando</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yusuke contra Rando. Magie după magie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke vs Rando: Midare Tobu Youjutsu</title>
<summary>As Yusuke’s energy dwindles, the evil Rando reveals his true and monstrous form. Can the injured Yusuke beat the human-hunting demon’s 99 deadly techniques and close the case?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4107" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助復活! 新たなる使命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke`s Back</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour à la vie</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yusuke s-a întors!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke Fukkatsu! Aratanaru Shimei</title>
<summary>Back in the flesh, Yusuke finds he can see supernatural creatures hiding in the living world and quickly hunts down a demon criminal. With this move, he learns his adventure is only beginning. Yusuke is now a Spirit Detective!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4108" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮城の四聖獣! 霊界への挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beasts of Maze Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi du Château Maléfique</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Cele patru bestii sacre din Castelul Labirint</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meikyuu Shiro no Yon Seijuu! Reikai e no Chousen</title>
<summary>Yusuke must take action to stop sinister forces from flooding the earth with demons. With Kuwabara at his side, Urameshi prepares to face four deadly creatures known as the Saint Beasts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4109" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗闇の死闘! 桑原・霊気の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuwabara`s Spirit Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel dans les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Spada spirituală a lui Kuwabara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurayami no Shitou! Kuwabara: Reiki no Ken</title>
<summary>The candidates for Genkai’s apprenticeship have been narrowed to eight. Among them: Yusuke, Kuwabara, and the disguised demon Rando! Genkai announces the final test will be a tournament – fought in total darkness.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6759" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美しきバラの舞! 華麗なる蔵馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Genbu, the Stone Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kurama et le combat de la rose</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Cele patru bestii sacre. O provocare pentru lumea spirituală</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utsukushi Kibara no Mai! Karei Naru Kurama</title>
<summary>Kurama and Hiei join Yusuke and Kuwabara in battle against the Saint Beasts. After the awkward allies struggle through the Gate of Betrayal, they face the first Beast: a giant made of solid stone!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6843" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗黒武術会への招待者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toguro Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour des frères Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Vrem să fim puternici! Intoarcerea fraţilor Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ankoku Bujutsukai e no Shoutaisha</title>
<summary>Spirit World makes a chilling discovery: the Toguro Brothers faked defeat! Now Yusuke must enter a competition run by the criminal world – or everyone he knows will be hunted down and destroyed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6844" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の船出! 地獄の島へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark Tournament Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tournoi des arts martiaux de l`ombre</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Începe competiţia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Funade! Jigoku no Shime e</title>
<summary>The Dark Tournament attracts the most dangerous demons and humans that the world has ever seen. But before the competition begins, Yusuke’s crew must survive the boat ride to Hanging-Neck Island.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6845" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐ろしき強敵! 三鬼衆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Deadly Triad</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Sanki-Shu</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Duşmanul de temut, Sankishuu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osoroshiki Kyouteki! Sankishuu</title>
<summary>Struggling their way to the front gates of Tarukane’s stronghold, Yusuke, Kuwabara, and Botan now face a much greater challenge: three notorious demon fighters known throughout Spirit World as the Triad!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6846" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えろ桑原! 愛の底力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuwabara`s Fight of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pouvoir de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Lupta, Kuwabara! Puterea dragostei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moero Kuwabara! Ai no Sokojikara</title>
<summary>One battle stands in the way of Yukina’s rescue: Yusuke and Kuwabara versus the Toguro Brothers! Elsewhere, Kurama races to stop Hiei, who is entering Tarukane’s stronghold with his own violent agenda!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7442" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の四聖獣・朱雀!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suzaku, Leader of the Beasts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suzaku, le dernier des Shiseiju !</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Suzaku, ultima bestie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Yon Seijuu: Suzaku!</title>
<summary>Humans controlled by the Makai Insects have been sent to hunt down Kayko! Yusuke’s only chance to save her is to destroy the Makai Whistle, which rests in the hand of Suzaku, the final Saint Beast!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7443" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伸びよ霊剣! 桑原・男の勝負</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Byakko, the White Tiger</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat de Kuwabara et son Épée Astrale</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Vino, sabie spirituală! Lupta lui Kuwabara!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nobi yo Reiken! Kuwabara: Otoko no Shoubu</title>
<summary>One of Yusuke’s teammates has been badly injured, and Kuwabara insists on fighting the next enemy all by himself. Before the bickering group can disagree, a roar slices through the castle – the second Saint Beast is set to attack!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7444" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白虎・地獄の雄叫び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Byakko`s Lair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Byakko, le dévoreur d`énergie</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Strigătul de război al tigrului alb</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byakko Jigoku no Osakebi</title>
<summary>Byakko is seemingly defeated – until Yusuke’s team enters the Beast’s secret lair! Does Kuwabara have what it takes to crush Byakko once and for all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7445" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奥義激突! 七人の朱雀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seven Ways to Die</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat maléfique</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Tehnici secrete, dublurile lui Suzaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougi Gekitotsu! Nananin no Sujaku</title>
<summary>As three battles rage simultaneously, Suzaku reveals his most incredible technique of all: multiplying himself for a total of seven deadly Suzakus! Can Yusuke overcome these odds and save the girl he cares about most?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7446" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛影出戦! 切り裂く剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seiryu, the Blue Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat de Hieï</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Hiei luptă! Sabia lui îi taie pe duşmani in bucăţi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiei de Ikusa! Kirisaku Ken</title>
<summary>Two of the four Saint Beasts are dead – or so Yusuke and his team believe! But in the chamber of Seiryu, a Beast who can trap his enemies in ice, an unexpected guest arrives. How can two Beasts in one room be stopped?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7447" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助・命を賭けた反撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke`s Sacrifice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yusuke contre-attaque</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yusuke işi riscă viaţa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke: Inochi o Kaketa Hangeki</title>
<summary>In Maze Castle’s highest tower, Suzaku forces the exhausted Yusuke to his knees. Clearly, there is only one way for the war against the Saint Beasts to end. Yusuke must surrender his life!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9912" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみの美少女・雪菜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lamenting Beauty</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yukina, la princesse triste</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Frumuseţea tristă, Yukina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Bishoujo: Yukina</title>
<summary>The Ice Apparition Yukina, whose tears transform into jewels, has been abducted by Tarukane. Yusuke, Kuwabara, and Botan quickly plot a rescue mission – but why is Hiei not allowed to know?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9913" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな強敵! 鈴駒の秘技</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La première rencontre</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Începe prima luptă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Kyouteki! Suzu Koma no Higi</title>
<summary>Team Urameshi is slated for the first fight against the Rokuyukai Team, but with Yusuke locked in deep slumber, the role of team captain falls on Kuwabara. With Spirit Sword drawn, he volunteers for the first match.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9914" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の使者! 戸愚呂兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Toguro Brothers Gang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les messagers des Ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Mesagerul fraţilor Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Shisha! Toguro Kyoudai</title>
<summary>Yusuke’s Spirit Detective team continues toward Tarukane’s mountain stronghold, facing a small army of grotesque demon guards. And Kuwabara fights with extra passion after declaring he’s in love with Yukina!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9915" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇アイテム・死出の羽衣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cape of No Return</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le point de non retour</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Atuul lui Shishiwakaramu, Promontoriul fărş întoarcere!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami Item: Shide no Hagoromo</title>
<summary>Kuwabara is set to square off against Shishi Wakamaru, but his source of power, Yukina, is nowhere to be found. Shishi’s secret weapon sends Kuwabara through a dimensional portal. What will he find on the other side?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9916" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野望を粉砕! 光りの洗礼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ambition Destroyed: A Trial of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épreuve de la lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O ambiţie distrusă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yabou o Funsai! Hikari no Senrei</title>
<summary>The doctor’s human experiments are clearly fighting against their will! As Yusuke prepares to put them out of their misery, the Masked Fighter intervenes and suggests a peculiar plan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9917" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆烈! 目覚めた妖狐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beast Within</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le réveil de Yoko</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Monstrul a fost trezit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakuretsu! Mezameta Youko</title>
<summary>Kurama finds himself facing the dangerous Karasu. Kurama, believing that it’s his only chance to defeat his eerie opponent, transforms himself into the powerful and equally ruthless Yoko Kurama.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9918" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蔵馬無惨! 死の化粧</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kurama`s Stand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le masque</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Tragedia lui Kurama! Machiajul morţii</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurama Muzan! Shi no Keshou</title>
<summary>The fighters of Team Masho are revealed to be the Shinobi of Spirit World, an ancient ninja sect. Now, thanks to Gama’s curse, Kurama must face the Ice Master Touya without the use of his body or his energy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9919" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻海散る! 50年目の決着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Death of Genkai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mortelles retrouvailles</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Genkai moare. Un final după 50 de ani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi Umi Chiru! 50 Nen Me no Kecchaku</title>
<summary>The history of Genkai and Toguro is finally revealed! Genkai is at the mercy of her former friend, and as Toguro prepares to deliver the final blow, Yusuke races toward the scene of the battle. What will he find when he arrives?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9920" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">究極奥義! ほえろ黒龍波</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wielder of the Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ultime technique</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Atacul suprem, Kokuryu-Ha!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukyoku Ougi! Hoero Kuroryuu Ha</title>
<summary>Hiei unleashes his most powerful attack, the Dragon of the Darkness Flame, but Bui is able to turn the Dragon against his master. Will Hiei be swallowed and destroyed by his own power?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9921" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残された力! 幻海の死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Genkai`s Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force illimitée de Genkai</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Genkai. Luptă cu ultimul strop de putere!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokosareta Chikara! Maboroshi Umi no Shitou</title>
<summary>Unmasked and without the power of her Spirit Wave, Genkai must rely on her wits to survive in the ring. But is the wise woman’s intellect enough to combat the horror of Shishi Wakamaru’s Chorus of a Thousand Skulls?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9922" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血の花を咲かす蔵馬!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flowers of Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Du sang sur le ring</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Flori pe ringul de luptă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi no Hana o Sakasu Kurama!</title>
<summary>In the second match, Kurama’s opponent holds a secret that threatens the person he holds most dear! Can Roto be defeated before the unthinkable happens?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9923" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔闘家・鈴木の挑戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suzuk`s Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi de Suzuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Provocarea luptatorului Suzuka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matouya: Suzuki no Chousen!</title>
<summary>Onji has his work cut out for him when he takes on Kuwabara and Genkai. However, the old man is not who he appears to be, and what lies beneath the surface could spell a major upset for Team Urameshi!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9924" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! ベスト8出そろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day in Waiting</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi des 8 finalistes</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Al optulea învingător</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Best 8 Desorou</title>
<summary>When he’s ambushed by a loose-cannon competitor, Yusuke learns that even quiet moments on Hanging-Neck Island are dangerous. Meanwhile, Hiei faces the consequences of his deadly dragon attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9925" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風使い陣! 嵐の空中戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jin, the Wind Master</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jin, le maître du vent</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Jin, stăpânul vântului. O încăierare pe cinste</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazetsukai Jin! Arashi no Kuuchuusen</title>
<summary>Jin, Team Masho’s fourth member, is a fast-talking Master of Wind who hates authority. He identifies with Yusuke more than any guy ever has, but with everything at stake, they must lay their friendship aside.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9926" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波瀾の決勝戦開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beginning of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En route pour la finale</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Un final memorabil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haran no Kesshousenkaishi!</title>
<summary>Each team must take on an extra member in order to compete in the tournament finals. Who are the two new fighters and what could they possibly bring to their new teams?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9927" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻海からの最大の試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke`s Final Test</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ultime épreuve de Genkai</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Încercarea suprema</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi Umi kara no Saidai no Shiren</title>
<summary>As his team prepares for the semi-finals, Yusuke is taken to a cave in the woods where Genkai will give him his final test. Is Yusuke’s soul pure enough to handle the intense mental and physical trial?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9928" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">粉砕! 幽助怒りの鉄拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crushing Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La colère de Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Pumnul nimicitor al lui Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funsai! Yuusuke Ikari no Tekken</title>
<summary>Yusuke tries to step in for the unconscious Kurama, but the crooked tournament committee announces that Kurama must remain. Can Yusuke overcome the rule-makers, save Kurama, and fight the last three opponents himself?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9929" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決死の蔵馬! 最後の手段</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoko`s Magic</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand sacrifice</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ultima armă a lui Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kesshi no Kuraba! Saigo no Shudan</title>
<summary>Karasu is set to take the victory! Taking his own life into his hands, Kurama prepares to sacrifice his life energy to defeat the demon. But with no life energy remaining, Kurama may stay down forever.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9930" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未完の奥義・炎殺黒龍波</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragon of the Darkness Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">le feu du dragon noir</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O tehnică secretă neperfectată</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikan no Ougi: Honooya Kuroryuuha</title>
<summary>Hiei takes on Rokuyukai’s leader, Zeru, whose explosive fire attacks ravage the stadium. Hiei must resort to an unbelievable technique, one that could take his life as well: he must summon the power of a dragon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9931" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脅威! 鎧を外した武威</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beneath Bui`s Armor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère de l`armure</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">E în pericol! Bui ii scoate armura!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui! Yoroi o Hazushita Take Takeshi</title>
<summary>After a disappointing verdict is handed down in the Kurama versus Karasu match, Hiei seeks to recover from the setback in the ring with Bui. Will the power lurking beneath Bui’s armor be too much for him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9932" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄! 黒桃太郎の変身</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Many Faces, Many Forms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La transformation de Momotaro</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Teribila transformare a lui Kurumomotaro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu! Kuro Momotarou no Henshin</title>
<summary>Hiei’s attacks have proven useless against Kuro Momotaro, and as his raging opponent prepares to make a third and final transformation, Hiei prepares to join his shattered sword on the arena floor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9933" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒り爆発! 桑原の反撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakyo`s Proposal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand pari de Sakyô</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Propunerea lui Sakyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikari Bakuhatsu! Kuwabara no Hangeki</title>
<summary>Before Yusuke’s grudge match with the younger Toguro can begin, intrigue at Team Toguro culminates in a shocking proposal from Sakyo – and an even more shocking response from Koenma!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9934" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の忍・魔性使いチーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Master of Disguise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`équipe de Masho, les ninjas des Ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Războinicul nopţii. Echipa Masho</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Nin: Mahoutsukai Team</title>
<summary>Team Urameshi must face Team Masho, but a scheme by the team’s owner ensnares Hiei and the Masked Fighter before the fight! With Kuwabara injured, Yusuke and Kurama will have to take this entire team alone!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9935" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覆面の正体?! 美しき戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glimpse Beneath the Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un guerrier fascinant</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Adevărul din spatele măştii, un luptător chipeş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukumen no Shoutai!? Utsukushiki Senshi</title>
<summary>During a three-on-three battle, a rip on the Masked Fighter’s headdress gives a surprising peek into the warrior’s true identity! But there’s little time to ponder the ramifications, as Kuwabara now refuses to fight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9936" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決死の桑原! 愛の突撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Matter of Love and Death</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Disperarea lui Kuwabara. Puterea dragostei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kesshi no Kuwabara! Ai no Totsugeki</title>
<summary>Team Masho’s leader looks impossible to beat, but as Yukina tries desperately to enter the stadium, Kuwabara will have to find the strength to save his team. He’s Team Urameshi’s only hope!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9937" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイフエッジデスマッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knife Edge Death-Match</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontre mortelle</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Pe viaţă şi pe moarte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Knife Edge Death-Match</title>
<summary>Yusuke and Chu, both drained of their Spirit Energy, struggle to win the first round of the Dark Tournament for their team. They agree to settle it with a Knife Edge Death-Match, an intense and fatal arena of combat.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9938" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の前! 悲しみを越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overcoming Grief</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au-delà de la tristesse</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Revino-ţi, Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Zen! Kanashimi o Koete</title>
<summary>Yusuke’s emotions over the death of Genkai are like no trial he has ever faced. There is no time to waste – his team must move on and overcome their despair.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9939" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊光弾! 意外な決着?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reverse Decisions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un résultat inattendu</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Reikoudan. Un rezultat neaşteptat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikoudan! Igai na Kecchaku?!</title>
<summary>When Yusuke realizes his regular attacks won’t help him against Jin, he decides to try the Spirit Wave. But even if he can somehow execute the move and defeat his opponent, will the corrupt Tournament Committee let him win?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9940" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛影連戦! 撃て黒龍波!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hiei Battles On</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`onde du dragon noir</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Hiei continuă lupta! Foloseşte lovitura dragonului negru!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiei Rensen! Ute Kuroryuu wa</title>
<summary>Hiei faces Kuro Momotaro, an opponent with the ability to prevent certain attacks by adapting his body. Hiei’s only chance lies in a dangerous technique that could easily finish his opponent – but at the cost of his own life!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9941" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝率0.05%の死闘!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Percentage of Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour de la bataille</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Marea bătălie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouritsu 0.05% no Shitou!</title>
<summary>Round two of the tournament arrives and Team Urameshi must face Dr. Ichigaki’s fighters, a group with a habit of chopping off their opponent’s heads! Will Yusuke be the doctor’s next guinea pig?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9942" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の盗賊! 妖狐・蔵馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary Bandit: Yoko Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le légendaire Yoko Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Legendaru bandit, Yu-Ku Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Touzoku! Youko Kurama</title>
<summary>After fifteen years in his borrowed human form, the demon Yoko Kurama has returned. Ura Urashima’s evil plan causes the ultra-powerful Spirit Fox to reveal his true power. What could this mean for Team Urameshi?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9943" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覆面戦士の厳しき素顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Masked Fighter Revealed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le visage du guerrier masqué</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Frumosul chip al luptătorului mascat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukumen Senshi no Kibishiki Sugao</title>
<summary>With his Spirit Beast finally hatching, Yusuke faces the possibility of it swallowing his soul forever. And there’s yet another surprise in store for Urameshi, when the true identity of the Masked Fighter is at last exposed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9944" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よいどれ戦士! 酎の酔拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stumbling Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La technique de l`ivrogne</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Luptătorul turmentat, Shaku Suiken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoidore Senshi! Chu no Yoiken</title>
<summary>Yusuke jumps out of his slumber, ready for the final fight against a new fighter named Chu. He’s rude, he’s crude –and he claims to be Team Rokuyukai’s true leader.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9945" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戸愚呂兄の不気味な影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shadow of Elder Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un adversaire terrifiant</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Umbra ciudată a lui Toguro senior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toguro Kei no Bukimi na Kage</title>
<summary>After hearing of Genkai’s death, Kuwabara strikes Toguro with the Trial Sword and splits the demon in half! The arena watches in horror as the evil Toguro rises from the floor unharmed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9946" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の対決! 戸愚呂の影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arch-Rivals</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour de Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Un adversar foarte puternic. Umbra lui Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Taiketsu! Toguro no Kage</title>
<summary>The strengths of Team Toguro are revealed in full as they take the arena floor. Meanwhile, Yusuke is caught in a deep slumber as Genkai heads off to face her former partner in battle – and settle a 50 year old score!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9950" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戸愚呂100%の恐怖!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toguro`s Full Power</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Toguro monte en puissance !</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Toguro. Lupta 100%</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toguro 100% no Kyoufu!</title>
<summary>Yusuke removes the Spirit Cuffs before launching an attack at his nemesis. But Toguro has powered up to his top level and stares down Yusuke’s Spirit Blast.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9951" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闘技場と共に消える野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Out with a Bang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les adieux de M. Sakyô</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ambiţiile cad odată cu stadionul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tougijou to Tomo ni Kieru Yabou</title>
<summary>Yusuke must begin to cope with the loss of his best friend at the hands of Toguro. Meanwhile, after Sakyo asks Koenma to take his life, the billionaire unveils his final plan: destroying the stadium with everyone still inside!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9952" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戸愚呂の償い・一番の望み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toguro`s Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dernier voeu de Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Remuşcările echipei Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toguro no Tsugunai: Ichiban no Nozomi</title>
<summary>Team Urameshi prepares to return to the world of the living and leave their fallen mentor and friend behind. But, far away, a chance encounter between two former allies offers a hint of things to come.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9953" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなるプロローグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to the Living World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nouveau prologue</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Noul prolog. Începutul următoarei lupte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata naru Prologue</title>
<summary>Yusuke falls into the hands of powerful new adversaries, forcing Kuwabara to round up the old gang in order to stage a rescue attempt!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9954" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐るべき真実! 新たな謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Genkai`s Ruse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le véritable objectif</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Adevărul îngrozitor. Încă un mister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osorubeki Shinjitsu! Arata na Nazo</title>
<summary>The gang reaches the captive Yusuke, but Kido has a final game to play with the Spirit Detective. One of his friends is an imposter, and Yusuke has only minutes to determine which one it is! With his decision made, Yusuke attacks!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9955" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助! 限界への悲しい試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke`s Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une puissance sans limites !</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yusuke, o misiune tristă. La maxim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke! Genkai e no Kanashii Shiren</title>
<summary>Toguro begins to suck the souls of the spectators in order to enrage the fallen Urameshi and bring out his full power. But Toguro soon learns that the best way to provoke Yusuke is to kill one of his friends!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9956" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四次元屋敷にひそむ罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Setting the Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le manoir de la 4e dimension</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Capcane ascunse în Yojigen-Yashiki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zon Jigen Yashiki ni Hisomu Wana</title>
<summary>At the Rokurokubi Estates, Kaitou explains the rules of his territory to Kuwabara, Kurama, and Hiei. Can the three warriors be of any use in a place where all forms of violence are strictly prohibited?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9957" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の対決! 嵐の大将戦開始</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke vs. Toguro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat des chefs</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yusuke contra Toguro. Începe lupta finală</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Taiketsu! Arashi no Taishousen Kaishi</title>
<summary>The ultimate showdown between Yusuke and Toguro finally begins, and Urameshi reveals the power he inherited from Genkai with a colossal blast of his Spirit Gun. Is it enough to bring down Toguro once and for all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9958" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">禁句(タブー)のパワー! 蔵馬の頭脳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of Taboo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ruse de Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Puterea tabuu-lui. Întelepciunea lui Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taboo no Power! Zouba no Zunou</title>
<summary>Kurama places his soul on the line and issues a challenge to Kaitou: one by one, the letters of the alphabet will become taboo. If any of the taboo sounds are uttered, the speaker will face a terrible penalty.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9959" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘決着! 最後のフルパワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toguro`s Desire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`explication finale</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Finalul luptei. La putere maxima</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou Kecchaku! Saigo no Full Power</title>
<summary>After Yusuke powers up to the same level as Toguro, the demon must power up to 120% of his capacity. Can either fighter, each completely devoid of any remaining energy, survive to claim the prize?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9960" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫り来る恐怖! 魔界の扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La porte des ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Eroarea. Poarta spre lumea spiritelor rele</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semari Kuru Kyoufu! Makai no Tobira</title>
<summary>Between the Living World and the Demon World, a tunnel is being carved that could usher in darkness and chaos. In a bold move, Sensui begins his search for the person that will finally allow him to complete the tunnel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9961" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍び寄るドクターの魔の手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Doctor`s Disease</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`effrayant docteur Kamiya</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Capcana doctorului</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobiyoru Doctor no Manote</title>
<summary>Yusuke’s mind reader, Murota, is shot while attempting to weed out the psychic responsible for the tunnel between worlds. When the gang takes Murota to the hospital, new dangers appear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9962" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出撃! ダークエンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Divide and Conquer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`assaut du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Sortie, îngerul întunericului!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugeki! Dark Angel</title>
<summary>Yusuke and Sensui continue their battle, but despite all his efforts, Yusuke is not able to prevent the dark detective’s kidnapping of Kuwabara.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9963" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊界探偵の黒い過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensui`s Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un passé sanglant</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Trecutul întunecat al unui detectiv din lumea spirituală</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikai Tantei no Kuroi Kako</title>
<summary>Yusuke learns the dark secret behind Sensui’s traumatic fall from Spirit Detective to the one who would wipe out all humanity. After hearing the truth, Urameshi begins his quest to defeat the fallen Spirit Detective once and for all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9964" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テリトリーを打ちやぶれ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sleep, Doctor, Sleep</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et de un !</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Încălcarea teritoriului</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Territory o Uchi Yabure!!</title>
<summary>The Doctor, a super-strong human with immense psychic powers, has infected the entire hospital with a deadly virus. In order to save his friends, Yusuke may have no choice but to destroy the wretched creature.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9965" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲームマスター脅威の実力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If You Could Play Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force cachée de l`adversaire</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Asul din mâna lui Amamuna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game Master Kyoui no Jitsuryoku</title>
<summary>Yusuke’s team must win three more rounds to defeat the Game Master and move on to Sensui’s lair. The hole to the Demon World is rapidly expanding. Can they make it there in time to prevent the end of the world?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9966" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シーマン・雨に潜む罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caught in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Embuscade sous la pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Seaman. Capcana ascunsă in ploaie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seaman: Ame ni Hisomu Wana</title>
<summary>Yusuke has defeated the Doctor, one of the seven psychics trying to forge a tunnel between worlds. Somewhere in Mushiyori City, six more – Game Master, Sniper, Gourmet, Sea Man, Gate Keeper, and Black Angel – remain.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9967" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桑原復活?! 目覚めた力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuwabara: Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chapitre noir</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Kuwabara s-a ântors! Puterea renăscută!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuwabara Fukkatsu?! Mezameta Tsutomu</title>
<summary>Kuwabara is struggling to keep up with Sea Man’s power – and with Kurama, Yusuke, and Genkai nowhere to be seen, it appears no one is coming to the rescue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9968" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助激走! 桑原を救え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Human Race</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Course contre la montre</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yusuke aleargă cu mânie! Salvarea lui Kuwabara!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke Gekisou! Kuwabara o Sukue!</title>
<summary>As Yusuke continues his chase of Sensui, the unbelievable Sniper appears. As Genkai and the rest of the team follow, can Yusuke escape Sniper’s endless barrage, reach Sensui, and save Kuwabara?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9969" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">洞窟の中のゲームワールド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let the Games Begin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un univers virtuel</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Lumea jocurilor din peşteră</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doukutsu no Naka no Game World</title>
<summary>When Yusuke, Kurama, Hiei, and Mitarai enter the Game Master’s territory, they’re forced into a twisted game where everyone must play by the rules in order to survive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9970" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔界の使者! 七人の敵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reader</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le visage de l`ennemi</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Mesagerul din lumea de apoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makai no Shisha! Nananin no Teki</title>
<summary>The Spirit Detective’s best chance to uncover the truth behind the tunnel lies with the mind reader, Murota. But mere hours after entering Mushiyori City, Yusuke and team find themselves being hunted by an unseen evil.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9971" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">刃霧の標的! 死紋十字斑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moving Target</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pouvoir du tireur</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ţintele lui Hagiri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakiri no Hyouteki! Shimonjuu Jimura</title>
<summary>Hiei has finally returned to his former teammates to join in their crusade, but will that be enough to free Kuwabara before Gourmet can consume his power and tear the Kekkai Barrier to shreds?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9972" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒の時! バトル再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waking the Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le réveil d`un Mazoku</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Renaşterea. Incă o bătălie!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei no Toki! Battle Futatabi</title>
<summary>Kuwabara, Kurama, and Hiei charge into the tunnel in an effort to rid all worlds of Sensui forever. Meanwhile, King Yama’s soldiers arrive to take Yusuke’s body away in order to ensure he is never revived.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9973" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残された手段! 蔵馬の決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game Over</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une décision héroïque</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ultimele mijloace. Decizia lui Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokosareta Shudan! Zouba no Ketsudan</title>
<summary>With only two hours until the tunnel opens and unleashes a horde of demons upon the world of the living, Kurama steps forth to battle Game Master for the right to move on to Sensui’s lair.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9974" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予感! 全てが止まる時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death of a Spirit Detective</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Requiem pour Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Prevestirea. Când totul se opreşte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokan! Subete ga Tomaru Toki</title>
<summary>Filled with rage, Kuwabara watches helplessly as Yusuke struggles in battle against Sensui. He manages to free Kurama and Hiei, but it appears Yusuke Urameshi is doomed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9975" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蔵馬の怒り! 正体は誰だ?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kurama`s Anger, Gourmet`s Guest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La colère de Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Furia lui Kurama. Dezvăluirea identităţii</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuraba no Ikari! Shoutai wa Dare Da?!</title>
<summary>Yusuke’s gang reaches Sensui’s lair, but their battle to save humanity is just beginning. As the opening to Demon World widens rapidly, an old nemesis appears – and he’s got Kurama in his sights.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9976" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友の意志を継げ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attempting Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Îndeplinirea dorinţei unui prieten</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo no Ishi o Tsuge!</title>
<summary>Kuwabara, Kurama, and Hiei unleash their most devastating attacks on Sensui, who retreats within the tunnel. Meanwhile, King Yama reveals a dark secret to Botan. What does he know about Yusuke that the others do not?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9977" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エピローグ! 明日へ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Topside</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les uns et les autres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Epilog pentru ziua de mâine!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Epilogue! Ashita e!</title>
<summary>When Yusuke’s team returns topside, King Yama’s soldiers arrive with orders to destroy Yusuke once and for all.  Could this be the end? How much energy does the Spirit Detective have after his exhausting battle with Sensui?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9978" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助の運命・危険の足音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yusuke`s Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le destin rattrape Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Destinul lui Yusuke. Paşi periculoşi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke no Unmei: Kiken no Ashioto</title>
<summary>Yusuke Urameshi suffers from a recurring nightmare that he just can’t shake. In order to figure out the deeper meaning behind the bizarre dreams, Genkai sends Yusuke to the home of a former Spirit Detective.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9979" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔界へ! 父との対面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to Demon World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontre avec Raizen</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Plecarea în lumea spiritelor rele. Întâlnirea cu tata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makai e! Chichi to no Taimen</title>
<summary>Control of Demon World is divided among three rulers: Raizen, Yomi, and Mukuro. From his deathbed, Raizen invites his descendant, Yusuke, to return to Demon World to train – and challenges him to a battle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9980" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れ・それぞれの旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departing Living World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au revoir mes amis</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">La revedere! Toată lumea pleaca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare: Sorezore no Tabidachi</title>
<summary>Two kings of Demon World offer Kurama and Hiei dangerous propositions. Meanwhile, Yusuke learns that the only thing more difficult than making an irreversible decision is convincing Kayko that everything will be all right.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9981" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘れ得ぬ記憶・誕生の時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haunted by the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenir de naissance</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Amintire de neuitat. Naşterea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasure Enu Kioku: Tanjou no Toki</title>
<summary>After years in exile, Hiei finally returns to his homeland with one thing on his mind: revenge. But to complete his mission, Hiei must first survive an encounter with yet another demon from his past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9982" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">究極の戦い! 魔族の証</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Proof</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`étoffe des combattants</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Lupta supremă. Dovada Ma-Zoku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukyoku no Tatakai! Mazoku no Akashi</title>
<summary>Although Yusuke’s skill and strength have increased, he is still clumsy with his new abilities. Unfortunately, there is no time to adjust and practice his new powers – Sensui is ready for their final confrontation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9983" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着! 魔界の死闘!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensui`s End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shinobu tire sa révérence</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Dovada finală. Viaţă sau moarte în lumea de apoi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku! Makai no Shitou!</title>
<summary>As the battle against Sensui concludes, Koenma tells Yusuke that he must choose between Demon World and Living World. Without hesitation, Yusuke makes his decision!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9984" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の訪問者・深まる謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three Strangers, Three Kings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les étranges visiteurs des ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Vizitatorii întunericului. Misterul se amplifică!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Houmonsha: Fukamaru Nazo</title>
<summary>Yusuke learns that his ancestor is a king in Demon World! Unless Urameshi travels to Demon World soon, the balance of power could shift and spell the end of humanity’s reign at the top of the food chain.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9985" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霊界探偵・宿命の一騎討ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spirit Detective Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel des détectives</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Detectivii lumii spirituale. Lupta om la om</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reikai Tantei: Shukumei no Ichiki Uchi</title>
<summary>The tunnel to Demon World is opening. Can Yusuke’s team still save the human race? Only a dramatic showdown between past and present Spirit Detectives will reveal the truth!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9986" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽助苦戦! 決定的な差</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Difference Maker</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dure réalité pour Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Suferinţa lui Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusuke Kusen! Ketteiteki na Sa</title>
<summary>The battle between Yusuke and Sensui continues, and Yusuke learns he is no match for the former Spirit Detective. As Sensui prepares the finishing blow, aid comes in a most unexpected package.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9987" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コエンマ・覚悟の魔封環!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Power Between the Teeth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Junior et l`Anneau Anti-Maléfices</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Koenma, fatalul Maffukan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koenma: Kakugo no Maffukan!</title>
<summary>As Itsuki explains more about the bizarre Sensui, Koenma prepares to use his most powerful weapon to create a barrier that may stop the demons from flooding Living World.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9988" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仙水・解き放たれた聖光気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The True Face of Sensui</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Energie Divine</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Sensui. Eliberarea lui Seikou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensui: Tokihanatareta Hijiri Hikariki</title>
<summary>Koenma’s tactics have saved Yusuke for now, but Yusuke won’t allow the Prince of Spirit World to use his pacifier.  While they discuss their next move, the terrible gateway between Demon World and Living World opens.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9989" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蔵馬, 過去との決別</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Kurama</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`adieu au passé</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Kurama. Adio trecutului</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurama, Kako to no Ketsubetsu</title>
<summary>Kurama must face Shigure in the ring, and as tempers and anxieties flare, the resurgence of Yoko Kurama begins! Will Kurama find a way to keep his anger from taking over?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9990" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">意外な提案・魔界の変動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Every Demon for Himself</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La proposition de Yusuke</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O propunere neaşteptată. Schimbarea lumii de apoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Igai na Teian: Makai no Hendou</title>
<summary>Raizen’s death has upset the balance of power in Demon World. As Mukuro and Yomi prepare their next move, Yusuke arrives at a brilliant decision that just might preserve the peace. But at what cost?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9991" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フォーエバー! 幽遊白書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`héritage</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Yu Yu Hakusho! Pentru totdeauna!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Forever! Yuu Yuu Hakusho</title>
<summary>Kuwabara is studying hard for his college entrance exams, but nothing could prepare him for what happens when he arrives at a mysterious meeting with Genkai. One after the other, the old gang shows up – but where is Yusuke?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9992" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父の遺言・遠い日の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inheritance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort de Raizen</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Dorinţa tatălui meu. O amintire de preţ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi no Yuigon: Tooi Hi no Omoi</title>
<summary>It’s been nearly a year since Yusuke, Hiei, and Kurama arrived in Demon World. With the former teammates in high positions on conflicting sides, can Yusuke prevent an inevitable clash and keep Demon World at peace?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9993" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔界大戦・予選開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Preliminaries</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les épreuves éliminatoires</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Turneul lumii de apoi. Prima partidă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makai Taisen: Yosen Kaishi!</title>
<summary>By embracing Yusuke’s unlikely proposal, Yomi and Mukuro have secured peace for the moment. Nonetheless, the battle to control Demon World must begin. Who will win the tournament and grasp complete power?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9994" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闘う親子! 黄泉と修羅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of Father and Son</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entre père et fils</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Bătălia dintre tată şi fiu. Yomi vs Shura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakau Oyako! Yomi to Shura</title>
<summary>As the preliminary round of the tournament draws to a close, one match between a father and son still rages on. Before the competition can continue, the vigor of youth must defeat the patience of age.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9995" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! 夢に賭けた男たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon World Tournament Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les déceptions du premier tour</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O luptă dură. Visul fiecărui luptător</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Yume ni Kaketa Otoko-tachi</title>
<summary>As the main bouts of the Demon World tournament get underway, it looks like some of the fighters’ motivations for entering aren’t exactly what they seemed. They all have their eyes on one warrior as the prize – Yusuke.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9996" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明かされる邪眼の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Jagan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret du 3e œil</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Secretul lui Jagan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akasareru Yokoshima Me no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Now that Hiei has become strong enough to easily slay A-Class Demons, Mukuro calls forth an even tougher foe: the demon that implanted Hiei’s Jagan Eye! Does Hiei have the strength – and desire – to survive the encounter?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9997" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の力・これが全てだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Reason to Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le doute s`immisce</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Puterea mea. Asta e tot ce am</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Chikara: Kore ga Subeta Da!</title>
<summary>As the Demon World Tournament rages on, Yusuke finds himself staring down Yomi. Both warriors have their own reasons for competing, but one soon learns he may not have any reason to continue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9998" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! 飛影とムクロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love and War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La confrontation entre Hiei et Mokuro</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">O luptă pe viaţă. Hiei şi Mukuro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Hiei to Mukuro</title>
<summary>Hiei steps into the ring against Mukuro, who proves willing to exploit the horrors of Hiei’s past. Will this give the shackled fighter the advantage? In order to survive, Hiei prepares to unleash his ultimate weapon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9999" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔界盗賊・千年目の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion of the Bandits</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après mille années de séparation</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Bandiţii din lumea de apoi. După 1000 de ani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makai Touzoku: Sennenme no Saikai</title>
<summary>Yomi, one of the three Kings of Demon World, has summoned Kurama to his inner sanctum. Just as Yusuke and Hiei were forced to face their demons, Kurama must now confront the secrets of his own past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10000" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖狐変化! 忍び寄る殺意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Torn Between Identities</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La force meurtrière de Yoko</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Transformarea lui Youko. Îndemnul de a ucide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youko Henka! Shinobiyoru Satsui</title>
<summary>Yomi has forced Kurama to serve as his advisor, but the alliance is hardly stable due to the ancient hatred they share. Meanwhile, some familiar faces from the past return for one more shot against Yusuke!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10001" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着! 激闘の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Closure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`unification des ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Decizia finală</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku! Gekitou no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Yusuke awakens from his fight with Yomi to discover all but one fighter has been eliminated! Demon World has its new King! Who emerged victorious? And what does it mean for the three worlds?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42379" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42380" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118519" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120463" update="2010-07-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120465" update="2010-07-29">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Interview 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120466" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120467" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120469" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120470" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120471" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120472" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120473" update="2012-01-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120474" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像白書~暗黒武術会の章~上巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Hakusho: Dark Tournament, Vol. 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Hakusho: Ankoku Bujutsukai no Shou - Joukan</title>
<summary>Skip to the brawling greatness and relive the epic battles of the Dark Tournament with a full recap of the best Team Urameshi fighting scenes including the epic bout between Genki and Toguro!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120475" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像白書~暗黒武術会の章~下巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Hakusho: Dark Tournament, Vol. 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Hakusho: Ankoku Bujutsukai no Shou - Gekan</title>
<summary>Experience a full recap of the best Team Urameshi fight scenes! Featuring the bruising match between Yusuke and Chu, a tough brawl against the Dr. Ichigaki Team, and watch Hiei call upon the flames of the Demon Realm against Zeru.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120476" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像白書II~幽助の章~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Hakusho II: The Yusuke Chapters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Hakusho II: Yuusuke no Shou</title>
<summary>After getting dumped by his girlfriend Keiko, Yusuke travels to the Demon Realm for a showdown with Yomi. Even after the break-up, Yusuke promises that he will return in three years time to take her hand in marriage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120477" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像白書II~蔵馬の章~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Hakusho II: The Kurama Chapters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Hakusho II: Kurama no Shou</title>
<summary>During a quest to steal three spirit realm treasures, Kurama and Hiei meet Yusuke for the first time. A shift to the mysterious origin story of Kurama and a heated battle versus Shigure shows the true heart of this rose-whipping fighter!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120478" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像白書II~桑原の章~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Hakusho II: The Kuwabara Chapters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Hakusho II: Kuwabara no Shou</title>
<summary>The reckless Kuwabara reminisces about a first encounter with Yusuke while being held captive by Shinobu. Will his anger be enough to power his escape and help Yusuke defeat Shinobu?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120479" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像白書II~飛影の章~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Hakusho II: The Hiei Chapters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizou Hakusho II: Hiei no Shou</title>
<summary>During a stress-relieving sparring match, Yusuke and Hiei come face to face with a pair of stout beasts from the Demon Realm. After doing away with the monsters, the story turns to Hiei and his mysterious origin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120480" update="2010-07-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Tokuten PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120481" update="2010-07-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Eizou Tokuten PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189225" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Dream Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu Mu Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189226" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Dream Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu Mu Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189227" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Dream Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu Mu Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189228" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Dream Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu Mu Hakusho: Nightmare Hakusho 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
