<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3127" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-06-21</startdate>
<enddate>1996-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Blue Seed 1.5</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブルーシード 1.5</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="385" type="Sequel">Blue Seed 2</anime>
<anime id="644" type="Prequel">Blue Seed</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="872" type="Original Work">Takada Yuuzou</name>
</creators>
<description>A two-episode retelling of the Blue Seed storyline with one episode from http://anidb.net/ch35064 [Momiji]`s point of view and the other from http://anidb.net/ch35065 [Kusanagi]`s.
Note: Released as two separate VHS tapes in May of 1996 and later as a single LD in July of the same year.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="66">5.38</permanent>
<temporary count="67">6.76</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4867.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7398</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3952</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3620</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2079" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-05">
<name>magatama</name>
<description>Magatama are curved beads which first appeared in Japan during the Joumon period. They are often found inhumed in mounded tumulus graves as offerings to deities. They continued to be popular with the ruling elites throughout the Kofun Period of Japan, and are often romanticised as indicative of the Yamato Dynasty of Japan. They are mainly made of jade, agate, quartz, talc, and jasper. Some consider them to be an Imperial symbol, although in fact ownership was widespread throughout all the chieftainships of Kofun Period Japan. It is believed that magatama were popularly worn as jewels for decoration, in addition to their religious meanings. In this latter regard they were later largely replaced by Buddhist prayer beads in the Nara period. In modern Japan, the magatama`s shape of a sphere with a flowing tail is a common visual representation of the human spirit.
The most important magatama is the Yasakani no Magatama, which is part of the Imperial Regalia of Japan, added some time around the Heian period. The Yasakani no Magatama stands for benevolence, and is one of the three items used in the ceremony of imperial ascension. In Japanese mythology, the jewels, along with the mirror, were hung on the tree outside of Amaterasu`s cave to lure her out. It is believed to be a necklace composed of jade magatama stones instead of a solitary gem as depicted in popular culture. It is believed to be enshrined in Kokyo, the Japanese Imperial Palace.
The consensus among Japanese archaeologists is that magatama originated in Joumon Japan before spreading to the Asian continent through the Korean peninsula. It is claimed that the earliest Korean prehistoric magatama date to the Early Mumun (post-850 BC) and are generally found in the southern part of peninsula in proximity to Japan. Charles Keally, an archaeologist who has conducted research on magatama, states: The magatama`s origins are more controversial. These curved jewels of jadeite are common in Kofun Period burials, and they are common also in Korean sites of the same age. But magatama are found in Yayoi sites, too, and unquestionable true magatama are reported also in Jomon sites in Tohoku as early as about 1000 B.C., long before true magatama appeared in Korea. The magatama is found also on early Korean royal gold crowns and has long been considered a sign of royalty in Korea as well as being a connection with Shamanistic elements.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>62069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35064" type="main character in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="10">6.56</rating>
<name>Fujimiya Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35065" type="main character in" update="2011-07-31">
<rating votes="4">7.64</rating>
<name>Kusanagi Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="11325" update="2011-07-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>1996-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Theater - Dancing Little Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="77826" update="2010-04-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="77827" update="2010-04-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
