<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="313" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-08-06</startdate>
<enddate>1994-08-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Street Fighter II: The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Street Fighter 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Street Fighter II: O Filme</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Уличен Боец 2: Филмът</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SF2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ストリートファイターII</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Street Fighter II: The Animated Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Street Fighter II - The Animated Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Street Fighter II - Le film</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Уличный боец - 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Uliczny wojownik II</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Street Fighter II</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Οι Μαχητές των Δρόμων 2</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">STREET FIGHTER 2 - THE MOVIE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6283" type="Sequel">Street Fighter IV: Aratanaru Kizuna</anime>
<anime id="772" type="Alternative Setting">Street Fighter 2 V</anime>
<anime id="9862" type="Other">Street Fighter II: Yomigaeru Fujiwara-kyou - Toki o Kaketa Fighter-tachi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325382">The only production worthy of its title. A classic movie of a classic game.

This is the anime i`ve re-watched most times in my life. Had it on VHS and upgraded it many times since.

Highly recommended, not only for Street Fighter fans!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="1283" type="Original Plan">Capcom</name>
<name id="3665" type="Direction">Sugii Gisaburou</name>
<name id="1761" type="Character Design">Murase Shuukou</name>
<name id="774" type="Animation Work">Group Tac</name>
<name id="2309" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>An evil crime syndicate known as Shadow Law is trying to gather the greatest street fighters in the world in order to to ensure the security of their presidential candidate who may win the next American election. The leader of Shadow Law is none other than the powerful http://anidb.net/ch85071 [Vega]. Through psychic manipulation, he is able to force people to do his bidding. Little does street fighter http://anidb.net/ch5047 [Ryuu] know that Bison is after him, because of his extraordinary fighting abilities. Meanwhile Interpol and the American Military are trying to devise a plan to destroy Shadow Law.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1260">4.85</permanent>
<temporary count="1272">6.82</temporary>
<review count="2">5.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>6409.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2302</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1362</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>390</identifier>
<identifier>mrlezl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Street_Fighter_II:_The_Animated_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ストリートファイターII_MOVIE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>684</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>street-fighter-ii-the-animated-movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DV3DP4X</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2456" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-02">
<name>ki manipulation</name>
<description>Ki, also chi or qi, is believed to be a vital force forming part of any living thing. It literally translates as "breath", "air", or "gas", and figuratively as "material energy", "life force", or "energy flow", and it is the central underlying principle in traditional Chinese medicine and Chinese martial arts.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2682" parentid="2812" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Nevada</name>
<description>Nevada is a state in the western, mountain west, and southwestern regions of the United States. Nevada is the 7th most extensive, the 35th most populous, and the 9th least densely populated of the 50 United States. Over two-thirds of Nevada`s people live in one single county, Clark County, which contains the Las Vegas–Paradise metropolitan area, where the state`s three largest incorporated cities are located. Nevada`s capital is Carson City.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214274.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2684" parentid="2812" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>New York</name>
<description>The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States. New York City is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2928" parentid="2682" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Las Vegas</name>
<description>Las Vegas is the most populous city in the U.S. state of Nevada and the county seat of Clark County. Las Vegas is an internationally renowned major resort city for gambling, shopping, and fine dining. The city bills itself as The Entertainment Capital of the World, and is famous for its consolidated casino–hotels and associated entertainment.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5091" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>India</name>
<description>India, officially the Republic of India, is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area, the second-most populous country, and the most populous democracy in the world. It is bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest, and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast. It shares land borders with Pakistan to the west; China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the northeast; and Myanmar (Burma) and Bangladesh to the east.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5047" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="51">9.01</rating>
<name>Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryu is a pretty simple guy. He wears the same outfit wherever he goes - white gi, black belt, red headband, period - and he has the same aim wherever he goes as well. He wants to fight whoever he thinks can make him a stronger fighter.</description>
<picture>21382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2043" picture="21383.jpg">Shimizu Koujirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5076" type="main character in" update="2015-10-20">
<rating votes="9">8.97</rating>
<name>Guile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2080" picture="43095.jpg">Tsukayama Masane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13766" type="main character in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="26">9.27</rating>
<name>Ken Masters</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Street Fighter 2 V voice actor: 羽賀研二</description>
<picture>40634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33853" picture="93213.jpg">Haga Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13767" type="main character in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="69">7.95</rating>
<name>Chun-Li</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9823" picture="36572.jpg">Fujitani Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13769" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-20">
<rating votes="5">6.94</rating>
<name>Mike Bison</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mike Bison is depicted as an African American boxer wearing blue trunks with white trim and a torn white shirt under a blue tank top. He wears red boxing gloves and boxing shoes. His hairstyle consists of short hair cut in an odd pointing style in the front, similar to Mike Tyson`s haircuts from the time Street Fighter II was made. Although usually removed when these illustrations are published outside Japan, some character illustrations feature his Japanese name, "Bison" on the waistband of his trunks. In Street Fighter IV, the waistband now reads "Champion".
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>40592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13770" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="7">6.97</rating>
<name>Fei-Long</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33852" picture="93214.jpg">Funaki Masakatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13771" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="5">9.10</rating>
<name>Sagat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8057">Sasaoka Shigezou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13772" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="7">6.14</rating>
<name>Dhalsim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3317" picture="24700.jpg">Kishino Yukimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13774" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<name>Balrog</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13775" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="27">8.62</rating>
<name>Cammy White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2986" picture="144766.jpg">Sasaki Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13777" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="9">7.48</rating>
<name>Zangief</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79577" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-24">
<name>Edmond Honda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85068" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-24">
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<name>Blanka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blanka is a fighter from Brazil. He was once human, but after being struck by a lightning during the plane crash he mutated, resulting in his green colouring and his ability to generate electricity.
Blanka fights in a self-taught, animalistic style. In several of his special moves he rolls into a ball, launching himself at an opponent. In Blanka`s signature attack, he crouches and emits an electric current shocking anything it touches.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>191726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85069" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-24">
<name>Thunder Hawk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thunder Hawk is a Native Mexican fighter who challenges http://anidb.net/ch13766 [Ken Masters].</description>
<picture>191727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85070" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-24">
<name>Dee Jay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dee Jay is a Jamaican kickboxer.</description>
<picture>191728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2201" picture="34284.jpg">Matsuo Ginzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85071" type="main character in" update="2016-09-24">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Vega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vega is the leader of Shadow Law.</description>
<picture>191729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33854" picture="93212.jpg">Kusaka Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3902" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>1994-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Get your quarters ready, because the world`s top fighters are about to go head to head in this explosive animated adaptation of the classic Street Fighter II arcade game! M. Bison`s plan to crush those who would oppose his organization, Shadowloo, is simple: brainwash the strongest martial artists around with his dreaded psycho power, and turn them into living weapons! To stop him, Interpol agent Chun-Li must team up with Major Guile of the United States Air Force, but that`s no small feat.
They`ll have to put aside their differences and learn to work together, and fast. Bison is closing in on Ryu, a traveling vagabond said to be the best fighter in the world. Fortunately (or not), Ryu is a hard man to find, but the same can`t be said of his eternal rival, Ken. And it might just be through Ken that Bison will get what he wants! Can the World Warriors beat Bison to the punch?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716295</identifier>
<identifier>street-fighter-ii-the-animated-movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10870" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1994-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11134" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1994-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
