<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3135" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>1991-04-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shizukanaru Don: Yakuza Side Story</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Quiet Don</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Quietened Don: Yakuza Side Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">静かなるドン YAKUZA SIDE STORY</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="59863" type="Work">Kiyomatsu Nobuo</name>
<name id="22076" type="Original Work">Nitta Tatsuo</name>
<name id="3579" type="Direction">Kamegaki Hajime</name>
<name id="1966" type="Character Design">Nabeshima Osamu</name>
<name id="3477" type="Work">Katou Shunzou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr22076 [Nitta Tatsuo]`s 1988 manga, serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Shonen Sunday].
Being the only son of the leader of the largest criminal organization (yakuza) in Kantou area, Shizuya Kondou chose not to join the gang and became a rookie designer of an underwear company. However, the assassination of his father forced him to inherit the gang, with one condition: keeping his day job while hiding his true identity from his coworkers, including an aspiring female designer who is his love interest as well as the only person capable of keeping his violent instincts contained.
Source: ANN
Note: Nitta`s story was also adapted into a live-action television drama.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8">4.68</permanent>
<temporary count="9">5.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>244495.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7333</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3207</identifier>
<identifier>negkqn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shizukanaru_Don_–_Yakuza_Side_Story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>静かなるドン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88492</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2740</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="53695" update="2010-04-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1991-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
