<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3168" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2005-09-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Amaenaide yo!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ah! My Buddha</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Не приставай ко мне!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Amaenaideyo!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">极乐天师</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">amaenaide yo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あまえないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ah My Buddha!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">응석부리지마!!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4145" type="Sequel">Amaenaide yo!! Katsu!!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="35" approval="43" total="50">Love Hina</anime>
<anime id="124" approval="2" total="3">Asagiri no Miko</anime>
<anime id="3299" approval="1" total="4">Tonagura!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="350228">must see for fanservice/etti lovers. DVD extras for both seasons is almost porn :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473022">A must see, if you like this genre! :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="459124">A really refreshing watch. It is a classic in the genre, makes you smile.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/amae/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1546" type="Character Design">Horii Kumi</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="1539" type="Direction">Motonaga Keitarou</name>
<name id="1551" type="Music">Iwasaki Yasunori</name>
<name id="21293" type="Original Work">Sogabe Toshinori</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7122 [Satonaka Ikkou], an apprentice Buddhist priest, is sent to live with his grandmother http://anidb.net/ch7114 [Kawahara Joutoku], the chief priestess of the Saien Temple. Waiting for him there are severe training, purification jobs, and six lively and quite attractive nuns. Living with same-age nuns may sounds enviable, but he is actually treated like an errand boy, since his purification skill cannot compare with theirs. However, when he has less pure, more worldly desires, his powers awaken to become quite impressive, usually saving the day.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3460">4.10</permanent>
<temporary count="3514">6.78</temporary>
<review count="3">5.11</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4851.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5381</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1734</identifier>
<identifier>uprrgd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/amae/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rightstuf.com/rssite/luckyPennyEntertainment/seriesSites/ahMyBuddha/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ah_My_Buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あまえないでよっ!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>625</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322667</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7435</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2005/amaenaideyo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="587" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>doll</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3363" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Buddhism</name>
<description>Buddhism is a nontheistic religion or dharma, "right way of living", that encompasses a variety of traditions, beliefs and practices largely based on teachings attributed to Siddhartha Gautama, commonly known as the Buddha ("the awakened one").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169453.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7113" type="appears in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="16">8.58</rating>
<name>Amanogawa Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The chief priestess of Saichouji and older sister to Haruka. Like her younger sister she is flirtatious and doesn`t mind if Ikko thinks anything perverted about her.</description>
<picture>2105.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7114" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-23">
<rating votes="11">6.76</rating>
<name>Kawahara Joutoku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2869.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7115" type="appears in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="16">7.07</rating>
<name>Kazusano Kazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main antagonist of the second season, her purpose is to awaken Ikko so that she can release her innate and uncontrollable spiritual powers. Kazuki seems to believe that the very nature of his powers are essentially good and therefore incapable of doing harm. Her catchphrase in Japanese is "mata joudo" (またじょうど).</description>
<picture>2864.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="7116" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="28">8.07</rating>
<name>Amanogawa Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Represents the Devas Realm (Heaven Realm) is the most powerful exorcist of the group. (Excluding times when Ikkou awakened.) She flirts with Ikkou on more than one occasion to get a response only to sit back and watch when he gets beaten by the other girls. She has the biggest cup size of all the novice nuns. She seems to take most everything in good humor, and might even come off as a ditz. However, she might be more intelligent than she looks.</description>
<picture>2866.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7117" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="21">5.89</rating>
<name>Sugai Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Represents the Hungry Ghosts Realm, is the sister of Hinata, and has the incredible ability to eat anything without ever feeling satisfied and without changing her appearance. Also has some political skills, as she is the president of the student council of the High School the group attends. Her love of politics seems based in a joy of enforcing the rules. All in all, she is a somewhat sadistic character, but she is not without concern for other people, and is especially attached to her younger sister, Hinata.</description>
<picture>2865.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7118" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="26">7.64</rating>
<name>Sugai Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Represents the Naraka Realm (Hell Realm), has a little fire-spitting-demon pet by her side at all times that converts to a full sized demon when Hinata can`t suppress her Naraka bosatsu. She is Sakura`s younger adopted sister. She appears very calm and rarely speaks. Her hobby is collecting and studying haniwa and she is in the Haniwa Research Club, the school`s smallest club.</description>
<picture>2868.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7119" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="21">6.04</rating>
<name>Ikuina Sumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Represents the Animal Realm. She is a kind girl who doesn`t mind Ikkou and some times tries to defend him verbally only to fail and let him get beaten up. Her kindness extends even to animals, and this seems to be where her spiritual talents lie.</description>
<picture>2870.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7120" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="21">6.06</rating>
<name>Atouda Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Represents the Asura Realm, she is a tomboy and doesn`t hesitate to join fights in her High School, she is the sole enemy of a High School Gang that has used Ikkou as a hostage. She tends to be jealous of girls that have big breasts compared to her own and angry with guys that prefer such girls. She has no romantic attachments, and seems to think that she would need to change her personality to something more "girly" in order to have a successful romantic relationship with a male. Like most of the others she likes to physically hurt Ikkou on a daily basis but it is hinted that she still likes him in the second season.</description>
<picture>2867.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2140" picture="21615.jpg">Higuchi Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7121" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="27">6.36</rating>
<name>Nanbu Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chitose represents the Human Realm, although she has a crush on Ikkou, she constantly denies it. Even though she acts nice much of the time, she fails to admit her crush to herself or Ikkou, often harming him when others flirt with him. She is usually the first to put Ikkou down as low as possible at times as well as beat him with little provocation. She enjoys horror films.</description>
<picture>25380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7122" type="main character in" update="2010-03-15">
<rating votes="16">5.32</rating>
<name>Satonaka Ikkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the series, Ikko is able to release a powerful but uncontrollable power when confronted with intense lust. Each time, in the aftermath of his "awakening," he will bear a face of lust, and will "attack" Chitose or the other nuns, who respond by running from him and attacking him. Ikkou seems not to enjoy his life at the temple (at least at the beginning of the series) and often complains that he is missing out on his youth. He seems not to have chosen the monastic life and resents the work given to him. He does not seem to have good grades in school nor does he seem to participate in any particular club at school.</description>
<picture>2863.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15527" type="appears in" update="2010-07-15">
<rating votes="5">4.43</rating>
<name>Ayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikkou and Chitose are called by studio producers after they hear weird voices in a CD recording, when Ikkou and Chitose get to the studio and start praying, she comes out.
She is still wandering this world because she died in a car accident when she was going to the studio for her first day of recording, so she borrows Chitoses body to sing through her.
It is later revealed that, she didn`t die in the car accident, she took her life because her boyfriend was left in a coma and the doctors told her he wouldn`t recover. After her boyfriend awakens from the coma, she then feels relieved and is able to leave the world of living.</description>
<picture>44109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15528" type="appears in" update="2010-03-04">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Yume Karyuudo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4757" picture="46951.jpg">Masukawa Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32461" type="appears in" update="2013-09-20">
<name>Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3845" picture="25484.jpg">Nishimoto Riichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32462" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>Kougen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32464" type="appears in" update="2013-09-20">
<name>Sakon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59849" type="appears in" update="2013-09-15">
<name>Yanagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a "pro" peeper. He knows good peeping spots by taking everything into consideration (time, sun, view etc).
He is a former student.</description>
<picture>143155.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59850" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-15">
<name>Demon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>It is normally a tiny demon, which can sit on the shoulder of a small girl, but can transform into a massive demon when its owner, Sugai Hinata, releases her spirit demonic powers.</description>
<picture>143157.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59851" type="appears in" update="2013-09-15">
<name>Yousen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59852" type="appears in" update="2013-09-15">
<name>Yellow Spider</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143162.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59853" type="appears in" update="2013-09-15">
<name>Ryuukan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He travels with Miayaki.</description>
<picture>143165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="37935" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">2.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38179" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒[い]かせないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Get Me Aroused!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä havahdu!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikasenaide yo!!</title>
<summary>Ikkou is placed in charge of the sutra for the Doll Burning Ceremony. He couldn`t possibly mess this up right?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713527</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38518" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜遊[あそ]ばないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Fool Around!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä pelleile!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asobanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>After working hard all day to clean the temple, Ikkou and Chitose sneak out for some karaoke fun. They find more than they bargain for when they stop by a nearby arcade.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713529</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38593" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覗かないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Peek!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä kurki!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozokanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>Girls` underwear is being stolen at school and everyone is blaming Ikkou. Meanwhile Ikkou`s friend Yanagi begs him for help getting close to Sumi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713531</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38745" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怯えないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Be Scared!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä ole peloissasi!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obienaide yo!!</title>
<summary>Chitose tries to get Ikkou, Sumi, Yuko and Hinata to join her for a movie marathon of horror flicks. When a young girl shows up asking for help, they may wind up in a real life horror story!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713533</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38746" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コスらないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Cosplay!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä leiki puvuilla!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kosuranaide yo!!</title>
<summary>The school festival has all the girls competing in cosplay to attract the most customers to their class` food booths. Meanwhile, Sakura is tracked down by one of her website visitors.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713535</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38747" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身[か]わらないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Transform!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä muutu!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaranaide yo!!</title>
<summary>Ikkou, Chitose and Haruka are sent to a local department store to investigate reported problems. It seems the sentai show on the roof may be haunted!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713537</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="39599" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">探さないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Search!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä etsi minua!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sagasanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>When Hinata takes in a stray kitten, Devilkin is feeling out in the cold. When he runs away, she drags Ikkou along to help find him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713539</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40326" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白[コク]らないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Confess!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä tunnusta!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuranaide yo!!</title>
<summary>Yuko receives a love letter from a classmate! Will this tomboy turn into the ultimate girl for her beau?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713541</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40328" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌わないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Sing!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä laula!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utawanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>When Ayako and Ikkou investigate a haunting at a recording studio, Ayako agrees to allow the spirit to use her body to finish her record.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713543</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40329" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">濡らさないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Get Me Wet!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä kastele minua!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nurasanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>Ikkou, Chitose, Sumi and Hinata are sent to a remote temple. They`re looking forward to the hot springs, but there’s something sinister awaiting them at this seeming paradise.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713545</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="40330" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">焦らさないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Tease Me!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä ärsytä minua!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jirasanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>It`s Christmas Eve, but there`s no merriment for the trainees at the Saienji Temple. They must exorcise the spirits from a horrible train wreck that occurred 45 years ago.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713547</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="41306" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒(めざ)めないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Awaken!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä herää!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezamenaide yo!!</title>
<summary>It`s New Year`s Eve and Ikkou has been chosen to ring the bell. But as he does so, massive amount of spirits begin to gather and get out of hand.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713549</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="46235" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">休まないでよっ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Rest!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Älä ole uninen!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasumanaide yo!!</title>
<summary>After winning at trip on a game show, the gang takes a well deserved vacation!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>713551</identifier>
<identifier>ah-my-buddha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="104228" update="2010-09-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122054" update="2010-09-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
