<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3186" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2006-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">+دم</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Kraujas Plius</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Blood TV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">B+</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BLOOD+</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Кровь+</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">BLOOD+</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Blood+</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">BLOOD+</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">BLOOD+</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">BLOOD+</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Кръв+</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">BLOOD+</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="43" type="Same Setting">Blood: The Last Vampire</anime>
<anime id="8348" type="Other">Blood-C</anime>
<anime id="8375" type="Other">Gekijouban Blood-C: The Last Dark</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6113" approval="22" total="29">Ga-Rei: Zero</anime>
<anime id="32" approval="7" total="17">Hellsing</anime>
<anime id="4522" approval="6" total="9">Red Garden</anime>
<anime id="7268" approval="5" total="16">Shiki</anime>
<anime id="9518" approval="4" total="18">Kyoukai no Kanata</anime>
<anime id="3296" approval="2" total="11">Hellsing (2006)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="17">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="204142">For fans of girlie anime. They took all of the dark brooding and horror of having lived and killed her own kind for millenia, the utter sorrow of her growing isolation, threw it away with `memory-loss` and time-warp. They then wrapped the character in a sugary coating with an evil twin sister escaped from being locked in the attic and a hard-on for her adoptive brother. And somehow this made it to 50 episodes.

Now that Clamp is doing a remake in Blood C, they should call this Blood B(-).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281330">It was long but i enjoyed it,but i think it`s not for newguys :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="308233">If your looking for an anime that keeps your attention the whole time and manages to keep you asking for more while it really feels round in the end, this is the right one!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="322928">Just get past the first 5 episodes and you`ll be in for a treat. Great anime, blew my expectations out of the water</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="417064">Story of romance and vampires. Saya, a girl with no memories, is in the middle of a war between humans and vampires fought around the world (the story takes place in Japan, Vietnam, France, England, Russia ....). The first episodes are a little slow but then the story continues to improve, especially when Diva appears.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="316273">Blood++</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396387">it fits different age people, even who is searching for something deeper blood+ will worth the watch.
The soundtrack is simply  a w e s o m e</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432591">This was a true piece of art. I`ve watched all the elements combined into a masterpiece of 50 episodes, and that is romance, drama, action, motivation, admirable heroes, lovely main character and so on (I could go on for days); with the main theme revolving around vampires. The way they illustrated this theme was really smart, they`ve arranged it as a dilemma. I can say the plot might seem typical or "skimpy" (maybe not the right word though) at the beginning, but it unveils its quality shortly. Even for people not interested in this genre, I would definitely recommend this to everyone ! Must see imo.

P.S.: Maybe some people like short series, but I love the fact that they made 50 episodes, they took their time, the plot was well developed thanx to this and it never got boring, it kept me glued to the screen.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.blood.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3573" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Akiharu</name>
<name id="11144" type="Character Design">Hashii Chizu</name>
<name id="7076" type="Direction">Fujisaku Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="3573" type="Animation Character Design">Ishii Akiharu</name>
<name id="7076" type="Series Composition">Fujisaku Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="721" type="Original Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="762" type="Original Work">Aniplex</name>
<name id="1420" type="Chief Direction">Matsumoto Atsushi</name>
<name id="54376" type="Music">Mark Mancina</name>
</creators>
<description>The war never stops: in a different time, on a different battlefield, hiding deeply in the folds of history... They are called Chiropterans. They can change their form and disguise as human beings, but they are not. They are immortal creatures that feed off blood.
An organization, named Red Shield, has been fighting to exterminate this pestilence, and the struggle has now evolved into something of a much bigger scale.
Okinawa, Japan. Year 2005. Now.
The high school girl http://anidb.net/ch8508 [Otonashi Saya] is living peacefully with her family or it seems, since she has no memory of her life except for the past year. One day, a startling event causes her happy life to shatter to pieces.
An enemy to destroy, a mission to accomplish — the vortex of an ancient struggle is dragging Saya back to her destiny. A young and handsome cello player in dark clothes appears — his name is http://anidb.net/ch7346 [Haji]. The moment he hands Saya a Japanese sword, history starts on a new course.
Will Saya be able to restore her memory and find her own identity?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7351">6.46</permanent>
<temporary count="7513">7.77</temporary>
<review count="13">7.15</review>
</ratings>
<picture>74983.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1715</identifier>
<identifier>nabfka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/blood-plus/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.blood.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blood+</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Blood+</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>688</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7652</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2047" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-31">
<name>human weapon</name>
<description>This tag applies to weapons that can take up a human-shaped form (Bleach and Soul Eater), artificially created human-like entities (Angeloids from Sora no Oto, Dragoons from ScrappedPrincess) and engineered humans (Chise from Saikano, Saiko Yuki from Silent Möbius).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2664" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-07">
<name>catholic school</name>
<description>A setting for this anime is a school run by the nuns and/or priests of the Church Of Rome.
Religious instruction may be an integral part of the plot. Religious icons - particularly crosses and crucifixes are usually prominent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2681" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Okinawa</name>
<description>Okinawa Prefecture is the southernmost prefecture of Japan. It encompasses two thirds of the Ryukyu Islands in a chain over 1,000 kilometreslong. The Ryukyu Islands extend southwest from Kyushu (the southwesternmost of Japan`s four main islands) to Taiwan. Naha, Okinawa`s capital, is located in the southern part of Okinawa Island.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214299.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3222" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Vietnam</name>
<description>Vietnam, officially the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, is the easternmost country on the Indochina Peninsula in Southeast Asia. Vietnam is bordered by China to the north, Laos to the northwest, Cambodia to the southwest, Thailand across the Gulf of Thailand to the southwest, and the Philippines, Malaysia and Indonesia across the South China Sea to the east and southeast. Its capital city has been Hanoi since the reunification of North and South Vietnam in 1976, with Ho Chi Minh City as the most populous city.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214337.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3326" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-18">
<name>jumping very high</name>
<description>The character can jump unnaturally high.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3513" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>special bullet</name>
<description>Custom made bullets that have special effects (and often shapes, too), which take action when hitting the enemy/ally.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3818" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-21">
<name>kids in war</name>
<description>When minors participate in armed conflict.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4021" parentid="36" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-08">
<name>evil military</name>
<description>The military is depicted as being of a nefarious nature in this anime. Be it through the heartlessness that their soldiers convey, or the ruthless killing of innocents, the military in this anime is not to be messed with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4268" parentid="7231" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Vladivostok</name>
<description>Vladivostok is a city and the administrative center of Primorsky Krai, Russia, located around the Golden Horn Bay, not far from Russia`s borders with China and North Korea. The city is the home port of the Russian Pacific Fleet and the largest Russian port on the Pacific Ocean.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214372.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5047" parentid="2675" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moscow</name>
<description>Moscow is the capital and most populous city of Russia, it is recognized as Russian federal city. Moscow is a major political, economic, cultural, and scientific centre of Russia and Eastern Europe, as well as the largest city entirely on the European continent.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214369.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5213" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-04">
<name>the effects of time and distance on human relationships</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6076" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-01">
<name>paparazzi</name>
<description>Paparazzi (singular: (m) paparazzo or (f) paparazza) are photographers who take pictures of athletes, celebrities, politicians, and other prominent people usually while they are going about normal life routines. Many experts consider their behavior to be synonymous with stalking, and anti-stalking bills in many countries have tried to reduce harassment of public figures and celebrities, especially in regard to minors. Many public figures and celebrities have expressed concern about the extent to which paparazzi invade their personal space, and the filing and receiving of judicial support for restraining orders against paparazzi is increasing as are lawsuits with judgments against them.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6328" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-01">
<name>biological weapons</name>
<description>Use of biological agents (bacteria, viruses, fungi, etc.) to inflict harm on humans and/or other targets.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6849" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-19">
<name>organism cloning</name>
<description>Organism cloning, also called reproductive cloning, is the creation of an organism that is genetically identical to another. While this is a natural phenomenon in many species, this tag is specifically about artificial organism cloning, as in Dolly the sheep. Cloning of multicellular organisms, and especially of human beings, remains both a scientific frontier and a highly controversial subject, especially in regards to its ethics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7231" parentid="2675" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-02">
<name>Eastern Russia</name>
<description>Eastern Russia / North Asia consists of the Russian regions of Siberia, Ural and the Russian Far East – an area east of the Ural Mountains. The region is sometimes also referred to as Asian Russia (as opposed to the smaller but more densely populated European Russia to the west)</description>
<picurl>228642.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7346" type="main character in" update="2011-07-07">
<rating votes="65">7.84</rating>
<name>Haji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Age 142 (appearance age 22): He is partly instrumental in Saya`s "awakening" and his right arm is covered in bandages, hiding some Chiropteran features that he is unable to change back into human form. This might be due to trauma when Saya sliced his hand during the Vietnam incident. Haji first met Saya when he was a child of age 12 and was brought by Joel to be her companion and hopefully mate and create more specimens someday. At this time Saya was 43 although she doesn`t appear to be since she stopped aging in 1863. He lived with her in Joel`s mansion for many years. But one day he fell from a cliff in an attempt to pick a flower that Saya wanted as a present for Joel`s birthday. Seeing him bleeding everywhere and not really understanding that people don`t drink blood to remain healthy, Saya gave him her own blood. Thus she unwittingly turned him into her "Chevalier."
Since then, Haji`s single wish is to protect Saya and fulfil her wishes. It is also revealed that unlike Saya who "created" him, Haji neither eats, sleeps, nor go into long periods of hibernation.</description>
<picture>74910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8508" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="119">7.26</rating>
<name>Otonashi Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2238.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8509" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="25">3.35</rating>
<name>Miyagusuku Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2239.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8510" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="44">6.28</rating>
<name>Diva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2240.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8511" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="13">2.39</rating>
<name>Miyagusuku Riku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2241.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8512" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="17">4.99</rating>
<name>Solomon Goldsmith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Solomon Goldsmith was a medical doctor who was introduced to Diva by Amshel in 1917 during the Russian Revolution. At this time, he became one of her chevaliers, after which he wears only white clothing as a symbol of his being Diva`s chevalier because it was what he was wearing when he met her. At the time, he wanted to free himself from seeing humans kill each other, but afterwards, he started seeing humans as insignificant and beneath him. As time passed, he realized the world of the chiropterans are just as full of war as the human one.</description>
<picture>2242.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9474" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-07">
<rating votes="25">6.13</rating>
<name>David</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12883" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="14">5.53</rating>
<name>Jahana Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jahana Mao, the daughter of the head of the Jahana Yakuza, is often bossy and likes to be in control, a trait she probably picked up from her father. Her blunt, confrontational demeanor seems to be a brave facade she puts up whenever things don`t go her way or she`s scared.</description>
<picture>2798.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14146" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-18">
<rating votes="21">6.76</rating>
<name>Lewis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lewis is responsible for providing gadgets and transportation for the Red Shield operatives. He also provides intel from the CIA during American operations thanks to the connections formed when he was CIA agent, working under the name of Sammy. He regularly accompanies David during operations, and after Kai becomes a member of Red Shield they frequently work together as well.</description>
<picture>41605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1998" picture="21301.jpg">Nagasako Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14147" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<name>Irene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Irène fights with a wide, double-sided sword, and is one of several Schiff with the ability to locate Saya from great distances. Killing humans to drink their blood bothers her to the point that she refuses to continue to do so, though it leaves her in a weakened state.</description>
<picture>74979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14148" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="4">1.53</rating>
<name>Van Argiano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Van Argiano is the head scientist studying chiropterans for Cinq Flèches. He was in charge of the development of Delta 67, working under Solomon and with his assistant Archer.</description>
<picture>74972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14149" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="2">6.47</rating>
<name>Karman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karman is a tall, slender boy with a tendency to be aggressive, particularly towards humans. He can be hot-headed and impulsive, but seems to genuinely care for his fellow Schiff.</description>
<picture>74978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14150" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="5">4.25</rating>
<name>Okamura Akihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okamura Akihiro, a somewhat jaded, down-on-his-luck, chain-smoking newspaper reporter, Okamura is the son of the photographer and Vietnam war correspondent who had taken several mysterious black and white photos depicting a young girl killing soldiers, villagers, and grotesque monsters with a sword. After seeing them as a child, the photographs have always haunted Okamura, spurring him to discover the truth behind them. After tracing wine dumped by the military to Vietnam, Okamura sees Saya fighting Karl and manages to take some pictures of her.</description>
<picture>74965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14151" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="5">2.80</rating>
<name>Joel Goldschmidt VI</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joel Goldschmidt VI is the current head of the Red Shield and a descendant of the original Joel who found Saya and Diva. Every man in his family who bears the name Joel must live and fight against the chiroptera throughout their life until they are no longer a threat. Joel became the head of the Red Shield in 2002, Joel primarily works in the background, trusting his operatives to handle the day-to-day work while he supports them.</description>
<picture>74964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14152" type="appears in" update="2011-07-11">
<rating votes="3">1.33</rating>
<name>Carl Fei-Ong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karl Fei-Ong was introduced to Diva in 1917 by Amshel. When he met her, he requested that she turn him into a chevalier. Karl`s body was heavily modified by Amshel`s experiments, including having the arm Saya destroyed in Vietnam in 1972 replaced with a spiked arm. His traumatic past, Diva`s inability to give him the love he sought, and forced conversion seems to have left Karl severely mentally unbalanced.</description>
<picture>75247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14153" type="appears in" update="2010-01-18">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Aston Collins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Aston Collins was once the second-in-command of the Red Shield, primarily in charge of researching the chiroptera with Julia as his assistant. He grew increasingly frustrated at being unable to ever publish his research.</description>
<picture>41615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14154" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-07">
<rating votes="10">5.09</rating>
<name>Julia Silverstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Julia Silverstein is a medical doctor working for the Red Shield. She is first seen in the series acting as Saya`s doctor and supervising Saya`s blood transfusions. She is committed to researching the true nature of chiropterans to help destroy them.</description>
<picture>74914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14155" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="10">2.49</rating>
<name>Amshel Goldsmith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amshel Goldsmith was the assistant of the original Joel Goldshmidt, and was responsible for bringing Diva food and taking care of her basic needs while she was locked in the tower. In 1883, after Diva`s release from the tower, Diva spares Amshel during her murder spree and turns him into a chevalier.</description>
<picture>74973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14156" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="14">6.93</rating>
<name>James Ironside</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James Ironside became one of Diva`s chevaliers in 1945 in Berlin, Germany during the second World War. He is the Cinq Flèches` contact with the US military, and later was appointed by Amshel as leader of the Corpse Corps and to take on the task of killing Saya. He is extremely devoted to caring for and protecting Diva.</description>
<picture>41618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14157" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="5">3.16</rating>
<name>Nathan Mahler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nathan Mahler appears to be one of the oldest of Diva`s chevaliers, though when and how he became one is unexplained.</description>
<picture>41619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14158" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="2">3.72</rating>
<name>Moses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Moses is the leader of the Schiff who uses a scythe. He was the one who had encouraged the Schiff to leave the lab for the sake of hope.</description>
<picture>74977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41" picture="16630.jpg">Yanagi Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14159" type="appears in" update="2010-01-18">
<rating votes="2">5.76</rating>
<name>Darth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darth is a member of the Schiff.</description>
<picture>41626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14160" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-11">
<rating votes="7">6.05</rating>
<name>Lulu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lulu is a member of the Schiff, a diminutive young girl with sunken eyes. Lulu has a somewhat innocent and child-like personality, and comes to enjoy some of the human elements of life such as watching television.</description>
<picture>75248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14161" type="appears in" update="2010-01-18">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Gudrif</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gudrif is a member of the Schiff.</description>
<picture>41628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34275" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-07">
<rating votes="5">7.16</rating>
<name>Miyagusuku George</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34276" type="appears in" update="2011-07-07">
<name>Kurara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34283" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Spencer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34284" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<name>Makkoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34285" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Rodgers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34286" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="2">3.74</rating>
<name>Elisabeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34287" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<name>Kinjou Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34288" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="2">2.09</rating>
<name>Min</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34289" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Annamarie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34290" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Ms. Lee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34291" type="appears in" update="2011-07-08">
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<name>Mui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74971.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34293" type="appears in" update="2011-07-12">
<name>Phantom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34449" type="appears in" update="2011-07-11">
<name>Glay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34450" type="appears in" update="2011-07-11">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Monique</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34451" type="appears in" update="2011-07-11">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Nahabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34452" type="appears in" update="2011-07-11">
<name>Javier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41436" update="2005-09-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41691" update="2005-09-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">30-second TV Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42072" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="45">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファーストキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier Baiser</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">První polibek</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az első csók</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Primul sărut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42073" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="30">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法の言葉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic Words</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mots Magiques</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Kouzelná slova</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Varázslatos szavak</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Cuvinte magice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou no Kotoba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42085" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="24">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじまりの場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Place Where It All Started</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`endroit où tout a commencé</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Kde všechnno začalo</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Ahol minden elkezdődött</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Locul unde a început totul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Basho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42086" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アブない少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dangereux Garçon</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Nebezpečný hoch</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Veszélyes alak</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Un tip periculos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abunai Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42350" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="22">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗い森の向こうへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond the Dark Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers la Sombre Forêt</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Za temným lesem</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A sötét erdőn túl</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Dincolo de pădurea întunecată</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurai Mori no Mukou e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42351" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おとうさんの手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Father`s Hands</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les mains de mon Père</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Ruce mého otce</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Apám keze</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Mâinile tatălui meu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otousan no Te</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42352" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="22">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私がやらなきゃ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Must Do It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce que je dois faire</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Musím to udělat</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Meg kell tennem</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Trebuie să o fac</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ga Yaranakya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44649" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントム・オブ・ザ・スクール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom of the School</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Fantôme de l`École</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Fantóm školy</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az iskola fantomja</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Fantoma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom of the School</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44785" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの虹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rainbow for Each</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaque Arc-en-Ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Duha pro každého</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Békét mindenkinek</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Curcubeu pentru fiecare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Niji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44786" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたに会いたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to See You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je veux te rencontrer</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Chci tě vidět</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Látni akarlak</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Doresc să te văd</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata ni Aitai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44834" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンスのあとで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après la Danse</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Po tanci</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A tánc után</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">După petrecere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dance no Ato de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44835" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い霧にさそわれて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lured by White Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attiré dans le Brouillard Blanc</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Vábeni bílou mlhou</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Csali a ködben</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ademenit de ceaţa albă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Kiri ni Sasowarete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45370" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャングル・パラダイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jungle Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Paradis de la Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Ráj v džungli</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A dzsungelben</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Paradisul din junglă</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jungle Paradise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45371" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さいごの日曜日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Sunday</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Dernier Dimanche</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Poslední neděle</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Utolsó vasárnap</title>
<title xml:lang="ro">Ultima Duminică</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Nichiyoubi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45372" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おいかけたいの!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Pursue!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je te poursuivrai !</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Chci tě sledovat</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Követni fogom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oikaketai no!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45373" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シベリアン・エクスプレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Siberian Express</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Siberian Express</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Sibiřský expres</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A Transzszibériai expressz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Siberian Express</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46249" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束おぼえてる?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Remember the Promise?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Te rappelles-tu ta promesse ?</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Emlékszel az ígéretre?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku o Oboeteru?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46250" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エカテリンブルグの月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon over Ekaterinburg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lune sur Iekaterinbourg</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A hold Jekatyerinburg felett</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ekaterinburg no Tsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46251" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">折れたココロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Broken Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cœur Brisé</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Zlomené srdce</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Megtört szív</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oreta Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46252" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュヴァリエ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chevalier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chevaliers</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Chevalier</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Chevalier-ék</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chevalier</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47180" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すっぱいブドウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sour Grapes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aigre Raisin</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Kyselé hrozny</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A sifuk támadása</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suppai Budou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47686" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動物園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">ZOO</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az állatkert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doubutsuen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47740" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりのシュヴァリエ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Chevaliers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Deux Chevaliers</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Dva Chevalieři</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Két chevalier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Chevalier</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48557" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軽やかなる歌声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Airy Singing Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un doux chant</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Prostořeký zpěvný hlas</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A titokzatos dal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karoyaka Naru Utagoe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48563" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い盾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Shield</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Red Shield</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Rudý štít</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A Vörös Pajzs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Tate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48564" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サヤに従うもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Serve Saya</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Servants de Saya</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Ti, kteří slouží Saye</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Akik Sayát szolgálják</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saya ni Shitagau Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48565" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パリ・ジュテーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paris Je t`aime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Paris, Je t`aime</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Miluji tě, Paříži</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Szeretlek, Párizs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Paris, Je t`aime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48566" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限りあるもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Existence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Existence Limitée</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Omezená existence</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Határozott élettartam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagiriaru Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48841" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呪われた血</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cursed Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sang Maudit</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Megátkozott vér</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Norowareta Chi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48842" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョエルの日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Joel`s Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Journal de Joel</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Joelův deník</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Joel naplója</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joel no Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49859" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壊れゆく盾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breaking Shield</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Bouclier qui doit être cassé</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Rés a pajzson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koware Yuku Tate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49860" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーイ・ミーツ・ガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boy Meets Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Boy Meets Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A találkozás</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boy Meets Girl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49919" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じるチカラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of Believing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Pouvoir de la Foi</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A hit ereje</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjiru Chikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49920" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺たちのいる世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World Where We Exist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Monde dans lequel nous sommes</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A világ, amiben élünk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oretachi no Iru Sekai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50538" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望のない明日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tomorrow Without Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lendemain sans Espoir</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Remény nélkül</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou no Nai Ashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50539" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="16">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれちがう想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mismatched Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sentiments Inégaux</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Vegyes érzelmek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigau Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50540" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂おしいまでに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Level of Sheer Madness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jusqu`à devenir fou</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Na pokraji čirého šílenství</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Az őrület határán</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuruoshii made ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50912" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦の島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown Island</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`île de la confrontation</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Ostrov zúčtování</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Csapda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen no Shima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50913" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法の言葉をもう一度</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magic Words, Once More</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les mots magiques, une fois encore</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Kouzelná slova, ještě jednou</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A varázslatos szavak mégegyszer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou no Kotoba o Mou Ichido</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51606" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュヴァリエの見る夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams That Chevaliers Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les rêves d`un chevalier</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">O čem sní Chevalieři</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Egy chevalier álma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chevalier no Miru Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51607" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私の居場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Place Where I Belong</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Là où je dois être</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Místo, kam patřím</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Ide tartozom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Ibasho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51608" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">響く, 歌声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soprano of Miracles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chant qui résonne</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Zázračný soprán</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A csodás szoprán</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibiku, Utagoe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51609" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こころ乱れて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confused Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cœurs indécis</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Megzavart szív</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro Midarete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51610" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手のひらを太陽に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turn the Palm of Your Hand Toward the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand les rayons du soleil transpercent nos mains</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Fordulj a fény felé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Te no Hira o Taiyou ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51611" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あした天気になあれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">May Tomorrow Be a Clear Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Faites qu`il fasse beau demain</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Ať je zítra jasný den</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Talán holnapra kiderül</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita Tenki ni Naare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52268" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="17">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光の中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Into the Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans la lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A fénybe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari no Naka ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57724" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全ての血を超えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond All Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au-delà du sang</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Több mint vérrokon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete no Chi o Koete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="57725" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">摩天楼オペラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skyscraper Opera</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`opéra du gratte-ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Opera mezi mrakodrapy</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A bemutató</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matenrou Opera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62000" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の女王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Queens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux reines</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Dvě královny</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">A két királynő</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Joou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62001" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="34">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナンクルナイサ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`ll All Work Out</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nankurunaisa</title>
<title xml:lang="cs">Nan-kuru-nai-sah</title>
<title xml:lang="hu">Nankurunaisza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nankurunaisa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73988" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108249" update="2018-09-08">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108250" update="2018-09-08">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108251" update="2018-09-08">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108252" update="2018-09-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108253" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108254" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108255" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108256" update="2010-03-29">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154447" update="2013-10-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15-second TV Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172753" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Writer and Director Junichi Fujisaku and Voice Actors Eri Kitamura and Katsuyuki Konishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172754" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Voice Actors Toru Okawa and Keiji Fujiwara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172755" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Voice Actors Nozomu Sasaki and Hideyuki Umezu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172756" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Voice Actors Naoki Yanagi and Megumi Toyoguchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172757" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Voice Actors Kenji Nojima and Chiwa Saito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172758" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Voice Actors Joji Nakata and Koji Tsujitani</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172759" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Voice Actors Eri Kitamura and Katsuyuki Konishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172760" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interviews with Yuko Kaida and Junichi Suwabe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172761" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interviews with Kentaro Ito and Ami Koshimizu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172762" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interviews with Jurota Kosugi and Takashi Nagasako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172763" update="2016-01-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2008-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interviews with Hiroyuki Yoshino and Hochu Otsuka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172764" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2008-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Interviews with Eri Kitamura and Katsuyuki Konishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176337" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview of Akiko Yajima and Mai Kadowaki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206490" update="2018-09-08">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
