<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3193" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>48</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-10-18</startdate>
<enddate>1991-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mitsume ga Tooru</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Here Comes Three Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">三つ目がとおる</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Three-eyed One</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2991" type="Character">Hyakumannen Chikyuu no Tabi Bander Book</anime>
<anime id="7876" type="Character">Ravex in Tezuka World</anime>
<anime id="7341" type="Other">Akuma Tou no Prince: Mitsume ga Tooru</anime>
<anime id="8488" type="Other">Tezuka Osamu ga Kieta?! 20 Seiki Saigo no Kaijiken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/48.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="683" type="Series Composition">Sekijima Mayori</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="4289" type="Direction">Ueda Hidehito</name>
<name id="4508" type="Music">Watanabe Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="5236" type="Character Design">Udagawa Kazuhiko</name>
</creators>
<description>This TV series is about a boy named Sharaku who is an innocent child when the third eye on his forehead is covered with a patch. But once the patch comes off, he is transformed into a member of the evil three-eyed tribe, who possesses supernatural powers and had once built an ancient civilization. While the original Manga included Tezuka Osamu`s studies on highly sophisticated ancient civilizations and a great number of sexual scenes involving Wato, the partner of Sharaku, these elements were subdued for the TV version in consideration of a younger audience. This was the first animated work based on Tezuka Osamu`s Manga that was planned following his death.
Source: official homepage</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="27">4.16</permanent>
<temporary count="27">5.16</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4445.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2589</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2147</identifier>
<identifier>ujtslw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/48.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/en/anime/48.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Three-Eyed_One</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>三つ目がとおる</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89144</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1334</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="79398" type="appears in" update="2016-01-05">
<rating votes="14">5.43</rating>
<name>Tezuka Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Osamu Tezuka`s anime/manga version of himself</description>
<picture>181241.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="35352" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪植物ボルボック出現! 七本の柱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seven Pillars Appear! (Wearied Plant Bolbocc, pt 1)</title>
<summary>A mysterious stone circle appears following an earthquake that hits a village. Dr. Kenmochi and the boys discover ruins in a cave at the center of a group of pillars lined up in a circle. A notebook discovered there contains the mysterious records of Dr. Tejima, Japan`s first researcher on the three-eyed family.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35353" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の国の写楽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sharaku in Wonderland</title>
<summary>Sharaku and his friends visit an antique shop that Wato`s uncle is running. As soon as they find a uniquely shaped jar in the warehouse, Sharaku is swallowed into it. When Wato peeps inside, Sharaku disappears like smoke.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35354" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわいい赤ちゃんは侵略者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cute Little Baby Is an Invader</title>
<summary>Wato and Sharaku go to the hospital to see a baby born to their friend`s family. At the hospital, babies are fully taken care of by computers. In the presence of Sharaku and Wato, a computer with a will of its own starts to take over babies` minds.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35355" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日への誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Sharaku Hosuke - Pledge for Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita e no Chikai</title>
<summary>It is the three-eyed girl Moegi who has been manipulating Super Bolbocc. Her true objective is to ruin the human race in order to protect all nature of the earth. Sharaku and Wato take up the challenge of a last battle with the firm belief in the future and values of human beings.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35356" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ目イヌ誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Three-eyed Dog Is Born</title>
<summary>A puppy named Hokusai has a bandage on his forehead. Sharaku becomes interested in this dog, and declares that he will make this dog with a little scar on its forehead into a three-eyed dog.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35357" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪植物ボルボック 不思議少女モエギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Girl Moegi (Wearied Plant Bolbocc, pt 2)</title>
<summary>Sharaku and Wato are rescued by a mysterious girl from mud that moves like a creature. Sharaku and his friends enter the mysterious limestone cave with a monument of the ancient three-eyed family as a clue. There, they find a mysterious bulb, Bolbocc, which has the intellect to manipulate other plants.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35358" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イースター島航海 結婚? ポゴと写楽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marriage of Pogo and Sharaku? (Easter Island Voyage, pt 3)</title>
<summary>The speaking monkey is named Pogo. She has been trained to speak by a mysterious organization planning to take control of the entire world. The group performs an operation on monkeys living on Easter Island and turns them into soldiers in order to make Sharaku cooperate.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35359" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代王子ゴダル 地球乗っ取り計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Earth Hijacking Plan (Ancient Prince Godal, pt 4)</title>
<summary>After activating Gomora, Godal and Sharaku set their heads to conquering the world. Their scheme is to kidnap all leaders of the world, who are to gather at a summit meeting, and replace their souls by using the power of Godal`s jar! Moreover, Godal is even trying to deceive Sharaku!
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35360" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪植物ボルボック 動き出した大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Land Starts to Move (Wearied Plant Bolbocc, pt 4)</title>
<summary>Bolbocc finally starts to cover the ground and take revenge on human beings. In the midst of big earthquakes and landslides, the slate that Moegi points to bears an inscription stating that the three-eyed family was ruined by Bolbocc.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35361" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラーメン戦争! 怒りの一撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ramen War! An Angry Blow</title>
<summary>Sharaku, who works part-time at a ramen shop, is instigated by Kido and a gang who regard him with enmity. Wato, who finds Sharaku mysteriously charming, helps him get out of the situation, but the gang takes the bandage from Sharaku`s forehead. With his third eye uncovered, his superhuman power is fully revealed.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35362" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪盗オズマの挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge of the Mysterious Thief Ozuma</title>
<summary>A mysterious thief named Ozuma, who is always after swords and armor of medieval times, appears in Japan. The museums are on strict guard in anticipation of his appearance. Then, a battle starts between Sharaku and Ozuma, who can produce illusions.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35363" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷子のUFOをさがせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Looking for the Missing UFO</title>
<summary>Sharaku, working part-time at a ramen shop, happens to see his classmates getting excited about the discovery of a small UFO. Sharaku takes the tiny UFO home with him. He seems to have been able to identify the small UFO at first sight. From the next day on, unusual phenomena are observed in volcanoes and power plants.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35364" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ目族の謎・財宝をさがし出せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search for the Treasure (Mystery of the Three-eyed Family, pt 3)</title>
<summary>It was a descendent of the Lake Biwa guard named Kuge who saved Sharaku and Wato from Baron Goblin. Sharaku, Wato, and Kuge open the door of the ruins, and go into the underground labyrinth where the treasures of the three-eyed family are kept.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35365" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心を開け古代魔神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Open Your Mind, Ancient Devil</title>
<summary>The awakened Devil Garon is a robot that the ancient three-eyed family had invented. It cannot stop destroying unless the consciousness of Garon (a bullet ball) is set into its chest. Sharaku and his friends start to look for his consciousness after coming to know that the whole world will be set on fire if they leave him alone.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35366" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イースター島航海 上陸!悪魔の住む島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Landing on Devil Island (Easter Island Voyage, pt 2)</title>
<summary>The talking monkey is named Pogo. Wato and the others, who get on an unmanned boat, discover a mummy. A mysterious voice is heard from the mummy.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35367" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代王子ゴダル もう一人の写楽!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Sharaku (Ancient Prince Godal, pt 1)</title>
<summary>Three-eyed Prince Godal has had his soul encapsulated in a jar for 4,500 years. The moment Wato peeps into the jar at a museum they visit on a school trip, she is taken over by Godal`s spirit. In return, Wato`s spirit possesses a cat.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35368" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハイテク暴走車を追え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pursue the High-tech Speeding Car</title>
<summary>A car without a driver suddenly starts to move, and a mysterious machine created by Sharaku seems to be involved in this strange incident.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35369" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪党文福あらわる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Villain Bumpuku Appears</title>
<summary>A mysterious man named Bumpuku appears in front of Sharaku. He has created a spider-shaped machine based on a design sketch that Sharaku drew three years ago. It is a terrible machine that bites and steals the intellect of human beings.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35370" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代王子ゴダル 魂を取り戻せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Back the Soul! (Ancient Prince Godal, pt 5)</title>
<summary>Godal, still in possession of Wato`s body, takes Sharaku hostage by covering his third eye. He demands that a jar be brought to Mt. Kurama so that he can use it to replace his soul. It now seems that he plans to possess Sharaku`s body so that he can conquer the world.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35371" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イースター島航海 サルが喋った!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monkey Speaks! (Easter Island Voyage, pt 1)</title>
<summary>A big group of monkeys starts to rage about in the zoo, and take Sharaku away. The leader of the monkeys seems to speak human language. Wato follows the monkey, who hijacks a bus and flees by boat kidnapping Sharaku.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35372" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メキシコ上空大バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Battle Over the Mexican Sky</title>
<summary>Sharaku has been captured alive and taken to Mexico together with Moa. Sharaku breaks out of the cage, and in the desert he meets a girl who looks identical to Wato.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35373" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">文福再びあらわる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bumpuku Reappears</title>
<summary>A series of burglaries happens, and as a result of police inspector Unmei`s investigation, the criminal is proven to be Bumpuku based on fingerprints left at the site. But Bumpuku is still serving a prison term. Sharaku and Wato set out to capture the criminal who is serving time.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35374" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙われたモア!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going After Moa</title>
<summary>Having grown as big as 6 meters in length, Moa goes out to town every time he is hungry. A mysterious organization that has been watching Moa`s behavior dispatches a group of three men to capture Moa alive.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35375" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">のっとられた写楽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sharaku Haunted</title>
<summary>Dr. Kenmochi, who is taking care of Sharaku, finds a necklace in ancient ruins. Ever since Sharaku took it away without the doctor`s permission, he has totally changed. The necklace was made by an ancient three-eyed family, and Sharaku apparently is awakened to the secrets of his ancient s bloodlines.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35376" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議鳥モア!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Bird Called Moa</title>
<summary>Sharaku goes to the sea with Wato, and they come upon a mysterious bird. It is a great big bird that makes a sound like a jet plane when it flies. They examine the egg they receive from the bird, and discover that it is an egg of the legendary bird Moa, a species that should have been extinct for more than 100 years.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35377" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代魔神めざめる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ancient Devil Awakened</title>
<summary>Metal pieces are excavated from different ruins. Dr. Kenmochi perceives them to be over 8,000 years old. When the pieces are put together, it becomes a giant devil image. Sharaku puts the last missing piece to its forehead, and then, .....
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35378" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活! スーパーボルボック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Bolbocc Is Revived!</title>
<summary>The evil organization has finally obtained the legacy of the three-eyed family, a cell strengthening virus, and sent the mightiest weapon--Super Bolbocc--to Tokyo Bay. In the meantime, Sharaku is in Mexico still with a bandage on. If things don`t change, Tokyo will be ruined.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35379" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ目登場・ボクが写楽だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Debut of the Three-eyed Boy: I am Sharaku</title>
<summary>While his big bandage is on his forehead, Sharaku Hosuke is a coward and is always being bullied by everyone in the class. But he has changed ever since he saw an image of God with a cross on its forehead at the museum. A secret seems to be hidden under that big bandage.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35380" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ目族の謎 古代からの使者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Messenger from the Ancient Times (Mystery of the Three-eyed Family, pt 1)</title>
<summary>The moment Sharaku recognizes the ancient script of the three-eyed family inscribed on a mysterious ball sent from Baron Goblin, he revives a "heavenly bird" from inside. The bird attacks anyone who tries to contain the power of the three-eyed ones.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35381" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守れ! 第三の目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protecting the Third Eye (Capital in Underground, pt 3)</title>
<summary>The archeologist named Kusai was in fact a ruins robber. Not knowing this, Dr. Kenmochi gets upset with Sharaku for messing up his research on the ruins. Declaring that he will forcibly perform an operation on Sharaku`s forehead so that he will never make any trouble, Dr. Kenmochi takes him to the hospital.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35382" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">321・ドカーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3, 2, 1, Bang!</title>
<summary>Sharaku and his friends find a strange jar while they are excavating the ruins. It is a device that corrects the wicked ones of the three-eyed family, and it explodes if you think something bad three times. The jar sticks to Sharaku and the others, and won`t go away!
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35383" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪植物ボルボック 決戦!写楽VSボルボック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown; Sharaku vs. Bolbocc! (Wearied Plant Bolbocc, pt 5)</title>
<summary>Bolbocc`s weakness is finally identified: it is salt water. Sharaku discharges salt water by using an underground tank. But Bolbocc turns salt water into fresh water with the terrible power of his aura. At the end of their rope, Sharaku and the others finally find an unexpected hint in the stone circle.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35384" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ岩山の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Three-Rock Mountain</title>
<summary>Sharaku, who is just like a little kid while the bandage is on his forehead, gives a bouquet to pretty Wato. Wato is delighted, as she is somewhat in love with Sharaku. But when Wato and Sharaku are forced to join the Judo Club as a punishment; it is revealed that Sharaku has stolen the flowers from the flowerbed that the Judo Club keeps. An unimaginable discovery awaits them at the three-rock mountain when they go there for training camp.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35385" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ目族の謎・湖底に眠るひみつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Under the Bottom of the Lake (Mystery of the Three-eyed Family, pt 2)</title>
<summary>After narrowly escaping the attack of the heavenly bird, Wato and Sharaku start to look for the treasure of the three-eyed family. Baron Goblin follows them, also hoping to make the treasure his own.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35386" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発見! 伝説の怪物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Monster Is Discovered!</title>
<summary>Sharaku goes on a hot-spring trip with Wato and other friends. Although they expect it to be a countrified place, they find it very crowded with people. They hear that a dinosaur has been spotted in a nearby swamp. Sharaku and the others start out to capture the dinosaur.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35387" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代王子ゴダル 最終兵器を探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Look for the Ultimate Weapon! (Ancient Prince Godal, pt 2)</title>
<summary>Wato`s body is still possessed by Godal`s spirit. Sharaku conspires to revive the three-eyed empire in cooperation with Godal.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35388" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イースター島航海 さようなら, ポゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Pogo (Easter Island Voyage, pt 4)</title>
<summary>Sharaku leaves for the Easter Island with Pogo. The mysterious organization also departs for the island following Sharaku. They intend to have Sharaku reveal the secret of the moai. Sharaku believes that the moai, the giant statues on Easter Island, could have been made by the three-eyed family.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35389" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ目族の謎・秘められた使命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Mission (Mystery of the Three-eyed Family, pt 4)</title>
<summary>The only thing they find of the treasures of the three-eyed family is a plain sheet of metal. But the very moment they expose it to the sunlight, it explodes. Sharaku`s third eye sheds tears as he starts to read the letters of the three-eyed people inscribed on the burnt wall. It is the will of the three-eyed family.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35390" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆発! 宇宙パワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Power Explodes!</title>
<summary>Do you know anything about pyramid power? Pyramids all over the world may be means of gathering cosmic energies. A group of three men try to monopolize the massive pyramid energy by using Sharaku.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35391" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超能力VS超魔術</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Psychic Power vs. Super Magic</title>
<summary>Sharaku goes to Garanputta`s super magic show with Wato. Garanputta performs magnificent magic capitalizing on his "mysterious three-eye" power. What if those eyes are real ..... Sharaku tries to meet him to confirm whether or not he is three-eyed.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35392" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代王子ゴダル 始動せよ! ゴモラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Activate Gomora! (Ancient Prince Godal, pt 3)</title>
<summary>Godal discovers the ultimate weapon, Gomora, from underground by using Sharaku. Gomora was a weapon that can freeze the vapor in the air, turn it into huge hailstones, and make them fall from the sky.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35393" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守れ! 地下の都</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect the Underground Capital (Capital in Underground, pt 2)</title>
<summary>An archeologist named Kusai appears and says he wants to investigate the ancient ruins that Sharaku has discovered. Sharaku and the party go on digging the ruins, and suddenly discover an underground capital. There even seem to be some residents.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35394" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モア暗殺計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassination Plan Against Moa</title>
<summary>The ultimate technology of the three-eyed family is hidden in the pyramid remains on the Yucatan. The evil organization has been after Moa because the bird holds the keys to opening the door of the remains. It is then revealed that only some blood of Moa can serve as the key. Once again, Moa faces danger.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35395" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守れ! ボクの宝物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect My Treasure! (Capital in Underground, pt 1)</title>
<summary>Dr. Kenmochi is planning to remove Sharaku`s third eye to deprive him of his super powers, thinking that he would be better off without it. But sensing danger, Sharaku starts to dig a hole in the ground to hide his treasure. Under the ground, there is a cavity housing ancient ruins.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35396" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うそ!? 写楽が悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Kidding? Sharaku Is a Devil?</title>
<summary>Sharaku is expelled from school on the grounds that he has been hanging around at nightclubs with a boss of the underground world. Unable to believe it, Wato starts to look into the truth.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35397" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女はヘビの使い?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is the Pretty Girl a Snake`s Messenger?</title>
<summary>Sharaku and his friends go camping in the deep woods. Sharaku and Wato sense something odd in Dr. Hebiya, a biologist and the father of twin girls, who has shown them to the log cabin.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35398" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪植物ボルボック 地底にひそむ影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow Lurking Under the Ground (Wearied Plant Bolbocc, pt 3)</title>
<summary>The girl who saves Sharaku and Wato is named Moegi, and she is the one who was growing Bolbocc. She is also three-eyed! For trying to win Bolbocc over to his side, Sharaku`s third eye is sealed by Bolbocc, who became violent.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="35399" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">受験戦争と平和!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Entrance Examinations and Peace?</title>
<summary>Sharaku is like a little kid while he has his bandage on. That`s why he does so poorly at school. Teachers start to threaten him that if he gets a "zero" on the upcoming test, he will be transferred to a different school.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="124150" update="2010-10-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1990-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124151" update="2010-10-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1990-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189337" update="2017-07-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189338" update="2017-07-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
