<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3205" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>54</episodecount>
<startdate>1967-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>1968-04-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Perman</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Super Dínamo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Paaman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Parman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">パーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">SUPERKID (1967)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3204" type="Sequel">Perman (1983)</anime>
<anime id="9025" type="Side Story">Ninja Hattori-kun Plus Perman: Ninja Kaijuu Jippou Tai Miracle Tamago</anime>
<anime id="9026" type="Side Story">Pa-Pa-Pa the Movie: Perman</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/tv/data/t_pa_man.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4732" type="Original Work">Fujiko F. Fujio</name>
<name id="4444" type="Music">Tsutsui Hiroshi</name>
<name id="782" type="Work">Tokyo Movie</name>
</creators>
<description>After Mitsuo receives a mask from a retiring superhero, he becomes Paaman.
Note: Each episode contains 2 stories.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="22">3.32</permanent>
<temporary count="22">5.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204408.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1438</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6303</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1766</identifier>
<identifier>cfcqyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/tv/data/t_pa_man.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Perman_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>パーマン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89635</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1092</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="52352" update="2015-02-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン誕生 / ロボットママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth of Perman / Robot Mother</title>
<summary>Each episode was divided in 2 sub-episodes (A and B). (Sandwhich format)
Episode 1A = Birth of Perman
Episode 1B = Robot transformed Mitsuo`s mother</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="70265" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘パーマン2号の巻 / そうなん救助の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70266" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン野球 / お花見はこわい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70267" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット騒ぎ / ひろったピストルの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70268" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">どっちがパーマンの巻 / ブルドック騒動の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70269" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パー子にまかせて / 砂漠のジン魔神の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70270" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンの親孝行の巻 / パーマンのおくりものの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70271" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぬけ出したロボットの巻 / パーマン出動せよの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70272" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">空飛ぶダンプカーの巻 / パーマンくらべの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70273" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">まいった迷子の巻 / ニセ札を追えの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70274" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パー子はだあれ? の巻 / ぼくはぼくだの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70275" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パパ・パーマンの巻 / 手紙はささ舟にのせての巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70276" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生げき退作戦の巻 / レイ・カーの秘密とホットケーキの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70277" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">がっちりパーやんの巻 / パーマン・忍者大決闘の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70278" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン用心棒の巻 / 川でマグロが大漁の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70279" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐竜はどこにいるの巻 / パーマン対ガンマンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70280" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ズボンを川に流したの巻 / ウソつき合戦の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70281" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン臨海学校の巻 / 海底探検の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70282" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">小鳥の怪獣の巻 / パーマン花火の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70283" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">南の島に石が降るの巻 / ゆうれい温泉の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70284" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン林間学校の巻 / 荒野のパーマンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70285" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙われたパーマンの巻 / パーマン基地計画の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70286" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン全員集合の巻 / 時速は364キロの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70287" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パー子は迷コックの巻 / 怪人200面相の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70288" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンアルバイトの巻 / ポップコーン作戦の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70289" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポンコツロボットの巻 / でて来いスパイ団の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70290" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン5号は? の巻 / ワニザメ船長の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70291" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンひとりぼっちの巻 / 地獄谷のパーマンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70292" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">イナイ, イナイ屋敷のもやし君の巻 / ギャングとおばあさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70293" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンと新聞少年 / 宿なしパーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70294" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン冒険記 / 女の子はこわい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70295" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画にでようの巻 / パーマンに手を出すなの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70296" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガン子の千歳飴 / パーマン5号の初手柄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70297" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンはジャンケンに弱い / ロボット・ギャング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70298" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">盗まれたパーマンの巻 / パーマンプロレス一本勝負の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70299" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン2号は社長さん / 怪人200面相の挑戦状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70300" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンの落しものの巻 / 怪人ゴリアテ大暴れの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70301" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍者がクリスマスにやってきたの巻 / パーマンはおもちゃの王様の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70302" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">年賀状をさがせ / ことしもがんばるぞ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70303" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンはラッパでよぼう / パーマン絶対絶命の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70304" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">のぞかれたパーマン / オカメ仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70305" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ここほれパーマンの巻 / 1000万人の中の1人の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70306" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パー坊捕物作戦 / のろわれたダイヤの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70307" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪男退治 / 冷凍魔あらわる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70308" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うしパーマン / 逆襲パーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70309" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">うわさのパーマンの巻 / 動物が人間になったの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 46</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70310" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">密林の王者パーザン / 夜の魔王アカベロンの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 47</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70311" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">おひなさまを守れ / パーマン西遊記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 48</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70312" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">きらわれたパーマンの巻 / とうめい人間の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 49</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70313" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">新兵器はいかが / パーマンピンチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 51</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70314" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の流れ星 / 流れ星作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 50</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70315" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマン大決心 / パーマン家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 52</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70316" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーマンのメイ探偵 / 動くな! パーマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 53</title>
</episode>
<episode id="70317" update="2007-04-02">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パー子という名の女の子 / パーマンよいつまでも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 54</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195741" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195742" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195743" update="2018-02-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213730" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">再放送用オープニングＡ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening A for rebroadcasting</title>
<summary>Starts with name of anime showing on screen, letters moves, perman fly out, perman money fly behind him...</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="213731" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">本放送用エンディングＡ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending A for this broadcast</title>
<summary>We see Perman standing from behind, he put on his mask...</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="213732" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">本放送用オープニング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening A for Main Broadcasting</title>
<summary>Opening ends with Milky candy box falling on ground</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="213733" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">本放送用オープニングＢ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening B for this broadcast</title>
<summary>Opening ends with Milky candy box falling on ground</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="213734" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">小学館の学習雑誌CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shogakkan learning magazine CM</title>
<summary>Perman CM for Shogakkan magazine</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="213735" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">週刊少年サンデーCM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weekly Shonen Sunday CM</title>
<summary>Perman Weekly Shonen Sunday CM</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
