<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3207" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2007-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Demashita! Powerpuff Girls Z</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Las Chicas Superpoderosas Z</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Atomówki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Demashitaa! Powerpuff Girls Z</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Power Puff Girls Z</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ppgz</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">出ましたっ! パワパフガールズZ</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Les Supers Nanas Zeta</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Powerpuff Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Super Poderosas</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">As Meninas Superpoderosas: Geração Z</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Powerpuff Girls Z</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7529" approval="5" total="14">Panty &amp; Stocking with Garterbelt</anime>
<anime id="6055" approval="1" total="4">Stitch!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="431902">Apparently America raping stuff coming outta Japan also goes the other way around. It can be slightly funny at times, but that`s about it (not to mention it`s extremely rare). Don`t expect anything other than superficial references to the original series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="117027">It may not resemble very much the original US animation but is a good non serious approach in anime style of the story adding some of the cliches and humor common in anime, the main difference they now are magical girl heroines. Enjoy it only if you don`t take it seriously.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/ppgz/</url>
<creators>
<name id="762" type="Unknown Relation">Aniplex</name>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="4243" type="Series Composition">Urasawa Yoshio</name>
<name id="6474" type="Character Design">Shimogasa Miho</name>
<name id="6474" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shimogasa Miho</name>
<name id="9330" type="Music">Nakamura Hiroshi</name>
<name id="14429" type="Music">Taichi Master</name>
<name id="10090" type="Original Work">Craig McCracken</name>
<name id="10169" type="Direction">Ishiguro Megumu</name>
</creators>
<description>Whilst Professor Utonium and his son assistant Ken were studying the unknown substance Chemical X, a rice cake accidentally fall into it. A violent chemical reaction occurs, transforming Chemical X into a whole new substance, Chemical Z.
That same day, a huge iceberg suddenly appeared off the coast of Tokyo City and Ken fires a Chemical Z ray-beam at the iceberg. The Chemical Z beam changes into white and black lights which are released into Tokyo City. Ordinary first-year junior high girls Akatsutsumi Momoko, Gotokuji Miyako, and Matsubara Kaoru are bathed in white lights and their normal lives are disrupted.
Thus, the Powerpuff Girls Z are born!
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="364">2.63</permanent>
<temporary count="380">5.55</temporary>
<review count="2">5.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10887.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1221</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3753</identifier>
<identifier>penxut</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/ppgz/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Powerpuff_Girls_Z</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>出ましたっ!パワパフガールズZ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>940</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>325715</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8297</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2796" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>movie</name>
<description>Based on a live action film, Japanese or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3714" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Western animated cartoon</name>
<description>An anime series which originally started as a Western/American cartoon series or movie, but was later changed/adapted and remade specifically for the Japanese audience, and done through local anime studios within Japan.
See also: http://anidb.net/t4424 [American derived]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4424" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>American derived</name>
<description>A work which was created as a continuation/remake of an American based franchise or cartoon series. These works are completely Japan original, but which lack roots within Japanese media.
See also: http://anidb.net/t3714 [cartoon remake]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1718" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Hyper Blossom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momoko is the first member of the Powerpuff Girls Z squad. She transforms using the phrase "Hyper-Blossom" and fights villains with a yo-yo. Like the original, she is the self-proclaimed leader of the team. She is a bit boy-crazy, and is an otaku (a nod to the original Blossom`s nerdy intelligence). She is very familiar with the mahou shoujo genre, along with some typical anime/super sentai concepts and is famous for being a "hero maniac" in school, especially by Kaoru. Momoko also has a strong appetite for candies and other sweets, and spends much of her time snacking. Because of this, most of her attacks are named after food. In addition, she dislikes vegetables and is afraid of bugs and dentists. Although she can be easily distracted and has been known to whine, Momoko tries her best to protect Tokyo City, lead the girls, and help her friends regardless of her situation. Often she can be very clever and crafty when needed, usually being the first to come up with a plan to trick or defeat villains/monsters. She is the elder daughter of Hachizou and Kakiko Akadutsumi and has a younger sister named Kuriko. She is represented by hearts. She dreams of being married in the future.</description>
<picture>16264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14444" type="main character in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Rolling Bubbles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyako is the second member of the Powerpuff Girls Z team. She transforms using the phrase "Rolling Bubbles" and uses a bubble wand staff as a weapon. In comparison to the original Bubbles, who was known for being the most childish of the girls, Miyako is quite mature, as she was the most successful at being a mother to Ken, but she`s the ditziest member of the three, often appearing a bit clueless, and doesn`t seem to understand her powers completely, along with a few other things. She is the only member of the girls who, like some villains, end a few sentences with a phrase. Her phrase is desu wa. She is very friendly and polite, as she always uses honorifics at the end of names, although she too can be angered when provoked and is not above pretending to cry to get what she wants. Trendy and stylish, Bubbles enjoys shopping and fashion the most. Although she is popular with the boys at school, she already has feelings for Takaaki (Taka-chan), a boy who saved her from bullies when she was six who she later visits in the hospital everyday. She also uses curlers (3 balls on each pigtail) when going to bed. Miyako remains typified, however, by the original`s compassion, gentleness and innocence, as well as her love of animals and her favorite doll, Octi. She lives with only her grandmother. Her parents live in Kyoto. She is represented by bubbles. She dreams of being a fashion designer or model in the future.</description>
<picture>42036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2360" picture="228063.jpg">Miyahara Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14445" type="main character in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Powered Buttercup</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaoru is the third and final member of the Powerpuff Girls Z team. She transforms using the phrase "Powered Buttercup" and uses a Daruma Otoshi hammer. She hates skirts and other girly things, which is the reason why she was reluctant to join the group. In fact, she even hates girls who are too feminine. Like the original Buttercup, Kaoru is a tomboy and is the most easily enraged of the three. Famous for being the most athletic girl in school, Buttercup enjoys all kinds of sports and spends a great deal of time watching sports on television. She is especially good at soccer. She speaks with a hard and masculine edge and rarely uses honorifics when speaking, though she will speak a little more like a girl in later episodes. Her greatest fear is ghosts. Kaoru also has a slight crush on Butch Z after holding her kiss until told she could stop. Kaoru lives with her father, who is a professional masked-wrestler, mother and two brothers, one older and one younger. She is represented by stars. She dreams of being a professional wrestler like her dad in the future. Her jacket is yellow-green.</description>
<picture>42038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7041" picture="78916.jpg">Kawana Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14446" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<name>Akazutsumi Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momoko is the first member of the Powerpuff Girls Z squad. She transforms using the phrase "Hyper-Blossom" and fights villains with a yo-yo. Like the original, she is the self-proclaimed leader of the team. She is a bit boy-crazy, and is an otaku (a nod to the original Blossom`s nerdy intelligence). She is very familiar with the maho shoujo genre, along with some typical anime/super sentai concepts and is famous for being a "hero maniac" in school, especially by Kaoru. Momoko also has a strong appetite for candies and other sweets, and spends much of her time snacking. Because of this, most of her attacks are named after food. In addition, she dislikes vegetables and is afraid of bugs and dentists. Although she can be easily distracted and has been known to whine, Momoko tries her best to protect Tokyo City, lead the girls, and help her friends regardless of her situation. Often she can be very clever and crafty when needed, usually being the first to come up with a plan to trick or defeat villains/monsters. She is the elder daughter of Hachizou and Kakiko Akadutsumi and has a younger sister named Kuriko. She is represented by hearts. She dreams of being married in the future.</description>
<picture>42039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14447" type="main character in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Goutokuji Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyako is the second member of the Powerpuff Girls Z team. She transforms using the phrase "Rolling Bubbles" and uses a bubble wand staff as a weapon. In comparison to the original Bubbles, who was known for being the most childish of the girls, Miyako is quite mature, as she was the most successful at being a mother to Ken, but she`s the ditziest member of the three, often appearing a bit clueless, and doesn`t seem to understand her powers completely, along with a few other things. She is the only member of the girls who, like some villains, end a few sentences with a phrase. Her phrase is desu wa. She is very friendly and polite, as she always uses honorifics at the end of names, although she too can be angered when provoked and is not above pretending to cry to get what she wants. Trendy and stylish, Bubbles enjoys shopping and fashion the most. Although she is popular with the boys at school, she already has feelings for Takaaki (Taka-chan), a boy who saved her from bullies when she was six who she later visits in the hospital everyday. She also uses curlers (3 balls on each pigtail) when going to bed. Miyako remains typified, however, by the original`s compassion, gentleness and innocence, as well as her love of animals and her favorite doll, Octi. She lives with only her grandmother. Her parents live in Kyoto. She is represented by bubbles. She dreams of being a fashion designer or model in the future.</description>
<picture>42040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2360" picture="228063.jpg">Miyahara Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14448" type="main character in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Matsubara Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaoru is the third and final member of the Powerpuff Girls Z team. She transforms using the phrase "Powered Buttercup" and uses a Daruma Otoshi hammer. She hates skirts and other girly things, which is the reason why she was reluctant to join the group. In fact, she even hates girls who are too feminine. Like the original Buttercup, Kaoru is a tomboy and is the most easily enraged of the three. Famous for being the most athletic girl in school, Buttercup enjoys all kinds of sports and spends a great deal of time watching sports on television. She is especially good at soccer. She speaks with a hard and masculine edge and rarely uses honorifics when speaking, though she will speak a little more like a girl in later episodes. Her greatest fear is ghosts. Kaoru also has a slight crush on Butch Z after holding her kiss until told she could stop. Kaoru lives with her father, who is a professional masked-wrestler, mother and two brothers, one older and one younger. She is represented by stars. She dreams of being a professional wrestler like her dad in the future. Her jacket is yellow-green.</description>
<picture>42041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7041" picture="78916.jpg">Kawana Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14449" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Kitazawa Utonium</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This series`s version of Professor Utonium. His real name is unknown, aside from his family name Kitazawa. In this incarnation, he has a son named Ken, who is responsible for all those affected by the Chemical Z lights, especially the Powerpuff Girls Z. Professor Utonium was originally experimenting with the substance Chemical X and strove to find a way to change its chemical properties. Professor Utonium has created several inventions throughout the series; the most important one being his Chemical Z Particle Ray, which allows him to transform those affected by the lights back to normal (although it doesn`t prevent recurring transformations nor is it able to work on all black light victims). He seems to be aware of the effect Ken`s lack of a mother has had on his son, assuming that it had caused him to be a bully to the girls. However, this does not change his behavior towards Ken. He appears to be a gentle father figure like the original Professor Utonium was in The Powerpuff Girls. He treats the girls like members of his family and is very close to the Mayor and Miss Bellum. While he is very gentle and serious, Professor Utonium may, at times, act a little less mature than he usually does. In episode 37, when the Powerpuff Girls Z are "grounded" from using their powers for a day when they have to take a test in school, Professor Utonium fills in for them, donning an exosuit with a laser beam gun and rocket pack, calling himself "Utonium Z" (this is most likely based on the American cartoon episode "Powerprof" in which he also donned a fighting suit but drove the girls crazy with lame one-liners during battles). He also appears to have a mecha that looks like Utonium Z, which he uses against the Mojo Robo. Although he seems unsuccessful at first, he is able to defeat Mojo Jojo, Fuzzy Lumpkins, and the Amoeba Boys. His main attack is the Uto Beam. At the end of the episode, Ken, Peach and himself call themselves "Powerpuff Boys Z" as their own self-proclaimed superhero team.</description>
<picture>42042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14450" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Kitazawa Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young boy genius, the 8 year-old son of Professor Utonium who is somewhat responsible for turning regular girls into the Powerpuff Girls Z and numerous other characters into villains using Chemical Z. He used it to blast a glacier in order to set the weather back to normal, but the impact resulted in the explosion of several lights, which affected all those who came in contact with it. Despite being younger than the girls, he acts a lot more mature and the education he receives from his father is considered more advanced than what the girls learn in their school, earning his PhD at an early age. Ken, in a later episode, attended school in order to gain social skills and make friends. While he considers grade school life boring, he has made several friends, including Jou (who was originally his rival) and Cassey (Blossom`s little sister). Ken sees the girls as older sisters and has to often put up with them, though he still cares for them deeply. Ken interchanges between calling Professor Utonium Papa and Professor. During a serious situation (such as a monster attack or investigative purposes) he will try to refer to Utonium as "Professor," but in less serious situations (like packing a lunch) he will call him "Papa." Ken often corrects himself, because he usually uses the wrong honorific (eg. "Papa, I mean, Professor"). In Episode 26, it is revealed that Ken`s mother works on a space station, therefore making her very busy and unable to be with Ken. Thanks to the girls and Santa Claus (whom he believed did not exist at first based on a 70% possibility), he was able to see her and is now able to communicate with her clearly on the lab`s monitor. In episode 37, when the Powerpuff Girls Z are "grounded" from using their powers for a day when they have to take a test in school, Ken fills in for them, donning a superhero suit consisting of a black bodysuit, a white cape, white gloves, white boots, a red vest with gold shoulder pads and a yellow "Z" on it, and a blue helmet with the yellow letters "KK" on it, while brandishing a blue polearm with a yellow "U" at the end, and calling himself "Ken Kitazawa Z". Despite having no powers or attacks, he uses traps and other props as weapons when he defends their lab from the Gangreen Gang, ultimately driving them off by tricking them into drinking bottles of hot sauce (thinking they were the containers of Chemical Z). Ken`s pre-production art bares a strong resemblance to Dexter from Dexter`s Laboratory, even the current incarnation. However, in one of the special edition DVD booklets, it is explained the design originated from Kid Utonium from the original series.</description>
<picture>42043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3969" picture="48838.jpg">Oomoto Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14451" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Peach</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ken`s pet robot dog. Peach was also affected by a white light, gaining the ability to talk, as well as a considerable boost in intelligence. Peach`s shout prompts the girls to transform either in person or through a long-distance communication device, although a modification to the girls` compacts allows them to transform on their own. Additionally, Peach can re-summon the girls` powers, even when their powers are drained. Peach is also capable of sniffing out those who are affected by the black lights, white lights, and Him`s black particles. The black light monsters/villains that have been sniffed by Peach are stored in his data banks for later reference. This ability, however, is hindered if his target is wearing heavy cosmetics (as was the case with Sedusa). Peach is also capable of sniffing and identifying others more clearly than other dogs, even when someone`s appearance has been completely changed. Peach`s phrases always end with a bark (or "wan," literally his bark). He is also able to understand cats. It is possible Peach is based after "The Talking Dog" as well as the Powerpuff Hotline. Like many recurring characters, he was given his own symbol, a Bone. In episode 37, when the Powerpuff Girls Z are "grounded" from using their powers for a day when they have to take a test in school, Peach fills in for them, wearing a skintight brown jumpsuit with black trim, and brandishing a nunchaku made of two bones linked together, and calling himself "Peach Z". He assists Ken in dealing with the Gangreen Gang, making short work of them with his nunchaku.</description>
<picture>42044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14452" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Mayor-shichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Mayor of Tokyo City. His design is distinctly different from his American counterpart, as he is of normal height and has no monocle or top hat. A caveman version of the Mayor that is closer to the original design does make an appearance in episode 51 briefly. While less extreme in comparison to the original Mayor, the Mayor in this series is very childish and has a very short attention span. He seems to worry quite a lot when the girls are fighting, and wishes that they could cause a little less damage. The Mayor, like many of the characters in the anime, loves sweets. The Mayor also has a younger brother, who is the Principal of the school Blossom, Bubbles, and Buttercup attend. It was through him that Miss Bellum and the Mayor were able rearrange the classes, so that the girls would be in the same class. However, the Mayor and the Principal, don`t always get along, and even the most minor of things will set off an argument, which often time leads to name calling. He also deals with his brother when the girls aren`t doing well in class due to them skipping class to save the city.</description>
<picture>42045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14453" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Miss Bellum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Like the original Miss Bellum, her face doesn`t appear on screen; however, unlike the original, she is now blonde. Usually, Miss Bellum covers her face with a tablet computer, which has lips imprinted on it. While the Mayor is different from his original counterpart, Miss Bellum still does most of his work for him, and still appears to be the brains of the operation. She also instructs the girls a bit, which she has done several times in the original. Fuzzy Lumpkins has a crush on her; however, she dislikes Fuzzy. In Episode 51, a pre-historic version of Miss Bellum is shown as the inventor of fire after being hit by a way-ward Chemical Z Light particle that scattered across Earth`s timeline. At one point in pre-production, Miss Bellum had facial features. She is represented by lip prints like the one on her tablet computer.</description>
<picture>42046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3732" picture="25105.jpg">Kawanami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14454" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Keane-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another "returning" supporting character, Miss Keane first appears in episode 3. She is very pretty and loved by her male students, although the female students don`t like her as much, especially Himeko. Miss Keane, like the original, is kind and incredibly patient. She is talented in many ways, which she used to counter Blossom, Bubbles, and Buttercup`s excuses; this includes knowledge on medicine for non-existent medical conditions, such as dislocation of the stomach, and is able to speak mole and English. She is also unfazed by the destruction Mojo causes and speaks to him as if he were a normal human being. In fact, in episode 33 when Mojo asks her out on a date, she gladly accepts and even enjoys the date (though she still treats him as a monkey, as in ordering a "monkey ticket" for him at a movie house while getting an adult ticket for herself). At the end of that episode, though, it is also revealed that Miss Keane has a mole-man boyfriend named Uneo, who appears in an earth-tunneling vehicle that emerges from the ground to pick her up.</description>
<picture>42051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1940" picture="21213.jpg">Akiya Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14455" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="1">9.03</rating>
<name>Mojo Jojo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most frequently recurring villain in the series. His speech follows the conventions of Mojo Jojo in the original Japanese dub of Powerpuff Girls; he does not speak quickly, but ends his sentences with "Mojo". He was a normal monkey mistreated by some humans in the Tokyo City Zoo until he was affected by a black light from Chemical Z making him highly intelligent, seeking revenge on all humans. Now he can fly and has some martial arts abilities. He is still about the same size as the original as the giant cape conceals his small figure (in some concept art, Mojo controls mechanical legs under his giant cape, which makes him look taller than he really is). Mojo Jojo`s height with mechanical legs is 7`10" tall. Mojo also possesses a destructive - though largely redundant - robot called Mojo Robo, which is often modified in each episode. Mojo currently lives in an abandoned house next to the Tokyo City Tower, where he repairs Mojo Robo, builds other devices, eating whatever food he bought or stole, and spends some quality time watching TV. He seems to have an obsession with food, mainly sweets (which he shares with Blossom). Mojo Jojo`s true plan is to take over the world, but it appears that food is important to him to accomplish his ambition. Like the original, he is also responsible for the creation of the Rowdyruff Boys. Unfortunately, the boys don`t have any respect for him and use his parental love for them to their advantage. They refer to him as "Mama", until they abandon him when they no longer need to use him. Since Episode 33 it becomes apparent that Mojo harbors feelings for Ms. Keane, who was very kind to him despite both his appearance and his actions in episode 19, but in the end Ms Keane rejects his affections for a Mole Man. Like many recurring characters he has his own symbol, a bunch of bananas. However, in the TV airing of episode 1, Mojo had his Initials (M J Y, The first letter of each Kana of his name) in the background. During the DVD release, and re-airings, they were changed to bananas. Mojo is one of the few monsters has not had Professor Utonium`s reversion ray used on him.</description>
<picture>42047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14456" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Fuzzy Lumpkins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second villain shown in the series. Made his debut in episode 6. After the explosion of the Chemical Z ray, one of the black lights landed in the forest, creating the monster Fuzzy Lumpkins. Fuzzy`s height is 6`1" tall. In this incarnation, the PPG villain is more or less the same as the original Fuzzy Lumpkins. While his cabin and (boomstick) are missing, he is still very destructive and rude, although nice enough to at least move an old man out of the way and signing a girl`s autograph before going on his rampage. To Fuzzy, whatever he touches is considered his property, which he usually marks with his paw print. Those around him are considered to be trespassers. He is incredibly strong and can withstand most of the Powerpuff Girls Z`s attacks and can even effortlessly stop Powered Buttercup`s hammer with his bare hand, until they became stronger and more experienced than him. His big weakness is that he has a crush on Miss Bellum. Fuzzy is also very talented when it comes to playing the banjo. It is never revealed what Fuzzy Lumpkins originally was before he was hit by the black light. Fuzzy ends all of his sentences with the phrase de mon da. He is represented by a hand print, the same one he uses to mark what he wants as his property. He is among the unique villains in that the ray created by Professor Utonium to revert black light affected persons to normal had no effect on him.</description>
<picture>42048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14457" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<name>Shirogane Himeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although she made her appearance as early as episode 1, she officially appeared as a villain in episode 6. Based on the original villain Princess Morbucks, this incarnation of Princess is an incredibly snobby rich young girl who was affected by the black Chemical Z light. At first, it didn`t take effect, but her anger towards the Powerpuff Girls Z became unbearable, and soon she turned into a psychotic looking version of her former self, which was appropriately dubbed "Princess-sama" (or Monster Princess by girls). Himeko is constantly looking for attention from her classmates, but the current popularity of the Powerpuff Girls Z infuriates her as well as anyone who gets more attention than she does (her reason for not liking Ms. Keane). This is all due to her jealousy towards her more talented older sister Miko, who gets her parents` attention and in turn causes them to neglect Himeko. Whenever Himeko`s cat Sapphire screeches (usually by accident), she transforms into Princess. Princess` abilities change from episode to episode, but she possesses basic abilities similar to the girls such as flight and enhanced strength. She appears to have some sort of hammerspace as she can produce items at any time, such as a rocket launcher, her diamond claw, and money. In episode 16, Princess` hair style and abilities change based on which special collar Professor Utonium places on Sapphire, each of the collars has an animal on it. Himeko has no memory of Princess` activities. Himeko is also very suspicious of Momoko, Miyako, and Kaoru`s habit of skipping class. She tries to unveil the truth, although she fails to do so. A common running gag with Princess is whenever she is caught by the Powerpuff Girls Z, they knock her out of the air and catch her in a giant purse, often calmly saying `yes, okay` before leaving. She is represented by a small crown, similar to the one worn on her head, as well as various monetary symbols. Like the girls she is given a henshin sequence.</description>
<picture>42049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3180" picture="24696.jpg">Ikeda Chigusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14458" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<name>Princess</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although she made her appearance as early as episode 1, she officially appeared as a villain in episode 6. Based on the original villain Princess Morbucks, this incarnation of Princess is an incredibly snobby rich young girl who was affected by the black Chemical Z light. At first, it didn`t take effect, but her anger towards the Powerpuff Girls Z became unbearable, and soon she turned into a psychotic looking version of her former self, which was appropriately dubbed "Princess-sama" (or Monster Princess by girls). Himeko is constantly looking for attention from her classmates, but the current popularity of the Powerpuff Girls Z infuriates her as well as anyone who gets more attention than she does (her reason for not liking Ms. Keane). This is all due to her jealousy towards her more talented older sister Miko, who gets her parents` attention and in turn causes them to neglect Himeko. Whenever Himeko`s cat Sapphire screeches (usually by accident), she transforms into Princess. Princess` abilities change from episode to episode, but she possesses basic abilities similar to the girls such as flight and enhanced strength. She appears to have some sort of hammerspace as she can produce items at any time, such as a rocket launcher, her diamond claw, and money. In episode 16, Princess` hair style and abilities change based on which special collar Professor Utonium places on Sapphire, each of the collars has an animal on it. Himeko has no memory of Princess` activities. Himeko is also very suspicious of Momoko, Miyako, and Kaoru`s habit of skipping class. She tries to unveil the truth, although she fails to do so. A common running gag with Princess is whenever she is caught by the Powerpuff Girls Z, they knock her out of the air and catch her in a giant purse, often calmly saying `yes, okay` before leaving. She is represented by a small crown, similar to the one worn on her head, as well as various monetary symbols. Like the girls she is given a henshin sequence.</description>
<picture>42050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3180" picture="24696.jpg">Ikeda Chigusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14459" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Silk Hat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silk Hat is the leader of the group. He has green eyes and blue `skin`. Like his name suggests, he has a top hat and a pipe to go along. He is the equivalent of Bossman, the leader of Amoeba Boys in the original Powerpuff Girls.</description>
<picture>42052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14460" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Amoeba Boys</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Amoeba Boys made their debut appearance in episode 7. Despite their name, they are two males and one female. They were three ordinary amoebas before they were hit by one of the black lights. The Amoeba Boys wish to be real criminals, but like their original counterparts, they are unsuccessful, with their size, about the size of a persons foot, being the primary reason for their constant failure as well as their own incompetence. They also have the ability to merge and grow into a giant yellow amoeba that, despite its size, is too weak to cause any real damage. The Amoeba Boys, like Mojo, have yet to have the reversion ray used on them, and are unique in that they are the only villains to date who have never been captured by the girls.</description>
<picture>42053.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14461" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Poncho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In spite of his name, he does not have a poncho. He does have a cowboy hat that is tied around his neck. Poncho has green skin and blue eyes. His blue eyes are often hidden by his hat. Poncho seems to be the tough guy of the group. The attitude and the hat are possible references to Clint Eastwood.</description>
<picture>42054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14462" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Lady</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As her name suggests, she is the only female in the group. She wears a feminine hat with a rose on the side. She has pink skin and yellow eyes. Lady is the only amoeba wearing lipstick. She appears to be the voice of reason in the group. She later leaves the group and joins Princess and Sedusa in episode 28. In this episode it is also revealed that Lady has the power to inflate herself for battle into an enlarged version of herself that`s slippery enough to fend off most attacks. However, if she`s not careful in this form she`ll pop like a balloon and will have to reform herself.</description>
<picture>42055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1827" picture="55501.jpg">Uran Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14463" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Ace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once again the leader of the Gangreen Gang. Ace`s height is 6`1 tall. Ace lives with his parents, who constantly argue about how he has changed due to the lack of good parenting, and his four sisters. Ace is always at the forefront of the Gangreen Gang`s schemes and always has final word on whatever the gang does. However, after their first defeat at the hands of the Powerpuff Girls Z, he begins to hold a grudge against them and swears revenge after being again defeated by Buttercup. He is well respected by the rest of the gang, especially by Snake. In battle, Ace tosses cards at his opponents, most of which are aces.</description>
<picture>42056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14464" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Big Billy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The muscle man for the Gangreen Gang. Big Billy`s height is 7`5 tall. Unlike the original Big Billy, this incarnation appears to be capable of thought and can speak properly without having to say `duuh`. Big Billy has a bigger and stronger aunt, uncle and older brother, who wish Big Billy would work for once. Like the original, he is a cyclops, but this time his eye is actually visible through his hair. Big Billy loves to eat and will gobble more junk than the rest of the gang. He uses his size and sheer power to his advantage in battle. However, his strength pales in comparison to Buttercup`s.</description>
<picture>42057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14465" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Little Arturo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The shortest of the Gangreen Gang. Little Arturo is now a girl, but the fast speech pattern of the original remains. Little Arturo has nine siblings and is often overlooked by her parents because of this. She is the least patient of the Gangreen Gang and will begin to fidget if she stays in one place too long. She is the fastest of the Gangreen Gang, but she doesn`t use it to her advantage in battle. Furthermore, she tires out fairly easily.</description>
<picture>42058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3645" picture="25834.jpg">Yamamoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14466" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Snake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second tallest of the Gangreen Gang. Snake`s reimagining is a far cry from his original incarnation. Snake has a father, who appears to be involved in some high position or profession. Snake ends his sentence with `su` and will occasionally toss in English phrases. He appears to be the least confident of the Gangreen Gang. He does, however, have a lot of respect for Ace as he considers Ace to be the only true leader of the gang. (It was also implied that he &amp; Ace have an intimate relationship, but that seems to be kept a secret to the public). Snake is very good at massaging and will use it to hypnotize his enemies.</description>
<picture>42059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14467" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Grubber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oddest member of the Gangreen Gang. Like the original, Grubber ordinarily is unable to speak properly. Rather than blowing raspberries, Grubber instead makes an odd grunt. His father resembles him and has the same speech pattern. Possibly in reference to the original, Grubber can change his form to match anyone he wants. Unlike Sedusa, who has a similar ability, Grubber`s disguise is never complete. His green skin, eyes, and tongue are still visible through his disguise. Oddly enough, with the exception of the Powerpuff Girls Z, no one can see through his disguise.</description>
<picture>42060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14468" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Gangreen Gang</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>This series` Gangreen Gang, who appeared in episode 14. Like in the original series, they are more of a group of juvenile delinquents than criminals. Each of the Gangreen Gang members came from families that resemble themselves, except that the families do not share the gang`s green skin color. Unlike previous villains, it is never shown how the Gangreen Gang received the black light, however they do emit the black aura that signifies a black light villain/monster. The Gangreen Gang continually seeks to cause trouble, going as far as playing a prank on the restaurant manager to get free food or spraying graffiti all over a building. Unlike the originals, the Gangreen Gang is less cowardly and will face those who stand in their way. Unfortunately, they`re incredibly weak against the Powerpuff Girls Z and are unable to overpower or outsmart them. Besides Fuzzy Lumpkins, the Gangreen Gang are the only characters unable to return to normal through Professor Utonium`s Chemical Z Particle Ray. True to their name, they are represented by the color green, instead of a symbol.</description>
<picture>42061.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14469" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Kintoki Sakurako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sedusa officially appeared in episode 8. Sedusa can drastically alter her appearance by adding or removing makeup and is a master of disguise, which Sedusa was known for in the original Powerpuff Girls alongside her seductive manner. She takes the form of many people in order to get into stores and steal from them, including Bubbles and Buttercup. Sedusa is the alter-ego of the girls` friend, Sakurako. Sakurako works at a shop, well-known around the area for her desserts (Momoko, Miyako, Kaoru, Himeko, and Miss Bellum often visit the shop because of this). When working at her shop, she wanted to be sexy after seeing Miss Bellum. Sakurako has a crush on Rukuro, a boy who comes to her shop often; this was her primary reason for wanting to be "sexy" like Miss Bellum. In order to become Sedusa, Sakurako must use lipstick. With a little makeup, she can take on the appearance of anyone, although anything like the scent of perfume won`t be masked. She, with her looks, is also able to coax many nearby males into doing what she wants. She is also able to perform the original Sedusa`s signature hair whip/tentacle attacks. She was defeated and later transformed back into Sakurako through the use of Professor Utonium`s Chemical Z Particle Ray. Sakurako was able to win Rukuro`s heart at the end of episode 8, although the two are still shy to each other. Sakurako later appears in episode 25, receiving flowers from Rukuro and she also soothes Here, a flower who fell victim to the black powder. Like Himeko/Princess, Sakurako can still transform into Sedusa at any time as long as lipstick is applied on Sakurako. It was revealed in episode 28 that the lipstick doesn`t even need to be applied directly to her lips; she will still transform into Sedusa if it`s smeared on her face. Like Sakurako, Sedusa loves Rukuro, but Rukuro, although generally nice to her, does not love her the way he loves Sakurako. In episode 45, Rukuro finds out about Sakurako/Sedusa when Sakurako decides to visit him at the college he attends. Upon finding this out, Rukuro confesses that he loves Sakurako but hates Sedusa. This confuses Sedusa to the point where she faints out of stress. After turning back to normal, Sakurako has no memory of what happened as Sedusa. She is represented by red snakes like the one in her collar and a purple background, while her Good Civilian side is represented by the same flower image as on her bandanna.</description>
<picture>42062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14470" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Sedusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sedusa officially appeared in episode 8. Sedusa can drastically alter her appearance by adding or removing makeup and is a master of disguise, which Sedusa was known for in the original Powerpuff Girls alongside her seductive manner. She takes the form of many people in order to get into stores and steal from them, including Bubbles and Buttercup. Sedusa is the alter-ego of the girls` friend, Sakurako. Sakurako works at a shop, well-known around the area for her desserts (Momoko, Miyako, Kaoru, Himeko, and Miss Bellum often visit the shop because of this). When working at her shop, she wanted to be sexy after seeing Miss Bellum. Sakurako has a crush on Rukuro, a boy who comes to her shop often; this was her primary reason for wanting to be "sexy" like Miss Bellum. In order to become Sedusa, Sakurako must use lipstick. With a little makeup, she can take on the appearance of anyone, although anything like the scent of perfume won`t be masked. She, with her looks, is also able to coax many nearby males into doing what she wants. She is also able to perform the original Sedusa`s signature hair whip/tentacle attacks. She was defeated and later transformed back into Sakurako through the use of Professor Utonium`s Chemical Z Particle Ray. Sakurako was able to win Rukuro`s heart at the end of episode 8, although the two are still shy to each other. Sakurako later appears in episode 25, receiving flowers from Rukuro and she also soothes Here, a flower who fell victim to the black powder. Like Himeko/Princess, Sakurako can still transform into Sedusa at any time as long as lipstick is applied on Sakurako. It was revealed in episode 28 that the lipstick doesn`t even need to be applied directly to her lips; she will still transform into Sedusa if it`s smeared on her face. Like Sakurako, Sedusa loves Rukuro, but Rukuro, although generally nice to her, does not love her the way he loves Sakurako. In episode 45, Rukuro finds out about Sakurako/Sedusa when Sakurako decides to visit him at the college he attends. Upon finding this out, Rukuro confesses that he loves Sakurako but hates Sedusa. This confuses Sedusa to the point where she faints out of stress. After turning back to normal, Sakurako has no memory of what happened as Sedusa. She is represented by red snakes like the one in her collar and a purple background, while her Good Civilian side is represented by the same flower image as on her bandanna.</description>
<picture>42063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14471" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Brick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most outspoken of the Rowdyruff Boys and most likely acts as their leader, although the boys often act in unison. Like the original, he wears a hat, but his hair is much shorter. He also has a band-aid on his cheek. His weapon of choice is Momoko`s curly straw, which he uses as a spitball shooter. He is represented by a triangle.</description>
<picture>42064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2128" picture="216210.jpg">Kiuchi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14472" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Boomer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Boomer, like the other boys, acts obnoxious, cheery and enjoys causing trouble. His hair style resembles the original Boomer`s hair style in his second appearance, although the anime Boomer`s hair is slightly longer and spikier. His attitude is the opposite of Miyako`s attitude. His weapon of choice is Miyako`s used cotton swab to toss his ear wax. He is represented by an X.</description>
<picture>42065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9599" picture="222797.jpg">Aoyama Touko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14473" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Butch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although he acts like the other boys, he seems to be the least talkative and his voice sounds slightly more mature than the other boys. Butch`s hair style resembles the original Butch`s first hair style, although Butch`s bangs in this version are longer and usually cover his right eye. Butch`s skin is much paler than his brothers and his eyes are slightly longer and more "Asian" looking. Butch`s weapon is Kaoru`s smelly sweat sock, which he uses as a boomerang, he keeps his weapon in his shoe[thats why it gets smellier everytime]. The sock emits its odor when thrown. He is represented by a diamond.</description>
<picture>42066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4703" picture="27477.jpg">Tamaki Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14474" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Rowdyruff Boys</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The anime counterparts to the original Rowdyruff Boys, who first appeared in episode 20. Mojo Jojo broke into Professor Utonium`s lab in order to steal a sample of Chemical Z for his own purposes. While leaving the lab, Mojo Jojo stole Momoko`s curly straw, Miyako`s used cotton swab, and one of Kaoru`s smelly socks. Using a machine he recently created, Mojo poured the Chemical Z, the items he stole, and snips of his own hair. His machine exploded and the result was three boys containing Chemical Z, the DNA of the girls, and the evil black Chemical Z in Mojo`s hair: The Rowdyruff Boys. The boys now appear younger than the girls, at approximately 10 or 11 years of age and resemble a street gang. When they aren`t doing anything, the boys are often seen picking their noses, so as to offend their surroundings. Despite the fact that Mojo brought the boys to life, the Rowdyruff Boys do not have any respect for Mojo Jojo as well as the rest of Tokyo City. Instead of following their evil Mama, as the boys called Mojo, the Rowdyruff Boys do nothing but play pranks and cause trouble within Tokyo City for their own enjoyment. The only time they show any respect for Mojo Jojo is when they need him to destroy the Powerpuff Girls Z, which is really them abusing the parental love Mojo has for the boys. As expected, they have even less respect for the girls as the boys gross out and humiliate the girls with their pranks, flipping their skirts to grope them, mooning at them and calling them hags by the end of the episode. At the end of the episode, the boys abandon their Mama, no longer having any use for Mojo. They are each represented by a polygon in their color.</description>
<picture>42067.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14479" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<name>Kare</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Appears in episode 22, his origins are explored in episode 30, and his true level of power exposed in episode 50. He has also effeminate manners and the new design has Him in more of a harlequin-esque motif/Joker-like. He now has a yellow skin color, but he retains the habit of changing the tone of his voice from soft and effeminate to loud and enraged. Like the original, no one can mention his real name, because of how frightening his name is (Professor Utonium actually tells Ken the name, but the viewer is unable to hear it. Just mentioning the name frightened Ken and Peach). In this version, Kare is a demon who brought about chaos and destruction in Edo (the city that eventually became Tokyo City) long ago. However, he was eventually defeated by the Ooedo Chakichaki Musume, three super heroines who resemble the Powerpuff Girls Z. Him`s powers were drained and his body was sealed in a coffin. The coffin was buried at Ueno Shrine, which later became an abandoned museum when the shrine was caught on fire long ago. It was there that Him remained dormant, until the most potent Chemical Z black light brought him back to life, although the seal prevented Kare from escaping. In order for Kare to escape, Kare created a mummy whose sole purpose was to undo the seal by obtaining the white energy of the Chemical Z white lights. The mummy, although defeated by the Powerpuff Girls Z, was able to drain their energy, and its bandages returned to the abandoned museum and broke the seal on the coffin, allowing Him to bring about chaos and destruction once more. Kare`s main power is the ability to unleash an evil black particles. These particles is able to sway people/objects to the side of evil and transform its victim into a monster (The black particles eventually takes the place of the black lights). In addition, Kare has total control over his particles. He is able to call them back at will, change the speed at which they move, communicate to his victims, and can view the memories of whoever or whatever was affected by his particles. In actual combat, Him is capable of stretching his limbs to lash out at his enemies. In episode 46, Him is able to control and unlock the true powers of the weapons used by the girls in a highly destructive nature. He also has several minor abilities, such as hypnosis. Kare can travel great distances by forming a black tornado. Any more abilities is currently unknown, but by episode 51 it becomes clear that Him is the most powerful of all the villains in the show. His only known weakness is his hatred of cold temperatures. His second weakness discovered in episode 49 is the emotion of love. It was his weakness to cold weather that led to his defeat at the hands of the Ooedo Chakichaki Musume as well as prevent him from leaving the abandoned house. He has a deep hatred towards the Ooedo Chakichaki Musume, which is now directed at the Powerpuff Girls Z for their resemblance to the Musume. At the end of episode 30, he returns to the abandoned museum, but swears that he will destroy the Powerpuff Girls Z. Ken also believes that the box that contained Kare`s drained powers was unleashed and caused the world`s climate shift. Ken`s theory is proven to be factual in episode 52 when Kare uses all of his power to control Mount Fuji and ends up causing abnormal climate shifts similar to the first episode. Professor Utonium then reasons that the Chemical Z lights that resulted from the explosion may have actually been Kennainium (the white lights that created the Powerpuff Girls Z, which also gave birth to the Ooedo Chakichaki Musume long ago) and Kare`s powers (the black lights that caused its victims to become villains/monsters). When his body and mind are separated, his mind and powers take on the form of the Black Particles while his body turns into a rag doll version of himself with X`s for eyes. He is represented by a scorpion.</description>
<picture>42068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="39737" update="2005-09-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilot - Small Clip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50901" update="2006-06-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51575" update="2006-06-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51704" update="2006-07-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズ, 参上! / ガールズ, 誕生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girls Appear! / The Girls are Born!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au secours des enfants / Le secret des Supers Nanas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls, Sanjou! / Girls, Tanjou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51709" update="2006-07-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほんわかバブルス! その1 / ほんわかバブルス! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pleasant Bubbles! Part 1 / Pleasant Bubbles! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ca pétille à New-Townsville</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanwaka Bubbles! Sono 1 / Hanwaka Bubbles! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52247" update="2006-07-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズ, 結集! その1 / ガールズ, 結集! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls, Concentrate! Part 1 / Girls, Concentrate! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elles sont enfin 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls, Kesshuu! Sono 1 / Girls, Kesshuu! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52496" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズ, 家族の絆! その1 / ガールズ, 家族の絆! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls, the Bond of Family! Part 1 / Girls, the Bond of Family! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quelle famille !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls, Kazoku no Kizuna! Sono 1 / Girls, Kazoku no Kizuna! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="55805" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モジョの復讐だモジョ! / 展望タワー・クラッシュ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mojo`s Revenge, Mojo! / Observation Tower Crash!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La revanche de Mojo-jojo / L`escalade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mojo no Fushuu Da Mojo! / Tenbou Tower Crash!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="58246" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファジー・ラムキンス! / 姫子なプリンセス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuzzy Lumpkins! / Himeko the Princess!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gros Filou / Princesse pleine aux as !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuzzy Lumpkins! / Himeko na Princess!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="58247" update="2006-08-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かなえ! ももこの恋 / 極悪トリオ? アメーバーボーイズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make it come true! Momoko`s love / The most evil trio? Amoeba Boys!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nouveau Maire / Les infâmes invertébrés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanae! Momoko no Koi / Gokuaku Trio? Amoeba Boys!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61930" update="2006-08-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魅惑の乙女! セデューサ その1 / 魅惑の乙女! セデューサ その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charming Maiden! Sedusa Part 1 / Charming Maiden! Sedusa Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sédusa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miwaku no Otome! Seducer Sono 1 / Miwaku no Otome! Seducer Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61935" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コーチかおるの特訓サッカー! / 恋するファジー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coach Kaoru`s special training soccer! / Fuzzy in love!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coach rebelle / Gros Filou est amoureux !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coach Kaoru no Tokkun Soccer! / Koi Suru Fuzzy!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62249" update="2006-09-06">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カリスマ美容師モンスター! その1 / カリスマ美容師モンスター! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charisma Beautician Monster! Part 1 / Charisma Beautician Monster! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gigi le grand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karisuma Biyoushi Monster! Sono 1 / Karisuma Biyoushi Monster! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62336" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙までプリンセス! / ケーキ泥棒を追え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess Even in Space! / Chase the Cake Thief!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vive la Princesse / Bon anniv`, New-Townsville</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu made Princess! / Cake Dorobou o Oe!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63189" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初恋のシャボン玉 その1 / 初恋のシャボン玉 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Love of Soap Bubbles Part 1 / A New Love of Soap Bubbles Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le premier amour de Bulle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsukoi no Shabondama Sono 1 / Hatsukoi no Shabondama Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63190" update="2006-09-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モジョに弟子入り! アメーバーボーイズ / カメラモンスターの逆襲!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Apprenticed by Mojo! The Amoeba Boys / The Camera Monster`s Counterattack!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mojo Jojo et les invertébrés / La vengeance de Négatron</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mojo ni Deshiiri! Amoeba Boys / Camera Monster no Gyakushuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63191" update="2006-09-15">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャングリーンギャング! その1 / ギャングリーンギャング! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gangreen Gang! Part 1 / The Gangreen Gang! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le gang des Véreux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gangreen Gang! Sono 1 / Gangreen Gang! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64071" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙われたフアッションショー! / 男! ラーメンモンスター!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fashion Show is Targeted! / Man! Ramen Monster!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fashion Victim / Le culte de la nouille !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta Fashion Show! / Otoko! Ramen Monster!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64072" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀れ! プリンセスの秘密 その1 / 哀れ! プリンセスの秘密 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pity! The Princess`s Secret Part 1 / Pity! The Princess`s Secret Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nuits blanches à New-Townsville</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aware! Princess no Himitsu Sono 1 / Aware! Princess no Himitsu Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64268" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャッターチャンスを逃すな! / 兄弟愛! 電波モンスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shutter chance let loose! / Sibling Love! Electro-magnetic Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal de l`école / La revanche de Phonicor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutter Chance o Nogasuna! / Kyoudai Ai! Denpa Monster</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64399" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンスター·タッグバトル! その1 / モンスター·タッグバトル! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Tag Battle! Part 1 / Monster Tag Battle! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Mojo Jojo ripoux Club !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monster Tag Battle! Sono 1 / Monster Tag Battle! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="64724" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しきピアノレッスン! / 最強! キーン先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A sad piano lesson! / The strongest! Kiin-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trois petites notes de musique / Prof à tout faire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Piano Lesson! / Saikyou! Kiin-sensei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65029" update="2007-01-05">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラウディラフボーイズ! その1 / ラウディラフボーイス! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rowdyruff Boys! Part 1 / Rowdyruff Boys! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sales petits mecs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rowdyruff Boys! Sono 1 / Rowdyruff Boys! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65179" update="2006-11-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プヨプヨアヒルのモンスター! / 嫌われ野菜の大脱出!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Waddling Rubber Duck Monster! / The Disliked Vegetables` Great Escape!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Petit canard deviendra grand / La révolte des légumes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Puyopuyo Ahiru no Monster! / Kiraware Yasai no Dai Dasshutsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65180" update="2006-11-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最凶最悪のかれ その1 / 最凶最悪のかれ その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The most evil, the worst, Him Part 1 / The most evil, the worst, Him Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un appétit féroce</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Saiaku no Kare Sono 1 / Saikyou Saiaku no Kare Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65571" update="2006-12-10">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌舞伎モンスター, 恋の道! / 昆虫王は誰だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama Monster, The road of Love! / Who`s the bug master!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quelle comédie ! / Le combat des scarabées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabuki Monster, Koi no Michi! / Konchuu Ou wa Dare Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65572" update="2006-12-10">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンの友達探し! その1 / ケンの友達探し! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ken`s Friend Search! Part 1 / Ken`s Friend Search! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ami d`un jour, ami pour toujours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ken no Tomodachi Sagashi! Sono 1 / Ken no Tomodachi Sagashi! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65968" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イタズラ文房具! / 花・はな・ハナ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischievous Stationery! / Flowers Flowers Flowers!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bonne mine et Capitaine Gomme / Le pouvoir des fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itazura Bunbougu! / Hana Hana Hana!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="65969" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンタさんを救え! その1 / サンタさんを救え! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect Santa! Part 1 / Protect Santa! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Noël de Ken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Santa-san o Sukue! Sono 1 / Santa-san o Sukue! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66425" update="2007-01-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66806" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">握って食べて! 寿司モンスター! / ピーチとサファイア!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grabbing and Eating! Sushi Monster! / Peach and Sapphire!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigette Tabete! Sushi Monster! / Peach to Sapphire!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66934" update="2007-01-17">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レディース・タッグバトル! その1 / レディース・タッグバトル! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ladies Tag Battle! Part 1 / Ladies Tag Battle! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ladies Tag Battle! Sono 1 / Ladies Tag Battle! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66960" update="2007-01-27">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歯医者さんへ行こう! / サタデー・パワパフ・フィーバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s go to the Dentist / Saturday Powerpuff Fever</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Vamos ao dentista! / PowerPuff nos embalos de sábado a noite!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haisha-san e Ikou! / Saturday Powerpuff Fever</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66961" update="2007-01-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズトカレ! その1 / ガールズトカレ! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girls and Him Part 1 / The Girls and Him Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">As garotas e Ele! parte 1 / As garotas e Ele! parte 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls to Kare! Sono 1 / Girls to Kare! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67017" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フン太の夢 / セデューサの恋は駆け引き!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funta`s Dream / Sedusa`s Love Tactics</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A vontade de Funta! / As estratégias de conquista da Sedusa!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funta no Yume / Sedusa no Koi wa Kakehiki!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67018" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ももこの恋2 その1 / ももこの恋2 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Momoko`s Love 2 - Part 1 / Momoko`s Love 2 - Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Devotado à Momoko parte 1 / Devotado à Momoko parte 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momoko no Koi 2 Sono 1 / Momoko no Koi 2 Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69009" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛び出すマンガのモンスター! / ガールズ, 休業!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burst-Out Comic Monster! / Girls, Day Off!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Monstros de mangá aparecem! / Garotas, dia de folga!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobidasu Manga no Monster! / Girls, Kyuugyou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69010" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズ, 解散!? その1 / ガールズ, 解散!? その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls, Break Up!? Part 1 / Girls, Break Up!? Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Briga das Garotas?! Parte 1 / Briga das Garotas?! Parte 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls, Kaisan!? Sono 1 / Girls, Kaisan!? Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69011" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレたちゃ雑草じゃない! / モンスター, 憐れみの令!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re Not Weeds! / Monster, The Laws of Compassion!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Não somos mato! / Monstros e a Lei da Compaixão!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oretacha zassou shanai! / Monster, awaremi no rei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69012" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お化けが住む家!? その1 / お化けが住む家!? その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The House Where the Ghost Lives!? Part 1 / The House Where the Ghost Lives!? Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Casa assombrada? Parte 1 / Casa assombrada? Parte 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obake ga Sumu Ie!? Sono 1 / Obake ga Sumu Ie!? Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="69013" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ももこの家出とナポリタン! / キーンの同情, モジョの愛情!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway Momoko and Neapolitan! / Keane`s Sympathy, Mojo`s Affection!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A fuga de Momoko e Napolitan! / Simpatia de Keane, o amor de Mojo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momoko no Iede to Neapolitan! / Keane no Doujou, Mojo no Aijou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71956" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりはトリマキーズ! その1 / ふたりはトリマキーズ! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are the Courtiers! Part 1 / We Are the Courtiers! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari wa Torimakees! Sono 1 / Futari wa Torimakees! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71957" update="2007-04-16">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さなケンの大きなお願い! / ガールズ, 飛行禁止令!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Ken`s big wish! / Girlz, banned from flying!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Ken no Ookina Onegai! / Girls, Hikou Kinshirei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71958" update="2007-04-16">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズとテレビとプレゼント!? その1 / ガールズとテレビとプレゼント!? その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girlz and TV and a present?! Part 1 / Girlz and TV and a present?! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls to Televi to Present!? Sono 1 / Girls to Televi to Present!? Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71959" update="2007-04-16">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出ましたっ! シロガネーZ / ガールズ, 転身!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She`s here! Shirogane-Z / Girlz Switch Bodies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Demashita! Shirogane Z / Girls, Tenshin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75560" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズ, 最後の戦い! その1 / ガールズ, 最後の戦い! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls, The Last Battle! Part 1 / Girls, The Last Battle! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls, Saigo no Tatakai! Sono 1 / Girls, Saigo no Tatakai! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75561" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガールズ, 時空を超えて! その1 / ガールズ, 時空を超えて! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls Crossing Time! Part 1 / Girls Crossing Time! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls, Jikuu o Koete! Sono 1 / Girls, Jikuu o Koete! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75562" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">打倒ガールズ協同組合! その1 / 打倒ガールズ協同組合! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defeat the Girlz Alliance! Part 1 / Defeat the Girlz Alliance! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datou Girls Kyoudoukumiai! Sono 1 / Datou Girls Kyoudoukumiai! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75563" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一撃必殺!?ラブラブビーム! / モジョのナースな一日!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Killer Move!? Love Love Beam! / Mojo`s Nurse Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichigeki Hissatsu!? Love Love Beam! / Mojo no Nurse na Ichinichi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75564" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャボン・フリーダムの奇跡 その1 / シャボン・フリーダムの奇跡 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shabon Freedom Miracle Part 1 / Shabon Freedom Miracle Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shabon Freedom no Kiseki Sono 1 / Shabon Freedom no Kiseki Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75565" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅は道連れ, モジョとキーン! / いきなり登場! パワパフキッズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A trip is all about you companion, Mojo and Keane! / Suddenly appearing! Powerpuff Kids!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi wa Michizure, Mojo to Keane! / Ikinari Toujou! Powerpuff Kids!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75566" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶体絶命!?ガールズVSカレ! その1 / 絶体絶命!?ガールズVSカレ! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hopeless!? Girlz vs Him! Part 1 / Hopeless!? Girlz vs Him! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettaizetsumei!? Girls vs. Kare! Sono 1 / Zettaizetsumei!? Girls vs. Kare! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75567" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ももことカエルの王子様! / セデューサが消える日!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Momoko and the Frog Prince! / The day Sedusa disappears!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momoko to Kaeru no Ouji-sama! / Sedusa ga Kieru Hi!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75568" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かおるは上腕二頭筋がお好き! その1 / かおるは上腕二頭筋がお好き! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaoru likes big biceps! Part 1 / Kaoru likes big biceps! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaoru wa Jouwannitoukin ga Osuki! Sono 1 / Kaoru wa Jouwannitoukin ga Osuki! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75569" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらわれた博士たちを救え! / ウソつきももこの災難!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save the kidnapped Professors! / Lying Momoko`s disaster!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sarawareta Hakase-tachi o Sukue! / Usotsuki Momoko no Sainan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75570" update="2007-06-19">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パワパフ・ラウディ・ボーイズ! その1 / パワパフ・ラウディ・ボーイズ! その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Powerpuff Rowdy Boys! Part 1 / Powerpuff Rowdy Boys! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Powerpuff Rowdy Boys! Sono 1 / Powerpuff Rowdy Boys! Sono 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
