<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="326" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-03-15</startdate>
<enddate>1997-03-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shinseiki Evangelion Gekijouban: Shi to Shinsei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">NGE DR</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Евангелион: Смерть и Возрождение</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">신세기 에반게리온 극장판: 사도신생</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Evangelion - Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Evangelion - Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Neon Genesis Evangelion - Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Євангеліон - Смерть &amp; Відродження</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">NGE D&amp;R</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">edr</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新世紀エヴァンゲリオン劇場版 シト新生</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">新世纪福音战士剧场版 死亡与新生</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion - Death and Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion - Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">신세기 에반게리온 - 죽음과 재생</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Evangelion: Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: Death &amp; Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Θάνατος και Αναγέννηση</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อีวาเกเลี่ยน: จุติภาค</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Neon Genesis Evangelion: Surm ja taassünd</title>
<title xml:lang="gl" type="official">Evangelion: morte e resurrección</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="202" type="Sequel">Shinseiki Evangelion Gekijouban: Air / Magokoro o, Kimi ni</anime>
<anime id="22" type="Full Story">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="379739">I think I`ll speak for the community if I`ll recommend to watch original series + End of Evangelion instead.
Watch only for the sake of completion.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="231746">excellent</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/eva/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1389" type="Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="718" type="Original Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="58" type="Direction">Tsurumaki Kazuya</name>
<name id="57" type="Original Work">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="57" type="Chief Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="3612" type="Direction">Masayuki</name>
<name id="9882" type="Series Composition">Satsukawa Akio</name>
</creators>
<description>Originally a collection of clips from the Neon Genesis Evangelion TV series, Death was created as a precursor to the re-worked ending of the series. Rebirth was intended as that reworked ending, but after production overruns Rebirth became only the first half of the first episode of The End of Evangelion, with some minor differences.
Over time, two newer director`s cuts of Death were produced, each including new footage not seen in the series - these were called Death(True) and finally Death(True)^2.

* Death(True) aired on 02.01.1998 on the Japanese satellite TV channel WOWOW. This version of Evangelion: Death was personally re-edited by Masayuki, removing much of the new footage from episodes 21-24 that was contained in the original Death release.
* Death(True)^2 was released on 08.03.1998 as part of the Revival of Evangelion release, which is a unification of the movies Death(True)^2 (a further edit of Death(True), with a few removed shots edited back in) and The End of Evangelion.

Note that despite containing clips from the series, Death (True)^2 &amp; Rebirth should be seen after the main TV series itself to be fully understood.
Note: The 2003 Renewal of Evangelion is the final remastered version. It includes:

* http://anidb.net/a22 [The original TV series], episodes 1-20
* The Director`s Cut of episodes 21-24 of the original TV series
* http://anidb.net/a326 [Death(True)^2], released on the ninth disc with the label of Revival of Evangelion
* http://anidb.net/a202 [The End of Evangelion], released on the tenth disc, with the label Evangelion – The Feature Film
</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5117">4.87</permanent>
<temporary count="5165">6.97</temporary>
<review count="4">4.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11168.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>418</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>156</identifier>
<identifier>lroihr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/eva/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>472</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89709</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>623</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4555" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>man the hell up!</name>
<description>There is a male character in this anime that is overall not very manly. Most of the time he starts off as your typical high school student. In time there are, through major changes in his life, several more characteristics added to his personality. Usually these add up to be extremely pathetic and the character becomes quite annoying. This goes along with the viewers wish for him to get over it and do something about it. Hence, he should "Man the hell up!".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5872" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>bad luck</name>
<description>You are living a blessed life far from any troubles. Your sister is a famous reporter, you have a good looking girlfriend and you excel in your studies aiming to be a scientist. Your future is looking bright. But reality is, fate hates you. Your sister is killed, your girlfriend breaks up with you after being crippled in a terrorist attack and finally you end up as a pizza delivery boy.
And just when you thought it can`t get worse, it does. Your former girlfriend turns into a Darth Vader knock-off, tries to impose her world view on others by force and is out there to kill you. Yes, your life does truly suck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="39" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="1228">7.83</rating>
<name>Souryuu Asuka Langley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka is only one quarter Japanese, which accounts for her Japanese name but European appearance. Asuka is a native of Germany, having been raised there, though her nationality is technically American. Asuka`s native language is German, and in both the series and the manga she tends to curse in German. She is a child prodigy and has earned a university degree in an unspecified field as a teenager; she also speaks fluent Japanese, but has trouble reading and writing kanji. She is characterized by her fiery red hair and equally fiery temper. Asuka is very proud of being an Eva pilot, and near-constantly wears her A10 nerve clips in her hair, because she wants everyone around her to know that she is a pilot.</description>
<picture>14311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="309" type="main character in" update="2018-02-15">
<rating votes="1352">4.11</rating>
<name>Ikari Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikari Shinji is the "Third Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6997 [EVA-01]. He is the son of http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou] and the late http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui]. Abandoned by his father when he was a toddler, Shinji has grown up to be reclusive and withdrawn, often choosing to run away from difficult situations. He is reunited with his father when he is summoned to pilot EVA-01, and because of this meets his future caretaker http://anidb.net/ch5007 [Katsuragi Misato] and the mysterious pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00], http://anidb.net/ch310 [Ayanami Rei].
Over time and with encouragement from Misato, Rei and his classmates http://anidb.net/ch7981 [Suzuhara Touji] and http://anidb.net/ch8643 [Aida Kensuke], he learns to be more confident and appreciative of others. Shinji is put to task fighting the invading Angels, and later meets a foreign pilot whom he often comes in conflict with, http://anidb.net/ch39 [Souryuu Asuka Langley].</description>
<picture>128273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="310" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="1632">8.12</rating>
<name>Ayanami Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayanami Rei is the "First Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00]. Shrouded in mystery, she is socially withdrawn and rarely shows emotion. Seemingly completely devoted to her duty as an EVA pilot, her only apparent human relationship being with http://anidb.net/ch5009 [Nerv] commander http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou].
Rei comes to know http://anidb.net/ch309 [Ikari Shinji], and after some initial mistrust they come to better understand each other, revealing more of Rei`s emotional side and helping Shinji trust others again.
Rei`s body was created at Nerv in an attempt to bring back Gendou`s wife http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui], who was stuck inside http://anidb.net/ch8704 [EVA-01]. Soulless clones of her are kept hidden in the deepest levels of NERV, to be used both as replacement bodies for Rei should she die and as "cores" of the Dummy Plugs. Gendou, plans to make Rei help him control Instrumentality to reunite him with his wife.</description>
<picture>59479.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5000" type="appears in" update="2009-03-14">
<rating votes="399">5.35</rating>
<name>Ikari Gendou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At Nerv, Gendo is responsible for the research done on the Evas and the Human Instrumentality Project. He is the father of the Third Child, Shinji Ikari. At the start of the series, he is the only person having an effective connection to Rei Ayanami.
Gendo is a brilliant scientist and politician (the master of puppets in the series) who works diligently for his organization; however, he is an extremely cold and distant father towards his son, and has no qualms about using and discarding people to achieve his goals.</description>
<picture>21249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5007" type="main character in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="790">7.53</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The operations director at Nerv. Her duties at Nerv include acting as a field commander for the Eva pilots, issuing orders and relaying battle strategies as well as processing input from Akagi Ritsuko and the technicians monitoring the Evas. She also handles many bureaucratic aspects of Nerv`s operations.
At the beginning of the series, Misato first brings Shinji Ikari to Nerv and is able to convince him to pilot the Eva Unit 01. She then chooses to have Shinji move in with her rather than live alone, and later takes in Sohryu Asuka Langley. As the series progresses, through her former lover Kaji Ryouji she learns the truth behind the Human Instrumentality Project and the depths of deception that Nerv and Seele have gone to keep the Project secret, even from her.
While on the job, Misato is very professional and capable, in stark contrast to her life at home. Until Shinji`s arrival, her living space was a complete mess. She cannot cook for herself and relies solely on instant food (she is often considered gross by Shinji and Ritsuko for combining food like ramen and curry). She also drinks copious quantities of beer, and drinks one first thing in the morning to get her day started (later in the series she apparently switches to canned coffee as a supplement). She also smokes, though only occasionally and only during chaotic events.</description>
<picture>21277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5008" type="appears in" update="2009-03-15">
<rating votes="176">4.59</rating>
<name>Akagi Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nerv`s head scientist and heavily involved in the repairs and maintenance of Tokyo-3`s defences against the Angels, particularly the Evas.
She is the daughter of Akagi Naoko, the developer of the MAGI supercomputer system which controls Nerv. In many ways, Ritsuko is living in the shadow of her mother, whom she both admires and despises. Naoko was the head scientist working on the Evangelion project before her death, and Ritsuko is continuing the work her mother began with the Evas, as well as continuing the development of the Magi supercomputer system. Flashbacks to a teenaged Ritsuko reveal that she is a natural brunette, just like her mother.
Ritsuko is extremely intelligent, with a strong dedication to her work and a stoic, detached attitude which is frequently contrasted against Katsuragi Misato`s hot-headness, especially during Eva combat. Her occasional jibes at Misato are a source of comic relief in the series. She has a great affinity for cats, and Misato chides her at one point for substituting her cats for human affection. She also is a heavy smoker, as evidenced by an ashtray on her desk filled with cigarette butts stained by her lipstick.</description>
<picture>21278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6995" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="107">4.07</rating>
<name>Ibuki Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A First Lieutenant at Nerv and a computer technician who works primarily with Akagi Ritsuko. Her main role during the battles against the Angels is to constantly monitor the Eva pilots` synchronization ratios and send various emergency commands to the Evas as ordered by Misato or Gendou. In spite of her profession, Maya despises violence of any sort, and is frequently shown becoming nauseated and averting her eyes during battles with the Angels.</description>
<picture>25248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6996" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="15">6.51</rating>
<name>EVA-00</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Unit 00 is the Prototype, the first successful Evangelion, and is piloted by the First Child, Ayanami Rei. The head design is similar to that of the previous failed attempts, but with only one eye. There are two domes on the top of the head, one white and one transparent green; their function (if any) is never revealed. Unit 00 is the only one of the original Evas that is never seen without its armour (Unit 02 was revealed in End of Evangelion, and Unit 01 on multiple occasions) or opening its mouth; thus the appearance of its organic body is unknown.
Unit 00 was initially coloured orange like the previous prototypes, but its armour was damaged beyond repair by the Angel Ramiel`s particle beam. The subsequent repairs and upgrades included blue armour plating in addition to other alterations made in order to make it more suitable for combat conditions. The upgrades to Unit 00`s armour make it look more like the subsequent Evas, but there are still several differences or actual limitations. Shoulder "blades" are added to the Unit`s armour; though similar in appearance to the ones on Units 01 and 02, they are used to hold retro-rockets, as seen in the fight with the ninth Angel, Matariel. Because it is only the prototype, Unit 00 cannot be fitted with D-type equipment. The true nature of the soul inside Unit 00 is never specified, but it is implied to be directly connected to Rei in some fashion.
Unit 00 was self-destructed by Rei in order to destroy the sixteenth Angel, Armisael.</description>
<picture>30414.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6997" type="appears in" update="2009-05-20">
<rating votes="65">8.25</rating>
<name>EVA-01</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Created in the Third Annex of Gehirn`s Artificial Evolution Laboratory in Hakone from 2003 to 2004 and deemed a functional Eva unit in 2014, Unit 01 is piloted by Shinji Ikari (with Rei or a Rei Dummy Plug as backup pilots), and has the best battle record of all the Evangelions. It frequently acts independently (the "berserker" mode), without the instructions of a pilot and without any apparent power source. The Eva will also take action to protect its pilot while sometimes servicing other interests. The Eva`s resident soul, Ikari Yui (Shinji`s mother), appears to be responsible for such events. Unit 01 is called the "Test Type," perhaps because of the experimental way in which it was created: although Unit 01 seems to be an Adam-derived cybernetic organism like all other Evangelions, it is the sole Eva to have been born from Lilith.
Upon savagely disfiguring the fourteenth angel, Zeruel, it proceeded to devour the Angel and assimilated its S² Engine, making Unit 01 the first physically complete Evangelion prior to the construction of the Mass Production units. The S² Engine seems to be used only at Unit 01`s discretion; after acquiring it, the Eva is still sent into battle with an umbilical cable. Just before Unit 01 absorbed the S² Engine, it used one of Zeruel`s arms to regenerate its severed left arm, demonstrating the Angelic ability of regeneration. The Mass Production models were also equipped with Nerv-developed S² Engines but it is a common misconception that they also have the ability to regenerate.
Unit 01`s armour is primarily purple; some components are coloured neon green, light blue, orange, and black. The helmet, with its prominent horn and "frill," is vaguely evocative of a ceratopsid dinosaur. The pectoral plates are different from those seen on any other Eva. The humanoid entity beneath the armour has light brown skin, two emerald-green eyes, four small nostrils positioned preorbitally, and red blood.
As a result of Third Impact, at the conclusion of The End of Evangelion, Unit 01 is left floating adrift in space, fossilised and still containing the soul of Ikari Yui, where it will outlast the sun and moon, as an eternal testament that the human race existed.</description>
<picture>25244.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6998" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="26">7.38</rating>
<name>EVA-02</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Evangelion Unit 02, built by Nerv Germany, is the first Production Model Eva. It is piloted by Souryuu Asuka Langley and is the first Evangelion built specifically for combat. The Eva`s armour is primarily red with yellow and white on the arms and head. The head armour has two movable sections, one covering both the jaw and lower eyes and the other above the upper pair of eyes. These plates are hinged and can shift, displaying the Eva`s eyes underneath. This is first seen underwater during the fight with Gaghiel. As a result of being constructed by Nerv Germany, and also as an accommodation for its three-quarters-German pilot, its default language setting is German. Unit 02 features a different progressive knife from earlier Eva units as well as an internal weapon rack in the right shoulder binder which fires dartlike weapons.
Unlike Unit 01, it only goes truly "berserk" once, just before its destruction. It has achieved an unusually high sync ratio with its pilot(s), on two other occasions: once in combat against the 6th angel Gaghiel, and once under the influence of the 17th Angel. It is known to contain the maternal part of the soul of Asuka`s mother.
Unit 02 has blue blood, which is first seen when the fourteenth Angel, Zeruel, cuts off its arms. It has brown skin and four orange eyes, first seen when the MP Evas tear it apart.</description>
<picture>30415.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7187" type="appears in" update="2009-07-07">
<rating votes="21">5.06</rating>
<name>Seele</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Nerv and Gehirn`s secret backers, who wish to implement the Human Instrumentality Project, and arguably the "true villains" of the series. It consists of at least twelve prominent people; five of them form the Instrumentality Committee, which directly oversees Nerv`s progress, officially in the name of the UN. Its members are referred to as the "Old Men."
Seele is a secret organisation, the real puppetmasters behind the United Nations. Its origins are shrouded in mystery; they would claim to have existed since ancient times, functioning as an Illuminati-like power cabal over most of the world`s governments. This cannot be verified, but they have been operating since at least soon after World War II, when they acquired the secret sections of the Dead Sea Scrolls. The secret Dead Sea Scrolls predicted the arrival of the Angels and of Third Impact, and Seele began striving to develop means to defeat the Angels so that a human-centred Instrumentality process would proceed. Having decided that humanity as a whole had reached an evolutionary dead end, Seele seeks to bring about Instrumentality and unite all humans into one hyper-being, the next stage of existence.
In German "Seele" means "soul".</description>
<picture>1122.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7960" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="317">6.59</rating>
<name>Nagisa Kaworu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tabris, the seventeenth and final Angel, holds the form of a human, Kaworu Nagisa. Like the other Angels, he is "born of Adam", although it is implied that he was created by Seele. He contains the soul of Adam, similar to how Rei contains the soul of Lilith. Tabris` AT field is the most powerful ever detected, strong enough to block out "light, magnetism, sub-atomic particles, everything". He may control any Evangelion unit he wishes, even from outside the entry plug, so long as the soul inhabiting the Eva is dormant. Within the entry plug, he can set his synchronization ratio at any level he wishes. The nature or even the very existence of his core is not revealed.
Tabris, as Kaworu, infiltrated Nerv under the pretense of being sent to replace Asuka as Unit 02`s pilot. During his stay in Tokyo-3, he formed an extremely close relationship with Shinji. Kaworu later revealed himself as an Angel, seizing control of Unit 02 and descending with it towards Terminal Dogma. Shinji, in Unit 01, was sent to stop him, but was forced to battle Unit 02 while Tabris proceeded to Terminal Dogma. Tabris` AT field manifested during the battle, effectively cutting both of them off from all contact with anyone outside. After he reached Terminal Dogma, Tabris was surprised to discover that the Angel held there was not Adam, but Lilith. Shinji incapacitated Unit 02 and proceeded to try to stop the Angel. Tabris, gripped in Unit 01`s hand, stated his unwillingness to destroy mankind by causing Third Impact, and asked Shinji to kill him. Shinji, after a long period of hesitation, crushed the Angel in his Eva`s hand.</description>
<picture>128274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7981" type="appears in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="97">3.84</rating>
<name>Suzuhara Touji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toji is a tough boy, the stereotypical "jock," as evidenced by the fact that he is the only student in Shinji`s class that refuses to wear the school uniform (although he does actually wear it once, in the ninth episode). Toji is good friends with Kensuke Aida, and is in constant conflict with Asuka. Toji`s younger sister was injured in the battle between Sachiel and Unit 01, and after learning that Shinji was Unit 01`s pilot, he beats Shinji up as payback. However, after witnessing firsthand the suffering Shinji experiences piloting Unit 01 in the battle against Shamshel, Toji comes to respect Shinji and the two become friends.
Unbeknownst to Toji for much of the series, his normally by-the-book class rep Hikari Horaki actually has a crush on him, which she tries to repress and disguise by bossing him around. Later in the series, she begins bringing especially big homemade lunches to school for Toji, since he loves to eat ("Toji the Stomach," as Kensuke refers to him). Subsequently, her feelings begin to come to the forefront and Toji seems to return her affection.
Toji is eventually selected to be the Fourth Child, and agrees on the condition that his sister be moved to Nerv`s medical facilities. En route to the testing facility, Unit 03 is taken over by Bardiel. When Toji is inserted in the entry plug and the Eva is powered up, Bardiel takes over and the Eva goes on a rampage. All the other Evas are deployed to stop Unit 03, but Units 00 and 02 are quickly defeated, and Shinji refuses orders to destroy Unit 03, wanting to try to save the pilot. However, Gendo orders that Unit 01`s Dummy Plug system be activated, overriding Shinji`s control. Unit 01 proceeds to tear Unit 03 to shreds and crush its entry plug. After the battle, Shinji learns that Toji is the pilot as the wreckage of the entry plug is examined. Toji survives but is critically injured, losing his left leg. Along with Kensuke and the rest of his class, he is eventually evacuated from Tokyo-3; what happens to him after that is unknown. He appears at the end of episode 26 in Shinji`s subconscious.</description>
<picture>27097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8301" type="appears in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="95">5.47</rating>
<name>Kaji Ryouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaji Ryouji is employed by Nerv as a special inspector. He wears a ponytail, has a constant 5 o`clock-shadow, and is always referred to by his surname.
Kaji appears to be a triple agent, working as a special inspector for Nerv, while secretly investigating the organisation for the Japanese Ministry of the Interior, and at times seemingly acting as a cat`s paw both for and against Ikari Gendou and Seele. In addition, he seems to maintain personal motivations beyond loyalty to any organisation, and speaks frequently of his desire to "find the truth." Kaji can be said to have a green thumb, as he cultivates a watermelon patch close to Nerv HQ. (This is only seen in the anime; he is watering the watermelons while Zeruel is attacking the GeoFront.)
Kaji and Katsuragi Misato were lovers during college, but had long since broken up by the start of the series and do not see each other again until she flies out to the UN fleet ferrying Unit 02 and Souryuu Asuka Langley to Japan. After he returns to Nerv headquarters, Kaji and Misato flirt and fight, Kaji teasing Misato, and Misato constantly calling him "stupid." However, they rekindle their romance after Misato confesses that she broke up with him because Kaji reminded her too much of her father.
Most of the time, Kaji is very easygoing and jovial, always remaining cool and composed and maintaining his detached sense of humour even during times of crisis. He also flirts unabashedly with his female peers and co-workers, which further draws Misato`s ire. Despite his irresponsible public persona, Kaji demonstrates a great level of personal responsibility and worldly wisdom in his personal interactions. He acts as something of a father figure to both Asuka and Shinji, particularly the latter. Asuka is openly infatuated with him, something he coolly and repeatedly deflects. He offers Shinji contemplative advice and tries to help him understand the nature of social dynamics. Behind all of this, however, Kaji hints at being a very melancholic and lonely individual, plagued by doubts of his own sincerity and whether he is capable of true love.
Kaji is ordered by Seele to kidnap Deputy Commander Fuyutsuki Kouzou so that he can be interrogated. Kaji follows his orders, but disobeys Seele by rescuing Fuyutsuki later and returning him to Nerv. Prior to this, he remarks that his Nerv I.D. card is the colour of blood; also, during their last meeting, Kaji gives Misato a small capsule which contains the information for the Human Instrumentality Project, then says "This may be the last gift I give you." He then leaves Misato a farewell phone message, indicating that he knew he would likely be dead when she heard it. Fuyutsuki even remarks that his actions will cost him his life. Kaji is eventually shot and killed by an unknown assailant.</description>
<picture>27415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8642" type="appears in" update="2011-07-12">
<rating votes="129">3.32</rating>
<name>Fuyutsuki Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nerv`s Deputy Commander and Ikari Gendou`s right hand man. He does not especially like Gendou, but he is the closest thing to a confidant that Gendou has in the series.
Once a professor of meta-biology at Kyoto University, Fuyutsuki became interested in the research and theories undertaken by Ikari Yui, and became her sponsor and mentor. Shortly thereafter, he was directed by his superiors to initiate a similar arrangement with Rokobungi Gendou.
Later, after the Second Impact, Fuyutsuki travelled with Gendou to the ruins of Antarctica, and began to suspect that Gendou and his associates in Seele were more powerful and dangerous than he originally realized. In 2003, Fuyutsuki discovered for himself the true nature of the events leading up to Second Impact and Seele`s involvement in initiating that catastrophe. Gendou led him into the GeoFront and Central Dogma, and asked Fuyutsuki to join him in "creating a new future for mankind."</description>
<picture>75303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8643" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="110">3.12</rating>
<name>Aida Kensuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An otaku, a military buff, Touji`s best friend, and one of the "Other Children," Eva pilot candidates in the same class as Shinji, Touji, Rei, Asuka, and Hikari. His hobbies include camping in the mountains surrounding Tokyo-3 and playing at simulated war re-enacting - by himself. Kensuke solidifies his friendship with Shinji after Shinji saves him and Toji during the fight against the fourth Angel, Shamshel. Kensuke dreams of becoming an Eva pilot and ceaselessly begs Shinji to pull strings in Nerv so he can be selected as a pilot, despite Shinji telling him that he has no say in the matter. He also seems oblivious to the intense physical and psychological distress endured by Eva pilots. Nevertheless, Kensuke enjoys the privileges of being the friend of an Eva pilot. Like Touji, Kensuke has a crush on Katsuragi Misato.</description>
<picture>27935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8644" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="11">2.38</rating>
<name>Keel Lorenz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of Seele, represented as Seele 01 in the monoliths. Among his most defining characteristics are his ancient appearance and the futuristic visor that he wears throughout the series. Little is revealed about him in the series, but he is believed to hold great political power in the UN. At some time between Second Impact and 2015, most of his body below the neck was replaced with cybernetic implants. Although he uses his visor to see, production drawings show that he still has eyes.</description>
<picture>27936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8665" type="appears in" update="2009-06-07">
<rating votes="100">4.23</rating>
<name>Horaki Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Class representative of the class that Shinji and the other Eva pilots attend. She has a by-the-book demeanour and takes her responsibilities as "class rep" seriously. Although she frequently bickers with Touji, she reveals to Asuka that she has an enormous crush on Touji but is unable to openly express her feelings to him. She also appears to be Asuka`s only friend. Hikari is an accomplished cook who appears to take care of her two sisters.</description>
<picture>27961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8666" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="53">4.61</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A First Lieutenant at Nerv and one of the three main computer technicians directly serving under Commanders Ikari and Fuyutsuki in the command post of Central Dogma, the others being Aoba and Ibuki. Hyuga at first gives the impression of being something of a nerd, reading manga while on his break time, but is a highly skilled technician. His quick thinking and bravery help save Nerv headquarters from the attack by Matariel, and he acts as a spy for Misato, helping her obtain information regarding Nerv`s machinations.
The true extent of his feelings for Misato is shown in The End of Evangelion as Rei/Lilith takes the form of Misato during Instrumentality and passionately kisses him; his body reverts to LCL.</description>
<picture>75305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8667" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="58">4.05</rating>
<name>Aoba Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoba Shigeru is a First Lieutenant at Nerv and a computer technician. At times a stereotypical metalhead, he is a cynical nihilist and plays guitar (he can also sometimes be seen playing air guitar). Of the three technicians seen regularly in Central Dogma, his character is explored the least in the series.
In The End of Evangelion, during Instrumentality, Rei/Lillith appears to him not as any loved one but rather as a bombardment of Reis which forces their way through his AT Field while he cowers and screams in horror under his desk.</description>
<picture>75304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9620" type="appears in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="62">7.11</rating>
<name>Ikari Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She was a student of genetic engineering at Kyoto University, where she met Fuyutsuki, who took an interest in her research and would later become a mentor and trusted friend, as well as her future husband Gendo. Afterwards, she joined the Artificial Evolution Laboratory (which would become Gehirn) in Hakone, Japan, and played an integral role in Project E.
Despite Fuyutsuki`s misgivings, Yui served as the test subject for the Contact Experiment of Unit 01 in 2004, saying that "everything happens as it must." She invited her son Shinji to Gehirn to watch what would be her final moments: Yui "disappeared" during testing — leaving no body behind — and was proclaimed dead that same year after efforts to recover her failed. Although Gehirn considered it an accident, it is arguably clear that what happened was Yui`s intention. Living on as the soul of the Eva, she continues to ensure a "bright future" for Shinji and the rest of humanity, seeing to it personally that Seele`s scenario is never entirely fulfilled.</description>
<picture>29299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4001" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>1997-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7178" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12819" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Subtitles</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12828" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="6">O4</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 (Part 1 of 2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12829" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="6">O5</epno>
<length>35</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 (Part 2 of 2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35811" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Genesis 0:0` - THE LIGHT FROM THE DARKNESS</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39568" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episodes 1-3 (Part 1 of 2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39569" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episodes 1-3 (Part 2 of 2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40366" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47088" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1997-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">休憩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intermission</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukei</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
