<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="327" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-12-17</startdate>
<enddate>1994-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boku no Chikyuu o Mamotte</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">나의 지구를 지켜줘</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Boku no Chikyuu wo Mamotte</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ぼく地球</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ぼくたま</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">psme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bokutama</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぼくの地球を守って</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Please Save My Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Réincarnations - Please Save My Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Пожалуйста, спасите мою Землю!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5015" approval="2" total="2">Sequence</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="265483">A truly lovely OVA anime about the reincarnation of human ETs to 1990s Japan, &amp; how what it is that binds them to their former lives affects each of them along with their relationships in this current life. It has that special `magic` type of feeling which only the animes of this generation can have.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/m-serve/ova/bokutama/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5505" type="Original Work">Hiwatari Saki</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="1640" type="Series Composition">Yamazaki Kazuo</name>
<name id="1640" type="Direction">Yamazaki Kazuo</name>
<name id="4523" type="Music">Mizoguchi Hajime</name>
<name id="3683" type="Character Design">Gotou Takayuki</name>
<name id="3683" type="Chief Animation Direction">Gotou Takayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr5505 [Hiwatari Saki], originally published in Hana to Yume magazine.
Ever since she was a little girl, plants and animals have always seemed to love the Japanese high school student, http://anidb.net/ch30829 [Sakaguchi Alice]. Her next door neighbour http://anidb.net/ch30831 [Rin] loves her too. Even though he is only eight years old, he is determined to marry Alice one day.
Alice`s classmates, http://anidb.net/ch30833 [Jinpachi] and http://anidb.net/ch30835 [Issei], tell her that they have been sharing the same dreams since they were in junior high. The people and objects in their dreams always have the same names, and they remember details and conversations as if they had been awake. The setting for the dreams is always the Moon, where seven scientists from another planet watch and study the Earth.
Alice has a Moon dream, where she recalls her life on the Moon and her love for http://anidb.net/ch30832 [Shion]. Together the three of them start the search for the rest of the seven scientists.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="536">5.50</permanent>
<temporary count="542">6.82</temporary>
<review count="1">9.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>68588.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10144</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>195</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>526</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10036</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>448</identifier>
<identifier>dyfzhw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/m-serve/ova/bokutama/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.productionig.com/contents/works/04_/000096.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Please_Save_My_Earth</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぼくの地球を守って</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3653</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1716</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30829" type="main character in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Sakaguchi Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakaguchi Alice is a shy, quiet high-schooler who recently moved to Tokyo from a town in Hokkaidou, which she misses for its peace and lack of pollution.</description>
<picture>69164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30830" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Mokuren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alice was a biologist Mokuren, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in her previous life. Mokuren was a gorgeous woman with long blonde hair. She has been obsessed with Earth since her childhood and longed to live among the humans she observed.</description>
<picture>69165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30831" type="main character in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Kobayashi Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kobayashi Rin is the seven-year-old neighbor of Alice, and has enjoyed tormenting her since she moved in next door.</description>
<picture>159260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30832" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Shion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin was a scientist Shion, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in his previous life.</description>
<picture>162500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30833" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Ogura Jinpachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ogura Jinpachi is a high school boy and Alice`s classmate.</description>
<picture>162226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30834" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Enju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Issei was an anthropologist Enju, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in his previous life.</description>
<picture>162502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30835" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Nishikiori Issei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishikiori Issei is a high school boy and Alice`s classmate.</description>
<picture>162499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30836" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Gyokuran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinpachi was an archaeologist Gyokuran, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in his previous life.</description>
<picture>162494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30837" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Kasama Haruhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasama Haruhiko is a junior high school boy with weak heart who lives with his mother.</description>
<picture>162501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30838" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Shuukaidou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruhiko was a physician Shuukaidou, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in his previous life.</description>
<picture>162230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30839" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Dobashi Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dobashi Daisuke is a high school boy. He started having the moon dreams first, as he started having them when he was seven.</description>
<picture>162228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30840" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Hiiragi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daisuke was a scientist Hiiragi, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in his previous life. He was the team leader.</description>
<picture>162229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30841" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-08">
<name>Yakushimaru Hokuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yakushimaru Hokuto is an old friend of Tamura`s from the days when the organization Tamura works for was illegitimate/Yakuza. Also being Mikuro`s older step-brother, Hokuto makes it possible for Tamura to get in touch with Mikuro in order to help Tamura figure out what is wrong with Haruhiko and how to deal with Rin.</description>
<picture>162450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4932" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30842" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Kokushou Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kokushou Sakura attends the same school as Daisuke. They discover each other during a near-fatal traffic accident while on a field trip.</description>
<picture>162227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30843" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Shusuran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura was a physicist Shusuran, who observed the Earth from the Moon, in her previous life.</description>
<picture>162503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30844" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Tamura Kazuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamura Kazuto is a servant/bodyguard for the wealthy Matsudaira family and friend to Haruhiko.</description>
<picture>162231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30845" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Sakaguchi Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hajime is Alice`s younger brother. He is very protective of his sister and will do anything to keep her safe.</description>
<picture>162498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30846" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Lazlo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lazlo was Shion`s kind and patient foster father and veeda, one who guides those with special talents, after Shion had been rescued from the war-torn Tess.</description>
<picture>69184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30847" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Kyaa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyaa is the alien pet and companion of Lazlo, Shion`s foster father. Appears as a giant cat.</description>
<picture>69185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31035" picture="83149.jpg">Hayashi Tamao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30848" type="appears in" update="2011-04-05">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Rin no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4105" picture="39793.jpg">Kawashima Chiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70542" type="appears in" update="2014-10-08">
<name>Yakushimaru Mikuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yakushimaru Mikuro is a man with ESP and the younger step-brother of Hokuto. Tamura contacted him through his brother, Hokuto, for advice about dealing with Rin and Haruhiko.</description>
<picture>162449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70543" type="appears in" update="2014-10-08">
<name>Kaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10297" picture="222992.jpg">Horimoto Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70553" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Haruhiko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruhiko`s mother.</description>
<picture>162489.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70554" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Matsudaira Raozou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsudaira Raozou was the leader of the Yakuza gang that took Tamura and his younger brother in when they were both very young. He is Takashi`s father.</description>
<picture>162490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70555" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Alice no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alice and Hajime`s mother.</description>
<picture>162491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10375" picture="186266.jpg">Arima Mizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70556" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Matsudaira Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsudaira Takashi is the teenage son of Mr. Matsudaira and the leader of the Bakutou biker gang.</description>
<picture>162492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70557" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Suzuki Mariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzuki Mariko is Alice`s classmate and a member of choir club.</description>
<picture>162493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5994" picture="30645.jpg">Iwatsubo Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70558" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Chibi Shion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Shion.</description>
<picture>162495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70559" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Lian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lian are called priestess of the Sarjalim faith.</description>
<picture>162496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70560" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<name>Lian Karsh</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lian Karsh is the only person Shion cares about throughout his terrible childhood during his fostering with LazLo and after LazLo dies.</description>
<picture>162497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4431" picture="26696.jpg">Midori Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70561" type="appears in" update="2014-10-09">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Okamura Ayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okamura Ayako is an associate of Tamura and a piano teacher.</description>
<picture>162504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1901" picture="186579.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70663" type="appears in" update="2014-10-15">
<name>Rojion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rojion is Mokuren`s father, he was a Kiches Sarjalian like Mokuren.</description>
<picture>162764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70664" type="appears in" update="2014-10-15">
<name>Sai Chourou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The top Kiches Sarjalian.</description>
<picture>162765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70665" type="appears in" update="2014-10-15">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Mokuren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Mokuren.</description>
<picture>162766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4002" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒[めざ]め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éveil</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">각성</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4003" update="2005-09-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出合い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Meeting</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontres</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">만남</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4004" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lune d`autrefois</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">달의 기억</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4005" update="2005-09-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thoughts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">생각</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4006" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">E·S·P</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ESP</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Téléportation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">E·S·P</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">E.S.P</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4007" update="2005-09-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1994-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">転生, そして...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reincarnation, and then...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épilogue</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">환생 그리고...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensei, Soshite...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122468" update="2014-02-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1995-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">金色の時 流れて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Passing of the Golden Age</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">뮤직비디오 - 황금 빛 시간이 흘러</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kin`iro no Toki Nagarete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176010" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>1994-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編完全版 ~亜梨子から, 輪くんへ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Rin-kun, from Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen Kanzenban: Alice kara, Rin-kun e</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
