<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3298" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2005-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">PaniPoni Dash!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Пани Пони</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">พานิ โพนิ แดช</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">PaniPoni Dash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Pani Poni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Pani Poni Dash!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">不可思议的教室</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">PPD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">PPD!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぱにぽにだっしゅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Paniponi Dash!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">파니포니 대쉬!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8168" approval="80" total="90">Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="106" approval="42" total="60">Azumanga Daiou The Animation (2002)</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="23" total="30">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="1697" approval="18" total="22">Sensei no Ojikan: Doki Doki School Hours</anime>
<anime id="5083" approval="3" total="4">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
<anime id="4565" approval="2" total="3">Negima!?</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="278370">Madcap comedy for people who like a-gag-a-second otaku references and "out of left field" sketch comedy. Hilarious for those who do, tiresome for those who don`t.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="135820">absurd comedy at finest...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="152406">Seriously amazing show</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="398315">It shares the same basic structure/atmosphere as Azumanga Daioh, but it`s seemingly been written by a staff who begins each workday with several pots of of black coffee laced with LSD. The fast pace and lunacy may be overwhelming for some viewers, but it`s well worth the effort for fans of weird/twisted humor and cultural references (note: this is a rare case where the English dialog is a worthwhile alternative). And while fans of other SHAFT comedies should not expect something quite as well done as the similarly zany Sayonara Zetsubo Sensei, it`s still worthwhile.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="163935">The dumbest humor is the best one (c)
Love this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="451638">Hilarious, fast paced, absurd with lots of japanese humor and amusing characters - But us Gakujin won`t get many jokes anyway unless explained - I read the Alien Captain was voiced by the same voice actor as Picard in the Enterprise series - which makes the character here a parody - maybe there are other cases I haven`t found yet ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="162058">Very fast, fresh and immensely entertaining take on parody anime. Also the animation and character design is unique and stylish.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.paniponi-dash.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="987" type="Animation Work">Gansis</name>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="1565" type="Character Design">Oota Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="1564" type="Direction">Oonuma Shin</name>
<name id="2323" type="Series Composition">Kanemaki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="1565" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oota Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="3926" type="Music">Haneoka Kei</name>
<name id="9149" type="Chibi Character Design">Aboshi Mako</name>
<name id="9368" type="Original Work">Hikawa Hekiru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr9368 [Hikawa Hekiru].
The 10-year-old http://anidb.net/ch9100 [Rebecca Miyamoto] becomes the new teacher of a classroom full of weirdos. Despite her cute looks she is a little beast and can be pretty sarcastic and offensive. The school is not safe any more now that she is in charge of a class and her students, http://anidb.net/ch9103 [Himeko], http://anidb.net/ch9112 [Ichijou], http://anidb.net/ch9106 [Rei] and http://anidb.net/ch9102 [Mesousa] a white rabbit who took a liking to Rebecca help her to rough up the school and the neighbouring class with its teacher ojii-chan.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1987">6.57</permanent>
<temporary count="2010">7.56</temporary>
<review count="3">6.71</review>
</ratings>
<picture>168255.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5556</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5419</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>490</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1742</identifier>
<identifier>ezkzee</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.paniponi-dash.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pani_Poni</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぱにぽにだっしゅ!#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.89.88.E3.80.8C.E3.81.B1.E3.81.AB.E3.81.BD.E3.81.AB.E3.81.A0.E3.81.A3.E3.81.97.E3.82.85.21.E3.80.8D</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322809</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7568</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1754" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>kappa</name>
<description>They are legendary creatures, a type of water sprite found in Japanese folklore.
Kappas are typically depicted as roughly humanoid in form, and about the size of a child.
Their scaly, reptilian skin ranges in color from green to yellow or blue.
Kappas supposedly inhabit the ponds and rivers of Japan and have various features to aid them in this environment, such as webbed hands and feet.
They are sometimes said to smell like fish, and they can certainly swim like them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6443" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="792">8.94</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Nozomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23897.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6445" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="262">8.14</rating>
<name>Kitsu Chiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23910.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6447" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="214">8.54</rating>
<name>Tsunetsuki Matoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23912.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7967" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="76">7.45</rating>
<name>Pen Pen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pen Pen (often styled as Pen²) is a "hot spring penguin" and Misato`s pet. He lives in a custom refrigerator in Misato`s apartment, enjoys taking warm baths, eating whatever food he can get his hands (or wings) on, and going to hot springs. He also appears to have a relatively high degree of intelligence, as he is also shown watching TV and reading newspapers. He is voiced by Megumi Hayashibara in the Japanese series. He is the result of a genetics experiment at Misato`s former workplace, and she adopted him after the experiment`s conclusion rather than let him be euthanised. His wingtips have retractable claws, which normal birds do not have.</description>
<picture>27070.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9100" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="21">8.49</rating>
<name>Rebecca Miyamoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9102" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="6">8.83</rating>
<name>Mesousa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5009" picture="28633.jpg">Yamazaki Vanilla</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9103" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="12">7.23</rating>
<name>Katagiri Himeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9106" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="8">7.07</rating>
<name>Tachibana Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9109" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="4">6.93</rating>
<name>Momose Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9110" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="7">4.93</rating>
<name>Uehara Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9112" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="14">8.01</rating>
<name>Ichijou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9114" type="main character in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="7">4.55</rating>
<name>Suzuki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3182" picture="55949.jpg">Sakata Kayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9116" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="3">6.17</rating>
<name>Igarashi Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9118" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Momose Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9121" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="3">5.28</rating>
<name>Kashiwagi Yuuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9122" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Kashiwagi Yuuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9124" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Kurusu Yuzuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="163" picture="25711.jpg">Nakase Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9126" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Saotome-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="277" picture="223606.jpg">Hanawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9128" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="2">6.34</rating>
<name>Shiratori Suzune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9130" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="1">7.57</rating>
<name>Akiyama Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5011" picture="68997.jpg">Higasayama Tsugumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9131" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Watanuki Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2140" picture="21615.jpg">Higuchi Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9133" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Yankee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="277" picture="223606.jpg">Hanawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9135" type="appears in" update="2019-07-05">
<name>Zoola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9136" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Jijii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="278" picture="44088.jpg">Ootake Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9137" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="2">7.98</rating>
<name>Behoimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9139" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="4">6.60</rating>
<name>Serizawa Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9141" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>Inugami Tsurugi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9142" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nanjou Misao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9143" type="appears in" update="2010-08-16">
<name>Miyata Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyata Akira has a reputation for being clumsy because she frequently trips and falls. She is very sensitive about her clumsiness, but she is, ironically, also a member of the Intelligence Club in the anime episodes. Her number is 002. Her only redeeming characteristic is her razor buzz haircut. Due to her clumsiness, Akira is frequently referred to by Inugami as dojikko, which usually translates to a stereotypical clumsy girl. Akira is also seen and talks about her membership in the Falling Club, an obvious joke about her clumsiness.
Her data as mentioned in the anime:
Study: 1
Athletics: 1
Cooking: 1
Style: 5</description>
<picture>28631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9152" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>1 Nen C Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Year 1 - Class C of Momotsuki Gakuen.</description>
</character>
<character id="9154" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>1 Nen A Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>First Year - Class A of Momotsuki Gakuen</description>
</character>
<character id="9155" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="1">9.74</rating>
<name>1 Nen B Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Year 1 - Class B of Momotsuki Gakuen.</description>
</character>
<character id="9156" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<name>1 Nen D Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Year 1 - Class D of Momotsuki Gakuen.</description>
</character>
<character id="9157" type="appears in" update="2009-12-10">
<name>Momotsuki Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The school all Pani Poni Dash! Characters go to.</description>
<picture>40050.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12865" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-08-14">
<rating votes="22">7.88</rating>
<name>Ume-sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ume is a mysterious green creature that represents the manga`s author, http://anidb.net/cr1530 [Aoki Ume]. The character does not actually play any significant role in the story.</description>
<picture>2898.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="13677" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Tanuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanuki is the Japanese word for the Japanese raccoon dog (Nyctereutes procyonoides viverrinus). They have been part of Japanese folklore since ancient times. The legendary tanuki is reputed to be mischievous and jolly, a master of disguise and shapeshifting, but somewhat gullible and absent-minded.
Tanuki sometimes transforms into students of Peach Moon academy. She appeared in episode fourteen for the first time. Later, she became a member of the Intelligence Club as "004".
When she transforms, she is not able to do this completely, which leaves all but her face looking like what she intended to transform into. However, there was one instance in the anime where she made a complete transformation. She also ends her sentences with "Nyansu".</description>
<picture>40047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13679" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-10">
<rating votes="1">8.26</rating>
<name>Alien Commander</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Alien Commander belongs to a group of aliens who observe Becky from a spaceship in orbit around Earth. They are often involved in numerous silly antics, but seem to be adhere to a code of non-interference with the humans.</description>
<picture>40049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13680" type="appears in" update="2009-12-10">
<name>Taeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taeko is a little girl, who is an apprentice to a goddess of jinx. She has a black hair and wears a black robe. Whenever she meets someone, she politely asks whether it is okay to put a jinx on the person.</description>
<picture>40051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="427" picture="47184.jpg">Mochizuki Hisayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13681" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Nekogami-sama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Neko-gami-sama (Lord Cat) is a cat-like creature that often stays inside vending machines to warm the drinks to "body temperature". He sometimes uses mysterious powers to play tricks on Mesousa, such as dropping him into a hole appearing out of nowhere. He almost always ends his sentences with the phrase "-desu nya".
In each episode Lord Cat is shown with his fur and eyes a different color. Lord Cat has a younger brother that looks nearly identical to him who appears once late in the anime.</description>
<picture>40088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16968" type="appears in" update="2010-04-22">
<name>Alien (Subordinate)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19376" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="61">8.12</rating>
<name>Arashiyama Hotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clumsy Arashiyama is a girl with a love for mysteries and a knack for getting into trouble. She works for an old lady`s lackluster maid café in a small shopping district. The cafe is largely unsuccessful in attracting customers aside from Sanada, a regular and one of Arashiyama`s classmates (who has a secret crush on her).</description>
<picture>130800.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20606" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-10-07">
<rating votes="12">7.30</rating>
<name>Isohata Uki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56085.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20609" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-10-07">
<rating votes="31">7.68</rating>
<name>Tatsuno Toshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56081.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29077" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="407">7.44</rating>
<name>Hatsune Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatsune Miku is a singing synthesizer application and its female character, developed by Crypton Future Media. It uses Yamaha Corporation`s Vocaloid 2 synthesizing technology. The name of the character comes from a fusion of the Japanese for first (初 hatsu), sound (音 ne) and future (Miku (ミク) sounds like a nanori reading of future, 未来, normally read as mirai), referring to her position as the first of Crypton`s Character Vocal Series. She was the second Vocaloid to be sold using the Vocaloid 2 engine and the first Japanese Vocaloid to use the Japanese version of the Vocaloid 2 engine. Her voice is sampled from Japanese voice actress, http://anidb.net/cr1673 [Fujita Saki]. Hatsune Miku has performed onstage as a projection.
Miku`s popularity has seen various references to her in anime. During an episode of http://anidb.net/a5576 [Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei], Miku is seen auditioning for the voice of http://anidb.net/ch13125 [Otonashi Meru] (Kagamine Rin and Len are referenced in the same episode). Miku`s voice is used in the last http://anidb.net/s10696 [ending theme] for the anime series http://anidb.net/a6182 [Akikan!]. In the http://anidb.net/a5932 [Lucky Star OVA], http://anidb.net/ch32 [Hiiragi Kagami] gets magically transformed into Miku cosplay. http://anidb.net/ch11062 [Kondou Mikoto] in the anime http://anidb.net/a6685 [Kampfer] appears dressed as Miku in episode seven. Miku also makes a cameo appearance in the anime http://anidb.net/a6176 [Sora o Kakeru Shoujo] as well as getting cosplayed by http://anidb.net/ch2254 [Kannagi Itsuki] in the second picture drama.</description>
<picture>84342.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45115" type="appears in" update="2013-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<name>Media</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Media, who enrolls in class 1-D after her first appearance in the anime as The Professor`s assistant, is sent to Momotsuki High to keep an eye on http://anidb.net/ch9100 [Becky]. She possesses superhuman strength and is always cheerful. She resembles http://anidb.net/ch9112 [Ichijo] in that she does the seemingly impossible, but she does this much less frequently than Ichijo. She and http://anidb.net/ch9137 [Behoimi] have a past together that they vaguely allude to but never explain fully. Media is nearly always smiling and never opens her eyes, except for one instance in episode 9. Also, she is almost never seen without wearing her trademark maid outfit in the anime. In later episodes, she attempts to persuade Behoimi to take on her role as the healing magical girl once more, even in one episode putting a smaller version of her magic wand in her hand, trying to invoke a response, but Behoimi does not fall victim to her suggestions. Apparently, she and Behoimi once fought. Similar to Behoimi, her name is a reference to a moderate healing spell from an RPG series, Shin Megami Tensei.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>61023.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="38510" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寒に帷子 土用に布子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summerwear in the Coldest Season, Winterwear in the Hottest Season</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fusa ni Katabira, Doyou ni Nuno Ko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38659" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅は園生に映えても隠れなし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Safflower Stands Out in Any Garden</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38660" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">病む身よりも見る目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Always Harder on the Ones Who Have to Watch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamu Mi Yori Mirume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39421" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">晴天をほめるには日没を待て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Count Your Chickens Before They Hatch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiten o Homeru ni wa Nichibotsu o Mate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39422" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">用に叶えば宝なり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is a Treasure If It Is Fulfilling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">You ni Kanaeba Takara Nari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39423" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">藪をつついて蛇を出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Poking s Bush Only Lures Snakes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yabu o Tsutsuite Hebi o Dasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40332" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吉凶は人によりて日によらず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good and Bad Luck Are Decided by the Person, Not by the Calendar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikkyou wa Hito ni Yori te Hi ni Yorazu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41073" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熊に山椒 鯉に胡椒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bear with Sansho Spice Is Like Carp with Pepper</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuma ni Sanjou Koi ni Kojou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41074" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八歳の翁 百歳の童</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are Eight-Year-Old Sages and 100-Year-Old Kids</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hassai no Ou Hyakusai no Warabe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41373" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名馬に癖あり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even a Thoroughbred Has Its Habits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maiba ni Kuseari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41374" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間万事 塞翁が馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inscrutable Are the Ways of Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen Banji Saiou ga Uma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41595" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人に高下なし, 心に高下あり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are No Classes Among Humans but There Are in Humans` Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito ni Kouge Nashi, Kokoro ni Kouge Ari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41596" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪の報いは針の尖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wages of Sin Come Like the Tip of a Needle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aku no Mukui wa Hari no Togari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41597" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">石を抱いて淵に入る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hugging a Stone and Jumping Into an Abyss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ishi o Idaite Fuchi ni Hairu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41598" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堅忍不抜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endure Patiently and You Will Not Wilt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenninfupatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41599" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">微かなるより顕かなるはなし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adversity Makes a Man Wise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasuka naru yori Kenka naru nashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41758" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天道は親なし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way to Heaven Does Not Favor Anyone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tentou to Oyanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41759" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">果報は寝て待て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good Things Come to He Who Waits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kahou wa Netemate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42336" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">芸が身の仇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Art Causes Harm to the Body</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42337" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君子危うきに近よらず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Wise Man Will Know Not to Approach Danger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kunshi Ayauki ni Chiakyorazu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42338" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼に衣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Demon Wearing Clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni ni Koromu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42605" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">槿花一日の栄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Today a Man, Tomorrow a Mouse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkaichijitsu no Hae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44644" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弱り目に祟り目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misfortunes Never Come One by One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yowari Me ni Tatari Me</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44791" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死して屍拾う者なし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Are Responsible for Your Own Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishite Shikabane Hirousha Nashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45398" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危急存亡の秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Time of Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikyuu Sonbou no Aki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45703" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一寸先は闇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No One Knows What May Happen Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issun Saki wa Yami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96870" update="2010-04-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96871" update="2010-04-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96872" update="2010-04-22">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99590" update="2010-04-22">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99591" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99592" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99593" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99594" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99802" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2009-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">断じて行えば鬼神もこれを避く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danjite Okonaeba Kishin mo Kore o Saku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103454" update="2009-05-31">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118719" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118720" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C28</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118721" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118722" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C26</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118723" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C25</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118724" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C24</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118725" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118726" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118727" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118728" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118729" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118730" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118731" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118732" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118733" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118734" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118735" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118736" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118737" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118738" update="2010-06-08">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
