<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3302" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>23</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-02-05</startdate>
<enddate>2006-08-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Ergoproxy</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Ergo Proksi</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ерго Прокси</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ерґо Проксі</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ерго проксі</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">死亡代理人</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">پروکسی مابعد</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">EP</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ergo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">エルゴプラクシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Эрго Прокси</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Ergo Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">ارگو پروکسی</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="673" approval="149" total="174">Texhnolyze</anime>
<anime id="6032" approval="92" total="120">Casshern Sins</anime>
<anime id="1085" approval="49" total="76">Gilgamesh</anime>
<anime id="99" approval="33" total="51">Serial Experiments Lain</anime>
<anime id="1087" approval="13" total="24">Avenger</anime>
<anime id="449" approval="8" total="17">Wolf`s Rain</anime>
<anime id="10932" approval="8" total="15">Harmony</anime>
<anime id="4906" approval="7" total="36">Darker Than Black: Kuro no Keiyakusha</anime>
<anime id="3311" approval="6" total="11">DT Eightron</anime>
<anime id="147" approval="4" total="11">Hyper Future Vision: Gunnm</anime>
<anime id="7902" approval="3" total="24">Deadman Wonderland</anime>
<anime id="5108" approval="3" total="21">Shigurui</anime>
<anime id="3427" approval="1" total="18">Utawarerumono</anime>
<anime id="13256" approval="1" total="9">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="58">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="251338">Great dystopian feeling around a destroyed world and people treated as robots without will</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="506415">This is one of my favorite series. Loved the plot and the ending was especially good. Also the main characters were awesome. If you like watching series with a dark atmosphere, dystopia, philosophy and twisted plot then this series is just made for you!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="475674">totally amazing and depressive... worths watching and pretty interesting ,recommended for those who love psychological animes and different philosophy concepts</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="47809">If you like a deep dark &amp; good story this is it for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="428672">I just love the dark, ominous, urban tones of this anime. Having a strong female lead character in such a setting is a nice change of pace. The ending is surprising as well.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97536">Definitly the best dystopia anime I`ve seen. The dark slightly surreal mood is consisten throught and I loved both the backgroud work and character design. If you are tired of generic brightcoloured ecchi and sappy romance and want something a little more thought provocing than ergo proxy is for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="564967">It`s one of my favorites, and that will never change. I have re-watched it several times and never get tired of it. The story is extremely good. It`s well thought out, and I love how complex it is. The setting is amazing, the characters are so believable. I love how they change trough the episodes. The story, again, is just great. They truly know how to twist things together and make an epic story. While I`d love to make this one a "must see", I realize it`s not for everyone. If you don`t feel like thinking much it`s probably not for you. But if you enjoy it? You`d love it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="297941">Top-notch animation, coloring work and story. A really enjoyable anime series about a man in search of who he is. Humor and quite serious events all wrapped up in a dystopian/post-acopalyptic setting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="691808">This is definitely one of the golden 5, top 5 anime out there.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="75663">One of the best series I`ve ever seen. Great story with great characters. The scene and music totally fits into the storyline.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="543946">the first episodes was a totally mess to understand , but at some point in a single episode u can understand all of what happened back there and u just want MORE , u will end up watching the whole anime in 1 day 
strong moralistic side of the story too with a strong dystopia concept i</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="472569">this is the best anime I`ve seen so far, i loved each episode, this anime is so philosophical and i truly appreciate the ones who made it. since each of the actions, settings, things that you see in the anime, has a background in a book, a philosophy, a mythology and are truly lovely, the Vincent`s split personality is just as splendid as it can be (i wonder why his image is not on the cover since he is the main char) even the smallest character like pino, says philosophical things like : "pino wa pino" which has a philosophy of awakening in it, which takes 2 pages to describe. u need to watch it, no matter what</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="533655">Incredibly great anime right here. Not for casual viewer, it`s very dark, very complicated (correct term would be "mindf*ck"), has a lot of character development, but is really slow-paced and may seem boring at first glance. Watching till the end is worth it and if you will then I bet that you`ll want more. Can be considered similar to Lain, Kurozuka, Texhnolyze as all of those are also cyberpunk. It may be really hard to understand what`s happening or what the plot is, but the anime has quite a lot of hints and most of it should be clear near the end. PS. it has a great soundtrack.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422558">My favorite anime of all time.Ah, i still remember the good old times when i had spent an overnight watching it and didn`t go write an exam of a lesson at university the next day.Anyway,it`s the best sci-fi series in my opinion and the only one than can compete with it is Ghost in the Shell, but i prefer Ergo Proxy.If you manage to get by the first 2 episodes which are complicated you will be rewarded.But this series is not for everyone.It has deep philosophical meanings on which the average viewer will have difficulty understanding.Deserves a much better rating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="406294">A definate must-see for the ones that prefer this kind of anime. The plot is deep and complex and is given in a very interesting and, many times, original way. Amd the characters are well-built for sure. Of course it is kind of difficult to watch and it`s not for any time and place.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="524135">a great seinen anime a treat for it`s genre</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="253067">This anime is where it`s at.  It will make you think the entire time, and the story, even if you can`t manage to pick it all up in one go, is wholly fulfilling.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="129583">In my opinion a must see, since Ergo Proxy is not just your usual kiddie anime, but a far more deeper series ...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="329173">Great! Athmosphere and filosophy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="216126">one of the best anime I`ve ever seen!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="323986">Perfect, from the opening to the characters, the story.. and that ending...! &lt;br /&gt;This is the reason why I watch anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="113345">Amazing anime, as someone else said, this is what makes me watch anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="374255">This is an incredible series, especially if you`re philosophically literate or even mildly intellectual.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="9461">Cyberpunk as it should be. Best Headtrip-Anime besides Berserk and NGE.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="478723">Absolutly one of the best series I have watched in a long time.

Overall, Ergo Proxy is the complete package in terms of story, animation, sound, character development.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260939">One of the best Animes ever!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="454880">Amazing Anime, I`d say the best ive seen yet, even beats Death Note. 10/10 from my humble self</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="424773">One of those rare anime that should deserve a perfect rating, in my opinion. The storyline is awesome and the graphics aren`t that bad. I got hooked up with it within the first couple episodes.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="986" type="Animation Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="3575" type="Story Composition">Satou Dai</name>
<name id="986" type="Original Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="1761" type="Direction">Murase Shuukou</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>Sometime in the distant future, humanity has managed to survive, but only in isolated cities and through the use of cloning and robotic servants called Autoraves. Life in the cities is strictly controlled by management dedicated to preserving their `utopian` way of life. But something is causing the Autoraves to become independent and is driving them to seek to escape the city. http://anidb.net/ch7557 [Re-l Mayer], a female inspector from the Citizen Information Board, learns that the awakening of the Autoraves is caused by an encounter with something called a Proxy. In seeking to learn more, Re-l stumbles into a secret that management is desperately trying to hide and will go to any length to keep suppressed.
— summary from MIKOMI</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="10076">7.35</permanent>
<temporary count="10305">8.10</temporary>
<review count="22">8.14</review>
</ratings>
<picture>226334.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5115</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3505</identifier>
<identifier>kklbon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ergo_Proxy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ergo_Proxy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>772</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8079</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01MYCFTDM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1633" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>xenophobia</name>
<description>An intense dislike and/or fear of people from other countries.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1994" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-25">
<name>flying</name>
<description>This character has wings, natural or artificial, which enable the character to take flight. Or is in command of some form of levitation (e.g. a witch using a broom to fly).
Not to be confused with "flying planes" or "flying helicopters".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2962" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>neo-noir</name>
<description>Neo-noir is a style that prominently utilizes elements of the now declined film noir, but with updated themes, content, style, visual elements, or media that were absent in films noirs of the 1940s and 1950s.
Films noirs were typically crime dramas or psychological thrillers featuring a pessimistic worldview and starring conflicted antiheroes trapped in difficult situations and making choices out of desperation or nihilistic moral systems, with crime, especially murder, being featured on the majority of them. Some of the most obvious visual elements included low-key lighting, striking use of light and shadow, black-and-white filming, and unusual camera placement such as low-angle, wide-angle, and Dutch angle shots.
Film noir is often associated with urban settings, private detectives, femmes fatales, and bleak endings, but they are not necessary to the genre; a large number of these films, including some of the genre classics, take place in small towns, suburbia, rural areas, or on the open road, feature neither character type, and have clearly happy endings.
Film noir and the early neo-noir would come to influence the formation of tech noir, a crossover of neo-noir and science fiction, in the late 1970s; some the most influencial tech noir works are the American movies Alien (1979), Blade Runner (1982), and The Terminator (1984). Tech noir itself would also help form http://anidb.net/t2861 [cyberpunk] in the early 1980s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3088" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-31">
<name>manipulation</name>
<description>When someone else is pulling the strings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3328" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>melancholic</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3569" parentid="1278" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-17">
<name>human-android love</name>
<description>There is a romance going on between a human (often male) and an android (usually female).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4226" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>paradise lost</name>
<description>Derived from the Biblical story of the Fall of Man: the temptation of Adam and Eve by the fallen angel Satan and their expulsion from the Garden of Eden.
This tag is used to demonstrate the unbearable loss, the feeling of losing everything along with every single bit of happiness. It prerequisites a small peaceful period of happiness. The main reason for losing "his/her paradise" can either be the death/sacrifice of an important character or even a betrayal. Usually the anime loses a lot of its former glory afterwards.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5047" parentid="2675" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moscow</name>
<description>Moscow is the capital and most populous city of Russia, it is recognized as Russian federal city. Moscow is a major political, economic, cultural, and scientific centre of Russia and Eastern Europe, as well as the largest city entirely on the European continent.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214369.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5530" parentid="2764" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-11-20">
<name>colony dome</name>
<description>A space colony with a dome to provide an atmospheric environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5868" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-14">
<name>rogue artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence devices may at times act outside their intended parameters. While this normally doesn`t mean much in reality aside from forceful shutdowns and loss of productivity, in fiction this may go as far as turning against their own human creators/masters, and, in extreme cases, even exterminating them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6010" parentid="1278" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-12-29">
<name>human-replacement robots</name>
<description>In an usually sci-fi setting robots, or quite probably actually androids, take the place of humans.
Examples: Humans have become infertile and androids now take the place of children. Or it may be a more sinister undermining of human society by artificial intelligence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6063" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-28">
<name>hallucination</name>
<description>Hallucinations can occur when excessive amount of drugs (normally illegal) are consumed / injected / smoked. A person hallucinating cannot differentiate between reality &amp; falsehoods. Surroundings &amp; environment looks crazy, bright and colourful. Everything seems to be moving.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7557" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="177">8.03</rating>
<name>Re-l Mayer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young female inspector from the Civilian Intelligence Office and granddaughter of Romdo`s most prominent leader, Donov Mayer. She is also the probation officer for the young immigrant man, Vincent Law. She ends up chasing after the mystery of "Proxy" after getting attacked by a deformed phantom. Would this strong-minded, beautiful heroine manage to unravel the mystery?</description>
<picture>55008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="627" picture="170955.jpg">Saitou Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8491" type="main character in" update="2015-01-08">
<rating votes="87">6.94</rating>
<name>Vincent Law</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An immigrant from Mosk working for Romdo`s AutoReiv Control Division within the Temporary Immigrant Sector FG, set up to hunt and dispose of infected AutoReivs. In the first few episodes, Vincent`s eyes remain closed, his hair is slicked down with a large cowlick, and he appears short and "dumpy." However, as the series progresses, he opens his bright green eyes more, stops styling his hair, and carries himself with more confidence and seriousness. He is originally driven to become a Model Citizen, but ultimately fails to suppress the burden of his traumatic past and flees from Romdo. He has a romantic interest in Re-l Mayer.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>27646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8492" type="main character in" update="2015-01-08">
<rating votes="116">8.95</rating>
<name>Pino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pino is a friendly autoreiv who ends up tagging along Vincent Law. Before meeting Vincent she was a substitute child for Raul Creed and Samantha Ross.</description>
<picture>27647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9416" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-11">
<rating votes="22">4.74</rating>
<name>Raul Creed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The newly appointed Director-General of the Citizen Security Bureau, who reports directly to the Regent. He and his wife took Pino as a surrogate child prior to the beginning of the series.
Initially loyal to the system, he comes to despise the ruling order responsible for the city`s slow decay and lashes out destructively. His mentality also slowly degenerates, as he frequently has hallucinations of a smirking Vincent Law close by. He is quite skilled and accurate with a pistol (as shown in the beginning scenes of episode 17). He eventually ends up wounded when "Real" Mayer, a clone of the original Re-l, attacks him. He then goes in search for Pino, his only surviving loved one, but is knocked aside by an infected armed AutoReiv and falls on a large shard of glass. He eventually dies from the wound and is found by his Entourage, Kristeva.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>28950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5104" picture="29292.jpg">Hanada Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9417" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-11">
<rating votes="23">3.17</rating>
<name>Daedalus Yumeno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief physician leading the Proxy Research Team, Director of the Division of Health and Welfare, and Re-l Mayer`s personal physician.
Daedalus displays a strange obsession for Re-l Mayer. He has two Entourages, Deleuze and Guattari. In the final episodes, Daedalus has been revealed to have created a fake Re-l (named "Real" Mayer) from Monad Proxy`s Amrita Cells as a replacement for the original Re-l and eventually gives her wings. Now mentally unstable, he no longer cares what happens to the world. The fake Re-l is taken over by Monad Proxy and leaves. Daedalus, concluding that Re-l has always left him behind, is crushed to death by falling rubble. He survives long enough to witness his clone Re-l be incinerated by sunlight.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>28951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9418" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-11">
<rating votes="24">5.87</rating>
<name>Iggy</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Entourage AutoReiv belonging to Re-l Mayer.
Iggy contracted a "weaponized" version of the Cogito Virus and grew to become enraged at Re-l`s lack of regard for him. He despises Proxies and blames Vincent for taking Re-l - his sole Raison d`Être - away from him. He develops an unusual state of both loving (because she is his master and raison d`être) and hating (because she is selfish and arrogant) Re-l, and locks her up to "protect" her, while he attempts to kill Vincent. Re-l escapes after being attacked by an AutoReiv belonging to a Proxy she killed, and the AutoReiv pursues her. The AutoReiv goes into a self-detonation mode, and Iggy sacrifices himself to protect Re-l, leaving little more than his broken head behind (which leaves Iggy conscious to some extent). In the end, not wanting to see Iggy suffer due to the virus, Re-l shoots him and buries his head.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>28952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3315" picture="196861.jpg">Mizuuchi Kiyomitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11288" type="appears in" update="2009-08-24">
<rating votes="22">6.64</rating>
<name>Proxy One</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main antagonist of Ergo Proxy.
 He calls Vincent his shadow. First alluded to in episode 15, he is the one behind the events of the entire series, having created Vincent and then sending him back to Romdo to start his plan. He is revealed to be the one who fired the thermonuclear missile Rapture, destroyed Amnesia to hide Vincent`s memories and killed Donov Mayer, though all of this isn`t revealed till the end. In the end, he is killed by a combination of Vincent`s attacks and sunlight. </description>
<picture>3404.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23518" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-07">
<rating votes="15">3.18</rating>
<name>Kristeva</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raul Creed`s Entourage AutoReiv, Kristeva carries out her duties to Raul loyally. She later takes up the role of being Pino`s guardian, per Raul`s request. It is strongly implied at the end of the series that she is infected with the Cogito Virus, though her new raison d`être, Pino, allows her to keep her sanity.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>58014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58346" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<name>Deleuze</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60943.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12673" picture="151697.jpg">Yazawa Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58347" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<name>Guattari</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60939.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4923" picture="51991.jpg">Tateno Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58348" type="appears in" update="2015-01-11">
<name>Dorothy</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vincent`s Entourage AutoReiv.</description>
<picture>60933.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58349" type="appears in" update="2013-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.02</rating>
<name>Regent Donov Mayer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The elderly debilitated Regent of Romdo City. He speaks by proxy through the voices of 4 Entourages in the form of stone statues named: Derrida, Lacan, Husserl and Berkeley. Donov is Re-l`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>60955.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="58350" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<name>Derrida</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60935.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58351" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<name>Lacan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60938.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58352" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<name>Husserl</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60950.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58353" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<name>Berkeley</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60936.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2823" picture="83143.jpg">Shimaka Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58354" type="appears in" update="2013-08-04">
<name>Petro Seller</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vincent`s boss. He dies in the final episodes. He bears a bizarre resemblance to Adolf Hitler</description>
<picture>60951.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58355" type="appears in" update="2013-08-04">
<name>Cage Seal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Re-l`s boss.</description>
<picture>60934.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58356" type="appears in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="6">7.90</rating>
<name>Hoodie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The self-appointed leader of the Commune and a compulsive liar.</description>
<picture>60942.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3384" picture="24411.jpg">Arikawa Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58357" type="appears in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="5">8.25</rating>
<name>Quinn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman who lives in the Commune. Some consider her weird.</description>
<picture>60941.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58358" type="appears in" update="2013-08-01">
<name>Timothy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quinn`s son and a friend of Pino.</description>
<picture>60940.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64882" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-22">
<rating votes="14">8.88</rating>
<name>Ergo Proxy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41432" update="2005-09-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45434" update="2005-12-26">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45731" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="88">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじまりの鼓動 awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pulse of Awakening: Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pulsation de l`éveil</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il battito del risveglio - awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пульс пробуждения - Пробуждение</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Przebudzenie</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Primeira batida cardíaca - Desperta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Kodou: Awakening</title>
<summary>Detective Re-l Mayer can`t help but feel that something strange is brewing in Romdo City. When she`s attacked late at night by a terrifying creature, her suspicions prove valid.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="45916" update="2006-07-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="2">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46576" update="2006-02-06">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Invitation 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46666" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="55">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">良き市民の告白 confession</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession of a Fellow Citizen: Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confession d`un concitoyen</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Confessione di un concittadino - Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Раскаяние достойного гражданина - Раскаяние</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Spowiedź</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Confissões de um cidadão ideal - Confissões</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoki Shimin no Kokuhaku: Confession</title>
<summary>Re-l`s account of her encounter with the mysterious phantom falls on disbelieving ears. If the truth is to be exposed, she will have to find it herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46667" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="50">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無への跳躍 mazecity</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leap into the Void: Mazecity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand saut</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Salto nel vuoto - Mazecity</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Прыжок в ничто - Город-лабиринт</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Miejski labirynt</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Se atirando no vazio - Cidade labirinto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mu e no Chouyaku: Mazecity</title>
<summary>Re-l discovers a tangent point between a male immigrant under her probationary supervision and the phantom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="46985" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="49">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来詠み, 未来黄泉 futu-risk</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Signs of Future, Hades of Future: Futu-Risk</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Signes du futur, Hades du futur</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Visione futura. l`ade del futuro - futu-risk</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Знак будущего, ад будущего - Футу-риск</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Niepewna przyszłość</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Oráculo do futuro, submundo do futuro - Futu-risco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai Yomi, Mirai Yomi: Futu-Risk</title>
<summary>Re-l finds a clue which she uses to follow Vincent Law`s footprints. Meanwhile, Vincent and Pino begin to explore the outside world?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47896" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="48">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">召還 TASOGARE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Recall: Tasogare</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rappel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Richiamo in patria - TASOGARE</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Воспоминания - Сумерки</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zmierzch</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Re-convocação - O Caso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoukan: Tasogare</title>
<summary>Re-l leaves Romdo for the first time. After she recovers from the initial shock, a colony appears made of rubble created from cast off scraps of Romdo. It was a place called the "Commune" where those who ran away from the dome gathered and lived.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47897" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="48">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還 domecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return Home: Domecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ritorno a casa - domecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Возвращение домой - Возвращение в купол</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Powrót</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Retorno - Volta ao domo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan: Domecoming</title>
<summary>Re-l catches an infectious disease while trying to rescue Vincent. The Commune`s residents tell him that they will give him a vaccine to treat the infection if he obeys a certain condition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47898" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="46">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リル124C41+ re-l124c41+</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re-l 124C41+: Re-l124C41+</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">re-l124c41+</title>
<title xml:lang="it">RE-L124C41+ - re-l124c41+</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">РИЛ 124С41+</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">re-l124c41+</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">RE-L124C41+ - A verdadeira para buscar o escolhido</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">RE-L124C41+</title>
<summary>Vincent, Pino and the surviving members of the commune escape from the shadows of Romdo. They push ahead down a single road to Vincent`s hometown, Mosko Dome. However, the harsh environment bears down on Vincent and his group.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47899" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="46">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光線 shining sign</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light Beam: Shining Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Faisceau lumineux</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Raggio di luce - shining sign</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Луч света - Пылающий знак</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Światło księżyca</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Sinal luminoso - Raio de luz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousen: Shining Sign</title>
<summary>The journey to Mosko has begun. Vincent and Pino single-mindedly forge ahead the frozen land where nothing can be seen. Armed helicopters and combat jeeps suddenly appear. They have entered a combat zone where those who fight against AutoReivs live.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47900" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="45">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝きの破片 angel`s share</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shards of Brilliance: Angel`s Share</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Éclats brillants</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Frammento lucente - angel`s share</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Осколки былой славы - Ангельская доля</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wysłannik absolutu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Fragmento brilhante - A partilha dos anjos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayaki no Hahen: Angel`s Share</title>
<summary>Vincent finds himself in an unfamiliar room. In front of the stunned Vincent appears Kazkis Hauer, a mysterious individual who is a lover of wine. What is the true identity of this beautiful man who invites Vincent?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48597" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="45">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">存在 cytotropism</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Existence: Cytotropism</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Existence</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Esistenza - cytotropism</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Существование - Цитотропизм</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Cytotropizm</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Existência - Citotropismo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonzai: Cytotropism</title>
<summary>Although referred to as "paradise" by it`s citizens, the administrative control system of Romdo is starting to fray. Realizing this, Raul and Daedalus insist on improving the system.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48598" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="45">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い闇の中 anamnesis</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the White Darkness: Anamnesis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ténèbres blanches</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Nella bianca oscurità - anamnesis</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">В белой тьме - Анамнез</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">We mgle</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Dentro da escuridão branca - Anamnese</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Yami no Naka: Anamnesis</title>
<summary>Vincent gets lost in thick fog and arrives at a used-book store. He enters the store to ask for directions. The creepy owner of the store recommends a certain book to him. Vincent`s name was engraved in the title of that book?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48599" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="42">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君微笑めば hideout</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When You`re Smiling: Hideout</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Si tu souris</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Se tu sorridi - hideout</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Когда ты улыбаешься - Укрытие</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kryjówka</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Se você sorrir - Esconderijo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi Hohoemeba: Hideout</title>
<summary>Vincent and Pino take a breather inside a deep forest. Pino sets out to explore their new surroundings and comes upon a girl picking flowers. But as soon as the girl realizes that Pino was there, she disappears into the forest. A fated reunion occurs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49865" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="41">9.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">構想の死角 wrong way home</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conceptual Blind Spot: Wrong Way Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Impasse conceptuelle</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Punti morti concettuali - wrong way home</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Концептуальное заблуждение - Ложный путь домой</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zagubiony</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A lacuna no plano - Caminho errado para casa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousou no Shikoku: Wrong Way Home</title>
<summary>Chasing after the flower girl, Pino enters a cave where, in front of her eyes, appear the girl and a mysterious giant sitting beside her. Around that time, a shadow approaches behind Vincent, who was searching for Pino.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49866" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="38">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴方に似た誰か ophelia</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someone Like You: Ophelia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quelqu`un comme toi</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Qualcuno che assomilglia a te - ophelia</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Похожий на тебя - Офелия</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ofelia</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Alguém que se parece com você - Ophelia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata ni Nita Dareka: Ophelia</title>
<summary>Vincent, Re-l and Pino stop at a deserted dome to replenish their supplies. Re-l discovers a beautiful verdant garden and proceeds to walk into it, totally unaware of the eyes staring at her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49867" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="48">2.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生悪夢のクイズSHOW! WHO WANTS TO BE IN JEOPARDY!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare Quiz Show! Who Wants to Be in Jeopardy!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cauchemar Quiz</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Who wants to be in Jeopardy!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Адская викторина - Кто хочет стать миллионером?</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zabójczy teleturniej</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O quiz show pesadelo - Ninguém quer estar em sabatina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ki Akumu no Quiz Show! Who Wants to Be in Jeopardy!</title>
<summary>The reality gameshow craze reaches out to touch our world weary travellers. Vincent goes head to head in a fatal face off with a host who knows much more than he should.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49868" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="50">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デッドカーム busy doing nothing</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Calm: Busy Doing Nothing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Calme plat</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Calma piatta - busy doing nothing</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мёртвый штиль - Праздные дни</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pracowicie bezczynni</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Calma morta - Ocupado fazendo nada</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Calm: Busy Doing Nothing</title>
<summary>The travelers are at a standstill. Without any way to get moving, they spend the days in anguish, just hoping for the wind to start blowing. An incident occurs that serves to permanently differentiate Re-l from a Good Citizen?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50417" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="33">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらない戦い terra incognita</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never-Ending Battle: Terra Incognita</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Battaglia senza fine - Terra incognita</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Бесконечная битва - Терра инкогнита</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ziemia niczyja</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Luta sem fim - Terra incógnita</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Tatakai: Terra Incognita</title>
<summary>The journey to Mosko is almost at its end. Along the way, Pino suddenly disappears. Vince and Re-l search for her and discover a cave leading underground. There they discover a truth that they could never begin to imagine?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50418" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="35">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終着の調べ life after god</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sign of the End: Life After God</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Enquête en destination finale</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Indagine finale - life after god</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Осмотр места прибытия - Жизнь после бога</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Życie po bogu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Inspecionando o destino final - Vida após deus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuchaku no Shirabe: Life After God</title>
<summary>Finally, Vincent and his group arrive at the Mosko Dome. As Vince walks all over the desolate dome city, he is unable to remember anything from his past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50419" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="46">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女スマイル eternal smile</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl with a Smile: Eternal Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille au sourire</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sorriso di bambina - Eternal smile</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Улыбка девочки - Вечная улыбка</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wieczny uśmiech</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Sorriso eterno - A garota do sorriso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Smile: Eternal Smile</title>
<summary>A thrilling and enjoyable story about the AutoReiv, Pino, and her friends exploring a theme park called "Welcome Land." But behind this seemingly happy place, lie hidden truths in the smile of an android.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50420" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="36">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚空の聖眼 Goodbye Vincent</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sacred Eye of the Void: Goodbye Vincent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au revoir Vincent</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`occhio sacro nel cielo - Goodbye, Vincent</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Глаз в небе - Прощай, Винсент</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Żegnaj, Vincencie</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O olho flutuante que tudo vê - Adeus, Vincent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuu no Seigan: Goodbye Vincent</title>
<summary>A pulse that beats out a rhythm like clockwork. A figure that wakes up in a hospital room and slowly raises his body. Who is this figure?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50421" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="34">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時果つる処 shampoo planet</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet at the End of Time: Shampoo Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Là où finit le temps</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Dove il tempo e esaurito - shampoo planet</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">На краю времени - Планета шампуня</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Czas na końcu czasu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O lugar que o tempo esqueceu - Planeta Shampoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki Hate Tsuru Sho: Shampoo Planet</title>
<summary>Vince suddenly disappears. Re-l and Pino desperately search all over the city in order to find him. Awakening.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="51692" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="35">8.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桎梏 bilbul</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bind: Bilbul</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaînes</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Catene - bilbul</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Узы - Билбул</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Udręka</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Laços - Bilbul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikkoku: Bilbul</title>
<summary>A sudden incident that falls upon Re-l and Pino. And the frequent appearances of Proxy. What could his true identity be?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="51693" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="41">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">代理人 deus ex machina</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Proxy: Deus Ex Machina</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Proxy</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Emissario - deus ex machina</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Прокси - Бог из машины</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Deus ex machina</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Proxy - Deus surgido da máquina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dairinin: Deus Ex Machina</title>
<summary>The closed paradise Romdo`s mysterious veil that covers the world is finally stripped off. What will become of Vince, Re-l and Pino.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="110712" update="2010-04-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122120" update="2017-12-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194094" update="2017-12-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先行紹介 Vol.2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exclusive Information Vol. 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou Shoukai Vol. 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194095" update="2017-12-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先行紹介 Vol.1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exclusive Information Vol. 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou Shoukai Vol. 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
