<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3308" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-11-22</startdate>
<enddate>2007-11-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou Shoujo Tai Arusu (2007)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アルス THE ADVENTURE</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mahou Shoujo Tai Arusu 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Arusu the Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Arusu2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MSTA2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法少女隊アルス (2007)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tweeny Witches: The Adventures</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">마법소녀대 아루스 (2007)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1607" type="Parent Story">Mahou Shoujo Tai Arusu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tweeny-witches.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8462" type="Original Work">Amemiya Keita</name>
<name id="7583" type="Direction">Ashino Yoshiharu</name>
<name id="5754" type="Music">Terashima Tamiya</name>
<name id="8475" type="Character Design">Nakayama Daisuke</name>
<name id="12621" type="Series Composition">Obara Shinji</name>
<name id="738" type="Animation Work">Studio 4C</name>
</creators>
<description>"Tweeny Witches" The Adventure created by Studio 4C in collaboration with "Garo" creator Keita Amemiya. Includes the Alice chapters "Sakana ni Natta Maho Shojotai" and "Fuin Sareta Kokoro," Sheila chapters "Yosei Hakusho" and "Kori no Majo to Hien no Taki," and Eva chapters "Dragon House no Himitsu" and "Shippu Doto no Maho Shojotai" on three DVDs. Created during the original run of the TV series but never released until it came out on DVD.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="317">5.83</permanent>
<temporary count="323">6.84</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>73946.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6191</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3991</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tweeny-witches.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Adventures_of_Tweeny_Witches</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法少女隊アルス#.E9.AD.94.E6.B3.95.E5.B0.91.E5.A5.B3.E9.9A.8A.E3.82.A2.E3.83.AB.E3.82.B9_THE_ADVENTURE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>328926</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11366</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2484" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-04">
<name>broom</name>
<description>A domestic utensil with fibers bound together at the end of a long handle, used for sweeping. Brooms are frequently associated with witches, which they use for flying.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3457" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-17">
<name>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland</name>
<description>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland (often shortened to Alice in Wonderland,) is an 1865 novel written by English author Charles Lutwidge Dodgson under the pseudonym Lewis Carroll. It tells of a girl named Alice falling through a rabbit hole into a fantasy world populated by peculiar, anthropomorphic creatures. The tale plays with logic, giving the story lasting popularity with adults as well as with children. It is considered to be one of the best examples of the literary nonsense genre. Its narrative course and structure, characters and imagery have been enormously influential in both popular culture and literature, especially in the fantasy genre.
The anime or an episode features important elements of the novel. This could mean that the main character is portrayed as Alice (with another name), accompanied by somebody portraying the white rabbit (possibly as a human). While the world can be a Wonderland, it does not have to be.</description>
<picurl>169452.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13370" type="main character in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="18">4.65</rating>
<name>Arusu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13371" type="main character in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="14">7.64</rating>
<name>Sheila</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13372" type="main character in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="10">7.43</rating>
<name>Eva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13374" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="3">6.17</rating>
<name>Ateria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66674.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13375" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="4">3.12</rating>
<name>Grand Master</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2363" picture="146785.jpg">Kinomiya Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66926" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2879" picture="170992.jpg">Hino Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101209" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Mileth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3180" picture="24696.jpg">Ikeda Chigusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101210" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Miletis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101217" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Gana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101218" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Jestor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4841" picture="55063.jpg">Iwasaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101219" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Magica</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101220" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Jiji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6982" picture="186155.jpg">Yamaguchi Noboru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101221" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48" picture="16640.jpg">Yono Hikari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101222" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Hata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101223" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Toma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101225" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Toma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During a war in the Witch Realm, an evil witch planted a wicked heart into her. Before her heart could be completely corrupted, Toma chose to be sealed away in order to keep her powers from being abused. Ever since, her heart is split into two opposing sides, who fight each other to keep it sealed away.</description>
<picture>230871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101226" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Toma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During a war in the Witch Realm, an evil witch planted a wicked heart into her. Before her heart could be completely corrupted, Toma chose to be sealed away in order to keep her powers from being abused. Ever since, her heart is split into two opposing sides, who fight each other to keep it sealed away.</description>
<picture>230872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101228" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Credelle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23927" picture="67010.jpg">Fujiki Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101229" type="appears in" update="2019-03-03">
<name>Presatio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230877.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="87851" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魚になった魔法少女隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Girl Squad Turned Into Fish</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">물고기가 되서 마법소녀대</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakana ni Natta Mahou Shoujo Tai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88343" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疾風怒涛の魔法少女隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Girl Squad Storm and Stress</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">질풍노도의 마법소녀대</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shippuu Dotou no Mahou Shoujo Tai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88344" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラゴンハウスの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Dragon House</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">드래곤 하우스의 비밀</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dragon House no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88345" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の魔女と氷炎の竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ice Witch and the Dragon of Fire and Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">얼음 마녀와 얼음 불꽃의 용</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Majo to Hyouen no Ryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88346" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精白書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairy Chronicles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">요정백서</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei Hakusho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88347" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">封印された心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heart Sealed Away</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">봉인된 마음</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuin Sareta Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88348" update="2008-02-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
