<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3309" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-10-01</startdate>
<enddate>2006-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Idaten Jump</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">韦驮天翔</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">韋駄天翔(ジャンプ)</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">يداتين جمب</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Idaten Jump</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เจ้าหนูนักซิ่ง สิงห์ภูเขา</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.idatenjump.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1136" type="Animation Work">Trans Arts</name>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="4502" type="Direction">Hamana Takayuki</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="6577" type="Character Design">Yatsu Miyako</name>
<name id="6577" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yatsu Miyako</name>
</creators>
<description>After a challenge from a rival mountain biking team, http://anidb.net/ch61334 [Shou] and friends find themselves mysteriously transported to another world.
Soon learning that the path that back to their world may be at the end of a series of dangerous Mountain Bike races, Shou enters carrying the hopes of all his friends on his shoulders.
Can Shou survive the Idaten Battle?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="69">2.64</permanent>
<temporary count="69">5.32</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221764.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6495</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1316</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3038</identifier>
<identifier>joneya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/idaten/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.idatenjump.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Idaten_Jump</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>韋駄天翔#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>680</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323505</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7738</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1049" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-06">
<name>cycling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="61334" type="main character in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Yamato Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61335" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Shidou Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1628" picture="19670.jpg">Ishige Sawa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61336" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Sakamaki Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2898" picture="228086.jpg">Tsumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61337" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Housuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61338" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Shidou Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61339" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Samejima Gabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16959" picture="147242.jpg">Kanada Akiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61340" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Yuuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61341" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Samejima Taiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3953" picture="25794.jpg">Kusuda Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61342" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Koei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61343" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Arthur</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1926" picture="156610.jpg">Kishi Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61344" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-08">
<name>Yamato Ayumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1995" picture="21297.jpg">Kanzaki Chiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="45752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これがMTBバトルだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This is an MTB Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore ga MTB Battle Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45803" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大脱走! 砂丘の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Escape! Sand Dune Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daidassou! Sakyuu no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45804" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">憧れのゴールドセレブリゾートシティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Admired Celeb Resort City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akogare no Celeb Resort City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45805" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃! 初めての敗北!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash! The First Defeat?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki! Hajimete no Haiboku?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45806" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネプチューン登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Neptune!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neptune Toujou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45807" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">船上バトル! チームSTの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Onboard Battle! Team ST`s Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou Battle! Team ST no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45808" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">学校バトル! 炸裂, 韋駄天クロス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Battle! Explosion, Idaten Cross!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakkou Battle! Sakuretsu, Idaten Cross!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45809" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の火山バトル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fiery Volcano Battle!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Kazan no Battle!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45810" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強の敵, 出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Rival Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Teki, Shutsugen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45811" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハイテク集団の挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A High-Tech Group`s Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">High-Tech Shuudan no Chousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45812" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面少年の正体!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Identity of the Masked Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen Shounen no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45813" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とり戻せ! オレのMTB</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Back! My MTB!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torimodose! Ore no MTB!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45814" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アウッ! MTBの墓場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ouch! MTB`s Graveyard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Auu! MTB no Hakaba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45815" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フレイムカイザーを倒した男!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Beat Flame Kaiser?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flame Kaiser o Taosu Otoko!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45816" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">MTBの王子様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince of MTB</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">MTB no Ouji-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73058" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨の中の死闘, 目覚めよネプチューン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Struggle in the Rain, Awakened Neptune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame no Naka no Shitou, Mezameru Neptune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73059" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ついにわかった! チームSTの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Finally Understand! Team ST`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsui ni Wakatta! Team ST no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73060" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たな刺客! 試練の兄妹バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Assassin! The Test`s Battle Between Siblings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratana Shikaku! Shiren no Kyoudai Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73061" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! フレイムカイザーVS.サンダーエンペラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Flame Kaiser vs. Thunder Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Flame Kaiser VS. Thunder Emperor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73062" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵! 忍者ライダー孤影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Formidable Opponent! Ninja Rider Kokage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki! Ninja Rider Kokage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73063" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Xシティの門番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">X City`s Gate Guardians</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">X City no Monban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73064" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">やったぜ到着! Xシティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrival! X City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yattaze Touchaku! X City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73065" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">韋駄天バトルトーナメント開幕!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Idaten Battle Tournament Begins!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idaten Battle Tournament Kaimaku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73066" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! フレイムカイザーVS.ネプチューン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash! Flame Kaiser vs. Thunder Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Flame Kaiser VS. Thunder Emperor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73067" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハンマーヘッド! 6台目の韋駄天バイク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hammerhead! The 6th Idaten Bike</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hammerhead! 6 Dai Me no Idaten Bike</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73068" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">必殺! 獅堂スペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Certain Kill! Shido Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hissatsu! Shido Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73069" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! ハンマーヘッドVS.エアロシザース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle! Hammerhead vs. Aero Scissors!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Hammerhead VS. Aero Scissors</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73070" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰謀の決勝戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Showdown`s Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inbou no Kesshousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73071" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファイナルバトル! 優勝は誰の手に?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle! Who Will be the Victor?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Final Battle! Yuushou wa Dare no Te ni?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73072" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">突入! Xタワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charge! X Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsunyuu! X Tower</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73073" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終決戦! フレイムカイザーVSブラッディファング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle! Flame Kaiser vs. Bloody Fang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuu kessen! Flame Kaiser VS Bloody Fang</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73074" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならXゾーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell X Zone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara X Zone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73075" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる強敵, その名はチームX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New, Formidable Enemy - The Name is Team X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Kyouteki, Sono Na wa Team X</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73076" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再びXゾーンへ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To X Zone Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matatabi X Zone e!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73077" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃! 生きていた翔の父</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock! Sho`s Father is Alive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki! Ikite Ita Shou no Chichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73078" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆走! インペリアルDG!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roar! Imperial Dragon!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baksou! Imperial DG!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73079" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖のダークエンブレム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Feared Dark Emblem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyofu no Dark Emblem</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73080" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">牙舞の誘惑, フレイムカイザー大ピンチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gabu`s Allure, Flame Kaiser`s in a Pinch!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gabu no Yuuwaku, Flame Kaiser Sai Pinch!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73081" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白熱! インペリアルDG VS. エアロシザース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Climax! Imperial Dragon vs. Aero Scissors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakunetsu! Imperial DG VS. Aero Scissors</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73082" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナナシの森の悪玉菌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nameless Forest`s Vermin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanashi no Mori no Akudamakin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73083" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アーサーの挑戦! 幻の島への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arthur`s Challenge! The Road to the Island of Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arthur no Chousen! Maboroshi no Shima e no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73084" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">韋駄天バイク大集合! チームXとの決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idaten Bike`s Big Gathering! The Showdown with Team X!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idaten Bike no Saishuugou! Team X to no Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73085" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">翔VS.獅堂! 魂を賭けたバトル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sho vs. Shido! Battle of Life or Death!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sho VS. Shido! Tamashii o Kaketa Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73086" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃の再会! インペリアルX出現!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shocking Reunion! Imperial X Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki no Saikai! Imperial X Shutsugen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73087" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二の島現る! 世界崩壊の始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Island Appears! The Beginning of the World`s Collapse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daini no Shima Arawaru! Sekai Houkai no Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73088" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大襲撃! チームX VS. インペリアルDG</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charge! Team X vs. Imperial Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daishuugeki! Team X VS. Imperial DG</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73089" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の練習場, 翔の特訓!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Training Grounds, Sho`s Special Training!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Renshoujou, Sho no Tokkun!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73090" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の力! 新必殺技炸裂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle Power! New Secret Move Explosion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Chikara! Shin Hissatsu Waza Sakuretsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73091" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フレイムカイザーVS.チーム韋駄天ライダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 49</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flame Kaiser VS. Team Idaten Rider</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73092" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! インペリアルアイランド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 50</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Imperial Island!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73093" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の対決, 山登翔 最後のバトル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 51</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Taiketsu, Yamato Shou Saigo no Battle!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73094" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい旅立ち, 世界よ甦れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 52</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Tabidachi, Sekai yo Yomigaere!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
