<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="331" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1986-08-02</startdate>
<enddate>1986-08-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tenkuu no Shiro Laputa</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Castle in the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Laputa: The Flying Island</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Laputa : Le château dans le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">لابوتا: قلعة في السماء</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Laputa: O Castelo no Céu</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Laputa: Castel în Cer</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Небесний замок Лапута</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Laputa</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Лапута</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">天空の城ラピュタ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">天空之城</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Laputa: Castle in the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Das Schloss im Himmel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le château dans le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Laputa - Il castello nel cielo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">El Castillo en el Cielo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Небесный замок Лапута</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">천공의 성 라퓨타</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Laputa - podniebny Zamek</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Laputa - Slottet i himlen</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">O Castelo no Céu</title>
<title xml:lang="no" type="official">Laputa: Himmelslottet</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">O Castelo no Céu</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Laputa: Nebeský zámek</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Laputa: Linna taivaalla</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Το Κάστρο στον Ουρανό</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">הטירה בשמיים</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Laputa - Az égi palota</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Dangaus pilis Laputa</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ลาพิวต้า พลิกตำนานเหนือเวหา</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Gökteki Kale</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Лапута: Замъкът в Небето</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Laputa, lendav kindlus</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1218" approval="61" total="80">Howl no Ugoku Shiro</anime>
<anime id="8073" approval="53" total="58">Hoshi o Ou Kodomo</anime>
<anime id="112" approval="49" total="88">Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi</anime>
<anime id="330" approval="40" total="41">Mirai Shounen Conan</anime>
<anime id="286" approval="37" total="57">Majo no Takkyuubin</anime>
<anime id="40" approval="36" total="41">Fushigi no Umi no Nadia</anime>
<anime id="7" approval="34" total="68">Mononoke-hime</anime>
<anime id="275" approval="15" total="16">Kaze no Tani no Nausicaa</anime>
<anime id="7873" approval="9" total="22">Fractale</anime>
<anime id="336" approval="8" total="24">Mimi o Sumaseba</anime>
<anime id="320" approval="7" total="14">Lupin Sansei: Cagliostro no Shiro</anime>
<anime id="3385" approval="5" total="11">Gin`iro no Kami no Agito</anime>
<anime id="8090" approval="3" total="17">Hagane no Renkinjutsushi: Milos no Seinaru Hoshi</anime>
<anime id="502" approval="2" total="9">Kumo no You ni Kaze no You ni</anime>
<anime id="2387" approval="1" total="4">Fantastic Children</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="312729">I just rewatched Laputa today with my son (he`s 3) and he sat through the whole film with a massive smile on his face! He`s truly enjoying the majority of the Ghibli films, but thought it was time to show him one of my favourites! The early ones are masterpieces, such rich characters and story, an absolute must watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="403447">Explore the fantasy world of Laputa!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="466624">This is a very good movie for all ages. Nice fantasy, great comedy, and great drama. I also love the romance in it... the romance between Sheeta and Pazu is cute.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="252254">Masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="357551">Miyazaki classic. It`s worthy to spend 2 hours to watch this film. It will be a fantastic experience and hope you really enjoy it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nausicaa.net/miyazaki/laputa/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40" type="Direction">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="40" type="Original Work">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
<name id="3619" type="Work">Hara Tooru</name>
</creators>
<description>A young girl, http://anidb.net/ch13889 [Sheeta], is kidnapped by secret agents working for a government. Rescued by the boy http://anidb.net/ch13891 [Pazu], together they must try to reach the legendary floating island Laputa, while avoiding both the pirates and the army.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6485">8.25</permanent>
<temporary count="6505">8.21</temporary>
<review count="5">8.73</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133583.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>481</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>237</identifier>
<identifier>hxevne</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nausicaa.net/miyazaki/laputa/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Laputa:_Castle_in_the_Sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天空の城ラピュタ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3072</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>149868</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>878</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>천공의_성_라퓨타</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天空之城</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2837" parentid="2628" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>floating island</name>
<description>A floating island is an island either floating in the sky, or actually floating in the ocean (mobile). The island`s flotation can be powered either by magic or science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6350" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Oofuji Noburou Award</name>
<description>The Oofuji Noburou Award is an animation award given to a group or individual at the Mainichi Film Awards to recognise animation excellence. It is named after Japanese animator http://anidb.net/cr5602 [Oofuji Noburou].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13889" type="main character in" update="2019-11-16">
<rating votes="23">5.91</rating>
<name>Sheeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young orphan girl with a glowing amulet around her neck, on the run from air pirates and the military.
It is later revealed that she is the princess of the flying city of Laputa.</description>
<picture>41038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9582" picture="219362.jpg">Yokozawa Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13891" type="main character in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="25">7.11</rating>
<name>Pazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pazu is a young orphan who works in the silver mines of a nearby canyon who dreams of finding the legendary city of Laputa which his father also sought.</description>
<picture>75853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34841" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="12">6.63</rating>
<name>Dola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40660" picture="159552.jpg">Hatsui Kotoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34842" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="7">1.83</rating>
<name>Muska</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29476" picture="77351.jpg">Terada Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34843" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="5">7.89</rating>
<name>Pom Jii-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4625" picture="220597.jpg">Tokita Fujio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34844" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="7">1.23</rating>
<name>Shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34845" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="4">6.98</rating>
<name>Okami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5061" picture="28866.jpg">Washio Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34846" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-14">
<rating votes="6">6.36</rating>
<name>Charles</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9443" picture="34858.jpg">Kamiyama Takuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34847" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-14">
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<name>Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3289" picture="203640.jpg">Yasuhara Yoshito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34848" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-14">
<rating votes="4">4.05</rating>
<name>Henri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3253" picture="24232.jpg">Kameyama Sukekiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34849" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="4">3.55</rating>
<name>Madge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3701" picture="25016.jpg">Tarako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34850" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="4">7.47</rating>
<name>Oyakata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3239" picture="225574.jpg">Ito Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34851" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="5">8.05</rating>
<name>Rou Gishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1814" picture="20690.jpg">Saikachi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34852" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="4">3.43</rating>
<name>Keiben Tetsudou no Kikanshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34853" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="4">3.41</rating>
<name>Sheeta no Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4063" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>125</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4341" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9120" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9121" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13319" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13320" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1986-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92687" update="2008-08-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92688" update="2008-08-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Introduction by John Lasseter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92689" update="2008-08-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Microphone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97268" update="2009-03-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97269" update="2009-03-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
