<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3310" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-06-24</startdate>
<enddate>2005-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shintaisou (Shin)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rhythmic Gymnastics</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">신체조(진)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shintaisou Kari 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shin Shintaisou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新体操(真)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Princess 69: Midnight Gymnastics</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1347" type="Prequel">Shintaisou (Kari) The Animation: Yousei-tachi no Rondo</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.seddnet.com/products/shintaiso.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1034" type="Original Work">Panda House</name>
<name id="14109" type="Direction">Okesawa Hisashi</name>
<name id="6312" type="Music">Sano Hiroaki</name>
<name id="1220" type="Animation Work">AT-2 Project</name>
<name id="13507" type="Character Design">Hino Kuniyoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a game by http://anidb.net/cr1034 [Panda House].
There`s a secret competition called dark rhythmic gymnastics. The entrees complete their beauty and lewd by their technique more difficult than rhythmic gymnastics.
http://anidb.net/ch65587 [Haneoka Fubuki] is a little brother-in-low of http://anidb.net/ch64501 [Haneoka Miku] who`s been missing. While he is looking for his sister, he finds her at the house of http://anidb.net/ch10063 [Tomomi], Miku`s classmate. Acceding to Tomomi, she is trapped in the dark side of dark rhythmic gymnastics. In order to help her out, he resolves his mind to become a coach of dark rhythmic gymnastics, and he gets close to http://anidb.net/ch65588 [Fujimiya Koyuki] who was chosen by Tomomi not knowing his fate...
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="489">4.40</permanent>
<temporary count="497">6.18</temporary>
<review count="2">4.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4945.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7212</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1632</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1716</identifier>
<identifier>taarde</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.seddnet.com/products/shintaiso.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3051</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="658" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>gymnastics</name>
<description>A competitive sport in which this character performs optional and prescribed acrobatic feats mostly on special apparatus in order to demonstrate strength, balance, and body control.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2704" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-15">
<name>cum play</name>
<description>Fetish of sorts where the focus is of the semen that is ejaculated. This can include snowballing, drinking copious amounts of semen, eating it off food, using it to brush one`s teeth, acting as a urinal for semen, gargling it, rinsing one`s mouth with it, or any other act where semen is involved that does not have to do with fertilization of an egg.
This should not be used if one cannot visibly see semen in scenes or if the scene is extremely short.</description>
<picurl>236279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2718" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male rape victim</name>
<description>Contrary to the more common situation, the rape victim is a male instead of a female. 
A common situation in hentai anime, a male character, commonly a lucky http://anidb.net/t1931 [harem lead], is sexually overpowered by their enticing and overly seductive female counterparts. These situations are usually undesired by the male character... though as a viewer, one might wonder why.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2735" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>enema</name>
<description>An enema is the procedure of introducing liquids into the rectum and colon via the anus for the purpose of cleaning the insides or for BDSM play.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2890" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>foot fetish</name>
<description>Anime contains scenes which revolve around foot-fetishism.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2903" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-21">
<name>scat</name>
<description>Coprophilia, also called scatophilia or scat, is a sexual fetish involving feces. This anime depicts defecation in the context of said fetish, be it as minor as a burst of brown liquid caused by an enema or as major as actual ingestion of pieces of excrement.
Scatophilia is a fairly common motif in Japanese animated pornography, and has even spawned a fairly successful meme inside the fandom, in which http://anidb.net/a735 [Yakin Byoutou] (more commonly known in the western world as Night Shift Nurses) character http://anidb.net/ch28915 [Nanase Ren] appears on screen with the superimposed line: "how can you say you love her if you can`t even eat her poop?"
Because, really, how can you? How dare you?</description>
<picurl>126784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2911" parentid="2890" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>footjob</name>
<description>A foot is used to invoke sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10063" type="main character in" update="2009-06-29">
<rating votes="15">7.55</rating>
<name>Shirakawa Tomomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5846" picture="210569.jpg">Oonami Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64501" type="main character in" update="2014-03-11">
<rating votes="7">6.84</rating>
<name>Haneoka Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151450.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65587" type="main character in" update="2014-03-11">
<rating votes="2">9.10</rating>
<name>Haneoka Fubuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24095" picture="64127.jpg">Kasahara Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65588" type="main character in" update="2014-03-11">
<rating votes="3">8.23</rating>
<name>Fujimiya Koyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2325" picture="21014.jpg">Kimura Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="37854" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37855" update="2006-03-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
