<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3333" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-05-21</startdate>
<enddate>1993-05-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginga no Uo Ursa Minor Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀河の魚 URSA minor BLUE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5588" type="Character">A Piece of Phantasmagoria</anime>
<anime id="1229" type="Character">Kujira no Chouyaku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3464" approval="3" total="3">Aru Tabibito no Nikki</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.tamurashigeru.com/imagebook5/gingadvd.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="891" type="Original Work">Tamura Shigeru</name>
<name id="891" type="Direction">Tamura Shigeru</name>
<name id="8819" type="Music">Teshikai Utollo</name>
<name id="890" type="Work">Ai ga areba Daijobu</name>
<name id="1064" type="Animation Work">Project Team Sarah</name>
</creators>
<description>This brief adventurous story of a boy named Yuri and his grandfather takes place in the cosmic Milky Way where the starfish live. This is the tale of their fantasy journey in search of the reasons behind disappearance of stars and following the mysterious monster fish.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="272">4.77</permanent>
<temporary count="273">6.16</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>4665.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3518</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3056</identifier>
<identifier>jwkugq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tamurashigeru.com/imagebook5/gingadvd.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>153723</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3234" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-31">
<name>space is an ocean</name>
<description>The difference between space and ocean is marginal. In fact the two are completely interchangeable. Spacecraft are usually called ships and space forces use naval ranks. Movement in space is two-dimensional. There is friction. And not to forget space pirates are roaming through the galaxy and just so often you will encounter space whales.
Some titles take this even a step further by actually displaying the space as a sort of gigantic liquid mass.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6350" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Oofuji Noburou Award</name>
<description>The Oofuji Noburou Award is an animation award given to a group or individual at the Mainichi Film Awards to recognise animation excellence. It is named after Japanese animator http://anidb.net/cr5602 [Oofuji Noburou].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="36392" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
