<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="335" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-05-05</startdate>
<enddate>1993-05-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Umi ga Kikoeru</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">海が聞こえる</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">聽到海濤聲</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Can Hear the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I can hear the ocean</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Tu peux entendre la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Je peux entendre l`océan</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Posso sentire il mare</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Здесь слышен океан</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Eu Posso Ouvir o Mar</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Ondas do Oceano</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Vandenyno Bangos</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Я чую море</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">海きこ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">うみきこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">OW</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ugk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">umikiko</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">海がきこえる</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ocean Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Flüstern des Meeres: Ocean Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">바다가 들린다</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Szum Morza</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Jag kan höra havet</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Aaltojen kuohu</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">גלי הים</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">A Tenger Zúgása</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">สองหัวใจ หนึ่งรักเดียว</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Ookeanilained</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13363" approval="1" total="4">Kimi no Suizou o Tabetai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="168407">Classic Studio Ghibli. Great style and beautiful slice of life movie. recommended for all fans of good solid anime</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="500" type="Direction">Mochizuki Tomomi</name>
<name id="499" type="Character Design">Kondou Katsuya</name>
<name id="8234" type="Music">Nagata Shigeru</name>
<name id="8995" type="Original Work">Himuro Saeko</name>
</creators>
<description>High school students http://anidb.net/ch30079 [Taku] and best friend http://anidb.net/ch30080 [Matsuno] are figuring out what they would like to do with their lives when a girl named http://anidb.net/ch30081 [Rikako] transfers into their school. Rikako is a smart, charming and sophisticated girl who had to move away from her urban surroundings, to a sea shore countryside village. But she has troubles of her own...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1972">6.21</permanent>
<temporary count="1986">7.23</temporary>
<review count="3">7.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>145633.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>208</identifier>
<identifier>wwsidb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nausicaa.net/miyazaki/umi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ocean_Waves_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>海がきこえる</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152129</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1884</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>바다가_들린다</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>海潮之声</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3146" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-29">
<name>divorce</name>
<description>The parents depicted in this anime have divorced, usually upsetting the life of their children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30075" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-21">
<rating votes="6">2.38</rating>
<name>Kohama Yumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kohama Yumi is Rikako`s closest friend in Kouchi.</description>
<picture>70267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30076" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-21">
<rating votes="5">1.88</rating>
<name>Yamao Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamao Tadashi is a friend of Taku, who has a crush on Yumi. He confesses this love to everyone at the class reunion prior to Yumi`s arrival, before collapsing into unconsciousness due to excess alcohol consumption.</description>
<picture>70271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30077" type="appears in" update="2011-04-21">
<rating votes="3">1.14</rating>
<name>Okada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okada is Rikako`s ex-boyfriend. While in Tokyo, Rikako heads to a restaurant near the hotel to meet with Okada. Over the course of the meal she discovers that he is not the type of person she once thought he was. He has also started dating Rikako`s best friend. She telephones Taku to ask him to rescue her from the situation.</description>
<picture>70269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9195" picture="33999.jpg">Kanemaru Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30078" type="appears in" update="2011-03-16">
<name>Kawamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2275" picture="21922.jpg">Tokumaru Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30079" type="main character in" update="2011-04-21">
<rating votes="9">5.68</rating>
<name>Morisaki Taku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morisaki Taku is the main protagonist. Taku, needing money for the school`s trip to Hawaii, took his restaurant busboy job to offset the expense, at the cost of falling grades and his teachers disapproval.</description>
<picture>70266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30080" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-21">
<rating votes="6">2.70</rating>
<name>Matsuno Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsuno Yutaka is Taku`s friend and rival for Rikako`s affections. Yutaka and Taku became friends when they jointly campaigned against the cancellation of their junior high school trip due to the school`s low test scores.</description>
<picture>70268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30081" type="main character in" update="2011-03-16">
<rating votes="8">5.39</rating>
<name>Mutou Rikako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67917.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30082" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-21">
<rating votes="6">5.78</rating>
<name>Shimizu Akiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shimizu Akiko is the female student-body president.</description>
<picture>70270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45062" type="appears in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Morisaki Taku no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="256" picture="188450.jpg">Satou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45063" type="appears in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Rikako no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikako`s dad lives in Tokyo in an apartment complex. He separated from his wife a few months before Rikako comes to Kouchi.</description>
<picture>88240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66752" type="appears in" update="2014-04-17">
<rating votes="2">2.60</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61736.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66753" type="appears in" update="2014-04-17">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Okami-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61737.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4067" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>1993-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46286" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46287" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46288" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1993-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67920" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1993-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67921" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1993-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192958" update="2017-11-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
