<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3363" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1986-09-10</startdate>
<enddate>1986-09-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Roots Search: Shokushin Buttai X</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ルーツ・サーチ 食心物体X</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Roots Search: Life Devourer X</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1132" approval="3" total="3">Lily C.A.T.</anime>
<anime id="6294" approval="2" total="2">Hell Target</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="59776" type="Direction">Sugai Hisashi</name>
<name id="34136" type="Character Design">Kobayashi Sanae</name>
<name id="1807" type="Series Composition">Shimada Michiru</name>
<name id="7069" type="Music">Shouji Osamu</name>
</creators>
<description>Roots Search is the story of a psychic research facility that becomes a stopover point for a spaceship full of dead people. Of course there was a bad thing on the ship that killed everybody, and now it`s going to hunt down the few people on the space station.
From:
http://animeworld.com/quicklooks/rootssearch.html</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="216">2.11</permanent>
<temporary count="222">4.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5167.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2250</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3386</identifier>
<identifier>ippcam</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88806</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1985" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-31">
<name>psychokinesis</name>
<description>The term psychokinesis (from the Greek ψυχή, "psyche", meaning mind, soul, heart, or breath; and κίνησις, "kinesis", meaning motion, movement; literally "mind-movement"), also referred to as telekinesis (Greek τῆλε + κίνησις, literally "distant-movement") with respect to strictly describing movement of matter, sometimes abbreviated PK and TK respectively, is a term coined by publisher Henry Holt to refer to the direct influence of mind on a physical system that cannot be entirely accounted for by the mediation of any known physical energy. Examples of psychokinesis could include distorting or moving an object, and influencing the output of a random number generator.
The following powers, among others, are psychokinetic powers:
- Telekinesis: movement of matter at the micro or macro (visible objects, life forms, etc.) levels; move, lift, agitate, vibrate, spin, bend, break, or impact)
-- Speed up or slow down the naturally occurring vibrations of atoms in matter to alter temperature, possibly to the point of ignition if combustible (also known as pyrokinesis when speeding up vibrations, and cryokinesis when slowing them down)
-- Self levitation (rising in the air unsupported, flying)
- Influencing events (sports, gambling, election, prolongation of life, etc.)
- Biological supernatural healing
- Teleportation (disappearing and reappearing elsewhere)
- Phasing through matter
- Electro-psychokinesis, the ability to control any and all electrical, electronic, or electro-mechanical devices such as computers, elevators, FAX machines, etc.
- Transmutation of matter
- Metamorphosis Shape-shifting
- Energy shield (force field)
- Control of magnetism
- Control of photons (light waves/particles)
- Thoughtform projection aka telepathic projection (a physically perceived person, animal, creature, object, ghostly entity, etc., created in the mind and projected into three-dimensional space and observable by others)
- Control of gravity
- Control of physical matter without physical interaction (water, air, ...)
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56518.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4281" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>mind games</name>
<description>An act or series of acts of calculated psychological manipulation, especially in order to confuse or intimidate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="72798" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Scott</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72799" type="main character in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Moira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72800" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Raymond</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3249" picture="24746.jpg">Kobayashi Michitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72801" type="main character in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Buzz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72802" type="appears in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Sander</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72803" type="appears in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Catherine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6820" picture="151692.jpg">Miyuki Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72804" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Norman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72805" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Marcus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1658" picture="203223.jpg">Kobayashi Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72806" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Buttai X</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="36751" update="2005-05-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1986-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
