<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3371" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-11-21</startdate>
<enddate>1993-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Choubakumatsu Shounen Seiki Takamaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Children Build The Future</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新・超幕末少年世紀タカマル</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3370" type="Prequel">Choubakumatsu Shounen Seiki Takamaru</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="787" type="Animation Work">Studio Live</name>
<name id="10088" type="Original Work">Jam Creation</name>
<name id="3489" type="Character Design">Ashida Toyoo</name>
<name id="3489" type="Original Work">Ashida Toyoo</name>
<name id="3489" type="Direction">Ashida Toyoo</name>
<name id="3489" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ashida Toyoo</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4">3.13</permanent>
<temporary count="4">3.25</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5174.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7265</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2822</identifier>
<identifier>caryrc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>超幕末少年世紀タカマル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88461</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2901</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="37051" update="2005-05-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の婦女子殿が空から降ってきたでござるの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Fujoshi-dono ga Sora kara Futte Kita de Gozaru no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37052" update="2005-05-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械人間あるふれっど殿, 汽笛を吹いて大暴走でござるの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikai Ningen Aru Fureddo-dono, Kiteki o Fuite Daibousou de Gozaru no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37053" update="2005-05-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うし建国記念祭! ぷろれすらーがやって来たでござるの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayaushi Kenkoku Kinsensai! ProWrestler ga Yatte Kita de Gozaru no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37054" update="2005-05-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">洋装のミライ殿, ドレスアップで大暴れでござるの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousou no Mirai-dono, Dress Up de Dai Abare de Gozaru no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37055" update="2005-05-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大反省! 拙者のまっちょは危険でござるの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daihansei! Sessha no Maccho wa Kiken de Gozaru no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37056" update="2010-07-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">立ち上がれ! ちゃんぽん王国, 未来を呼ぶ少年たちでござるの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tachi Agare! Chanpon Ookoku, Mirai o Yobu Shounen-tachi de Gozaru no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126515" update="2011-05-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
