<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3395" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2006-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ブラック・ラグーン</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Чёрная лагуна</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Juodoji Lagūna</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Kara Lagün</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Laguna Neagră</title>
<title xml:lang="lv" type="synonym">Melnā Lagūna</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Черната Лагуна</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Black Lagoon 1st Season</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Black Lagoon First Season</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Black Lagoon 1</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Чорна лагуна</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">مرداب سیاه</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BL1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BL</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BLACK LAGOON</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Пираты "Чёрной лагуны"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">블랙 라군</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">จารชนพันธุ์เถื่อน</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Пірати «Чорної Лагуни»</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">企業傭兵</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">黑礁</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4597" type="Sequel">Black Lagoon: The Second Barrage</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8842" approval="184" total="201">Jormungand</anime>
<anime id="23" approval="121" total="208">Cowboy Bebop</anime>
<anime id="1003" approval="68" total="109">Gungrave</anime>
<anime id="10733" approval="40" total="46">Gangsta.</anime>
<anime id="5779" approval="33" total="61">Michiko to Hacchin</anime>
<anime id="6275" approval="15" total="25">Canaan</anime>
<anime id="4906" approval="5" total="22">Darker Than Black: Kuro no Keiyakusha</anime>
<anime id="4776" approval="5" total="14">Devil May Cry</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="55">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="419578">Good storyline and the right mix of action, underwold, daily life (in a very special way) and violence. It is not boring, but sometimes difficult to figure what the characters may think. For fans of angst and violence aimes, this is the thing, but brace yourself for this, its bloody.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="274870">Excellent characters, action, and storyline.  A must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="36359">It`s barely a decent watch, except for fans of gunfights and brainless action.

The story is episodic, slightly pompous, and bordering stupidity. Flying boats, fighters jumping 10 meters from a full speed vehicle to another, a bunch of moron nazis... Black Lagoon often tries to be deep, then switches to silly entertainment.

The action scenes are mostly boring. Revi can stand motionless firing from both guns at a dozen of armed ennemies coming from opposite directions, she doesn`t get a scratch.  Some would think it is cool, I thought it was lame.

The anime is saved by the four main characters, especially Revi whose radicalness and instable mood are interesting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="255852">Over-the-top action series, emphasis on both action and over-the-top. If you like action at all, you will probably be able to enjoy this series, because there is a whole lot of it here.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="759284">Recommended if u love guns</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="402221">A great watch for anyone that enjoys action.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="438022">best action anime ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="338795">Good gunfight action with a badass female lead. Kinda feeling bad for the boys in the series not coping on the girls level.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="553695">Ensky`s choice.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="462157">It was actually better than I expected as I`m not really a huge fan of gunfights animes. However it has everything that great action anime should have and it doesn`t really bore you in any second of watching it. So if you`re bored and want to watch something with a lot of action, don`t hesitate and give it a try, `cause it`s worth it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="625481">One of the best anime in universe. Sadly manga was on 4 year hiatus and anime is stuck after 2 seasons ;/</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471794">A total must see without doubts: exceptional story and a badass soundtrack!! Plus some awsome characters that are among my favorites of all time!! Recommended :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="374287">This isn`t worth watching, it`s a MUST SEE.

I`m afraid of watching any other series after this; would most likely feel disappointed, this kind of a "level" is hard to reach.

One word: Revy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="444838">short and sweet</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="308076">really enjoy this anime.. love it soo much!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="137049">a must see anime. this will become a cult series - the beginning of a genre</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="336446">Favorite anime! :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373896">This was just brilliant. Nothing more to add. Man.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471611">I recommend this 10/10 this is a one hell of a anime action, sadness, violence, real life..... a must see SO STOP LOOKING AND START WATCHING !!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="199638">One of the few anime that mix adult-themed world, gun-play, good animations with very good plot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="533051">Naah... i just like the main heroine...she is awesome!!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="346737">Oh yea... hot girl with guns... what are you waiting for lol</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.blacklagoon.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="219" type="Series Composition">Katabuchi Sunao</name>
<name id="219" type="Direction">Katabuchi Sunao</name>
<name id="3780" type="Character Design">Shino Masanori</name>
<name id="3780" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shino Masanori</name>
<name id="10211" type="Original Work">Hiroe Rei</name>
<name id="13568" type="Music">Edison</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr10211 [Hiroe Rei].
When http://anidb.net/ch1194 [Okajima Rokuro] (aka Rock) visits Southeast Asia carrying a top secret disk, he is kidnapped by pirates riding in the torpedo boat, Black Lagoon. Although he thought he would be rescued soon, the company actually abandons him, and sends mercenaries to retrieve the secret disk. He narrowly escapes with his life, but has nowhere to go. He gives up his name and past, and resolves to live as a member of the Black Lagoon.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="12168">7.91</permanent>
<temporary count="12319">8.29</temporary>
<review count="17">7.93</review>
</ratings>
<picture>131090.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6159</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8440</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>889</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1822</identifier>
<identifier>kchqii</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.blacklagoon.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Lagoon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BLACK_LAGOON</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>803</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8086</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="178" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-28">
<name>insane</name>
<description>Insanity, craziness, or madness is a spectrum of behaviors characterized by certain abnormal mental or behavioral patterns. Insanity may manifest as violations of societal norms, including a person becoming a danger to themselves or others, though not all such acts are considered insanity; likewise, not all acts showing indifference toward societal norms are acts of insanity.
In modern usage, insanity is most commonly encountered as an informal unscientific term denoting mental instability, or in the narrow legal context of the insanity defense.
A more informal use of the term insanity is to denote something or someone considered highly unique, passionate or extreme, including in a positive sense. The term may also be used as an attempt to discredit or criticise particular ideas, beliefs, principles, desires, personal feelings, attitudes, or their proponents, such as in politics and religion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3342" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-19">
<name>Nazis</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3453" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-25">
<name>vile protagonist</name>
<description>The protagonist of this anime is portrayed as highly unsympathetic, cruel or even evil.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4202" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-17">
<name>contraband</name>
<description>The anime includes depiction of smuggling or smuggled goods.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1191" type="main character in" update="2017-05-08">
<rating votes="911">8.76</rating>
<name>Revy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rebecca - or Revy as she prefers others to call herself - is not the type of person anyone would want to cross. A member of the Lagoon Company, she is the one Dutch and the others turn to if they want someone dead really fast (there are rumors she committed several unsolved murders in New York City). She has an almost-passionate zeal for killing, and is often seen grinning maniacally during a shoot-out. Dutch once commented that Revy`s personality is similar to Charles Whitman`s, the University of Texas sniper who went on a shooting rampage after murdering his mother in 1965.
Revy earned the nickname "Two-Hand" because of her ability to shoot accurately with a gun in each hand... namely her customized chrome-plated Berettas. She also has a knack of being able to avoid bullets that are fired at her... traits the Chinese American picked up while surviving the mean streets of New York City before she made her way to Roanapur. She is also well-versed in other firearms, which range from grenade launchers to heavy sniper rifles.
Revy was the one responsible for making the decision of taking Rock hostage in the hopes of collecting ransom. And although she keeps making the promise of killing him one day, Revy cares deeply for the guy, and often saves him when the going gets tough. She is also a constant smoker, drinks heavily and swears a lot... mostly at Rock, if not just for not wearing the Hawaiian-print she bought him.</description>
<picture>15542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1194" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="250">5.91</rating>
<name>Rock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rock (real name Okajima Rokurou), is the protagonist of the series. He was a Japanese salaryman for Asahi Industries in Tokyo until he was taken hostage by the crew of the Black Lagoon. He joined the Lagoon Company after his department chief, Kageyama, abandoned him in an attempt to cover up the smuggling operation in which Rock had been an unwitting participant. Rock is a humble and mild-mannered person despite being on the business end of guns from friend and foe alike, and often seems surprised at the barbarity of the Southeast Asian crime world. He still wears a tie and short-sleeved dress shirt because although now a pirate, he still retains his business persona. He prefers to use words over weapons when interacting with others. Rock, after joining the Lagoon company, has wondered if he is experiencing Stockholm syndrome.
Within the Lagoon Company, Rock is usually responsible for account management, diplomacy, negotiation, interpretation, and the occasional errand. Having once worked in the resource investigation department of Asahi Industries, Rock is also skilled in geology. He is also a skilled linguist, being effectively bilingual in Japanese (his native language) and English as well as being familiar with other languages, including Spanish, Romanian and Russian. He also has a surprisingly high tolerance for alcohol, owing to the heavy-drinking lifestyle of a ladder-climbing salaryman. Rock`s earnest personality has earned him the interest of several figures in Roanapur, including Balalaika, Mr. Chang, Rowan "Jackpot" Pigeon, Yolanda, Eda (who develops a crush on him), and young Garcia Lovelace, whom he trusts to the greatest degree. In many ways, Rock is the heart of the Lagoon Company, serving as a balance for his more jaded teammates and as a bright spot in the world of darkness that is Roanapur. Dutch has stated that he believes Lagoon Company is complete with Rock not holding a gun, saying his bullets are the kind to ricochet back at them.
Rock is one of the "luckiest" characters in the series as he managed to survive every single thing he experienced from being taken hostage to being shot at. Thus far, he has survived the wrath of Revy, Balalaika, Roberta, and Sawyer. He is personally appointed by Mr. Chang to help Garcia Lovelace, much to Lagoon Company`s disapproval. Rock eventually begins to enjoy his life as a pirate and becomes even more comfortable with corruption. Later, in a conversation with Fabiola, he demonstrates a darker, sadistically ruthless side of his personality clearly influenced by Revy and the Roanapur environment. Benny even points out that there are things about him that scare almost everyone in Roanapur.
While Rock has a family in Tokyo, he does not seem to have much connection to them due to their somewhat apathetic attitude towards him. It was later revealed that he did not pass his college entrance exams on his first try, leading his family to lower their expectations of him. It is known that he has a father, a mother, and an older brother who was academically capable and thus attained a job in the Japanese government. He was born in the 49th year of the Showa period, according to the manga version, which corresponds to 1974. In the anime his birth date is given as August 21, Showa 45 (1970).</description>
<picture>54579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1198" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="368">8.03</rating>
<name>Balalaika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7754" type="appears in" update="2010-01-22">
<rating votes="46">8.33</rating>
<name>Lagoon Shoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Lagoon Company is a team of pirates/mercenaries, who smuggle goods in and around the seas of Southeast Asia in the early 1990s. Their base of operations is located in the fictional city of Roanapur in Thailand, and they transport goods in the 80-foot (24 m) Elco-type PT boat Black Lagoon. When on land, they move around and conduct business using Benny`s 1968 Plymouth Road Runner, although in episode 24 he`s seen driving a 1966-67 Pontiac GTO after his Roadrunner is blown up in episode 17. Lagoon Company does business with various clients, but has a particularly friendly relationship with the Russian crime syndicate Hotel Moscow. The team takes on a variety of missions—which may involve violent firefights, hand-to-hand combat, and nautical battles—in various Southeast Asian locations and when not doing much, the members of the Lagoon Company spend much of their down time at The Yellow Flag, a bar in Roanapur.</description>
<picture>41775.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7756" type="main character in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="186">6.42</rating>
<name>Dutch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="560" picture="41051.jpg">Isobe Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9465" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="170">7.46</rating>
<name>Eda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eda is a nun in the Church of Violence, with ties to the underground since the convent is mainly a smuggling organization. She is friends with Revy, but this does not prevent them from confronting each other, as they share the same hotheaded personality. She has taken a liking to Rock during the "Second Barrage" episodes, and makes fun of Revy by threatening to take Rock for herself.
Eda has blond hair, blue eyes, and wears angular pink sunglasses even with her nun`s habit and is often seen either chewing gum or smoking. Before she came to work for the Church, she claimed to have been born in Langley, Virginia. It must be noted that Langley, Virginia, is a metonym for the CIA as its headquarters is located there. Later on, it is revealed that Eda is an operative for the CIA and is being hosted by the Church of Violence in return for monetary payments. This justifies her appearance as a woman many years older (most likely her mid-30s) than Revy (mid-20s), though that does not correspond to her emotional immaturity, such as her distraction to the point of indecision when Gretel offered her a large amount of money. She is given an assignment by the CIA to track down Grey Fox, the same foe Roberta is hunting as they are a threat to her CIA division. She provides Mr. Chang with much of the intel about Grey Fox, but warns him about his actions.
Eda`s preferred firearm is a Glock 17L (as seen in manga chapter 41), which she wields proficiently despite Revy`s claims that she is a "second-rate gunman".</description>
<picture>54584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5100" picture="29012.jpg">Karasawa Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9467" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="8">3.78</rating>
<name>Bouryoku Kyoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Using their front as a Christian (specifically Catholic) church, their main business is illegal imports, mainly firearms. However, they are known to import other items, including drugs, which seems to offend Balalaika as it is bad for their business. So far they have consistently outsmarted Hotel Moscow in terms of imports. Dutch refers them as "The Rip-Off Church" due to the group charging heavily on goods, especially those needed for missions. So far, it seems Rock is able to arrange proper business deals with the Church. The Church is always money-hungry and are known to do double-dealings, much to the disgust of Revy.</description>
<picture>32019.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9468" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="28">5.80</rating>
<name>Sister Yolanda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yolanda is the leader of the Church of Violence. She appears to be quite old and wears an eyepatch over her right eye. Despite her age and gentle appearance, she leads her organization with an iron fist. As the head of her organization, Yolanda usually never fights, leaving this job to gunmen like Eda and Rico. However, she does carry a customized golden Desert Eagle and uses it without hesitation in due course. It should be noted that she can fire the Desert Eagle one-handed and with deadly accuracy, seemingly unaffected by the gun`s infamous weight and heavy recoil. Her looks could be based on Mother Angelica, a real-life Roman Catholic nun who, at one time, wore an eyepatch over her left eye. Yolanda is usually stern with Eda drinking alcohol in the church and seems to love tea. After an intelligent conversation with Rock, who convinces her to make a deal with Lagoon Company, she is impressed by his abilities and credits Dutch for finding someone as rare as him. She refers to Revy as "Rebecca" and tells her that she might learn a thing or two from Rock. She has connections with all the criminal organization in terms of intelligence though not officially part of the CIA, she serves as Eda`s informant and confidant. She gives Eda fair warning that her opponent is no rookie and that she should be careful.</description>
<picture>29428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5099" picture="29011.jpg">Takeguchi Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12560" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="9">9.00</rating>
<name>Hotel Moscow</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Hotel Moscow is a branch of the Russian mafia that is based in Roanapura. Led by http://anidb.net/ch1198 [Balalaika], it consists of men who served with her in Afghanistan, including Spetsnaz commandos. The entire unit is completely dedicated to Balalaika and will follow her orders no matter what.</description>
<picture>1356.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14144" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="137">7.76</rating>
<name>Roberta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roberta is a maid who worked for four years at the Lovelace household in Venezuela. Although her domestic skills such as cleaning and cooking were poor, she developed a close friendship with the young son of the Lovelace family, Garcia. Roberta was once known as Rosarita Cisneros, a former FARC guerrilla trained as an assassin in Cuba and an internationally wanted criminal. Balalaika refers her as a "hardcore terrorist" to the point that Hotel Moscow had to deploy all their commandos as well as Balalaika getting involved in the situation personally should things get out of hand. Revy refers her to "That Fucking Glasses Bitch". She earned the moniker "Bloodhound of Florencia" for her relentless drive to achieve her objectives. Her tormented past and the smell of blood, gunpowder and muck like that of a sewer rat emanating from her was something Revy understood full well.
In combat, Roberta is a truly fearsome opponent, having trained in a wide variety of martial, stealth, and weapon skills. Among the weapons she has used were a sniper rifle, combat knife, a SPAS-12 shotgun disguised as an umbrella, machine gun, grenade launcher hidden in a suitcase, spiked brass knuckles, trench spike, and twin M1911 pistols. Her strength, speed, endurance, and instincts were honed to almost supernatural levels, so much so that Rock at one point refers to her sardonically as "a killer robot from the future" (a reference to James Cameron`s Terminator movies).
It is ironic that while Roberta is one of the most powerful warrior-women in Black Lagoon, she is also humane, possessing warmth, kindness, remorse, and family love for her master and his son. Roberta and Revy fight each other, but only to beat themselves up. Rock interferes, but Roberta and Revy tell him to stay out of it. In the manga and anime, the fight ends in a draw right after they punch each other out simultaneously, (though Garcia claims she won because she remained conscious). Her kindness can easily change as seen in a humorous omake in Volume 1 of the manga when Garcia slapped her butt in a playful manner, which prompted her to pinch his arm and lift him up off the ground by the skin of his arm as punishment. There are a few hints that she may be religious, unlike many of the other main characters in Black Lagoon, specifically Catholic judging from the large crucifix she wears around her neck.</description>
<picture>54580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14237" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="3">1.72</rating>
<name>Kageyama Takanori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch14244 [Kageyama]`s eldest son. He is studying for his university entrance exams.</description>
<picture>1367.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14238" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="3">2.32</rating>
<name>Storm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A merc in the Extra Order Company. He serves as the http://anidb.net/ch14247 [Captain]`s second-in-command for their assault on the Yellow Flag.</description>
<picture>1365.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12410" picture="186205.jpg">Nishijima Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14239" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="36">5.23</rating>
<name>Bao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bao is the bartender and owner of the Yellow Flag bar. He is an ex-ARVN soldier who fought in the Vietnam War. He often feels harassed by Lagoon Company, especially Revy, for messing up his bar whenever they get into a fight with another party and reminds Revy to pay for the damage she has caused, which she always avoids doing. Balalaika seems to cover the repairs after Roberta destroyed it, which implies that the bar may be owned by Hotel Moscow. Seen as a great hang-out by most of the residents as it give many "jobs" to locals. After being rebuilt, he calls the Lagoon Company to tell them that Roberta is back in town. When Revy and Rock arrive along with Gustavo, they all meet up with Fabiola. After some words, Revy instigates a fight between Gustavo and Fabiola leading once again to the destruction of his bar. Bao claims that his bar has been destroyed more than 15 times, most of it done by Revy.</description>
<picture>54574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14240" type="main character in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="150">4.36</rating>
<name>Benny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Benny is a college dropout from a Florida university where he studied until getting into trouble with the FBI and the mafia, and would have ended up dead if Revy had not saved him. He works as the Lagoon Company`s mechanic, computer specialist, and researcher. He also functions as the Lagoon`s driver, and appears to be the owner of the 1969 Dodge Coronet R/T (with a 1969 Plymouth Roadrunner side-scoop hood) that Lagoon Company travels around Roanapur in. He is Jewish, or at least of Jewish descent as he puts it, and is often called "Benny-Boy" by Dutch. Benny joined the Lagoon Company two years before Rock, after Revy rescued him. Benny has an easygoing and non-violent personality: He readily admits to Rock that the two of them are not gunfighters in any way, shape, or form. Unlike Rock, however, Benny is willing to turn a blind eye to Revy and Dutch`s more violent methods. Conversely, he has a disdain for Nazis due to his Jewish descent, and tells Dutch that "fuck the Nazis" is a family motto. Benny also tends to be possessive of his computers, and will not let anyone else touch them. In the second season, he met Greenback Jane, and, after impressing her with his computer abilities, began an online relationship with her.</description>
<picture>54571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14241" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<rating votes="3">1.46</rating>
<name>Chuugokujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the gang that contracts EO to take out the Lagoon Company.</description>
<picture>54121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14242" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Fukushachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14243" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="3">1.52</rating>
<name>Senmu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Boss to both http://anidb.net/ch14244 [Kageyama] and http://anidb.net/ch1194 [Rock].</description>
<picture>1364.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14244" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="4">1.34</rating>
<name>Kageyama Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kageyama is one of the department chiefs of Asahi Industries, based in Tokyo. He was entrusted by its board of directors to ensure that their illegal activities were not exposed. Kageyama betrayed Rock by appointing Captain to kill him and the Lagoon Company, thus encouraging Rock to stay on with the Company. Although Kageyama is married and has three children (one teenage son, one teenage daughter, and one pre-teen daughter), he seems to place more emphasis on his job than on his family.</description>
<picture>1355.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14245" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="4">1.38</rating>
<name>Fujiwara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rock`s immediate boss, subordinate to Kageyama.</description>
<picture>1366.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7007" picture="31995.jpg">Morozumi Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14246" type="appears in" update="2010-04-19">
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<name>Kageyama (Tsuma)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kageyama`s wife.</description>
<picture>1368.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3245" picture="223600.jpg">Ikemoto Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14247" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="7">3.10</rating>
<name>EO-sha Taii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heads a unit of the Extra Order Company, a band of mercs that have seen fighting in Liberia and other places. Doesn`t take prisoners, fancies himself to be a bit of a gunman and enjoys playing with his targets.</description>
<picture>1353.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14254" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="3">2.32</rating>
<name>Meyer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A merc in the Extra Order Company. He serves as the http://anidb.net/ch14247 [Captain]`s co-pilot on the attack helicopter.</description>
<picture>1363.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14255" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="4">3.76</rating>
<name>Kageyama (Jijo)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch14244 [Kageyama]`s second daughter, still in her pre-teens.</description>
<picture>1354.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14256" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="2">2.99</rating>
<name>Senchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="12410" picture="186205.jpg">Nishijima Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14263" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="3">1.52</rating>
<name>Luak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luak is the captain of a pirate gang that operated in the rivers and seas of Thailand. He was contracted by Chin to kill off the Lagoon Company when Dutch wouldn`t accept Chin over Balalaika. Luak`s gang ambushed the Black Lagoon, but the entire gang was wiped out by Revy and Dutch.</description>
<picture>44217.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14264" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="8">1.83</rating>
<name>Verrocchio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Verrocchio is the boss of a branch of the Italian mafia based in Thailand. He once attempted to use the child assassins, Hänsel and Gretel, to kill the rival gang leaders, including Balalaika and Mr. Chang, in an attempt to seize complete leadership of Roanapur`s criminal underworld. Verrocchio was killed when Hänsel and Gretel turned against him on a murderous whim.</description>
<picture>44219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14265" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="4">3.02</rating>
<name>Lieutenant Colonel Matsuda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant Colonel Matsuda was an Imperial Japanese Army officer posted to Germany to study aeronautics, where he remained until the early part of 1945. Returning him to Japanese-held Batavia is the apparent final mission of the U-1324. He formed a fast friendship with http://anidb.net/ch14267 [Captain Ahbe] and was sociable with the crew, engaging them in games of shogi during the voyage from Kiel to Batavia. When the U-1324 was fatally depth charged and runs aground on the seabed near the Nicobar Islands, he committed seppuku (ritual suicide) using his katana. He does not appear in the manga.
Matsuda is based on the Imperial Japanese Navy lieutenant commander Genzo Shoji, who was posted to Germany to study aeronautics as well, and tried to return to Japan as a passenger of U-234. However, when Germany surrendered in the midst of the voyage, the captain of U-234 decided to surrender to the U.S. Navy. Consequently, Shoji committed seppuku—suicide—to avoid capture. This episode was turned into the movie Das Letzte U-Boot in Germany in 1990.</description>
<picture>1360.jpeg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14266" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="5">1.52</rating>
<name>Chin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chin is a Chinese crime boss who made several serious attempts to replace Balalaika as one of the major powers of Roanapur. Balalaika found out about his plans to kill the Lagoon Company and personally murdered him, which consisted of tying him to a chair and then blowing up his apartment using plastic explosives and gasoline.</description>
<picture>44220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10189" picture="3760.gif">Tookaichi Shuuetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14267" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="4">4.25</rating>
<name>Wentzel H. Ahbe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain (or Lieutenant Commander) Wentzel Ahbe was the decorated skipper of the Type IXC U-boat U-1324 and a survivor of the Battle of the Atlantic. His last order in the closing months of World War II in Europe was to take the U-1324 and its veteran crew along with two passengers from the Kriegsmarine naval base at Kiel to ostensibly return Lt. Col. Matsuda to Batavia. He succeeded in getting safely to the Indian Ocean, but ran into trouble with US Navy destroyers near the Nicobar Islands on March 25, 1945, which succeed in fatally crippling the U-1324 with depth charges, leaving it stranded on the seafloor. With only two hours of air left, he relieved his crew of their military duties and allowed them to face death however they chose. Ahbe was a patriot, but not a Nazi, expressing his bitterness to the SS Lieutenant Colonel that the Nazis had brought Germany to ruin and satisfaction that U-1324`s sinking had meaning if his children would never see the Nazi flag again, leading the latter to shoot him. In their last act of loyalty to their captain, his crew avenged him. Ahbe left behind a wife and two children.
His Knight`s Cross with Oak Leaves and Swords is sought after by Revy after she and Rock recover The Twelve Knights Led by Brunhilda for its value on the open market. Ahbe is also shown to have received the Iron Cross 1st Class among his other decorations. Additionally, the U-1324 has the famed laughing sawfish emblem of the U-96.
He is apparently modeled after Jürgen Prochnow`s character from Das Boot.</description>
<picture>44225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4185" picture="224827.jpg">Ushiyama Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14268" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="4">1.84</rating>
<name>Spielberger Chuusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>SS Lieutenant Colonel (Obersturmbannführer) Spielberger was the U-1324`s second passenger. A member of the SD, he was charged with the care of the painting The Twelve Knights Led by Brunhilda, which is part of a Nazi plot to prepare for the Nazis` eventual return to power following their defeat in World War II.
He boarded the U-1324 the night before it sailed. Unlike Lt. Col. Matsuda, he was not as sociable, tending to keep to himself belowdecks, even when the U-boat was safely cruising on the surface in daytime. Like Captain Ahbe he also had a family, a wife and child in Stuttgart, but unlike the former, was more focused on the failure of his mission rather than on them in his final hours. Ahbe`s anti-Nazi comments infuriated him, leading him to fatally shoot the captain. About to then shoot himself, he decided to take down as many of the U-1324`s crewmembers as possible in his final moments when they avenged their captain`s murder.</description>
<picture>44221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14269" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="8">1.21</rating>
<name>Fritz Stanford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fritz Stanford is the Captain (Sturmhauptführer/Scharführer) of the Nazi boat that is sent to obtain the World War II painting in the sunken U-boat. He is a physically huge man, and is filled with blind faith and overconfidence (Though, at the beginning of episode six he does display a sense of puzzlement as to whether it was necessary to sacrifice so many resources in retrieving the painting). In the end, it is this overconfidence that gets him killed when he brags about his weapon and threatens Revy (as she slowly reloads her weapon), who shoots him in the chest and then point blank in the head, mostly just to shut him up. He wields a large gold Luger chambered for the .454 Casull cartridge.</description>
<picture>44229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12410" picture="186205.jpg">Nishijima Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14270" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="3">1.52</rating>
<name>Rachmann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Überführer Rachmann is a short, fat man who leads the Aryan Socialist Union. He and his men are sent to retrieve a painting that was supposedly painted by Hitler and will reunite the Nazis and return them back to their former glory. He hopes that, by obtaining the painting, he will have proven himself and his men loyal enough to be accepted into the Neo Nazi underworld. Though he shows loyalty on the surface, he is a coward at heart. Ratchman`s lack of foresight and proper planning enables the Lagoon Company to sneak onto the ASU`s recovery ship and launch a surprise attack while his men are drunk from celebrating after they recover the painting. He is murdered by Revy and Dutch.</description>
<picture>44223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3276" picture="24272.jpg">Nakagi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14272" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="3">1.52</rating>
<name>Gruppenfuhrer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Gruppenführer is the commander of the Aryan Socialist Union`s Suicide Corps, the recovery team who was sent to retrieve The Twelve Knights Led by Brunhilda from the U-1324. He is the only man, other than Ratchman, to get emotionally worked up over the latter`s bombastic pronouncement of his mission. Feller leads his men down to the U-1324 using a special diving pod to connect with the U-boat`s hatch. Getting caught up in a firefight with Revy, he is the only member of his team to set foot in the U-1324 to make it out alive, recovering the painting in the process.
When Revy and Dutch assault the Aryan Socialist Union aboard their recovery ship, he attempts to arm himself with a MG42 to fight back, but is shot in the back by Revy in the ship`s magazine. In the manga, he is last seen fighting Revy inside the submarine; his fate afterwards is unknown.</description>
<picture>1357.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14273" type="appears in" update="2010-09-19">
<rating votes="7">2.46</rating>
<name>Alfred</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Little is known about Alfred, except he seems to be the head of the Neo-Nazi underworld. He is an elderly man, most likely in his 80s, since he was in the SS during the war, and it is implied that he is a combat veteran. Sir Alfred sets up a test of loyalty and ability for http://anidb.net/ch14270 [Rachmann] and his http://anidb.net/ch14274 [Aryan Socialist Union], in which he purposely sends them to face-off with the Lagoon Company. Even though he sets them up, he already knows that Rachmann will most likely be defeated. Rachmann and the Lagoon Company are unaware that they are being set up. Sir Alfred feels that Rachmann and his men are idiots and a disgrace to call themselves Nazis, seeing their easy defeat by a group of "racially inferior" members as proof of their incompetence in his view. He even thanks Dutch and Revy for killing them off for him, and even harbours an amount of respect for Dutch, despite being a black man. Before killing Rachmann, Dutch figures out that the Spanishman who hired him was in fact The Boss setting him up. In the manga, he is referred to as "Sir Alfred".</description>
<picture>44224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4478" picture="26750.jpg">Matsuoka Fumio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14274" type="appears in" update="2010-01-22">
<rating votes="3">3.08</rating>
<name>Hakujin Shakaishugi Danketsu Tou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Aryan Socialist Union is a paramilitary group of aspiring stereotypical Neo Nazis styling themselves along the lines of the Nazi Sturmabteilung. Though it`s not explicitly stated, it is implied they are based in the United States (in the manga they were apparently all German-Americans, due to the way they spoke such as "Fraulein" or "Jawohl"). They have a large arsenal of weapons such as MAC-10 machine pistols, MG3 machine guns, AK47 assault rifles, Luger and Colt 45 pistols (in the manga, they carried multiple kinds of handguns) and even TOW Anti-Tank Missiles.
However, they do not realize that they have been lied to and are being set up by Sir Alfred, the head of the Neo Nazi movement, who believes they are a waste. There are more than 30 of them aboard their recovery ship. It is unknown how many, if any, survived the conflict with the Lagoon Company.</description>
<picture>41788.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14276" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="3">4.78</rating>
<name>Oumu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A parrot that belongs to the Church of Violence.</description>
<picture>41790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12373" picture="223463.jpg">Yaguchi Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14277" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="3">2.66</rating>
<name>Takenaka Masahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takenaka Masahiro is a soft spoken co-leader of the terrorist group "Protectors of the Islamic Front" and a patient, sociable person who rarely loses his cool. Despite being involved with an Islamic terrorist group, he himself is an atheist. Born in the Adachi ward in Tokyo, Masahiro was once an enthusiastic activist for human rights before joining the Japanese Red Army during the Cold War. Later, he was forced to evade arrest by hiding overseas after most of its members were arrested. Takenaka is based on the Japanese Red Army member Kozo Okamoto.</description>
<picture>1361.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17216" picture="46573.jpg">Sasaki Katsuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14278" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="6">3.40</rating>
<name>Rowan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rowan "Jackpot" Pigeon is the owner and manager of the GoofFest strip club on Rachiada Street in Roanapur. Of African descent, he has offered Revy a job as an S/M dancer more than once, possibly putting her as a dominatrix. He is also a movie dealer who carries both legal and illegal genres (such as all forms of pornography and snuff films). He is extremely frightened of Hotel Moscow, especially of Balalaika.</description>
<picture>44228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="260" picture="17083.jpg">Aizawa Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14279" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="8">2.65</rating>
<name>Watsup Shochou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief Watsup is the chief of the corrupt Roanapur police. He receives a regular stipend from Roanapur`s criminal cartels, as well as the http://anidb.net/ch7754 [Lagoon Company], to stay away from their illegal activities. It is implied throughout the series that http://anidb.net/ch1191 [Revy] tends to cause a lot of trouble in public and he usually has to bail her out much to his chagrin. He gets used to Revy`s trouble making and he and Revy became sort of friends. For the most part, Watsup upholds this deal as long as his benefactors do not cause public incidents. He has dealt with http://anidb.net/ch1198 [Balalaika] on more than one occasion, although she detests him.</description>
<picture>1362.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14289" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="17">1.80</rating>
<name>Abrego</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abrego is a Colombian drug cartel boss of the Manisarela Cartel operating in Roanapur. Whilst very arrogant, he has a tendency to be cowardly. He was presumed dead after the South American maid Roberta detonated a bomb in the bar he was in, although his appearance in later episodes is evidence that he somehow survived. After the explosion and the loss of many of his gunmen, Abrego`s influence in Roanapur seems to have fallen, judging from the attitude he takes from Balalaika, Chang and Verrocchio. He is once again made a fool of, this time by Fabiola.
Ever since the incident with Roberta, the Cartel had tried numerous times to figure out where she was hiding; fortunately for Roberta, through her connection with the Lovelace family, Roberta was protected daily by local police and military forces. Thus, the Cartel couldn`t even touch her without causing an incident. Currently, he sends for many FARC Soldiers to assist the cartel in finding Roberta; however, much of the FARC has been suspicious of the cartel`s action and even threatened to betray them.</description>
<picture>44222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14290" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="39">2.42</rating>
<name>Garcia Fernando Lovelace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Garcia Lovelace is the only son of Diego Jose San Fernando Lovelace, aged about 12 to 13 at his first appearance. He was heir to the Lovelace family line, and as such, is its current head, the twelfth in succession after his father was assassinated. He was kidnapped for a short while by a Colombian cartel and was transported by the Lagoon Company as "goods". He and Roberta left Roanapur shortly afterwards, with some help from Hotel Moscow. He has apparently returned to Roanapur searching for Roberta with a new maid named Fabiola, waiting in a local hotel called the "Sunken Palace Hotel" and seemed to have matured greatly in terms of emotional strength, as commented by Rock, since his last appearance. He treats both Roberta and Fabiola as if they were his extended family and in return, both care for him equally. He requests help from Lagoon Company with additional help from Chang, Shenhua, Sawyer, and Rotton. However, the only person he truly trusts in Roanapur is Rock. To stop Roberta, Garcia comes up with the most drastic plan to stop her rampage, fake Caxton`s death with his own hands, thus taking away Roberta`s "Path of Justice"; this causes an angry Roberta to hallucinate once more causing her to shoot him; this enabled Garcia to snap Roberta out of it mainly because the promise Roberta made to Garcia of not harming him, a vow she broke.</description>
<picture>54573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8" picture="171393.jpg">Ikura Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14291" type="appears in" update="2014-01-23">
<rating votes="20">6.75</rating>
<name>Boris Gunsou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Boris is Balalaika`s second-in-command. He can be easily identified by the large scar running from the right side of his forehead to his left cheek. He is a calm, broad-built man with a deep Russian accent. Like Balalaika, he had served in the former Soviet army in the Soviet war in Afghanistan. She still refers to him as "Sergeant" rather than by his name, suggesting that he was her former platoon sergeant. He is very loyal and protective of Balalaika and often worries for her safety when she decides to fight in the field,as seen in episode 15. In an Omake, he used to be a weak girlish looking boy before joining the army.</description>
<picture>43209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14292" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="8">3.23</rating>
<name>Menshov Gochou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14293" type="appears in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="5">1.77</rating>
<name>Ibraha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ibraha is a co-leader of the "Protectors of the Islamic Front", leading one of its main cells in the Philippines, and is resolute in his hatred of Israel, as his son was killed by Israeli soldiers in Beirut, Lebanon in 1987, after which he dedicated his life to destroying the West. Compared to Takenaka, he is the exact opposite in personality, while Takenaka is calm, reasonable and clever; Ibraha is paranoid, unreasonable and always want to fight without thinking. While chasing Revy, Rock, and Shenhua towards a Basilan military base, he is shot and killed by Takenaka for refusing to pull their forces back for a retreat.</description>
<picture>42786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3370" picture="74440.jpg">Yamaguchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14294" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="4">2.68</rating>
<name>Salaryman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12410" picture="186205.jpg">Nishijima Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14295" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="122">7.65</rating>
<name>Shenhua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shenhua is a Taiwanese assassin in the employ of Mr. Chang. She prefers to use various edged weapons in close combat, in particular a pair of kukri knives linked together with a length of leather rope at the handles, thus using them as modified rope darts. She is also skilled in the use of throwing knives. Shenhua is a professional rival of Revy (who refers to her as "Chinglish" in the anime and "Yes Lady" in the manga; in return Shenhua calls Revy "Twinkie" in the anime (yellow on the outside (Chinese) and white on the inside), whom she has worked with and against at times. Her personal religion is Taoism, however she tells Eda in episode 17 that she is an Atheist and her religion means nothing to her, which probably suggests that she does not believe in organized religion. One of her most notable traits is her broken speech pattern, which is always moving between Chinese and English. She is last seen being helped to walk by Lotton (who says that he will take her to a doctor, despite her having suffered what she believes to be a fatal wound) after being shot by Eda while hunting for Greenback Jane. She is revealed to have survived the battle in chapter 57 of the manga after Revy is shown calling her on the phone, though her fate has not yet been confirmed in the anime. She agrees to take up Revy`s offer to help Garcia fight off the Colombian Cartel who is trying to kill Roberta. She showed her first glimpse of fear when in close range combat with Roberta when she managed to catch one of Shenhua`s kukri in her teeth and shattered the blade to pieces.
It is unknown if Shenhua has any unarmed hand-to-hand skills, although it seems likely. In the anime, she fights only with blades, and never engages anyone in true hand-to-hand combat. The only other person who does this is Sawyer the Cleaner, who frequently works with her in "disposal" jobs.</description>
<picture>54585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5073" picture="33047.jpg">Sasaki Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14296" type="appears in" update="2010-01-28">
<rating votes="6">4.34</rating>
<name>Leigharch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leigharch is an Irish driver who worked with Shenhua at one time. A compulsive smoker of marijuana (in the manga he actually snorts cocaine), he has a distressingly frequent tendency to hallucinate at inopportune times, such as in the middle of a car chase. Most of his hallucinations are actually references to Western pop culture, such as Playmates, Star Trek characters like Jean-Luc Picard and Klingons, or sixties rock music such as Jimi Hendrix. Leigharch is said by Shenhua to have suffered a massive overdose (he "couldn`t get back from Mars"), inducing psychological damage severe enough to commit him to full-time medical attention.</description>
<picture>42074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3303">Oomori Akimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14297" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<name>Zhou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Triad working directly under Chang.</description>
<picture>41812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14298" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="120">7.62</rating>
<name>Chang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bai Ji-Shin Chang is the boss of a Thailand branch of the Sun Yee On Triad. Like Revy, he is adept with dual-wielding pistols (Beretta 76 and AMT Hardballer) in a fashion similar to that of gun fu, the former of which are inscribed with a Chinese symbol, meaning "Heavenly King", on the grips. Chang is far more proficient in this dual-wielding gunfighting style than Revy, who, in episode 11, freely admits that she is "not on his level yet". It is implied that it is he who taught her this style of combat, though that is yet to be clarified.[citation needed] It may be this prowess in combat that makes Chang the only male whom Revy respectfully refers to as "Sir".
He has a deep respect for Balalaika (who annoys him by referring to him as "Babe"), though their beliefs are known to collide. Their relationship is almost playful in a business sort of way, which began after they survived a shootout with each other. They both have the ability to join forces, but choose not to because it would make their respective lives boring. He also comments that Rock`s actions will determine the fate of not only Garcia and Roberta, but of Roanapur itself, and is rather amused at Rock`s "unique" way of handling things. Unlike most criminal bosses in the town, he advocates cooperation and joint ventures to keep the status quo in Roanapur. He has a conversation with Eda (which might mean that she is one of his US Government contacts) concerning "Grey Fox", the unit responsible for the death of the head of the Lovelace Family, and gets irritated when Eda taunts him when suggesting that he was not to do anything "foolish" as it will mean the destruction of Roanapur at the hands of the United States.
Chang seems easily amused, and unusually-easygoing and lighthearted, especially given his position. This might be attributed to the fact that he was once a member of law enforcement, which he reveals after being called `an inhuman scumbag` by Rock and laughing out loud in response, and he might very well be seeing his current position as an ironic twist of fate.
His past as law enforcer may explain his combat expertise. Chang manages to survive a shootout with Balalaika, escape from ambush of superior number of Islamic front jihadists, and disarm Fabiola easily. His expertise is often overshadowed by his easygoing character, in comparison with the ill-tempered Revy and near-psychotic Roberta.
Mr. Chang is based on characters commonly played by Chow Yun Fat in films by John Woo,[citation needed] such as John Lee in Replacement Killers and especially Mark Gor in A Better Tomorrow, as both Chang and Gor are members of the Hong Kong Triads, wield dual pistols and don similar attire.</description>
<picture>54577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14300" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Triad</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>They are led by Chang, who is a proficient gun fighter in his own right. Chang is more patient than Balalaika in terms of getting into battle. Under his services are Shenhua, who is his top assassin; Sawyer, who does disposal jobs for him frequently despite not being a member of the organization, and Leigharch, who is their getaway driver until recent events prevented him from acting in this capacity.</description>
</character>
<character id="14301" type="appears in" update="2010-07-05">
<rating votes="13">3.54</rating>
<name>Diego Jose San Fernando Lovelace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diego Jose San Fernando Lovelace was the former head of the Lovelace family, eleventh in succession. While it is one of the thirteen noble families of South America, the Lovelace family fell upon hard times, with only the meager income from their plantations maintaining their lifestyle. He took in Rosarita Cisneros, when she was escaping from the Colombian Cartel as a favor to his old friend, Roberta`s father. He took her in and treated her as family. Recently, he was assassinated during a speech due to the fact his political beliefs were seen as a threat by many. This event makes Roberta take up the "Bloodhound" persona once more.</description>
<picture>50704.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14302" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="12">2.05</rating>
<name>Agent Sugar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>CIA Agent.</description>
<picture>1358.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14303" type="appears in" update="2010-04-18">
<rating votes="10">2.76</rating>
<name>Agent Blend</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>CIA Agent. He is aware of Revy`s past in New York, and lets her know as much.</description>
<picture>1359.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15591" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="21">3.87</rating>
<name>Hansel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hänsel and Gretel are two unnamed Romanian identical twin orphans, suggested to be male and female, who were abandoned in a state-run orphanage due to the Nicolae Ceauşescu regime`s ban on abortion. As a result of being repeatedly forced to participate in paedophilic snuff films in which they are either raped or forced to murder other children, the twins eventually became deranged, sadistic killers just to survive. Unknown to most people, "Hänsel" and "Gretel" are actually two personalities alternately adopted by the two children, both of whom suffer from Dissociative Identity Disorder, meaning they swap being "Hänsel" and "Gretel" with each other from time to time. There is also slight implications that they could be incestuous, though this may be due to the abuse they`ve suffered.
In combat, "Hänsel" wields a sharp, wicked-looking battle axe while "Gretel" uses a M1918 Browning Automatic Rifle that appears to be taller than `she` is. Both also carry additional sidearms. While they were mentally deranged, Hänsel and Gretel were also cunning, having used two other children as decoys to distract the "Hotel Moscow" ex-soldiers and using money to distract Eda. They were also not above using their innocent appearance to deceive their enemies.
As revenge for killing Balalaika`s men, Hänsel is shot from a distance and left to bleed to death in one of Roanapur`s parks, while Gretel manages to escape and eventually boards the Black Lagoon of her own volition. Due to Rock`s kindness, she begins to shed her psychotic personality and takes a genuine liking to him. However, just as Gretel starts to begin a normal life, she is gunned down by a hitman, hired by Hotel Moscow.
Within the story of Black Lagoon, Hänsel and Gretel may be two of the most evil characters, as they live for nothing other than random, senseless acts of murder. However, they may also be the most tragic characters as they believe that these acts of violence will prevent them from being harmed by others.
The characters` names are taken from the German fairy tale, Hänsel and Gretel. Many of the series` characters compare them to a similar pair of disturbed, sadistic twins from the American film The Shining. In the manga, the song sung by Gretel to Rock on the Black Lagoon is called "Midnight, the Stars, and You," the song used in the ending credits to "The Shining." In the anime, she sings "The World of Midnight," made for the anime and sung by Minako "mooki" Obata.</description>
<picture>44237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15592" type="appears in" update="2010-03-06">
<rating votes="34">5.34</rating>
<name>Gretel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hänsel and Gretel are two unnamed Romanian identical twin orphans, suggested to be male and female, who were abandoned in a state-run orphanage due to the Nicolae Ceauşescu regime`s ban on abortion. As a result of being repeatedly forced to participate in paedophilic snuff films in which they are either raped or forced to murder other children, the twins eventually became deranged, sadistic killers just to survive. Unknown to most people, "Hänsel" and "Gretel" are actually two personalities alternately adopted by the two children, both of whom suffer from Dissociative Identity Disorder, meaning they swap being "Hänsel" and "Gretel" with each other from time to time. There is also slight implications that they could be incestuous, though this may be due to the abuse they`ve suffered.
In combat, "Hänsel" wields a sharp, wicked-looking battle axe while "Gretel" uses a M1918 Browning Automatic Rifle that appears to be taller than `she` is. Both also carry additional sidearms. While they were mentally deranged, Hänsel and Gretel were also cunning, having used two other children as decoys to distract the "Hotel Moscow" ex-soldiers and using money to distract Eda. They were also not above using their innocent appearance to deceive their enemies.
As revenge for killing Balalaika`s men, Hänsel is shot from a distance and left to bleed to death in one of Roanapur`s parks, while Gretel manages to escape and eventually boards the Black Lagoon of her own volition. Due to Rock`s kindness, she begins to shed her psychotic personality and takes a genuine liking to him. However, just as Gretel starts to begin a normal life, she is gunned down by a hitman, hired by Hotel Moscow.
Within the story of Black Lagoon, Hänsel and Gretel may be two of the most evil characters, as they live for nothing other than random, senseless acts of murder. However, they may also be the most tragic characters as they believe that these acts of violence will prevent them from being harmed by others.
The characters` names are taken from the German fairy tale, Hänsel and Gretel. Many of the series` characters compare them to a similar pair of disturbed, sadistic twins from the American film The Shining. In the manga, the song sung by Gretel to Rock on the Black Lagoon is called "Midnight, the Stars, and You," the song used in the ending credits to "The Shining." In the anime, she sings "The World of Midnight," made for the anime and sung by Minako "mooki" Obata.</description>
<picture>44238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21117" type="appears in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="3">6.14</rating>
<name>Kyuukanchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12373" picture="223463.jpg">Yaguchi Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="48839" update="2006-04-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48909" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="58">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">«Чёрная лагуна»</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Czarna Laguna</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Black Lagoon</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kara Lagün</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Black Lagoon</title>
<summary>Mild-mannered Rokuro’s business trip to South East Asia takes an unexpected turn when he’s taken hostage by modern-day pirates Revy, Dutch, and Benny.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48910" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="40">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Mangrove Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mangrove Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Paradis des Mangroves</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мангровый рай</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Namorzynowe Niebo</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Mangue Paradisíaco</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Mercan Cenneti</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mangrove Heaven</title>
<summary>The Black Lagoon is pinned down by an attack chopper, and Rock devises a risky plan to turn the tables. When it’s all said and done, the disk is delivered - and the Black Lagoon gains a new crew member.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48957" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="37">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ring-Ding Ship Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ring-Ding Ship Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poursuite infernale</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Бешеная гонка</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pościg z efektami specjalnymi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Repercussão da Caça ao Navio</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Çanların Duyulduğu Geminin Peşinde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ring-Ding Ship Chase</title>
<summary>A gangster isn’t pleased with Dutch’s decision to throw in with Balalaika. Later, the Black Lagoon is attacked by a small nay of attack boats, and it might be a set-up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="48958" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="32">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Die Ruckkehr des Adlers</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Die Ruckkehr des Adlers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour de l`aigle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Возвращение орла</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Powrót "Orła"</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Morra Rückkehr des Adlers</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kartalın Dönüşü</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Die Ruckkehr des Adlers</title>
<summary>The crew is out to retrieve a painting from the wreckage of a sunken Nazi U-boat. As Revy and Rock take to the depths to claim their prize, the Black Lagoon falls under missile attack on the water’s surface.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49244" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="31">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Eagle Hunting and Hunting Eagles</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eagle Hunting and Hunting Eagles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chasse à l`Aigle et Aigles de Chasse</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Орёл на охоте и охота на орла</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Drapieżne orły</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Caçada à Águia e Águias Caçadoras</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kartal Avı Ve Avlanan Kartallar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eagle Hunting and Hunting Eagles</title>
<summary>Just as it seems that the painting is secure, Revy and Rock fall under attack in the sunken U-boat. The Nazis unload with everything they’ve got - but Dutch is already formulating a plan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49491" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Moonlit Hunting Grounds</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moonlit Hunting Grounds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chasse au clair de lune</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Под охотничьей луной</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Polowanie w świetle Księżyca</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Caçada à Luz da Lua</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ay Işığında Av Yeri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moonlit Hunting Grounds</title>
<summary>Under the cover of darkness, Dutch and Revy board the Nazi vessel to reclaim the painting. While he searches the ship, she takes extreme measures against the crew.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="49882" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="40">9.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Calm Down, Two Men</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calm Down, Two Men</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Du calme, Vous deux</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Расслабьтесь, ребята</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Spoko wodza</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Acalmem-se, dois homens</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sakin Olun, İki Kişiler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Calm Down, Two Men</title>
<summary>Dutch sends Revy and Rock into town to run errands - and to make them face the tension that’s boiling between them. Unfortunately, Revy’s more accustomed to settling her problems one bullet at a time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50254" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="33">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rasta Blasta</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rasta Blasta</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rasta Blasta</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Большой переполох</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Rasta blasta</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Rasta Blasta</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Rasta Blasta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rasta Blasta</title>
<summary>The Black Lagoon is hired to transport a young hostage whose wealthy family is in trouble with a South American drug cartel. The crew is growing uneasy with the mission - it seems violence is inevitable.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50375" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="37">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Maid to Kill</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid to Kill</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bonne à tuer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Служанка-киллер</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Zabójcza pokojówka</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Empregada para matar</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Öldürücü Hizmetçi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid to Kill</title>
<summary>The Lovelace family’s maid arrives to rescue Garcia. She’s no ordinary housekeeper; she’s an experienced warrior, and unfortunately for Rock and the crew, she’s cutting down anyone who gets in her way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50541" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Unstoppable Chambermaid</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unstoppable Chambermaid</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bonne invincible</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Неукротимая горничная</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Niepowstrzymana</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A camareira incontrolável</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Durdurulamaz Hizmetçi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Unstoppable Chambermaid</title>
<summary>Roberta’s rampage comes to an end, but before she can return Garcia to his family in South America, the maid’s still got one mess to clean up: an unfinished fight with Revy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50613" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Lock`n Load Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lock`n Load Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révolution ciblée</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Рок-н-ролльная революция</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wybuchowa rewolucja</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Na Mira da Grande Revolução</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Nişan Alma Devrimi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lock`n Load Revolution</title>
<summary>After the crew is hired to deliver documents to the CIA, the terrorist group featured in the intelligence reports unleashes an attack. Revy and Rock try to escape on dry land - but one of them is captured.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50664" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Guerrillas in the Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guerrillas in the Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Guérillas dans la jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Наёмники в джунглях</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Partyzanci w dżungli</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Guerrilhas na Floresta</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ormandaki Gerillalar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guerrillas in the Jungle</title>
<summary>Rock is interrogated at the terrorist camp, and if he doesn’t come clean about the documents, there’s a good chance his captors will resort to torture. Revy’s putting together a rescue mission - but time is running out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="50837" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63195" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody Sub</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81145" update="2010-07-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81146" update="2010-07-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81147" update="2010-08-10">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mell - Red Fraction (MV)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113104" update="2014-07-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法少女編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Girl Volume</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Shoujo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113105" update="2014-07-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高校編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">High School Volume</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116550" update="2014-07-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男の子女の子編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boys and Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otokonoko Onnanoko Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116551" update="2014-07-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バラライカの憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Balalaika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Balalaika no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117101" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119604" update="2011-10-16">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119835" update="2010-07-10">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BluRay Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126611" update="2011-01-06">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">English Voice Actors Interview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
