<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="34" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-07-05</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Cesta de frutas</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Корзинка фруктов</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Корзина Фруктов</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Owocowy koszyk</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Cesta de Frutas</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">เสน่ห์สาวข้าวปั้น</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Meyve Sepeti</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Giỏ Trái Cây</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Кошница с плодове</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Furuba</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Кошик фруктів</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">水果篮子</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">FB</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">fruba</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">フルーツバスケット</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">幻影天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">후르츠 바스켓</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">سلة الفواكه</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Fruits Basket - A Série</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">פרוטס באסקט</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ฟรุ๊ตส์บาสเก็ต</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="official">Hoá giải lời nguyền</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14490" type="Alternative Setting">Fruits Basket 1st Season</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4148" approval="80" total="119">Ouran Koukou Host Club</anime>
<anime id="9298" approval="57" total="71">Kamisama Hajimemashita</anime>
<anime id="199" approval="5" total="20">Kareshi Kanojo no Jijou</anime>
<anime id="21" approval="5" total="12">Full Moon o Sagashite</anime>
<anime id="4441" approval="3" total="14">Bokura ga Ita</anime>
<anime id="5787" approval="3" total="11">Natsume Yuujinchou</anime>
<anime id="285" approval="2" total="7">Kodomo no Omocha (1996)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="27">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="244610">good humour, characters, decent plot, average ending; manga follows.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372636">Pleasantly surprising. Shojo with a bit of depth to it allthough the manga is better. Def. worth watching anyhow.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="452392">Cute, Funny, Heartwarming anime.  In my experience, both girls and boys like this show, not just girls.  It really is a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="526796">It was very nice to watch. It`s slow (not a problem to me), cute, warm and funny. This is for those who enjoy watching relationships develop.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="31560">Want to get a girl hooked on Anime? Show her this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="51579">Fruits Basket is a must watch anime now that it`s practically a classic. The story came in a time where some "originality" would do some good in a vast common storyline animes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now something more personal: I`m glad I watched this anime at a certain age because I`m not that cute anymore, although I still like Kyou-kun ^____^&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And also Baka-Anime (the best fansub subbing this show at that time) made some nice moves by putting some slangs in japanese instead of english and it was very interesting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="151293">A few years ago I even couldn`t get over the first episode. Now after some years passed I decided to give it a try once again. And it got me so much that I couldn`t figure out why I didn`t liked it at first and found it boring. But I must say it is a very  heartwarming romantic comedy with a great storyline and great characters as well. Though it is not great as the manga and lot is missed out I must say this is definitely a must-watch romance!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="730211">Heartwarming story that could change your life with plucky, well-developed characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="556696">A must-see for those looking for an anime with a mix of humor, slice of life, and drama.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="286977">It is rare to find a romantic anime that is also a comedy without ecchi. You heard right. It`s a romantic comdey anime that does not use Ecchi to be funny. It also has a heartwarming and very deep plot. 9/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="266747">One of the best I`ve ever seen !! The emotions are incredible !! The caracters are magnificent !! A must see !!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/fruits_basket/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1423" type="Direction">Daichi Akitarou</name>
<name id="3615" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hayashi Akemi</name>
<name id="7019" type="Music">Mutou Seiji</name>
<name id="7026" type="Music">Abe Jun</name>
<name id="3615" type="Character Design">Hayashi Akemi</name>
<name id="4188" type="Original Work">Takaya Natsuki</name>
<name id="4302" type="Series Composition">Nakase Rika</name>
</creators>
<description>After the death of her mother, young http://anidb.net/ch108 [Honda Tooru] has been secretly living on her own in a tent. Her life changes forever when she stumbles upon the secret of the Souma family, whose land she has been living on. The secret is a curse that changes some members of the family into animals of the Chinese Zodiac when they are hugged by someone of the opposite sex. Now, living with the Souma family, Tooru is in the middle of ancient conflicts between Zodiac rivals as she wears the burden of the Souma family secret. Despite this, the members of the Souma family find peace thanks to the presence of Tooru.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6357">6.82</permanent>
<temporary count="6466">7.84</temporary>
<review count="17">7.60</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221603.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>120</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>165</identifier>
<identifier>fywzcb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/fruits_basket/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fruits_Basket</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>フルーツバスケット_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234395</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4711</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/38</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2001/fruitbasket</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="17">
<externalentity>
<identifier>furuba</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7558</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B073ZMLT93</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3694" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>dear mother in heaven</name>
<description>A form of veneration of ancestors, where people call upon their ancestors for help, advice and similar in their everyday life like in other cultures upon God, Jesus, the Virgin Mary or various saints. The veneration of the spirit`s of one`s ancestors is an integral part of Japanese culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4409" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-14">
<name>Chinese zodiac</name>
<description>The Chinese zodiac is a 12 year long cycle in which each year corresponds to an animal.</description>
<picurl>167484.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="108" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="42">7.29</rating>
<name>Honda Tooru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honda Tooru, aged 16-18, is an orphaned high school student who, at the start of the story, begins living with Shigure, Yuki, and Kyo Sohma in exchange for housekeeping. She loves to cook, describes herself as an excellent housekeeper, and has an after-school job as a janitor to pay her tuition fees to avoid being a burden on her grandfather. She is depicted as polite, optimistic, extremely kind, and selfless; several other characters, including Kyo, Rin, and Hanajima, tell her she needs to look out for her own interests and not shoulder everyone else`s burdens. In the original Japanese, Tooru habitually speaks formally (see Honorific speech in Japanese), but not always correctly, a habit she picked up from her father, Katsuya, after he died when she was three, as a way of replacing him in her mother`s eyes. Tooru`s mother, Kyoko, raised her alone until she died in a car accident shortly after Tooru entered high school, a few months before the start of the story. Tooru repeatedly calls Kyoko the most important person in her life and treasures her photograph; when she falls in love with Kyo she feels guilty of being "unfaithful" to her mother`s memory. Tooru feels conected to Kyo the most because they were both left out as kids.
In the first half of the series, as Tooru learns about the zodiac curse and its effects on those she loves, she becomes distressed, and when she learns that the dangerous Akito is the "god" of the zodiac, she resolves to break the curse. Only later does she admit that she wants to free Kyo most of all. Despite setbacks, both external and personal, she stubbornly persists in her goal and eventually frees Kyo and her friends. In the last chapter, she begins moving with Kyo to another city so he can continue his martial arts training, and in the final pages they are shown as a loving elderly couple with a granddaughter.</description>
<picture>25940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109" type="main character in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="23">7.25</rating>
<name>Souma Yuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuki Sohma, is the rat of the Chinese zodiac. Yuki is depicted as an attractive, reserved, and accomplished young man with many admirers, but who finds being friendly difficult. He is known as "Prince Yuki" and "Prince Charming" at school.</description>
<picture>14588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113" type="main character in" update="2010-04-15">
<rating votes="25">7.43</rating>
<name>Souma Kyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souma Kyou, is cursed by the cat, an animal not in the Chinese zodiac but which legend says would have been if it had not been tricked by the rat into missing the induction feast. He is depicted as an orange-haired young man who is short-tempered and charismatic.</description>
<picture>14590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="10">5.48</rating>
<name>Honda Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyoko Honda is the late mother of Tohru Honda, appearing only in flashbacks and photographs treasured by Tohru. When she was young, Kyoko was the leader of an all-female bosozoku gang called The Red Butterfly Suicide Squad, the name coming from how motorcycle tail-lights supposedly look like a red butterfly at night. She told Kyo Sohma she was ignored and rejected by her parents, and fell in love with a student teacher named Katsuya Honda who stood up for her when her parents disowned her after a gang fight. Katsuya and Kyoko married after she left middle school and had a daughter, Tohru, and Kyoko learned how to work through difficulties together with Katsuya. She was devastated by her husband`s death and nearly killed herself before remembering her young daughter needed her. Because of her experiences, Kyoko raised Tohru to believe that everyone needs to feel needed, and helped Arisa Uotani leave her own gang. Tohru calls Kyoko the most important person in her life, and repeats bits of her mother`s emotional wisdom throughout the series. Kyoko died a few months before the start of the series when she was struck by a car.</description>
<picture>15801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="361" picture="32014.jpg">Yasuhara Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="675" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<name>Honda Katsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Touru`s father. He appears only in flashbacks. Katsuya habitually spoke formally as a way of distancing himself from the world, a habit that, according to his father, Touru later adopted.</description>
</character>
<character id="677" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="13">6.22</rating>
<name>Uotani Arisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arisa Uotani, aged 16-18, is a former gang member and one of Tohru`s closest friends. Arisa is depicted as tough, brash, and sometimes violent; she wears long skirts, sometimes carries an iron pipe, and often speaks like a man. Arisa is tall for a girl, and once claims she wishes to reach 6 feet (1.8 m) tall. She is especially competitive with Kyo and bickers with him frequently.</description>
<picture>15804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="678" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="17">8.25</rating>
<name>Hanajima Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki Hanajima, is a psychic girl who has the ability to sense people`s "auras" and send out electric "waves" and one of Tohru`s closest friends. She is depicted as very perceptive, polite, with a dark side to her.</description>
<picture>15802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="361" picture="32014.jpg">Yasuhara Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="683" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="14">3.42</rating>
<name>Souma Akito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akito is the tyrannical head of the Souma clan. He is very frail and effeminate looking. Apparently, Akito`s health isn`t very good. Akito has a definite mean streak and has physically and emotionally scarred many members of the juunishi. He has a special interest in Yuki and despises Tohru.
In the anime, Akito is biologically male and will die at a young age because of the curse, while in the manga, Akito is biologically female but brought up as male and is not dying</description>
<picture>15805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="363" picture="17204.jpg">Wakaba Murasaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="684" type="main character in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="22">7.74</rating>
<name>Souma Shigure</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shigure is the owner of the house where Tooru, Yuki and Kyo live. He`s a writer who, in addition to writing serious/highbrow books, also writes romance novels under a pen name as a hobby.</description>
<picture>15803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1387" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-13">
<rating votes="9">7.88</rating>
<name>Souma Hatori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatori Sohma is the private doctor to the Sohma family. He is responsible for erasing memories (using a form of hypnosis that is handed down in his line of the family) of those outsiders who discover the Sohma family secret. He is quiet and usually depicted as emotionless.</description>
<picture>15806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1388" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="13">7.24</rating>
<name>Souma Ayame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayame Sohma is Yuki`s older brother. Ayame is depicted as vivacious, flamboyant, self-confident, and self-centered, with a knack for annoying Yuki and Kyo (one of the few things they initially agree upon). In an author`s note, Natsuki Takaya described him as a draining person to meet in real life.</description>
<picture>15809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1389" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="10">6.79</rating>
<name>Souma Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagura Sohma is depicted as a girlish young woman with great strength, and the impulsive behavior associated with those born in her zodiac year. The latter usually takes the form of berating and beating up Kyo, who she insists is engaged to her.</description>
<picture>15810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1390" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="7">6.54</rating>
<name>Souma Momiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momiji Sohma is depicted as a cute, cheerful boy who hides a sad family life behind his sunny demeanor. In an author`s note, Takaya described him as "the most comfortable" of the Sohmas with his spirit possession, and "the most successful of the boys.</description>
<picture>15811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="397" picture="43234.jpg">Saitou Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1391" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="10">8.44</rating>
<name>Souma Hatsuharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatsuharu Sohma , often called Haru, is depicted as having something of a Yin and Yang personality: He is usually calm, placid, and otherwise an all-around nice guy, but can be goaded into "stampeding," a state in which he is edgy and mean.</description>
<picture>15812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1392" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-19">
<rating votes="11">6.98</rating>
<name>Souma Kisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kisa Sohma is depicted as a cute but very shy and withdrawn girl. In an author`s note, Natsuki Takaya described her as "in competition to be the first or second most beautiful character" and also described her as a "girly-girl.</description>
<picture>15813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10011" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="6">5.49</rating>
<name>Souma Hiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiro Souma is the sheep of the Chinese zodiac. He depicted as a very intelligent but verbally aggressive and smart-mouthed sophist who is initially not very likeable.[Several characters express intense irritation with him, but he escapes physical punishment by hiding behind being "just a kid." Hiro loves Kisa and resents Tohru because she unwittingly monopolizes Kisa`s time and admiration.</description>
<picture>30198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10012" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">4.59</rating>
<name>Souma Ritsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souma Ritsu is the monkey of the Chinese zodiac. He is depicted as a beautiful but unstable young man with very low self-esteem and a tendency to overreact. He apologizes frantically for everything, even things that are not his fault. Ritsu dresses in women`s clothing because he says he then feels less pressure from society, and is initially mistaken for a woman by Tohru Honda because of his long hair and beauty.</description>
<picture>30199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13380" type="appears in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Prince Yuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Fanclub of Souma Yuki. It is said that half of the school`s girls are a member of it.</description>
<picture>39502.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13381" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="8">3.51</rating>
<name>Minagawa Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minagawa Motoko, aged 17-18, is the president of Souma Yuki`s fan club and a year ahead of him. As a devoted fan, she is depicted as obsessive and romantic. The fan club bans any member from being alone with their "prince" to keep him "safe" by preventing any one member from "stealing" him; as such, Motoko hates any girl who gets close to Yuki — in particular, Honda Tooru, Toudou Kimi, and Kuragi Machi. Motoko and the club vice-president, Kinoshita Minami, instigate multiple plots to undermine Tooru, including visiting Hanajima Saki, whom they see as protecting Tooru with her "poison waves", at home to find a weakness, and arranging to have Tooru cast as Cinderella`s wicked stepsister to make her behave badly. The few times Motoko does speak with Yuki, she gets so overwrought that all she can do is talk about banal things, such as what he had for breakfast. At her graduation, she finally confesses to Yuki that she loves him, though she knows she cannot have him, and wishes him happiness in the future.</description>
<picture>39503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13382" type="appears in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="4">5.27</rating>
<name>Yamagishi Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamagashi Mio is the #1 member of the Prince Yuki fanclub.</description>
<picture>39504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2009" picture="45037.jpg">Kajita Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13383" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="6">6.05</rating>
<name>Gotou Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gotou Mai is the #2 member of the Prince Yuki fanclub.</description>
<picture>39505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11007" picture="49286.jpg">Suzuki Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13384" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="7">2.99</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinoshita Minami is the vice-president of the Prince Yuki fanclub.</description>
<picture>39507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11008" picture="190791.jpg">Asai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13385" type="appears in" update="2009-12-01">
<rating votes="6">5.36</rating>
<name>Aida Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aida Rika is a special forces member of the Prince Yuki fanclub. Her special skills include picking locks.</description>
<picture>39511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45296" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="4">6.65</rating>
<name>Souma Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuma is a master of martial arts who runs a dojo near the Souma family compound, where he teaches several of the younger Soumas, including Kyo Souma, Kagura Souma, Yuki Souma, and Hatsuharu Souma. He is usually addressed as Shishou, meaning "Master".His daily routine is taken care of by his assistant at the dojo, Kunimitsu Tomoda.</description>
<picture>88560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45315" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="6">3.80</rating>
<name>Souma Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kana Souma is an outside member of the Sohma family, and is, as such, not part of the The Chinese Zodiac. She is one of the first few "outsiders" to learn of the Zodiac curse. She appears in v. 2 of the manga and episode 8 of the anime. She later gets married to an unnamed husband.</description>
<picture>88574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66841" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="3">4.27</rating>
<name>Motoko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3938" picture="25736.jpg">Aoki Kazuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72893" type="appears in" update="2015-01-28">
<rating votes="1">9.84</rating>
<name>Hanajima Megumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="198" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Tag: The Cursed Electric Wave Brother and Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Strongest Tag - The Cursed Electric Wave Brother and Sister</title>
</episode>
<episode id="199" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Source of Cheer Can Be Affected By Colds Too</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Source of Cheer Can Be Affected By Colds, Too!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Sophist Boy Has Captured the Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Sophist Boy Has Captured the Prince</title>
</episode>
<episode id="201" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayame`s Secret Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Ayame’s Secret Life</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1383" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strangest Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">A Strange Day</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1384" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Here Comes Kagura!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Here Comes Kagura!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1385" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">All Shapes and Sizes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">All Shapes and Sizes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1386" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sohma Curse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Sohma Curse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1862" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Invincible Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">A Secret Friendship</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1863" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Everybody Loves Chocolate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Everybody Loves Chocolate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1864" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Make It Clear If It`s Black or White</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Make it clear If It’s Black or White</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1865" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">A Rice Ball in a Fruits Basket</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">A Rice Ball in a Fruit Basket</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1866" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">A Solitary New Year</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">A Solitary New Year</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1867" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Cry, For the Snow Will Surely Melt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Don’t Cry, for the Snow Will Most Certainly Melt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1868" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">A Plum on the Back</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">A Flower on the Back</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1875" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">White Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">White Day</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1876" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">A New School Term Starts!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">A New School Term Starts!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1877" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Adult`s Episode: Yuki`s a Messed Up Snake!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Adult’s Episode - Yuki’s a Messed Up Snake!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1878" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are No Memories It`s OK to Forget</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">There Are No Memories It’s OK to Forget</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1879" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">If We`ve Three Then We Don`t Need to Fear Jason</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">If We’ve Three Then We Don’t Have to Fear Jason</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1880" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Because I`ve Been Loved That I`ve Become Stronger</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">It’s Because I’ve Been Loved That I’ve Become Stronger</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1881" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Let’s Go Home</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1882" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">True Form</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">True Form</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1883" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Curse of the Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">The Curse of the Cat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1884" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Is the Rumored Ri That Mother`s Daughter?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Is the Rumoured Ri That Mother’s Daughter?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1885" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Prince Yuki Fan Club</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Prince Yuki Fan Club</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11996" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P24</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">1.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18044" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2002-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18045" update="2010-02-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120864" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120865" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120866" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164792" update="2014-12-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
