<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3430" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-07-25</startdate>
<enddate>2006-04-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bible Black Only Version</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Czarna Księga: Jedyny</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">黑暗圣经 Only Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="synonym">바이블 블랙 온리</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バイブルブラック・オンリー版</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bible Black Only</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Чорна Біблія: Єдина версія</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="528" type="Parent Story">Bible Black</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1283" approval="2" total="4">Inbaku Gakuen</anime>
<anime id="1995" approval="1" total="3">Gakuen Nanafushigi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.ms-pictures.com/label/milky/products/1511/bb/</url>
<creators>
<name id="60274" type="Direction">Hanebu Shou</name>
<name id="795" type="Animation Work">Studio Jam</name>
<name id="939" type="Original Work">Active</name>
<name id="655" type="Character Design">Yoshiten</name>
<name id="831" type="Work">Image House</name>
</creators>
<description>Bible Black Only explores the sexual misadventures of the supporting cast from the main Bible Black series. Miss Takashiro reminisces on her demonic capture, Itoh reveals her sadistic side, and Saeki is stalked by her classmates. Bible Black Only is a series of stand-alone episodes that do not affect the continuity of the main Bible Black series, and it contains footage that was previously only available on the R2 Bible Black Perfect Collection DVD.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1177">5.97</permanent>
<temporary count="1203">7.20</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>188365.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6308</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2873</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5347</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ms-pictures.com/label/milky/products/detail.php?id=209</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ms-pictures.com/label/milky/products/1511/bb/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="893" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>dominatrix</name>
<description>A dominatrix is a woman, typically a paid professional, who takes the dominant role in BDSM activities. A dominatrix may be of any sexual orientation, which does not necessarily limit the genders of her submissive partners. The role of a dominatrix may not even involve physical pain toward the submissive; her domination can be verbal, involving humiliating tasks, or servitude. The umbrella term for BDSM activities involving a dominatrix is female dominance, female domination, or simply femdom.
Source: Wikipedia.</description>
<picurl>230370.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2429" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>futanari</name>
<description>Futanari (a compound word meaning "two form" in Japanese) depicts hermaphrodites, intersex or other individuals with female body-types and sexual organs resembling penises, whether or not those organs are in fact enlarged clitorises, or they possess both male and female reproductive organs.</description>
<picurl>165411.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2696" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>threesome</name>
<description>Tag for any scene where sexual acts take place with three people of any gender. Should not be used if more than three.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2701" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-10">
<name>pussy sandwich</name>
<description>A pussy sandwich is a sex act during which a man`s penis is pressed against ("sandwiched") by two (or potentially more) vulvas. In the classic pussy sandwich, two women lie atop each other, face to face, and the man either "penetrates" the space between their vulvas or alternates penetrating their vaginas.</description>
<picurl>237174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2704" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-15">
<name>cum play</name>
<description>Fetish of sorts where the focus is of the semen that is ejaculated. This can include snowballing, drinking copious amounts of semen, eating it off food, using it to brush one`s teeth, acting as a urinal for semen, gargling it, rinsing one`s mouth with it, or any other act where semen is involved that does not have to do with fertilization of an egg.
This should not be used if one cannot visibly see semen in scenes or if the scene is extremely short.</description>
<picurl>236279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2710" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-18">
<name>squirting</name>
<description>Squirt, a small, quick stream, a jet when girl gets orgasm.</description>
<picurl>227795.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2714" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>point of view</name>
<description>Point of view pornography (POV) is adult entertainment that is filmed as if the watcher had experienced the sex-acts themselves.</description>
<picurl>161100.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2732" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-04">
<name>female rapes female</name>
<description>Both the perpetrator and victim are female; a same-sex rape results.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2733" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>enjoyable rape</name>
<description>This anime features a rape scene during which the raped character also reaches orgasm or somehow else derives sexual pleasure from the act.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2735" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>enema</name>
<description>An enema is the procedure of introducing liquids into the rectum and colon via the anus for the purpose of cleaning the insides or for BDSM play.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2744" parentid="2429" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>futa x female</name>
<description>A futa girl having sex with a girl</description>
<picurl>165413.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2903" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-21">
<name>scat</name>
<description>Coprophilia, also called scatophilia or scat, is a sexual fetish involving feces. This anime depicts defecation in the context of said fetish, be it as minor as a burst of brown liquid caused by an enema or as major as actual ingestion of pieces of excrement.
Scatophilia is a fairly common motif in Japanese animated pornography, and has even spawned a fairly successful meme inside the fandom, in which http://anidb.net/a735 [Yakin Byoutou] (more commonly known in the western world as Night Shift Nurses) character http://anidb.net/ch28915 [Nanase Ren] appears on screen with the superimposed line: "how can you say you love her if you can`t even eat her poop?"
Because, really, how can you? How dare you?</description>
<picurl>126784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2921" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>throat fucking</name>
<description>The act of actively thrusting one`s penis into a persons mouth and throat.</description>
<picurl>236088.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3244" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>sexually dominant</name>
<description>Sexually dominant is a designation applied to those able to assertively assume and maintain control over the actions of their partner(s) during sexual activity, actively steering it towards their own intents and preferences and possibly to the detriment of those of their partner(s).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4046" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>foursome</name>
<description>When four people have sex with each other at the same time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4492" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>gang rape</name>
<description>Gang rape occurs when a group of people (at least 2) participate in the rape of a single victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5406" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-02">
<name>submission</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3090" type="main character in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="102">8.27</rating>
<name>Takashiro Hiroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The school art professor. She`s in charge of the art club, which both Minase and Imari are part of. She`s very popular among the students for her good looks and personality.</description>
<picture>32297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2073">Futami Nagisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31479" type="main character in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="55">8.26</rating>
<name>Imari Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minase`s childhood friend and de facto girlfriend. She comes over to wake Minase up every morning. She knows everything about Minase, and tries to help him in every way. Note: She is black belt holder of shrinji kempo and very tough. She is good at cooking and takes care of Minase when Yukiko is away.</description>
<picture>70410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15550">Nishijima Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31480" type="main character in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="79">8.73</rating>
<name>Saeki Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minase`s classmate. She`s obsessed with the occult, and has established a new occult group based on the one from twelve years ago. She knows a lot about black magic, and her fortune telling is very popular. She becomes interested in Minase after learning about Minase possessing the book.</description>
<picture>70412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15548">Kanbayashi Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42020" type="main character in" update="2012-07-02">
<rating votes="44">8.29</rating>
<name>Minase Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First presented to be his stepsister, she is actually Minase`s live-in cousin and guardian, with the two acting like siblings due to them being close. She`s a strong-willed person, and enjoys tormenting Minase as well as teasing him at home with flashy outfits. Since she learned Latin and French in grad school, she helps Minase translate the contents of the book.</description>
<picture>90394.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42035" type="main character in" update="2012-07-02">
<rating votes="21">7.52</rating>
<name>Itou Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minase`s classmate and one of Saeki`s followers. She defends Saeki when Minase makes fun of her. She`s the first victim of Minase`s practice of the book.</description>
<picture>90391.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42047" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-02">
<rating votes="14">4.66</rating>
<name>Nonogusa Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the school swim team. She was once in the same class as Minase. The other members of the swim team envy her.</description>
<picture>90389.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42049" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="5">7.84</rating>
<name>Mikimoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the school swim team. One of Kobayashi`s flunkies.</description>
<picture>82836.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42050" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="5">7.38</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of the school swim team. She loathes Nonogusa.</description>
<picture>82837.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42052" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="12">5.12</rating>
<name>Kurimoto Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Saeki`s occult club.</description>
<picture>82839.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42053" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="12">6.48</rating>
<name>Amatsuki Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of Saeki`s occult club.</description>
<picture>82840.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="38133" update="2018-12-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">職員トイレで... / 秘密の特訓 / 実録更衣室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Faculty Room Toilet... / Secret Lesson / Events in the Locker Room</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">W toalecie nauczycieli... / Sekretna lekcja / Wydarzenia w szatni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokuin Toilet de... / Himitsu no Tokkun / Jitsuroku Kouishitsu</title>
<summary>The episode details the effects of the psychological trauma a demonic assault caused on art teacher Hiroko Takashiro during her youth. It also shows student Mika Ito and her boyfriend helping swim team members Jun and Maki abuse their fellow swimmer Miyuki Nonogusa. Finally, Kaori Saeki experiences what goes on in the shower room after swim practice.
Source: Bible Black Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="47069" update="2018-12-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">童貞狩り ~淫舞する悪魔達~ / 秘密の調教 / それはセンセイ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Virgin Hunting: Obscene Dance of the Devils / Secret Torture / That`s a Teacher...</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Polowanie na prawiczków: Sprośny taniec demonów / Sekretne tortury / Nauczycielka...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douteigari ~Inmaisuru Akuma-tachi~ / Himitsu no Choukyou / Sore wa Sensei...</title>
<summary>Kaori Saeki and her witchcraft club friends Jun and Maki embark on a perverted quest to collect semen from male virgins at school before enjoying a threesome together. Yukiko Minase suffers from the effects of a demon from her cousin and is taken advantage of by one of her professors. And art teacher Hiroko Takashiro fantasizes about having it away with her students.
Source: Bible Black Wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="61836" update="2018-10-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2006-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伊万里 凌辱現場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imari Rape Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Scena gwałtu Imari</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imari Ryoujoku Genba</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
