<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3493" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-12-22</startdate>
<enddate>2000-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pichu to Pikachu no Fuyuyasumi (2001)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Pocket Monsters: Pikachu no Fuyuyasumi (2001)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ピチューとピカチュウのふゆやすみ2001</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pikachu`s Winter Vacation (2001)</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Pokémon: Pikachun talvirieha 3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3492" type="Prequel">Pocket Monsters: Pikachu no Fuyuyasumi (2000)</anime>
<anime id="230" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>The third annual winter video release of Pokemon specials featuring Pikachu and his friends.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="169">3.32</permanent>
<temporary count="174">5.53</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238610.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2755</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10917</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ピカチュウのふゆやすみ#.E3.83.94.E3.82.AB.E3.83.81.E3.83.A5.E3.82.A6.E3.81.AE.E3.81.B5.E3.82.86.E3.82.84.E3.81.99.E3.81.BF2001</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>182</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319977</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4714</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2439" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>PIC NEEDS IMPROVEMENT</name>
<description>This entry has a poor picture and needs to have it replaced by a higher-quality alternative. Causes may include: it is too small; its colours or lighting are bad; it has excessive compression or other encoding issues; it is from non-anime sources (anime/char); the face is hard to see (char/creator); the hair/eye/skin colours do not match the anime (char); it does not represent their usual appearance (char); among others. If you can, please swap a better picture in and remove this tag. Thank you.</description>
<picurl>224875.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="178" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Kusaihana</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gloom is a flower-like Pokémon that is a larger and stronger evolution of Oddish. Gloom are obtained when an Oddish gains enough experience to grow up to level 21. Gloom can also be found in most grassy areas of most regions.
The fluid that oozes from its mouth is a sweet nectar that is used to attract prey. Once the prey is attracted, the nectar will cling to the prey, trapping it. The nectar mostly attracts prey that lack a sense of smell, as the nectar smells horrible.
As well as its nectar, the pistil of Gloom`s flower smells incredibly foul; it can be smelled from over a mile away. It has been found that approximately 1 in 1,000 people enjoy the scent that Gloom emits. Those that don`t enjoy the smell have been known to faint upon smelling it. When Gloom is faced with danger, the stench worsens. If it is feeling calm or secure, it does not release the horrible aroma. Oddly enough, people have been known to sniff Gloom, just to get a reaction. This is similar to real world drug addiction.
It is said to widely shower its attacks; with moves such as Stun Spore, Poison Powder, and Sleep Powder, it has the ability to cause status problems on its foes. It is also notable that Gloom has two evolved forms (from the second generation onwards), Vileplume and Bellossom. Unlike other Pokémon that evolve via level, Gloom will not evolve until it is exposed to an evolution stone; a Leaf Stone will make a Vileplume, while a Sun Stone produces a Bellossom.</description>
<picture>242960.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="328" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="30">2.20</rating>
<name>Menokurage</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tentacool (メノクラゲ, Menokurage?) is an aquatic Pokémon based on the box jellyfish. It drifts aimlessly wherever the ocean currents take it, sometimes ending up in shallow waters where it may be accidentally caught in fishing lines. Tentacool may also end up stuck on beaches when low tide comes; since its body is largely composed of water, it will shrivel up, risking death from dehydration if it stays out of the sea for too long. Tentacool has two main weapons. At the tips of its tentacles are toxic feelers, which it uses to stab anything it touches with stinging acid. Due to its excellent camouflage in the water, Tentacool can often remain undetected by swimmers right up to the moment it stings them. Tentacool`s gelatinous, watery body can also absorb sunlight and refract it within, producing beam energy it shoots from its crystal-like eyes.
Tentacool is available in all Pokémon games to date. It is extremely common, especially while surfing on sea routes, and is in almost every single body of water.
In the anime, Tentacool was featured in the episode "Tentacool and Tentacruel" in which a raging mob of the titular Pokémon attacked the Porta Vista resort. The episode was banned after the attacks on September 11, 2001 due to its scenes depicting Tentacools and Tentacruels destroying buildings at a seaside resort.</description>
<picture>242982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="329" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">2.75</rating>
<name>Dokukurage</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Tentacruel" is probably a portmanteau of "tentacle", the reason for which is obvious, and the adjective "cruel", referring to its personality. The name may have something to do with the deep-sea jellyfish called Tentaculata. Its name was originally going to be Man-O-War, which refers to the Portuguese man o` war. The Japanese name, "Dokukurage," is a portmanteau, of 毒 doku (poison) and 水母 kurage (jellyfish). It resembles its pre-evolution Tentacool to a small degree - the "head" of Tentacool has now been made into a hat-like shape on top of a black orb containing its eyes and two very large hooks which resembles a long nose. Also, unlike Tentacool, it has up to 80 tentacles, most of which are hidden, leaving up to 14 exposed.</description>
<picture>242983.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="344" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="7">1.17</rating>
<name>Pawou</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seel are well suited to life in the most frigid reaches of the planet. They are nocturnal; in the daytime they are seen asleep on the seabed in shallow water. When hunting, Seel stay in the ocean because they cannot walk on land. Instead, they swim in a rather graceful fashion literally underneath sheets of ice floating on the water`s surface in their environment in search of their prey. Even though the air is a frigid 14 degrees Fahrenheit and the water itself is a somewhat less chilling 40 degrees, their fur hides are thick enough to insulate Seel from either degree of cold and their nostrils automatically close by themselves to ensure their ability to remain underwater. When they need to take in air, they will use their hard horns to punch holes through the ice sheet above and pop their heads out.</description>
<picture>242988.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="345" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Jugon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dewgong`s name is derived from the real animal which has a similar, but much larger, body: the dugong. In the beta versions of Red/Blue, Dewgong`s name was originally going to be Manaty, a reference to the manatee. The Pokémon first appears in the arsenal of a trainer named "Allison" outside of Saffron City, who cites her similar body fat percentage as a reason for her choosing to utilize the Water/Ice type Pokémon.</description>
<picture>242989.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="428" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Tattu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Horsea`s name comes from an inverting of the parts of the compound word seahorse. It is also a pun on the word "Horsey" but is spelled "horsea" because of its habitat. Its Japanese name seems to be derived from 辰 tatsu, the zodiac dragon.</description>
<picture>243010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="429" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Seadra</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seadra`s name is simply a shortening of "Sea Dragon", although there is a speculation it may have derived from Hydra, a mythic creature.</description>
<picture>243011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="444" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="64">7.09</rating>
<name>Koiking</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magikarp is a commonly found Pokémon that can survive in rivers, lakes,and oceans. Despite its adaptability, the Pokédex states that the Magikarp species has grown weaker over time, and it is one of the least viable for battling in the series. It eventually evolves into another, far more powerful Pokémon, Gyarados.
Magikarp is commonly thought of as the weakest Pokémon. They are only able to learn three moves: Splash (does absolutely nothing), Tackle (a weak attack), and Flail (which does more damage as Magikarp is more damaged.)
In the anime, Magikarp has appeared several times, most notably as the subject of a running gag in which a salesman attempts to trick Team Rocket into buying Magikarp in various guises. (This man also appears in Pokémon Red, Blue, Yellow, FireRed, and LeafGreen.) Team Rocket later adopted a Magikarp-shaped submarine.
Magikarp also appear many times in the video games. They can be found in almost any pond, river, lake, or sea. Many trainers have them, along with other weak Water Pokémon like Goldeen or Horsea. In Pokémon Pearl, one trainer named "Ander," found outside Lake Valor, possesses a Magikarp whose move "Quake" replaces the normal Magikarp`s equally useless "Splash".</description>
<picture>243021.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="445" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="15">9.08</rating>
<name>Gyarados</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyarados is the evolved form of Magikarp. It is a dramatically large change from Magikarp, going from a small fish to a long draconic, serpentine body. Gyarados tend to be very aggressive, and are powerful enough to destroy entire cities. They have a reputation for appearing where there is conflict, and shrivelling everything up with the Hyper Beam attack. Rampages like this have been known to last upwards of an entire month, and will not end until everything around them has been destroyed. Because they have been known to sink ships as well through the seastorms their rage causes, they are considered legendary among sailors, especially the red/ golden variety. Its big change in behavior is said to be attributed to a structural change occurring in its brain while evolving from Magikarp.
In the beta version of Pokémon Red and Green, Gyarados had the name of Skullkraken.
Shiny Gyarados is a particularly rare variety of Gyarados. While Gyarados are normally blue in color, there are some rare red/ gold scaled Gyarados. Though no more powerful than their more common blue counterparts, red Gyarados are valued for their rarity and individuality. This is caused in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal and the anime by a radio frequency transmitted by Team Rocket to force the Magikarp to evolve. The red coloration comes from the Magikarp evolving prematurely, and not undergoing the conversion from red to blue scale pigment. Thus, they retain the same color they had as a Magikarp. Red Gyarados are more commonly called Shiny Gyarados, or even Golden Gyarados due to the contrasting coloration.
In Generation II Pokémon games, a red Gyarados at the Lake of Rage is a main part of the plot. After its defeat or capture, a Red Scale is obtained, which can be given to Mr. Pokémon, or Marcus Spanier, in exchange for an Exp. Share. The red Gyarados is the only Pokémon in the Generation II games that will be shiny without fail.
In the anime, one is owned by Misty. At first, she fearfully dislikes Gyarados due to a traumatic experience, but manages to get over the fear, take over the Cerulean City Gym, and add one to her team. The red Gyarados in the anime is caught by Lance, the dragon trainer, to rescue it from Team Rocket. Team Rocket also uses a Gyarados-shaped submarine in early episodes, but trades it for a Magikarp-shaped submarine in later episodes.
Gyarados was noticeably larger in the Indigo Series, but has since become a lot smaller. Gyarados` most powerful attack is said to be Dragon Rage (however, this is not true in the games, given that Dragon Rage only ever does 40 damage), where many other Gyarados appear around the main Gyarados, then they start spinning around at such a speed they became one huge tornado, as seen in Episode #18: Island of The Giant Pokémon.</description>
<picture>64468.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="447" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="14">9.04</rating>
<name>Laplace</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lapras is a dual-type Water/Ice Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
While it is not known to evolve into or from any other Pokémon, it has a Gigantamax form.
Lapras is a large sea Pokémon that resembles a plesiosaur. It has a blue hide with darker blue spots and a cream-colored underside. It has large brown eyes, a short horn on its forehead, and tightly curled ears. It has a long neck and four flippers. The foremost flippers are larger than the hind. On its back is a heavy, gray shell covered in blunt knobs.
Lapras is a gentle, helpful Pokémon that enjoys ferrying people across bodies of water. In the past, its docility made it an easy target for hunters, and it was driven to near-extinction. Recent protection efforts have seen Lapras become overabundant instead, which is now affecting the fish Pokémon numbers in some areas. An intelligent Pokémon, it is able to understand human speech. Lapras have been known to travel in large pods across the seas, spanning both polar and tropical areas. To keep in touch with other of its kind, it sings enchanting melodies. In the anime it was shown that Lapras is able to develop psychic abilities such as telepathy.
As Gigantamax Lapras, it becomes larger in size and more armored. Its shell resembles a cruise ship with four gray and red stripes surrounding it, and it has four spikes on top of its shell with one steel spike resembling a funnel, which has three red clouds surrounding it. The sclera in Lapras` eyes change colors to white, yellow, and blue. A light blue ring of fine thin lines resembling a musical sheet created from ice particles circles around its shell.
5,000 people can ride on the shell of Gigantamax Lapras for a very comfortable ride without any issues. Lapras can use it giant ring to break any icebergs that may prevent it from swimming.
Gigantamax Lapras is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Resonance.</description>
<picture>68374.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="459" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<name>Kabigon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Snorlax is a Normal-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Munchlax when leveled up with high friendship. It also has a Gigantamax form.
In the Generation I and II games and their remakes, wild Snorlax can be found sleeping in inconvenient locations throughout Kanto. In order to catch one, a Trainer must first awaken it with music from either a Poké Flute or Pokégear set to the Poké Flute channel. A sleeping Snorlax makes a return in Pokémon X and Y, in which it is blocking the player`s way on Route 7.
Snorlax is a huge, bipedal, dark blue-green Pokémon with a cream-colored face, belly, and feet. Its body is composed of mostly its belly, as its limbs are comparatively small. Its head is large with small, pointed ears and two pointed teeth protruding from its lower jaw. It has round feet, which both have three claws and a circular brown paw pad, and short arms with five claws on each hand. Snorlax`s bulk makes it the heaviest Normal type.
Snorlax is often found in mountains and forests. It wakes up only to eat, requiring 900 lbs. (400 kg) of food per day before returning to its slumber. It is not a picky eater, as its strong stomach allows it to eat even moldy food without feeling any ill effects. It can even handle thorny plants or Muk`s poison. It can also eat while it is resting. Snorlax is docile enough to let children and small Pokémon bounce on its large stomach.
Snorlax can show awesome power when prompted. As Gigantamax Snorlax, seeds and small rocks that were tangled in its belly fur goes through immense growth and a tree spouts upon its belly. The tree has three red clouds surrounding it like a circle. It almost never moves; even when in battle it only slightly lifts its body and attacks by flailing with its arms and legs. However, its attacks are very powerful — Gigantamax Snorlax is considered to be the strongest Dynamax Pokémon to have been discovered.
It is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive Z-Move Pulverizing Pancake and G-Max Move G-Max Replenish.</description>
<picture>68376.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="463" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Miniryu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dratini is a serpent-like dragon Pokémon with a white circle shape on its forehead. It has two developing wings at the sides of its head, which grow to be enormous as it evolves. Dratini are born small, and as they shed their skin, they grow larger. They have a massive amount of energy rapidly increasing inside of their bodies, hence, they have great strength which grows exponentially as they evolve. They were thought to be purely mythical creatures, but they were discovered to be real by a fisherman. They live in colonies in the ocean in limited numbers and fetch a high price as Pokémon to be used for battling. They can only be obtained by the most determined and skilled trainers, as demonstrated on various episodes of the original Pokémon series.
The episode in which Dratini first appeared ("The Legend of Dratini") has never been seen on American television, due to use of guns and humor considered "politically incorrect" to American audiences (Meowth dressed as Adolf Hitler, Jessie seducing a guard by dressing up as a schoolgirl).</description>
<picture>243034.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="552" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Chonchie</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chinchou has a small blue body and two antennae sprouting from its head, both of which have a yellow globe at the end. These antennae are said to have evolved from fins. A Chinchou`s eyes are yellow and their pupils have the shape of plus signs. When blinking or closing its eyes, only the vertical parts close, making the pupils look like minus signs. Its habitat is the dark depths of the ocean floor. In the absence of any other light, Chinchou sees its surroundings and communicates by shooting positive and negative charged electricity particles between the tips of its antennae, creating an electric current and thus light. This can be said to be a form of bioluminescence. The charges Chinchou shoots between its antennae can also be used offensively, to stun its opponents with a flash of light or shock them with electricity.</description>
<picture>243056.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="568" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Marilli</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azumarill is the evolved form of Marill. Azumarill resembles a blue, bipedal rabbit with a large, ellipsoid body, long blue ears with red insides, and a blue ball on the end of its thin, elastic black tail. The white bubble-like pattern on its lower stomach helps it to camouflage itself from potential predators when it is in the water.
Azumarill`s long ears act as sensors to identify sounds even in fast running rivers. Otherwise, when alone, Azumarill plays in water as a natural pastime, though it must roll up its elongated ears to prevent the sensitive sensory materials inside them from getting wet. The ball at the end of its tail can act as a sensor and guide it while under water. It can make thick, liquid balloons out of thin air with the saliva-water stored in its body. If it spots a drowning Pokémon in any body of water, it fashions such air balloons and jumps in to give the troubled Pokémon air balloons to help it breathe.
In the Pokémon anime, Paul owned an Azumarill which he used in a gym battle against Roark. Although it knew powerful Water attacks like Hydro Pump, it lost to Roark`s Geodude, which prompted Paul to give it to a Pokémon trainer passing by, being disappointed by its strength.</description>
<picture>243068.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="594" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Eipam</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aipom resembles a purple squirrel monkey with its face forever frozen in a maniacal grin that can be described as rictus and a blank stare from its round eyes. On its thin tail is a three fingered hand-like appendage that is very dexterous. It provides both propulsion and balance while Aipom leaps from tree to tree. Aipom is not aggressive by nature and will attempt to tire its natural opponents through dexterous dodging of the opponent`s attacks in hope that the enemy will be discouraged and leave. Otherwise, if the enemy is persistent, the Aipom will try to retreat, but if it is unable to, it will attack by diving at its opponent from the trees.
In the anime, an Aipom steals Ash`s hat, and follows his group around until Ash battles and captures it. Ash`s Aipom is quite attached to him, getting incredibly jealous when it sees Pikachu on Ash`s shoulder. Aipom has the distinction of being the only Pokemon aside from Pikachu that Ash brought with him to Sinnoh, although inadvertently. Aipom seems to enjoy contests, and Dawn believes it prefers contests over battles. In "Throwing the Track Switch!", Ash trades Aipom for Dawn`s Buizel because both Pokemon seemed more interested in the other trainer`s training. In "Journey to the Unknown", Dawn`s Aipom evolves into Ambipom.</description>
<picture>243074.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="601" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Upah</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wooper are similar to Axolotl. They are light teal-colored Pokémon with round feet, no arms, and a long tail. Their simplistic face consists of mainly of a large mouth, primarily while open. They have purplish barbed antennae on the sides of their head. Three purple, though sometimes shaded blue or pink, gills are on its stomach. Wooper will usually live in cold water: however, they occasionally come out onto land in search of food. When doing so, they coat their bodies with slimy, poisonous film. Touching the slime with bare hands will cause a shooting pain. Male Wooper have two barbs on their antennae, while female Wooper have one barb. Males also have larger gills.</description>
<picture>243078.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="626" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Harysen</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Qwilfish is a porcupinefish-like fish that has a round body with many toxin-containing spikes and a teardrop-shaped tail. The spikes give it trouble swimming, but it also has defensive measures against predators. Qwilfish can swallow large quantities of water in very short notice, causing itself to inflate to a much larger size, which it uses to intimidate larger opponents. If the opponent isn`t scared, Qwilfish uses the pressure of the water it swallowed to shoot out its toxic spikes at, thus weakening, the opponent.</description>
<picture>243093.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="633" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Himeguma</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teddiursa is a bear cub, resembling a teddy bear more than a real bear. Teddiursa have a crescent mark on their forehead, which grows (both in thickness and in circumference) as the Pokémon ages. Once the crescent fully closes into a circle, the Teddiursa is ready to evolve into an Ursaring. Teddiursa, although an omnivore, has a diet that almost exclusively consists of honey. It makes its own honey out of fruit and pollen from Beedrill. It lets the honey soak in its paws, making it often lick its paws.</description>
<picture>243096.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="819" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Teppouo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Remoraid is a Remora-based suckerfish that scavenges for food and has a somewhat symbiotic relationship with Mantine. Remoraid will attach itself to the underbelly of Mantine with its dorsal fin, eating scraps of food that Mantine drops as well as the parasites on them that causes them to itch. In return, the Mantine helps defend the Remoraid from enemies. When not scavenging for food, Remoraid will strike down its own prey with precise accuracy using fast streams of airborne water, which Remoraid shoots from its mouth using abdominal muscles. Remoraid can move faster through the water by blasting water from its mouth in the opposite direction of where it intends to move.</description>
<picture>243102.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="826" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Mantain</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mantine is a dark blue manta ray with two large wings branching off its body. It is often depicted having a Remoraid attached to its side eating Mantine`s leftovers. In the anime, Mantine protects Remoraid`s offspring, while the parent Remoraid help the Mantine in tough decisions. Mantine swims in open sea, participating in schools. Its large and well-developed wings enable it to briefly leap over the sea`s surface if it builds up enough speed, in a manner similar to some real aquatic species. Mantine is a filter feeder, like whales; its diet consists of most things that happen to enter its mouth while swimming.</description>
<picture>243105.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="827" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Airmd</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skarmory is an avian Pokémon with a body of metal armor. Its bones are hollow, allowing it to fly over 180 miles per hour in the sky. Skarmory raises its offspring in bramble bushes, the thorny environment causing the offspring`s bodies to become more resistant. Skarmory`s wings become battered from repeated battles, so it grows the feathers back to the original state once a year. Feathers from Skarmory have been used by people of the past as knives and swords. It is based on the Stymphalian birds of Greek mythology.</description>
<picture>243106.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="830" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Kingdra</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kingdra is resemblant of a large, blue weedy sea dragon with two branch-like horns on its head and two pairs of flippers on each side. It is said that Kingdra lives and sleeps at the bottom of the sea floor, at extreme underwater depths that are otherwise devoid of life due to water pressure. It also usually hides in underwater caves. It is believed to create maelstroms by yawning. When a storm arrives, it is said to awaken and wander about in search of prey. When it comes to the surface, it creates a huge whirlpool that can swallow even ships.</description>
<picture>243109.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="835" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Doble</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smeargle is the painter of the Pokémon world, best known for its unique "Sketch" attack. It has a long tail that ends in a tuft of fur similar to a paintbrush. The tuft is continuously soaked by a special fluid secreted from the tip of the tail. The color of the fluid is predetermined for each Smeargle. The fluid is used to mark the boundaries of its territory and print its footprints on the backs of its fellows once they reach maturity. Over 5,000 distinctive marks left by the species have been found in the Pokémon world.
Smeargle has its "Sketch" technique, which is unique to Smeargle. When used, it will replace itself permanently with the last attack technique used by an opponent Pokémon against Smeargle. It learns Sketch every ten levels. There are a few attacks Sketch cannot copy, (Such as Chatots main attack Chatter) but it can learn nearly every attack in the game.</description>
<picture>243113.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="838" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Muchul</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smoochum is a the pre-evolution of Jynx that was introduced a generation after. It is a female-only species that uses its lips, the most sensitive part of its body, to examine new and unfamiliar objects, and remember its likes and dislikes. This sensitivity quickly develops as it grows. It actively runs about, but often falls. When idle, it rocks its head back and forth, as if it were kissing someone. It constantly searches for ways to see its reflection, so it can see if its face is dirty.</description>
<picture>243116.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="840" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Buby</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magby is the baby form of Magmar. Its body temperature and the fire that it breathes are constantly over 1100 F. Its health is determined by the state of its flame; healthy Magbys have pure yellow flames, while black smoke is mixed in with unhealthy ones. As it breathes, embers constantly dribble out of its nostrils and its mouth. It lives in volcanic craters, and an eruption is imminent when many Magby gather in one place.</description>
<picture>243118.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="951" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Ruriri</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azurill, a species of Pokémon introduced shortly before the official start of the third generation of the Pokémon franchise as a "preview Pokémon", is the younger pre-evolved form of the Marill species introduced in the second generation. Its circular tail is large and rubbery, and Azurill`s playful nature causes it to often be seen bouncing and playing on its bouncy tail. The tail is vital both for survival in peacetime and self-defense in battle; It is packed full with nutrients that supply itself to Azurill`s body in order for it to grow. It is also a floatation device in water, much like the tails of its evolutions Marill and Azumarill. Its tail is about 1.3x as large as its body. Azurill`s most intriguing habit with its tail involves spinning its tail as if it were a lasso, then hurling it out with intense force. The momentum of the throw sends its body flying, too. Using this unique mode of travel, one individual Azurill was seen to hurl itself a record 33 feet.
In the Pokémon RPGs, Azurill can only be acquired by hatching an egg produced by Marill holding the Sea Incense item. In the Pokémon anime, trainer Misty owns one after her previous "baby" Pokémon, Togepi, evolved into Togetic and departed. This Azurill is the offspring of Tracey`s Marill. It is shown to have a sweet and caring nature and loves to play with the other Pokémon.</description>
<picture>243262.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1058" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kakureon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kecleon possesses the ability to change its body coloration at will in order to blend with its surroundings, approaching invisibility. Kecleon puts this stealthy trait to good use when hunting, as it can sneak up on its prey undetected and trap it with its long and stretchy tongue. Kecleon does not have absolute control of its appearance, however: it can never change the color of the zigzag band in the middle of its body, which renders his cloaking useless to any fairly keen observer. Secondly, a Kecleon can involuntarily shift colors based on its emotions, so that a sudden mood swing will change its looks completely. Finally, a Kecleon will revert to its original colors if it is startled. In the video games, Kecleon`s unique Color Change ability changes its type to match that of the last damage-dealing attack that hit it.</description>
<picture>243307.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="appears in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8135" type="appears in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="73">8.01</rating>
<name>Sonans (Musashi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While Wobbuffet is technically Jessie`s Pokémon, it has been around so long that it has become a main character, appearing in almost every episode of the series since it debut.
Wobbuffet was first seen walking around with Benny, his previous trainer. Jessie traded her Lickitung for Wobbuffet and it has been with her ever since that day.
Wobbuffet rarely battles but when he does, his Counter and Mirror Coat moves have proved to be very effective. Unfortunately, Jessie`s tactics aren`t always sufficient to master Wobbuffet`s superior defensive skills.
Wobbuffet also randomly comes out of his Pokeball, especially during the Team Rocket motto. He is also seen blasting off with Jessie regardless if he was actually part of the action.</description>
<picture>56350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22305" type="appears in" update="2010-10-14">
<rating votes="17">5.12</rating>
<name>Togepii (Kasumi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The egg that Togepi was inside was taken care by Brock mostly but once Togepi hatched, the first thing it saw was Misty and so this was inprinted in its mind.
Ash, Brock, Misty and Meowth all had a battle to see who would keep Togepi but even though Ash won, Togepi would only want to be with Misty as she was the first person it saw.
Misty`s Togepi evolve into Togetic in the Mirage Kingdom and soon left Misty to look after soon Togepi.</description>
<picture>56692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22329" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<name>Ishitsubute (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock`s Geodude was first seen at the Pewter Gym where it is currently staying.</description>
<picture>56487.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22350" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="17">7.27</rating>
<name>Fushigidane (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanto Pokémon League Tournament
Round 4 - Vs Jeanette Fisher - Grass Field
Ash selected Bulbasaur as his first Pokémon whilst Jeanette choose her Beedrill. As the faster Pokémon, Beedrill charged at bulbasaur at full speed, however Bulbasaur mananged to evade and return a Razor Leaf attack. Once again Beedrill used its superior speed, avoiding the Razor Leaf attack whilst also getting itself in a good position to use a Twin Needle atttack on Bulbasaur. Despite being on the backfoot, Bulbasaur managed to dodge the Twin Needle attack and Beedrill`s Stinger. After jumping backwards, Bulbasaur created enough space to be able to use its Leech Seed attack which struck Beedrill on its attacking stinger. Beedril was stuck in Leech Seed forcing it to the floor and Ash had bulbasaur finish it off using a Tackle attack which gave Ash the Initial Advantage in the battle.
Like Beedrill, Scyther had an advantage in speed and used this by quickly trying to attack Bulbasaur with its blades. After beeing unsuccessful, Jeanette order Scyther to used a Swift attack which managed to hit Bulbasaur a few times and was useful in deflecting its Vine Whip attack. Jeanette ordered Scyther to use a Double Team attack to which Ash had Bulbasaur to attempt to hit the real Scyther. The attempt failed and Scyther was able to land a few strikes by charging at Bulbasaur and managed to evade Bulbasaur`s counter of a Razor Leaf and Vine Whip attack. Ash had Bulbasaur use its Vine Whip once more but told it to swing the vines towards all of the copies which Double Team created, knowing that Bulbasaur would have to hit the real one in the process. The plan worked and Scyther was struck by Vine Whip, eliminating it from the battle.
Jeanette released her final Pokémon of the round which was a Bellsprout. Her choice suprised her a few people including Bulbasaur, as by apperance alone Bellsprout could be considered a weak Pokémon.
Ash had Bulbasaur charge at Bellsprout but managed to flip it above its head using its own momentum against itself. Ash was stunned by Bellsprout`s agility. Bulbasaur was angered at being tossed aside so easily and charged once again at Bellsprout, but like before, was thrown away using its own momentum. Bellsprout took advantage of Bulbasaur being on the floor and thrown it towards Ash`s podium, showing great strength and eliminated Bulbasaur from the tie.
Ash quickly rushed Pikachu into battle to try and finish Bellsprout off.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Sand Field)
Bulbasaur was Ash`s fifth choice Pokémon in his winner`s trophy battle against Drake. Bulbasaur`s first opponent was against Drake`s Electabuzz.
Bulbasuar manage to shake of Electabuzz`s initial Thundershock attack and returned a Razor Leaf attack which struck Electabuzz, although, whilst being hit by Razor Leaf, Electabuzz manage to use a Thunderbolt attack that Bulbasaur quickly dodged.
Bulbasaur uses Tackle and causes some light damage to Electabuzz but taking advantage of how close Bulbasur was, it manage to hit Bulbasaur with a Thunderpunch which eliminated it.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22375" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<rating votes="3">8.37</rating>
<name>Chicorita (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56593.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22377" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<name>Hinoarashi (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash was separated from his friends and chased by Team Rocket into a cave where he found Cyndaquil.</description>
<picture>56598.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22378" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Waninoko (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Totodile first appeared while Ash and Misty were fishing. Both tried to capture it but it hid in the bushes.</description>
<picture>56602.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22379" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<name>Yorunozuku (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After Ash rescued Noctowl from Team Rocket, Ash battled and captured it.</description>
<picture>56603.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22405" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="52">8.55</rating>
<name>Koduck (Kasumi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Psyduck pressed the button on Misty`s Pokeball and caught itself.</description>
<picture>56637.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22540" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Santa Claus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once a year Santa will give away gifts to all good childen who beleive in him.</description>
<picture>56796.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27470" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<name>Pichu (Otouto)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Pichu Brothers live in Big Town.</description>
<picture>81322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27556" type="appears in" update="2011-01-26">
<name>Delibird (Santa Claus)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Santa`s Delibird was getting presents ready for Christmas delivery when Ash`s Totodile knocked it out with a large snowball and all its presents got spread around a large area. With the help of all the Pokemon, Santa`s Delibird was able to retrieve all the missing presents in time for Christmas delivery.</description>
<picture>64529.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27557" type="appears in" update="2011-01-26">
<name>Odoshishi (Santa Claus)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Santa`s Stantler was seen pulling Santa`s sled on Christmas. This Stantler is different than most as it has the ability to fly.</description>
<picture>64530.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="38652" update="2014-05-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2000-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デリバードのプレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delibird`s Dilemma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Delibird no Present</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38653" update="2014-05-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2000-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホワイトストーリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snorlax Snowman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">White Story</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38654" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2000-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくたちピチューブラザーズ・風船騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trouble in Big Town (We The Pichu Brothers)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi Pichu Brothers, Fuusen Soudou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
