<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3500" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-10-09</startdate>
<enddate>2005-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginban Kaleidoscope</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rink of Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Skating Rink Kaleidoscope</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">银盘万花筒</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ginban</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀盤カレイドスコープ</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="635" approval="10" total="17">Kaleido Star</anime>
<anime id="84" approval="3" total="6">Hikaru no Go</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="322738">Amazing that an aerobatic pilot and an ice skater made for such an enjoyable story.  Short and sweet.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="394403">for some reason i decided to pick up this series out of boredom, im really glad i did. this plot is extremely funny in my opinion. im not one for sports but if you like humourous romance then give it a shot.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/ginban/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1151" type="Animation Work">Karaku</name>
<name id="3467" type="Series Composition">Yamatoya Akatsuki</name>
<name id="2533" type="Music">Kameyama Kouichirou</name>
<name id="10057" type="Original Work">Kaibara Rei</name>
<name id="13318" type="Character Design">Makiuchi Momoko</name>
<name id="13318" type="Chief Animation Direction">Makiuchi Momoko</name>
<name id="113" type="Direction">Takamatsu Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>16-year old http://anidb.net/ch4334 [Sakurano Tazusa] is a Japanese figure ice-skater who considers herself to be worth $10 billion in beauty. While executing her moves in the Women`s Figure Skating Grand Prix, she stumbled and landed badly, hence resulting in her loss in the competition. At the same time in a different place, a Canadian youth by the name of http://anidb.net/ch4335 [Pete Pumps] was performing an air stunt when an accident happened which led to his passing. By a weird twist of fate, Tazusa began to hear strange voices and realized that a Canadian ghost has resided in her body. After futile attempts to get rid of Pete, Tazusa decides to get accustomed to his presence and in the meantime, improve on her techniques in order to get selected for the Olympics.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1480">5.90</permanent>
<temporary count="1498">7.42</temporary>
<review count="3">7.10</review>
</ratings>
<picture>5011.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6050</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>476</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3190</identifier>
<identifier>ugxmwe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonymusic.co.jp/Animation/ginban/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ginban_Kaleidoscope</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>銀盤カレイドスコープ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>709</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323488</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>冰上萬花筒</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1074" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-24">
<name>ice skating</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2814" parentid="2832" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Canada</name>
<description>Canada is a country located in the northern part of North America. Its ten provinces and three territories extend from the Atlantic to the Pacific and northward into the Arctic Ocean. Canada is sparsely populated, the majority of its land territory being dominated by forest and tundra and the Rocky Mountains. Its capital is Ottawa, and its three largest metropolitan areas are Toronto, Montreal, and Vancouver.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214271.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3421" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>aviation</name>
<description>"These magnificant men in their flying machines"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4677" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-27">
<name>Olympics</name>
<description>The Olympic Games play a significant part in the plot. Either one or more characters dream(s) of going to the Olympics (as either a competitor or spectator), or part of the anime takes place at the Olympics.
Japan has hosted the Olympics three times: the 1964 Summer Olympics in Tokyo; the 1972 Winter Olympics in Sapporo, Hokkaidō Prefecture; and the 1998 Winter Olympics in Nagano, Nagano Prefecture, so do not be surprised when shows set during these time periods have a significant showing of the Olympics.
Olympic parodies may also count, so long as it is a significant part of the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4334" type="main character in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="6">7.26</rating>
<name>Sakurano Tazusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Japanese figure skater known for her sharp tongue. She is on bad terms with the media and the public because of her cold attitude and string of bad luck in competitions. Her goal is to compete in the Winter Olympics in Torino (Turin, Italy). At the beginning of the series is possessed by the ghost of Pete Pumps and while she initially hated him, she gradually grew to accept his constant presence in her life.</description>
<picture>20378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4335" type="main character in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="3">7.39</rating>
<name>Pete Pumps</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Canadian stunt pilot who died when his stunt plane developed mechanical trouble and crashed in a fireball. As a ghost he needs to wait 100 days before he can go to Heaven (his date of ascension is February 23rd) and inadvertently ends up possessing Tazusa.</description>
<picture>20379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4336" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="1">2.53</rating>
<name>Shitou Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is one of Tazusa`s skating rivals. She is the preferred choice for the Japanese Olympic representative for Women`s Figure Skating because she is closer to the Skating Federation`s "ideal," and as such, she and Tazusa are quite competitive. She has a calm personality, and never likes to take risks.</description>
<picture>20380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4337" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">8.02</rating>
<name>Ria Garnet Juiltyve</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a world-class Russian figure skater and the favourite to win gold in at the Winter Olympics. As such, she is Tazusa`s strongest rival. She is a very quiet but dedicated figure skater worthy of her title.</description>
<picture>20381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4338" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Gabrielle Papie Pozzo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1980" picture="173075.jpg">Kurokawa Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4339" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Takashima Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tazusa`s Canadian coach. He is an all around nice guy, always seeing the good aspects in everyone. Tazusa and her younger sister live with him because of their parents` divorce.</description>
<picture>20383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4340" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="1">5.58</rating>
<name>Mishiro Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An official from the Japan Skating Federation who claims that Tazusa has a "stone face." In return Tazusa calls her Queen Nasty or Sarcastic the Third. However, she does believe that Tazusa has special potential, which is why she pushes her so hard.</description>
<picture>20384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1982" picture="171562.jpg">Suzuki Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4341" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">7.28</rating>
<name>Sakurano Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tazusa`s level-headed younger sister. She is often seen waking Tazusa up for breakfast and in her competition to cheer her as well.</description>
<picture>20385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4342" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="1">2.53</rating>
<name>Honjou Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tazusa`s quiet best friend and the designer of all of her skating outfits. A running gag in the anime consists of Tazusa yelling at Pete who is invisible to other people only to have Mika mistake the target of Tazusa`s tirade as herself.</description>
<picture>20386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4343" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<name>Nitta Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A freelance reporter. He has a secret crush on Kyouko and tries to help Tazusa in her battles with the mass media. He is a calm and collected figure who believes in and supports Tazusa.</description>
<picture>20387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4344" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-05">
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<name>Dominique Miller</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An American figure skater and one of Tazusa`s rivals. She is very antagonistic towards Tazusa.</description>
<picture>20388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="489" picture="43165.jpg">Okamoto Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40868" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<name>Waitress</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40869" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<name>Sister</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2895" picture="144797.jpg">Kigawa Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40926" type="appears in" update="2012-01-28">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Olga Motokova</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2895" picture="144797.jpg">Kigawa Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40978" type="appears in" update="2012-01-31">
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lost russian girl.</description>
<picture>80876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3131" picture="234931.jpg">Tanii Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41037" type="appears in" update="2012-02-03">
<name>Shishido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41043" type="appears in" update="2012-02-03">
<name>Chiba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reporter.</description>
<picture>80971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41044" type="appears in" update="2012-02-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tazusa`s mother.</description>
<picture>80972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2895" picture="144797.jpg">Kigawa Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41045" type="appears in" update="2012-02-03">
<name>Maruyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reporter.</description>
<picture>80974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5057" picture="28861.jpg">Matsuoka Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41048" type="appears in" update="2012-02-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yano Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Girlfriend of coach Takashima.</description>
<picture>80978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="42074" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">100億ドルの女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ten Billion Dollar Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakuoku Dollar no Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42330" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キーワードはトマト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Keyword is Tomato</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keyword wa Tomato</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42601" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリプル・トラブル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triple Trouble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Triple Trouble</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42949" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚愕のフリープログラム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shocking Free Program</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyougaku no Free Program</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43054" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人でデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On a Date Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori de Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43361" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チェンジ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Change!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Change!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43362" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷上のウェイトレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waitress on Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiyoujiyou no Waitress</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43363" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マスコミ戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle with the Press</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masscom Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44906" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トライアングル・ラブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triangle Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Triangle Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45027" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイムリミット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Limit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Limit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45028" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キス・アンド・クライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiss and Cry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiss and Cry</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45319" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンデレラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cinderella</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109093" update="2012-02-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109094" update="2009-10-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136529" update="2012-02-03">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136824" update="2012-02-03">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - episode 2-11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136825" update="2012-02-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136826" update="2012-02-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2005-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening - episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207804" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">高島コーチ取材コメント 完全版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coach Takashima`s Interview Comment - Full Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takashima Coach Shuzai Comment Kanzenban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207805" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotion Video 15sec</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207806" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotion Video 30sec</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
