<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3506" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-12-17</startdate>
<enddate>2005-12-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Black Jack: Futari no Kuroi Isha</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Black Jack: The Two Black Doctors</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Black Jack: The Two Doctors of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Black Jack Movie (2005)</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Блек Джак - Двамата Черни доктора</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BJ Movie (2005)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブラック・ジャック ふたりの黒い医者</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2389" type="Parent Story">Black Jack (2004)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://blackjack.jp/movie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4109" type="Character Design">Sugino Akio</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="2078" type="Music">Tomita Isao</name>
<name id="6275" type="Direction">Tezuka Makoto</name>
<name id="6355" type="Chief Animation Direction">Uchida Hiroshi</name>
<name id="723" type="Animation Work">Tezuka Productions</name>
</creators>
<description>The mega-corporate Daedalus Group is under attack by a small group of activists known as the Ghost of Icarus. While taking care of some of the victims of the bombing, Black Jack encounters Dr. Kiriko, also known as Death Incarnate, who just like him, asks his patients huge sums of money but instead of saving them, he offers them a painless death. When the activist group requests both doctors` collaboration, Black Jack finds himself caught in a spiral of life, death and treason while trying to save his patients` lives and avoid the breaking of a biological war that could destroy humanity.
Source:ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="182">6.03</permanent>
<temporary count="184">7.01</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>36696.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5861</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6242</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35859</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1983</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4070</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3219</identifier>
<identifier>frgmkm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://blackjack.jp/movie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Jack_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブラック・ジャック_ふたりの黒い医者#.E3.80.8E.E3.83.96.E3.83.A9.E3.83.83.E3.82.AF.E3.83.BB.E3.82.B8.E3.83.A3.E3.83.83.E3.82.AF_.E3.81.B5.E3.81.9F.E3.82.8A.E3.81.AE.E9.BB.92.E3.81.84.E5.8C.BB.E8.80.85.E3.80.8F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>520</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323900</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>323185</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7755</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10400" type="main character in" update="2016-01-04">
<rating votes="372">9.15</rating>
<name>Black Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Black Jack is a mysterious and charismatic young genius surgeon who travels the world performing amazing and impossible surgery. Because of his hatred of the hypocrisy and corruption of the medical establishment, Black Jack refuses to accept a medical license, and runs into frequent difficulties from the authorities, as well as from gangsters and criminals who approach him for illegal operations. Black Jack charges ludicrous fees for his services, and uses the proceeds for environmental projects and to aid the victims of criminals and corrupt capitalsts, but he rarely allows anyone to realize that he is a good person, preferring to be considered a heartless devil.</description>
<picture>3312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10401" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="88">3.49</rating>
<name>Pinoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pinoko, is a hyperactive, fiercely possessive little girl, who lives in Black Jack`s house, doing his cooking and laundry and serving as his nurse and assistant, and the only steady long-term companion the unlucky Dr. Black Jack has ever had, and just about the only person who can embarrass or joke with him. Insisting that she is the doctor`s wife despite her obvious youth, Pinoko puzzle to anyone who meets her, and especially to anime viewers who don`t know her origin and wonder why the grim and solitary Black Jack is living with what seems to be a cute, annoying little girl.</description>
<picture>31195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34865" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-21">
<name>Unico</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40457" picture="10178.jpeg">Tezuka Rumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53192" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-24">
<name>Sharaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3336" picture="177136.jpg">Satou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53193" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-24">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Wato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53194" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-24">
<name>Largo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="605" picture="226544.jpg">Ishii Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53208" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-24">
<rating votes="4">4.14</rating>
<name>Doctor Kiriko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40459" picture="158442.jpg">Kaga Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79431" type="appears in" update="2016-09-10">
<name>Rock Holmes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the world of show business, it is common knowledge that actors who start out playing the role of children rarely make it to the top of their profession. This is because child stars, who are loved in the role of cute children, even if they grow, are burdened with the fate of having to continue showing the same image to audiences. In the same way, in the Manga of Tezuka Osamu, loveable, law-abiding characters like Kenichi and Atom were restricted to continuously playing the same role. But Rock is different. He was not simply a virtuous character. From the time he started performing in child roles, he never believed in the image that "a bright future will be born if only justice triumphs". "The world is full of inconsistencies. The world will not weep even if the fight for justice is lost and evil triumphs. Come spring the flowers will still bloom, the sunshine will still pour down in the summer." Rock was a boy who stared these realities in the face. As might be expected from a character that got his name from Sherlock Holmes, Rock is a highly intelligent young boy. That`s why he never had to trade on his charms even as he grew up. He concealed the malicious face of the devil under his handsome visage. He built up his character as the portrait of a villain. Part of the appeal of Tezuka Osamu`s Manga lies in the fact that such warped boy stars are incorporated into the stories, and in the inclusion of elements of profundity and philosophy.</description>
<picture>191106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40460" picture="158441.jpg">Ishigaki Yuuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83804" type="appears in" update="2016-08-14">
<name>Honma Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of the late Dr. Honma who saved Black Jack`s life. Black Jack sees her as a sister and looks after her.
She is known as Kumi Yamashita in the manga.</description>
<picture>190091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3601" picture="38507.jpg">Kawase Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="38888" update="2013-05-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38889" update="2006-07-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38890" update="2006-07-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49107" update="2011-07-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dr. ピノコの森の冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dr. Pinoko`s Forest Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dr. Pinoko no Mori no Bouken</title>
<summary>Dr. Black Jack forgot his doctor`s bag, and his assistant (plus self-claimed "wife") Pinoko rushed to deliver the bag but found herself lost in the forest. Guided by a butterfly, she found that many animals in the forest are sick or injured, and Pinoko used her knowledge to help those animals.
Source: Ann</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67120" update="2007-02-04">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">A Reminder</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
