<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3510" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2004-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pikachu no Natsumatsuri</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pikachu`s Summer Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 7 Short</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ピカチュウのなつまつり</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1041" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters Advanced Generation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>This was shown on All Nippon Airways (ANA) domestic flights from August 1-31, 2004, and is titled "Pikachu`s Summer Festival", the story is as follows:
The Pokemon festival takes place today on the beach and all the Pokemon like Pikachu, Plusle and Minun help to prepare the festival. The idol that is going to sing that night, is Azumarill. Azumarill is on the way to the festival, together with Meowth and Wobbuffet, but they get stranded on the way, things get even worse when a Skarmory flies towards Azumarill and takes him away! Pikachu, Plusle and Minun are going to rescue Azumarill, since without Azumarill the festival wouldn`t have a star...
Source: Pokejello.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="121">3.10</permanent>
<temporary count="123">5.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>11545.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5845</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322899</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Fushigidane</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bulbasaur is known as the Seed Pokemon. Bulbasaur looks like small, rounder turquoise dicynodon, a mammal-like reptile from the Permian Period. Bulbasaur`s most distinctive feature is the green bulb planted on its back. The plant sprouts and grows with the Pokemon. The bulb synthesizes solar rays. It can later use the energy stored for recovering itself (Synthesis) or release it in the form of a Solarbeam. Because of this Bulbasaur is usually seen napping in bright sunlight. The bulb constantly takes in nourishment from the sun, allowing both the Bulbasaur and the bulb to grow over time. It also allows them to go days without eating by using the nutrients stored in the bulb.</description>
<picture>242931.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="163" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="22">5.81</rating>
<name>Nidoran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidoran are a species of poisonous rabbit-like Pokémon found in the Kanto, Johto, and Sinnoh regions of the Pokémon world. Male Nidoran are classified as a separate species of Pokémon from the females due to differences in appearance between genders, such as the female being light blue and having smaller horns than the male. It should be noted that these were the first Pokémon to have known genders until the release of Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver, although they remain as separate species to this date. This Pokémon protects itself with its venomous barbs.</description>
<picture>242947.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="171" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="13">8.73</rating>
<name>Rokon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vulpix is a fox-like creature with six curled tails, based on the Japanese fox spirit kitsune. Most commonly female, Vulpix are especially known for being beautiful. As Vulpix undergo Pokemon evolution, their red fur turns pale yellow and they grow three extra tails. Vulpix usually have a friendly, if not spoiled, temperament. Because of the flame in their bodies, when the temperature outside increases, they let flames out of their mouths to prevent their body temperature from getting too hot. In the wild, Vulpix will feign injury to escape from more powerful predators.
During the first season of the Pokemon anime, Vulpix appears often as one of Brock`s Pokemon. It was given to him by a girl named Susie who felt she could not take care of it well. Brock, who felt he was only "babysitting", gives it back to Susie in the season four episode called "Beauty and the Breeder".
Its Japanese name, Rokon is a portmanteau of six (六, roku) and kon (from kon kon, an onomatopoeic word describing the bark of a fox), or an alternate reading of the Japanese word for kitsune (狐, kitsune), meaning fox - in this case, the reading is ko (こ). Its English name may have been derived from the scientific name for a group of foxes, Vulpes.</description>
<picture>64414.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="173" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="2">7.03</rating>
<name>Purin</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jigglypuff, known as the "Balloon" species of Pokémon, are characterized by putting their enemies to sleep by singing a lullaby. Before beginning to sing, they mesmerize the opponent with their soft, glowing eyes, and if they inflate themselves, they can sing for longer periods of time. They can easily adjust the wavelength of their voices to that of the brain waves of a sleeping being, allowing for their pleasing melody to put its audience to sleep. They sing without pausing to take a breath, so if the opponent is resistant to sleeping, they potentially run out of air.
In the Pokémon anime series, Jigglypuff is a recurring character who aspires to be a great singer after the inspiration of Ash Ketchum and company. Unfortunately for it, every potential audience falls asleep before the song finishes. Jigglypuff does not usually choose an appropriate time to sing and has been a hazard many times, causing Ash Ketchum and his companions to often find themselves running away from Jigglypuff. It keeps with it a black marker, its "microphone," and uses it to scribble on anyone who falls asleep while it`s performing.
Its desire to have someone listen to the entire song was finally satisfied when it encountered a Whismur, who was able to stay awake due to its Soundproof ability.
Also, Jigglypuff`s Japanese name, Purin, translates into "pudding".</description>
<picture>242955.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="174" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Pukurin</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wigglytuff is a relatively large pink balloon-like Pokemon with a white underbelly, large blue baby-like eyes, a pair of large rabbit ears, and a twisty tuft of pink hair on its forehead. It evolves from Jigglypuff through a Moon Stone. In fact, it`s remarkably similar to its pre-evolved form, Jigglypuff, except the ears have grown larger and it now maintains an "oval" shape. Wigglytuff`s eyes are always covered by a thin layer of tears, so that if any dust gets into Wigglytuff`s eyes, it is quickly cried away. In the games, Wigglytuff`s fur is described to be "sublime", so much so that if two of them come into close contact with each other, they are difficult to separate. In the television series, Wigglytuff is generally accepted as the most powerful Pokemon.</description>
<picture>242956.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="177" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="23">9.04</rating>
<name>Nazonokusa</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oddish are a weed-like Pokémon found in all regions throughout the Pokémon world. (with the exception of Pokémon Blue and Pokémon Leaf Green) Oddish looks like a small animated onion/turnip plant with a rounded body. Its body is blue or purple with two small feet and red eyes. On top of its head grows a large clump of 5 long green blades of grass. Its name likely came from the words "odd" and "radish".
Oddish is a nocturnal Pokémon, using moonlight rather than the sun`s rays for photosynthesis. During the day, Oddish avoids the sun`s heat and brightness by burying itself into the earth, leaving only the leaves on top of its head visible above ground. In this way it disguises itself as a plant, misdirecting its carnivorous diurnal predators.
While buried, Oddish nourishes itself by absorbing nutrients from the soil using its feet, which are said to temporarily change into a root-like structure for this purpose.
Oddish has been known to use its leaves as hands, such as one who used this to climb a rope net and tried to fly like a Hoppip.
If anyone pulls at Oddish`s leaves and tries to uproot it while it is buried underground, Oddish will react by shrieking in a cute, high-pitched voice. This mirrors the behavior of the legendary mandrake in a similar situation, although it seems that Oddish`s squeaks do not have the same dire consequences as a mandrake`s.</description>
<picture>242959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="179" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="13">10.00</rating>
<name>Ruffresia</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vileplume is a huge flower-like Pokémon that is a larger and stronger evolution of Gloom. Vileplumes can be obtained by using a Leaf Stone with a Gloom.
Vileplume is known for its extremely offensive stench that comes from its large red flower. Vileplume uses this stench in battle, catching its foes off guard when they start to back away from the horrible smell. However, Vileplume`s flower can actually be a hindrance in battle due to it being very heavy and bulky. Due to of its weight, Vileplume walks very slowly, and it often must use its hands to help support the flower. Vileplume can be found in forests and they like to stay low to the ground. When they sleep, their huge petals droop over their head and they blend in more with the plants around them. They also release toxic, dense pollen into the air in this position so animals don`t go near them. At night, they sometimes gather together to perform odd rituals - during this time they release toxic pollen to deter intruders. The white markings on this flower are larger in the female than in the male. Paul uses Vileplume to battle Tyrogue, but his Vileplume is useless for Fighting-type Pokemon.</description>
<picture>242961.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="231" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="14">3.92</rating>
<name>Nyorozo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Poliwhirl is a large, amphibious, froglet-like Pokémon. Its hands make it seem as though it is wearing white boxing gloves. It is capable of living in or out of water; in order to live out of water, it must sweat to keep its body slimy. prefers to live underwater in ponds where there is less danger.
In battle, it subtly undulates the spiral-shape on its belly to put the foe to sleep, using a type of hypnosis. It is also capable of easily escaping the grasp of foes due to its greasy skin. Poliwhirl`s spiral goes in the opposite direction of Poliwag`s. Poliwhirl`s mouth is no longer visible after evolution, but it is concluded that it moved to the center of its spiral, since it now sprays water from there.
In the Pokémon anime, Misty had a Poliwhirl in the Johto series, which later evolved into Politoed. Red owns one in the Pokémon adventures which eventually it evolves into a Poliwrath.</description>
<picture>242973.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="235" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="8">9.08</rating>
<name>Foodin</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alakazam loses the thick tail it once possessed as Kadabra (which might explain why it is 19 pounds lighter than Kadabra). It stands on two legs and always holds two silver spoons. Parts of Alakazam`s body are brown, but its predominant coloring is gold. Alakazam has a long, gold moustache - nonetheless, some Alakazam are female, though in Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, females have dramatically smaller moustaches, while the males have longer ones.
Alakazam are described as extremely intelligent. With an IQ of 5,000, they can outperform supercomputers and can memorize anything. Alakazam use their superior intelligence to immediately identify their opponents` weaknesses and gain the edge in battles. This intelligence and superb memory are said to come from the fact that Alakazam`s brain cells never stop multiplying - as a result, the overly large head must be supported by its telekinetic powers. In fact, Alakazam use their psychic abilities to watch all "movement", as their muscles are too weak. Also their senses are incredibly strong: just by closing its eyes it can heighten all the other senses dramatically. Alakazam evolves from Kadabra when you trade it to another Pokémon game.
Alakazam is notable for having the highest Special Attack among non-legendary Pokémon, a statistic that affects the power of mental, fluid, and energy-based attacks, though it shares this title with another Pokémon, Porygon-Z. To balance its extremely high Special Attack, Alakazam`s other stats are atrocious, save for its high speed and average Special Defence, though this is offset by an awful HP stat. Alakazam made an appearance in Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Blue Rescue Team and Red Rescue Team, as the leader of Team ACT.</description>
<picture>64463.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="325" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="18">3.20</rating>
<name>Madatsubomi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellsprout is a carnivorous, flower-like Pokémon, hunting small insects with blinding agility despite its skinny body. It is said to ensnare its prey in its vines and devour it, and can also spit a highly corrosive fluid that can melt even iron. Bellsprout`s preferred habitat is warm and humid climates, since it can absorb more moisture from the ground by planting its root-like feet. In battle, Bellsprout can take advantage of its flexibility to bend and sway its way out of the range of its opponent`s attacks, no matter how powerful they may be.
In the video games, Bellsprout is commonly found among grassy routes, and is used by many Trainers who favor the Grass-type. In Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal, the Sprout Tower in Violet City is dedicated to Bellsprout.
Bellsprout has appeared numerous times in the anime series, most notably in "The Fourth Round Rumble," where Ash battled one during the Indigo League. He eventually defeated it with Muk.</description>
<picture>242979.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="335" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="13">7.27</rating>
<name>Yadon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Slowpoke is a dual-type Water/Psychic Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves into Slowbro starting at level 37 or Slowking when traded holding a King`s Rock.
In Galar, Slowpoke has a pure Psychic-type regional form, introduced in Pokémon Sword and Shield`s 1.1.0 patch. It will evolve into Galarian Slowbro using an item found on the Isle of Armor or Galarian Slowking using an item found in the Crown Tundra.
Slowpoke is a pink Pokémon that resembles a cross between a salamander and a hippopotamus. It has vacant eyes that never seem focused, curled ears, and a rounded, tan muzzle. It has four legs, each of which ends in a single white claw. Its long, tapering tail has a white tip. This tail drips a sweet, sappy substance that is attractive to many species of fish. Slowpoke uses the tail as a fishing lure. The tail often breaks off, but it will grow back. In Alola, its tail is often dried and used in home cooked stews.
Slowpoke has notoriously dim intellect, and often forgets what it was doing. It takes a long time to respond to outside stimuli. For example, it can take up to five seconds to process pain and can take an entire day to notice when its tail has been bitten. Slowpoke is commonly found at the water`s edge. In some places, it is believed that Slowpoke`s yawn causes rain. This Pokémon is worshiped in those areas.
In Galar, Slowpoke gains yellow markings on its forehead and tail.</description>
<picture>68399.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="339" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="33">6.04</rating>
<name>Coil</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magnemite is almost more of a machine than a creature, as it is a solid ball of metal with a pair of horseshoe magnets on either side, as well as a single, lidless eye. It has a pair of screws protruding from below the eye, and a large screw forming a sort of "cap" on top of its head.
It floats through the air, through a sort of electromagnetic antigravity field generated by the two magnets on either side of its body. When defending itself in the wild or fighting in a Pokémon battle at the orders of a Pokémon trainer, it can also generate powerful electric shocks. Magnemite consumes electricity, so they`re attracted to power lines and electronic gadgets. Magnemite tend to crowd around generators and power plants, and an individual Magnemite might be attracted to someone with a pocket radio or a Pokégear.
Despite their mechanical appearance, lack of gender, and alien tendencies, Magnemite are living things; they are not built, they feel the need to eat, and they have something similar to a mating urge. A trio of Magnemite may come together to create their evolved form, Magneton.</description>
<picture>242984.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="352" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Ghos</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gastly (Spirit in the Beta versions of the English language versions of Pokémon Red and Blue) is made of a very thin, gas-like substance, which grants it certain powers and weaknesses. Some say it is an other-dimensional lifeform, while others believe it is formed from toxic gas. It can sneak into any place if it so wishes thanks to the invasive properties of gas molecules. It can render itself nearly invisible and approach enemies undetected, and can envelop said enemies regardless of their size and induce sleepiness, slow poisoning through the skin, or even suffocation.
On the other hand, Gastly`s negligible weight and gaseous nature make it very easy for it to be blown off or even scattered to nothingness under a strong wind (although it is presumed the molecules can regroup later). A Gastly will not appear in windy weather if it can help it, but when it finds itself threatened by a strong wind, it clusters in groups under the eaves of houses to protect itself.</description>
<picture>242992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="440" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Boober</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magmar is born in the proximity of an active volcano, and if possible it spends its entire life there, or at least in a place hot enough to sustain its body temperature of 3,300 degrees Fahrenheit. If a Magmar finds itself in a cold place, it will try to make it more habitable by blowing scorching flames around. It has the ability to expel orange-colored fire from every part of its body, including its mouth. This serves both offensive and defensive purposes: a Magmar cloaked in flames resembles a big ball of fire. Together with its matching body coloration, Magmar can quite easily hide itself among flames, escaping detection. If Magmar is actually wounded, it can heal itself by dipping its wound(s) in lava. When it emerges, damp soil clings onto its body. In Gold and Silver, Magmar gets a pre-evolution, Magby, and in Diamond and Pearl, an evolution, Magmortar.
Magmar has appeared in the anime owned by various people but the ones of note are the Gym Leader Blaine, Ash`s now ex-rival, Gary Oak, and his new rival, Paul. Paul had been looking for a new fire Pokémon since the release of Chimchar in "Glory Blaze" and captured Magmar sometime between capturing Gliscor in ""Gliscor and Gligar: Getting Through the Wind Maze" and his Gym Battle, with Maylene which was shown as a flashback in "Lucario and the Aura Sphere of Rage."</description>
<picture>243019.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="459" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<name>Kabigon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Snorlax is a Normal-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Munchlax when leveled up with high friendship. It also has a Gigantamax form.
In the Generation I and II games and their remakes, wild Snorlax can be found sleeping in inconvenient locations throughout Kanto. In order to catch one, a Trainer must first awaken it with music from either a Poké Flute or Pokégear set to the Poké Flute channel. A sleeping Snorlax makes a return in Pokémon X and Y, in which it is blocking the player`s way on Route 7.
Snorlax is a huge, bipedal, dark blue-green Pokémon with a cream-colored face, belly, and feet. Its body is composed of mostly its belly, as its limbs are comparatively small. Its head is large with small, pointed ears and two pointed teeth protruding from its lower jaw. It has round feet, which both have three claws and a circular brown paw pad, and short arms with five claws on each hand. Snorlax`s bulk makes it the heaviest Normal type.
Snorlax is often found in mountains and forests. It wakes up only to eat, requiring 900 lbs. (400 kg) of food per day before returning to its slumber. It is not a picky eater, as its strong stomach allows it to eat even moldy food without feeling any ill effects. It can even handle thorny plants or Muk`s poison. It can also eat while it is resting. Snorlax is docile enough to let children and small Pokémon bounce on its large stomach.
Snorlax can show awesome power when prompted. As Gigantamax Snorlax, seeds and small rocks that were tangled in its belly fur goes through immense growth and a tree spouts upon its belly. The tree has three red clouds surrounding it like a circle. It almost never moves; even when in battle it only slightly lifts its body and attacks by flailing with its arms and legs. However, its attacks are very powerful — Gigantamax Snorlax is considered to be the strongest Dynamax Pokémon to have been discovered.
It is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive Z-Move Pulverizing Pancake and G-Max Move G-Max Replenish.</description>
<picture>68376.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="533" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">5.52</rating>
<name>Chicorita</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chikorita is the Grass-type Starter Pokémon in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. One may also get this Pokémon in Pokémon Emerald by completing the Hoenn Dex (not including Jirachi and Deoxys). It is reptilian in appearance, but it has a large leaf sprouting from its head, a collar of crystalline seeds around its neck, and a short tail. Chikorita, by nature, are docile Pokémon that love to soak up the sun`s rays. The leaf serves multiple purposes; in its natural environment, its leaf detects the density of humidity and temperature in the atmosphere to help it seek warm places. The pleasant aroma that wafts from the leaf can be used by Chikorita in battle by waving it around to becalm the foe and keep it at bay. In the Pokémon anime, Ash Ketchum caught a Chikorita early on its adventure through Johto, after saving it from a sudden snowstorm. Chikorita is very affectionate, stubborn, and powerful, often sees Pikachu as a rival for Ash`s affections, and apparently has a crush on Ash. In the episode "Current Events", Chikorita evolves into a Bayleef when Ash was almost in mortal peril.</description>
<picture>243038.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="543" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="14">7.27</rating>
<name>Ootachi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Furret live in colonies with tunnels much too small for normal Pokemon to traverse, yet it is a perfect fit for the slim build of Furret as it hides from the outside world at the surface by traversing through these tunnels like gophers. These tunnel colonies become very complex, especially if they are very deep, and can potentially stretch for miles. Occasionally, these colonies are found intertwined with Diglett colonies. The Furret evolves from Sentret at level 15.
Furret`s rudimentary paws and legs are deceptively nimble, making Furret a quick, unpredictable predator especially skillful at hunting Rattata, its main prey. Also, the fur of the Pokemon is thicker than it appears, and Furret can fluff up its fur to make itself look much stronger and larger than it actually is as an intimidation tactic towards potential foes.
Furret is based on a ferret or squirrel.</description>
<picture>243048.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="545" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Hoho</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoothoot is one of two owl Pokémon. Hoothoot seems to have one foot. However, it actually has two feet; at least one is retracted against its body at almost all times, and Hoothoot can switch between one foot and the other at speeds almost too fast for the human eye. Hoothoot are also known for having precise senses of time, due to a special mechanism in their brain that measures the rotation of the earth. Properly trained, they can be more accurate than all but the most precise of clocks. In nature, they always begin hooting at the same time every night.</description>
<picture>243049.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="564" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Mokoko</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flaaffy is the evolution of Mareep. Flaaffy is dark pink in color. Its fleece is white, and it grows over the top half of its body and its head. It has black stripes on its ears and its long tail, and it has small, beady eyes that look like black dots. It has a blue ball on the tip of its tail. Flaaffy usually likes to sit upright, although it can stand on two legs if necessary. Its wool quality changes as it matures so that it can generate a high amount of strong static electricity while still having a small amount of wool. Its bare, electric-resistant, parts of its hides enable it to prevent electrocution. As a result of storing too much, it develops patches even where wool won`t grow.</description>
<picture>243065.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="566" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="15">5.12</rating>
<name>Kireihana</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellossom is a diurnal plant Pokémon. It evolves from Gloom if exposed to a Sun Stone. Bellossom`s petals can rotate, and they usually do when it is absorbing sunlight. The color of their leaves vary from a sickly brown and gray to a fluorescent yellow and red, depending on how much sunlight it has absorbed in the past few hours. When its petals are moving, either due to rotating or dancing, they rub together to make relaxing, bell-like sounds. The petals on its head also create a sweet scent.
It is also noted that a Bellossom will be even more beautiful if it was an especially rancid Gloom. The worse it smells as a Gloom, the prettier its petals will be as a Bellossom. Although naturally a peaceful and friendly Pokémon, it can be very territorial and violent fights can break out if there is an intruder or a challenger. Despite this, it is very social in areas outside of its self-determined territory, and the most common time to find a group of Bellossom together is when they all meet in one location to dance. It is said that these dances summon the sun.
Its Japanese name, "Kireihana", translates to "Beautiful" (kirei) and "Flower" (hana).</description>
<picture>243066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="568" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Marilli</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azumarill is the evolved form of Marill. Azumarill resembles a blue, bipedal rabbit with a large, ellipsoid body, long blue ears with red insides, and a blue ball on the end of its thin, elastic black tail. The white bubble-like pattern on its lower stomach helps it to camouflage itself from potential predators when it is in the water.
Azumarill`s long ears act as sensors to identify sounds even in fast running rivers. Otherwise, when alone, Azumarill plays in water as a natural pastime, though it must roll up its elongated ears to prevent the sensitive sensory materials inside them from getting wet. The ball at the end of its tail can act as a sensor and guide it while under water. It can make thick, liquid balloons out of thin air with the saliva-water stored in its body. If it spots a drowning Pokémon in any body of water, it fashions such air balloons and jumps in to give the troubled Pokémon air balloons to help it breathe.
In the Pokémon anime, Paul owned an Azumarill which he used in a gym battle against Roark. Although it knew powerful Water attacks like Hydro Pump, it lost to Roark`s Geodude, which prompted Paul to give it to a Pokémon trainer passing by, being disappointed by its strength.</description>
<picture>243068.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="587" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Usokkie</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sudowoodo is a bending, bipedal creature vaguely in the shape of a tree trunk. It has a double-pronged protuberance on its head, tiny feet, a simple face, and a pair of three-fingered hands where the fingers are green spheres resembling leaves on a tree. Although Sudowoodo pretends to be a tree, its body is made not out of wood, but rock. It uses this as a form of camouflage, hiding among forest areas to avoid being attacked by enemies. Additionally, its signature technique is Mimic, which allows it to copy enemy attacks. It earns its classification as the imitation Pokémon through these practices.
In the winter seasons, when trees are either white with snow or have had their leaves fall off from autumn, Sudowoodo is easy to spot as a fake because its hands remain green, making winter a more dangerous time for Sudowoodo to be in the presence of foes. Also, as a creature whose composition resembles rock, Sudowoodo hates water, so it will disappear and seek shelter when rainfall begins. In the video games, it often blocks areas until sprayed with water, which causes it to battle. In Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, the twig-shaped appendage atop a Sudowoodo`s head is larger on a male than it is on a female. The origin of its name is: Pseudo (False) + Wood.</description>
<picture>243069.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="601" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Upah</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wooper are similar to Axolotl. They are light teal-colored Pokémon with round feet, no arms, and a long tail. Their simplistic face consists of mainly of a large mouth, primarily while open. They have purplish barbed antennae on the sides of their head. Three purple, though sometimes shaded blue or pink, gills are on its stomach. Wooper will usually live in cold water: however, they occasionally come out onto land in search of food. When doing so, they coat their bodies with slimy, poisonous film. Touching the slime with bare hands will cause a shooting pain. Male Wooper have two barbs on their antennae, while female Wooper have one barb. Males also have larger gills.</description>
<picture>243078.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="602" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Nuoh</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quagsire has an appearance and habitat similar to that of a giant salamander. Quagsire live a carefree life in muddy ponds and rivers. It acts oblivious to its environment, accidentally bumping its head on the hulls of boats and bottoms of whatever body of water it swims in as it swims, but seeming not to care. Quagsire always bear an absent-looking facial expression. This is likely due to Quagsire`s easy-going nature. It hunts by staying still in the water with its mouth open, waiting for small prey to swim into its mouth. It doesn`t move, and therefore, doesn`t get hungry. It`s not uncommon that a fishermen`s hook will get caught in the gaping mouth of a feeding Quagsire. Trying to eat what it has caught, the Quagsire would try to swallow, and end up pulling the fishermen off his boat and into the water. Male Quagsire have larger fins on their backs. They wait at the bottom of lakes waiting for prey to wander into its mouth. It also loves eating cherries.</description>
<picture>243079.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="827" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Airmd</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skarmory is an avian Pokémon with a body of metal armor. Its bones are hollow, allowing it to fly over 180 miles per hour in the sky. Skarmory raises its offspring in bramble bushes, the thorny environment causing the offspring`s bodies to become more resistant. Skarmory`s wings become battered from repeated battles, so it grows the feathers back to the original state once a year. Feathers from Skarmory have been used by people of the past as knives and swords. It is based on the Stymphalian birds of Greek mythology.</description>
<picture>243106.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="921" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Konohana</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nuzleaf is the larger evolved form of Seedot. Nuzleaf is a forest-dwelling Pokémon that is skilled at climbing trees, though they occasionally venture out of the forest to startle people. They live in holes bored in large trees. Its long and pointed nose is its weak point, and it loses power if the nose is gripped. For this reason, it dislikes having its long nose pinched. Nuzleaf will sometimes pull out the leaf on its head and make a flute with it. The sound of Nuzleaf`s flute strikes fear and uncertainty in the hearts of people lost in a forest. This is a reference to Pan, the Greek god of the forest.</description>
<picture>243239.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="925" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<rating votes="11">4.60</rating>
<name>Camome</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wingull is a common seagull-like Pokémon species found in the Hoenn region. A common annoyance to those surfing from place to place, it shows up on every water route. It has the habit of carrying prey and valuables in its beak, and has been known to hide them in all sorts of locations. Sejon rides the winds and flies as if it were skating across the sky.</description>
<picture>243243.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="931" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Ametama</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Surskit is a bug-like species of Pokémon based on the water strider insect. It was introduced in the third generation of Pokémon media in the fictional Hoenn region. Surskit frequents lakes and ponds, and it has the ability to walk, or at least glide, on the water`s surface thanks to an oily substance secreted from the tips of its feet which modifies the water`s surface tension, thus allowing the water to support its weight. Surskit`s diet consists of the microscopic organisms that are found at the base of a lake ecosystem`s food chain. Surskit can also secrete a thick, sweet syrup resembling honey from the tip of its head. This sap is said to appeal to some species of Pokémon such as Heracross. Surskit usually secretes the syrup when it finds itself in danger. The exact reasoning behind this is unclear, but it may aim at attracting Pokémon which will drive the danger away to lick the syrup off Surskit`s head.</description>
<picture>243247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="934" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kinococo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shroomish is a mushroom-like Pokémon species found in the Hoenn region. It has small feet protruding from the bottom of its body. Shroomish subsist on a diet of damp, composted soil, and can be seen feeding on it in swarms following rain storms. They produce a toxic spore from glands on its cap.</description>
<picture>243249.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="944" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gonyonyo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Whismur is a basic species of Pokémon found in the Hoenn region. Whismur is a very timid Pokémon who dwells in caves. Its most defining characteristic is its voice. Normally, a Whismur makes very little noise, murmuring at a barely audible volume. However, if it senses danger, a Whismur starts crying in an incredibly loud voice that rivals the noise made by a jet plane. Whismur will then be startled by their own crying and cry harder, until they tire themselves out and fall asleep. Once Whismur starts crying, it will probably go on for some time even if the danger goes away, because it is startled by its own crying and cries louder still. It doesn`t even pause to catch its breath, since it breathes in through its ear canals (a technique reminiscent of circular breathing). Therefore, if its ear covers are shut, Whismur will stop crying. Otherwise, it will continue until it cries itself to sleep.</description>
<picture>243257.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="945" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Dogohmb</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Loudred is a Pokémon species that is the larger and stronger form that the Whismur species takes when going through Pokémon evolution. A Loudred builds power by stamping the ground while shouting. After Loudred finishes shouting, it becomes incapable of hearing anything for a while, which is considered a weak point. Loudred`s bellowing can decimate a wood-frame house and its subsequent shockwaves can turn over a truck. It only needs to use its voice to punish its foes. Its round ears serve as loudspeakers, and they are positioned to assail foes with ultrasonic waves at massive volume. Loudred are also immune to Jigglypuff`s and Wigglytuff`s song.</description>
<picture>243258.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="971" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Cokodora</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aron has a body of steel. Aron feeds on iron ore it digs from mountains, and uses the nutrients to sustain its steel body. It usually lives in colonies very deep below the mountain, usually about a mile down. If iron ore becomes unavailable, the colony moves to another place to search for solid iron objects. This even includes steel bridges and rails, something which occasionally causes problems for humans. Because of this, Aron colonies are largely considered a pest to society. Manufacturers, however, can consider Aron a blessing. When Aron evolves, it sheds its old iron casing. This iron is very tough, and is used by humans to make iron products.</description>
<picture>243266.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="972" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kodora</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lairon`s name is derived from the word "iron", and possibly the word "lair", as its Pokédex entries reference to it being a Pokémon that is very territorial in guarding its lair. It is also very `lairy` as described in the Hoenn Pokédex.</description>
<picture>243267.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="973" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Bossgodora</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Aggron" is a conjunction of aggressive or "aggro", because it has an aggressive nature, and iron, because its whole body is plated with iron. However, the name may also come from "aggregate", a term used to refer to rock and gravel. Its Japanese name contains ボス bosu, the transliteration of boss. ゴドラ Godora is a variation of Kodora, making it the "boss of Kodora" or the "Boss Kodora." It also resembles the name Gojira.</description>
<picture>195363.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="978" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Prasle</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Plusle is a very friendly and social Pokémon. In battle, it encourages and rallies its partner on in a manner similar to a cheerleader. It flashes and crackles with electric sparks all over its body and can short out the electricity coming out of its paws to create an electric version of a pompom. If its friend loses besides its support, it begins to cry loudly. Plusle tends to absorb electricity by climbing up telephone poles. Plusle is pink with a plus sign for a tail, while Minun is blue, with a minus sign for a tail.</description>
<picture>243270.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="979" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Minun</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minun is the Cheering Pokémon, and Plusle`s counterpart. It likes cheering for its allies. It emits electricity based on the performance of its friends. On Firered and Leafgreen Its electricity was said to be good for your medical health. It represents the electrical charge not subtraction.</description>
<picture>243271.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="986" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Samehader</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The name Sharpedo originates from the words shark and torpedo. Sharp may be another influence on its name. The Japanese name, 鮫肌 (samehada), means "shark skin".</description>
<picture>64493.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="988" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Whaloh</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wailord is a gigantic, oceanic mammal with the largest known size of all Pokémon. Living in the vast oceans of the Pokémon world, Wailord swims languorously in pods of about four members or more, often at the surface so it can breathe through its upper nostrils. With huge mouths these Pokémon can eat massive amounts of undersea food, such as krill, in a single gulp. When chasing somewhat larger prey, Wailord herd them by leaping out of the water and making humongous splashes in what is often described as a breathtaking display. If a Wailord inhales to the maximum capacity of its gigantic lungs, it is able to dive close to 10,000 feet below the surface. Optionally by puffing itself up, it can float high on the ocean surface or beach on a shoreline if it wishes.</description>
<picture>243279.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1001" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Tyltto</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Swablu has light and fluffy wings that are like cottony clouds. This Pokémon is not frightened of people. It lands on the heads of people and sits there like a cotton-fluff hat. It loves to make things clean and to this end, if it spots anything dirty, it will wipe and polish it with its cottony wings. If these wings become dirty, it will find a stream to shower itself. After enduring winter, in which little food is available, Swablu flocks move closer to towns in the spring.</description>
<picture>243290.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8135" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="73">8.01</rating>
<name>Sonans (Musashi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While Wobbuffet is technically Jessie`s Pokémon, it has been around so long that it has become a main character, appearing in almost every episode of the series since it debut.
Wobbuffet was first seen walking around with Benny, his previous trainer. Jessie traded her Lickitung for Wobbuffet and it has been with her ever since that day.
Wobbuffet rarely battles but when he does, his Counter and Mirror Coat moves have proved to be very effective. Unfortunately, Jessie`s tactics aren`t always sufficient to master Wobbuffet`s superior defensive skills.
Wobbuffet also randomly comes out of his Pokeball, especially during the Team Rocket motto. He is also seen blasting off with Jessie regardless if he was actually part of the action.</description>
<picture>56350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22350" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="17">7.27</rating>
<name>Fushigidane (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanto Pokémon League Tournament
Round 4 - Vs Jeanette Fisher - Grass Field
Ash selected Bulbasaur as his first Pokémon whilst Jeanette choose her Beedrill. As the faster Pokémon, Beedrill charged at bulbasaur at full speed, however Bulbasaur mananged to evade and return a Razor Leaf attack. Once again Beedrill used its superior speed, avoiding the Razor Leaf attack whilst also getting itself in a good position to use a Twin Needle atttack on Bulbasaur. Despite being on the backfoot, Bulbasaur managed to dodge the Twin Needle attack and Beedrill`s Stinger. After jumping backwards, Bulbasaur created enough space to be able to use its Leech Seed attack which struck Beedrill on its attacking stinger. Beedril was stuck in Leech Seed forcing it to the floor and Ash had bulbasaur finish it off using a Tackle attack which gave Ash the Initial Advantage in the battle.
Like Beedrill, Scyther had an advantage in speed and used this by quickly trying to attack Bulbasaur with its blades. After beeing unsuccessful, Jeanette order Scyther to used a Swift attack which managed to hit Bulbasaur a few times and was useful in deflecting its Vine Whip attack. Jeanette ordered Scyther to use a Double Team attack to which Ash had Bulbasaur to attempt to hit the real Scyther. The attempt failed and Scyther was able to land a few strikes by charging at Bulbasaur and managed to evade Bulbasaur`s counter of a Razor Leaf and Vine Whip attack. Ash had Bulbasaur use its Vine Whip once more but told it to swing the vines towards all of the copies which Double Team created, knowing that Bulbasaur would have to hit the real one in the process. The plan worked and Scyther was struck by Vine Whip, eliminating it from the battle.
Jeanette released her final Pokémon of the round which was a Bellsprout. Her choice suprised her a few people including Bulbasaur, as by apperance alone Bellsprout could be considered a weak Pokémon.
Ash had Bulbasaur charge at Bellsprout but managed to flip it above its head using its own momentum against itself. Ash was stunned by Bellsprout`s agility. Bulbasaur was angered at being tossed aside so easily and charged once again at Bellsprout, but like before, was thrown away using its own momentum. Bellsprout took advantage of Bulbasaur being on the floor and thrown it towards Ash`s podium, showing great strength and eliminated Bulbasaur from the tie.
Ash quickly rushed Pikachu into battle to try and finish Bellsprout off.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Sand Field)
Bulbasaur was Ash`s fifth choice Pokémon in his winner`s trophy battle against Drake. Bulbasaur`s first opponent was against Drake`s Electabuzz.
Bulbasuar manage to shake of Electabuzz`s initial Thundershock attack and returned a Razor Leaf attack which struck Electabuzz, although, whilst being hit by Razor Leaf, Electabuzz manage to use a Thunderbolt attack that Bulbasaur quickly dodged.
Bulbasaur uses Tackle and causes some light damage to Electabuzz but taking advantage of how close Bulbasur was, it manage to hit Bulbasaur with a Thunderpunch which eliminated it.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56563.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22398" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-13">
<name>Foretos (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock caught Forretress as a Pineco near Azalea Town with one of Kurt`s Fast Balls while trying to pick Apricorns.</description>
<picture>56631.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23590" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Juptile (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Grovyle evolved during a battle against Guy`s Loudred.</description>
<picture>58815.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23592" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Ohsubame (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taillow evolved into Swellow in the final round of the Crossgate Town`s annual PokéRinger Tournament.</description>
<picture>58817.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23594" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Cotoise (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Torkoal were traveling through the Valley of Steel when they saw Torkoal being attacked.</description>
<picture>58819.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23595" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Heigani (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58820.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23596" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Yukiwarashi (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Snorunt was first seen stealing Ash`s badge case, causing him to chase after it into a blizzard.</description>
<picture>58821.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23599" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Mizugorou (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock`s Mudkip lived in a preserve run by Old Man Swamp. Brock first met the Mudkip after they both helped rescue a baby Mudkip on the preserve. Later another baby Mudkip fell off the cliff and Brock`s Mudkip managed to rescue it but was caught on a rock. It`s trust in Brock increased after Brock rescued it from the waterfall and also when they worked together to fed off Team Rocket.
After rescuing the baby Mudkips from Team Rocket, Old Man Swamp noticed how well the older Mudkip got along with Brock and he suggested that it should journey with Brock.</description>
<picture>58824.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23602" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Hasubrero (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock`s Lombre evolved right after Brock rescued it from a well.</description>
<picture>58827.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23616" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Agehunt (Haruka)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>May`s Silcoon evolved into Beautifly.</description>
<picture>58842.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23622" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Eneco (Haruka)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skitty had wandered in the desert and it lost its sense of smell. Brock suggested they take it to a Pokémon Aromatherapy Center where it recovered after it was sprayed with some medicine.</description>
<picture>58849.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23844" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Wakasyamo (Haruka)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Torchic then evolved into Combusken during a battle against some Breloom.</description>
<picture>58858.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="38954" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2004-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
