<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3529" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2000-10-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Corrector Yui</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">コレクター・ユイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Corrector Yui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Collector Yui</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">コレクターユイ</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Yui ragazza virtuale</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Corrector Yui</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Corrector Yui</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.shopro-entertainment.com/corrector.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="728" type="Animation Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="3748" type="Series Composition">Sumisawa Katsuyuki</name>
<name id="1021" type="Original Plan">Asamiya Kia</name>
<name id="4463" type="Direction">Mutou Yuuji</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="5751" type="Character Design">Muroi Fumie</name>
<name id="3661" type="Series Composition">Nishizono Satoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr1021 [Asamiya Kia] and Okamoto Keiko.
Set in the year 2020, Kasuga Yui arrives for her ComNet class where even the teacher is virtual, but she isn`t very good with computers. Her father works developing software, and she`s excited about the prospect of spending the day in a virtual fun park with him. But Grosser is working to take over ComNet and Yui must stop him. To do this she is sucked into the net itself and is given downloadable elemental suits which she uses to fight as the ComNet Fairy, Corrector Yui.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="139">4.23</permanent>
<temporary count="139">6.57</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5076.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1282</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>113</identifier>
<identifier>eodido</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shopro-entertainment.com/corrector.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Corrector_Yui</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>コレクター・ユイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159805</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2068</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3817</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="45037" update="2005-12-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49371" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コムネットへ出発!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to ComNet!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ComNet e Shuppatsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52187" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪口メールにご用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beware of Nasty E-Mail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waruguchi Mail ni Goyoujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52188" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おいしいものはホドホドに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take It Easy with the Food</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oishii Mono wa Hodohodo ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52189" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">占いネットで恋の予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trouble on the Fourtune Telling Net</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uranai Net de Koi no Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52190" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とどけ! 森の歌声 (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Listen to Nature`s Song Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoke! Mori no Utagoe (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52191" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とどけ! 森の歌声 (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Listen to Nature`s Song Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoke! Mori no Utagoe (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52192" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">O-EDOネット大騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Trouble in D-Edo Net</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oedo Net Daisoudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52193" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レスキューをたすけて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please Help Rescue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rescue o Tasukete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52194" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大宇宙のユイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui`s Space Odyssey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oouchuu no Yui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52195" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お菓子の家で食べられちゃう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger in the Gingerbread House!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashi no Ie de Taberarechau!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52197" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わくわくダブルデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Thumping Double-Date Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakuwaku Double Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52198" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どきどきダブルデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Thumping Double-Date Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki Double Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52199" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">8つのソフトの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secrets of the Eight Software</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yattsu no Soft no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52200" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウエスタンネットの決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at Western Net</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Western Net no Kettou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52201" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷探偵エクスプレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Orient Express Orientation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi Tantei Express</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52202" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャギーの大特訓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jaggy`s Training Course</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaggy no Daitokkun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52203" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォーウルフが吠える時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Howl of the War Wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wolf ga Hoeru Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52204" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">00ユイは新人スパイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Double `O` Yui, Rookie Spy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">00 Yui wa Shinjin Spy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52205" update="2007-09-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユイのプリンセス修行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui, Princess in Training</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui no Princess Shugyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52206" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれた春菜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seeking Haruna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta Haruna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52207" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後のソフト シンクロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Synchro: The Last Software</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Soft Synchro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52208" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い翼の天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Angel with Dark Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Tsubasa no Tenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52209" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! ダブルコレクター!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Double Correctors!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Double Correctors!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52210" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユイの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui`s Decision!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui no Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52211" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃グロッサー城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack on Grosser`s Castle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki Grosser Jou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52212" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日へ出発!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to Tomorrow!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita e Shuppatsu!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63238" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">IRはもういらない!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">IR No Longer Needed!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">IR wa Mou Iranai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63239" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんな友だち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are All Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna Tomodachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63240" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コレクター・ユイはもういらない!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Corrector Yui no Longer Needed!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Corrector Yui wa Mou Iranai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63241" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷子の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Little Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maigo no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63242" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユイと愛の演劇バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui and Ai: The Stage Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui to Ai no Engeki Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63243" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざせ!マンガ家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s What I`m Going to Be! A Cartoonist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase! Mangaka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63244" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイナス200°Cの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battlefield minus 200C</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minus 200C no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63245" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">占います!モテる条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prediction! How to Be Popular</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uranaimasu! Moteru Jouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63246" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">太陽を追いかけろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search for the Sun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyou o Oikakero!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63247" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユイちゃんアイドルになる!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui Becomes an Idol!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui-chan Idol ni Naru!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63248" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたネッティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nettie Has Disappeared</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Nettie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63249" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリーズの学園日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Freeze`s School Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Freeze no Gakuen Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63250" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の個人レッスン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ai`s Private Lesson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Kojin Lesson</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63251" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピース大ぼうそう!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Peace Goes on a Rampage!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Peace Daibousou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63252" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉旅行だよユイちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui Goes to the Hot Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen Ryokou Da yo Yui-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63253" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">8時間世界一周</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Around the World in 8 Hours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">8 Jikan Sekai Isshuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63254" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決めます!コレクター春菜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decide! Corrector Haruna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimemasu! Corrector Haruna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63255" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユイちゃん恋をする</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui Falls in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui-chan Koi o Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63256" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャギー図書館大さわぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trouble in Jaggy`s Library</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaggy Toshokan Daisawagi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63257" update="2007-09-23">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひまわりの中の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sunflower Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himawari no Naka no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63258" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリプルコレクター見参!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triple Correctors Meeting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Triple Corrector Kenzan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63259" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみのフリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragic Freeze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Freeze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63260" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コレクター・アイの正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Corrector Ai`s True Character</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Corrector Ai no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63261" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛とアイとi</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ai and Ai and I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Ai to I</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63262" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コムネット最大の危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ComNet`s Greatest Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ComNet Saidai no Kiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63263" update="2007-03-13">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コムネット崩壊!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ComNet`s Collapse!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ComNet Houkai!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63269" update="2006-09-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特典映像 パイロット版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227509" update="2020-03-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilote</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
