<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="353" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">HeatGuy J</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">H.G.J -Habitat Ground Jewdo-</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Habitat Ground Jewdo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">HeatGuy-J</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Heat Guy Jay</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HGJ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヒートガイジェイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Heat Guy J</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Heat Guy J</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Heat Guy J</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Горячий парень Джей</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="13201">Good animation. Good action scenes. Unique in many ways... cliche in others. It did leave me wanting more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="266262">It`s a great tv serie`s, the music, the plot, and the caracters evolution you must see this</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/hgj/</url>
<creators>
<name id="750" type="Unknown Relation">Bandai Visual</name>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="1043" type="Original Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="2217" type="Character Design">Yuuki Nobuteru</name>
<name id="1705" type="Series Composition">Akane Kazuki</name>
<name id="1705" type="Original Work">Akane Kazuki</name>
<name id="1705" type="Direction">Akane Kazuki</name>
<name id="13936" type="Music">Try Force</name>
</creators>
<description>In the city of Judoh, http://anidb.net/ch28485 [Claire Leonelli] has inherited leadership of the Mafia group Vampire following the death of his father. To keep Claire`s and other criminal activities in check, the city`s Bureau of Urban Safety has Special Services Division operative http://anidb.net/ch28481 [Daisuke Aurora] and the super android codenamed http://anidb.net/ch8048 [Jei] (whose identity is apparently kept secret, since androids are banned in the city). With both of them around, there is little room for crime in Judoh.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="710">6.33</permanent>
<temporary count="718">7.34</temporary>
<review count="2">6.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>37231.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1820</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1774</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>958</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1071</identifier>
<identifier>jriyti</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/hgj/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Heat_Guy_J</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヒートガイジェイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>263</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239550</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5602</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>creepy laugh</name>
<description>At least one character in the show inexplicably and repetitively seems to have the urgent need to laugh in a creepy, loud and usually very annoying way.
For male bad guys this seems to be a must, but some of the uppity (rich) female characters use the laugh as part of their condescending attitude as well.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8048" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">8.78</rating>
<name>Jei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An android with incredible power, J was created in cooperation between a government facility and a civilian enterprise; androids are illegal in Judoh, but a special exception is made for J, much to the dismay of wary city officials. Despite his hulking size, J can run at enormous speeds and packs a powerful punch. However, after prolonged bouts of action, J must cool himself down by venting a great deal of superheated air from pipes mounted on his shoulders, making a sound like a howling wolf.
J is maintained by the Civilian Enterprises Sect technician Antonia Bellucci. It is said that J is modeled after Antonia`s father. This is probably why J seems to be so human sometimes, with a noble character and strong beliefs on things like how a man should act.</description>
<picture>27162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28481" type="main character in" update="2011-02-11">
<rating votes="3">5.40</rating>
<name>Daisuke Aurora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28482" type="main character in" update="2011-02-11">
<rating votes="3">6.62</rating>
<name>Kyoko Milchan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28483" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-11">
<rating votes="3">5.80</rating>
<name>Boma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28484" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-11">
<rating votes="3">2.46</rating>
<name>Shun Aurora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28485" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-11">
<rating votes="4">3.29</rating>
<name>Claire Leonelli</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34161" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-03">
<rating votes="3">4.82</rating>
<name>Ken Edmundo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4356.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77262" type="appears in" update="2015-09-06">
<rating votes="1">1.55</rating>
<name>Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100824" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-14">
<rating votes="1">3.38</rating>
<name>Antonia Belucci</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67172.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4261" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">街 -GUY-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City: Guy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ville</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Machi -Guy-</title>
<summary>Special Services Division operatives Daisuke and Super Android J hit the streets, hot on the trail of a couple of shady characters who’ve arrived in Judoh with an android in tow.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4624" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弾 -GUNS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bullet: Guns</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Balle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama -Guns-</title>
<summary>An anonymous bomb threat is made on the Central Tower. Daisuke springs into action, heading to an old military base to ask about explosives being obtained from there and alone, J heads to a different ammunition depot to inspect their explosives records.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4625" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">童 -DOLL-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Child: Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poupée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warabe -Doll-</title>
<summary>The Vampire abducts a young boy, while across town, J begins behaving erratically. Later crossing paths with the boy in the street, J mistakes him for an android, and with all eyes on him, J grabs the boy by the neck, inciting panic in town.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4626" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獣 -CHAOS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beast: Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fauve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kemono -Chaos-</title>
<summary>As his casino, Claire Leonelli gains a hired gun over a game of Russian Roulette. The new recruit’s job: Deal a little destruction in Daisuke’s direction.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4627" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">噂 -BOMB-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rumor: Bomb</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rumeur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwasa -Bomb-</title>
<summary>A psychotic bomber has Judoh on edge after a series of random attacks. Daisuke’s at ground zero when one of the bombs goes off, and J’s rescue attempt puts the android in serious danger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4628" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎 -WAR-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blaze: War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Flamme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo -War-</title>
<summary>Claire Leonelli is tapped to replace his late father as head of Judoh’s criminal underground, and not everyone is pleased with the decision. Claire quickly quiets the opposition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4629" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆 -TRUST-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ties: Trust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna -Trust-</title>
<summary>Monica, despite being so young, has been the breadwinner for her family ever since her mother became a drunk. Daisuke learns of a group that is stealing passports from the citizens of Judo and it turns out Monica`s mother has been targeted by the group.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4630" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">響 -BROTHER-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sound: Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sonorité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibiki -Brother-</title>
<summary>Daisuke busts up a gang of hoods he sees assaulting a young man for money and comes to learn that the man he aided is Kia Freeborn, son of the famous Blues Dullia. Kia, however, harbors nothing but hatred and resentment for his absentee father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4631" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仇 -CIRCULATION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge: Circulation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vengeance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kataki -Circulation-</title>
<summary>An altered human makes an attempt at Daisuke`s life and though unsuccessful, he is able to strip Daisuke of his father`s bullet pendant, causing it to fall into the sewers of Judo. Dice is prepared to head underground to reclaim his father`s token.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4632" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">欲 -MONEY-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desire: Money</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cupidité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoku -Money-</title>
<summary>Claire Leonelli devises a scheme that will take care of two birds with one stone: fixing the commodities market and framing Daisuke for the financial burden of thousands that will ensue. The market will be closing soon and the Vampire is out for blood.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6762" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻 -MIRAGE-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Illusion: Mirage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi -Mirage-</title>
<summary>An old flame of Edmundo`s comes to him one night with a possible crime to report, but she is unable to remember the crime, lately having experienced gaps in her memory that she can`t account for. The officer contacts Daisuke and requests help on the case.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7973" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光 -VISITOR-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light: Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari -Visitor-</title>
<summary>Venturing to Judo every eighteen years, the Celestials prepare to meet with the government to see if the city is still civilized. If not, the Celstials have the power to turn off the station that supplies the essentials of life to the city.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10612" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">撃 -ENCOUNTER-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shooter: Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coup</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Geki -Encounter-</title>
<summary>With the Celestials ready to turn of the power to the city, Dice and J must race to stop the Vampire from crippling the city.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23459" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂 -ARROW-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soul: Arrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Âme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii -Arrow-</title>
<summary>Daisuke is given orders from Shun to head to the village of Siberbia where he is to find a witness with information about the death of their father. Leaving the city, Daisuke meets a young girl in need of a guide and postpones his own plans to help her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23460" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華 -TARGET-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower: Target</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fleur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana -Target-</title>
<summary>When Shun comes within an inch of his life after being struck by a sniper bullet, Daisuke is quick to arrive at his side in recovery. Meanwhile, J and Edmundo investigate the assassination attempt and Claire senses a traitor in his midst.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23461" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陸 -SURVIVAL-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Land: Survival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Riku -Survival-</title>
<summary>Finally able to set out on their overdue assignment, Daisuke and J arrive at the Siberian Village. But deep within a cave, a man having lived in solitude for 18 years dispatches his androids in order to keep those behind Marius` death in the shadows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23462" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裂 -INDEPENDENCE-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Split: Independence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rupture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare -Independence-</title>
<summary>When Dice reports to Shun on the findings of their father`s case, Shun shuts down the Special Unit. Meanwhile, a mob war has begun as the various families search for Claire, whose left eye is the key to unlocking the Vita Company`s safe filled with gold.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23463" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心 -TRUTH-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart: Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro -Truth-</title>
<summary>Offered a job with the Special Unit, Boma tries to end his friendship with Daisuke in fear of being betrayed. Meanwhile, a beast master has come to town in order to capture the beast he couldn`t tame and Daisuke and Boma face off in an abandoned stadium.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23464" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想 -FAKE-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thought: Fake</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Émotion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi -Fake-</title>
<summary>SECT, the company that created J, is suddenly closed due to a lack of resources and a new android that looks exactly like J has just killed a mob boss. Dice and Edmundo investigate further to uncover the truth and absolve their friend of any wrongdoing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23465" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友 -TEARS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend: Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo -Tears-</title>
<summary>When Romeo Visconti takes it upon himself to learn the whereabouts of the financial wing of the underworld, Senator Noriega has him eliminated. It`s up to Edmundo and Daisuke, to weed out those responsible for Romeo`s death and bring them before the law.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23466" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">島 -FORTRESS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Island: Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Île</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shima -Fortress-</title>
<summary>Swiftly appearing and disappearing into the ocean, a mysterious woman from the sea begins to attack sailors. When old tales surface of an island chain some 600 miles south of Judo, the Special Unit commandeer a vessel and head out to the curious islands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23467" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父 -PLAY-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father: Play</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Père</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi -Play-</title>
<summary>When her house is burned to the ground by a mob family, Daisuke offers Monica a job at the Special Unit. Edmundo takes an immediate dislike to her, J acts as her surrogate father, and Daisuke learns something about the bullet attached to his necklace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23468" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂 -ALTERATION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Craze: Alteration</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Folie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyou -Alteration-</title>
<summary>With another attempt made on Shun Aurora`s life, dire implications befall the city of Judo. The military tanks, silent for fifty years, begin to roll out. Shogun is attacked and J`s program is changed by a secret command buried deep within his system.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23469" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪 -REVOLUTION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow: Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki -Revolution-</title>
<summary>Below the darkened skies of Judo, military tanks patrol the city as Daisuke, Antonia, and Boma fight to save J. Shun tries to wrest control from the powers of Judo, but Claire and Dice team up to oppose him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23470" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漢 -GUYS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Real Man: Guys</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hommes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko -Guys-</title>
<summary>While Daisuke prepares for the final showdown with Shun, Claire and his resistance begin their attack on the military. With J reactivated and on his way to help, Daisuke must press onward and save his partner, his brother, and the people of Judo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24761" update="2017-12-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="3">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虜 -ANGEL-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hostage: Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Captif</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko -Angel-</title>
<summary>Thugs take out J and kidnap Daisuke, delivering him to the Vampire who seeks retribution. It`s up to Kyoko to rescue her colleague, but when she infiltrates the Vampire`s casino, she finds herself in a battle for the title of Vampire.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26697" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102414" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102415" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102416" update="2009-05-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
