<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3555" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>1995-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Montana Jones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Montana</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">モンタナ・ジョーンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Montana</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Montana</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Caccia al tesoro con Montana</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مونتانا</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="617" approval="2" total="2">Meitantei Holmes</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="220711">for nice childish moment and to remember some good days try this really it will touch your heart</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/archives/montana_index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1181" type="Animation Work">Studio Junio</name>
<name id="4538" type="Character Design">Nishino Rie</name>
<name id="4282" type="Direction">Imazawa Tetsuo</name>
<name id="38474" type="Original Work">Marco Pagot</name>
<name id="38475" type="Original Work">Gi Pagot</name>
<name id="53534" type="Music">Mario Pagano</name>
<name id="58174" type="Music">Gianni Bobbio</name>
</creators>
<description>Italian-NHK joint production.
Montana Jones is about two archaeologists, Montana Jones and his cousin Alfred Jones, and the pretty young reporter Melissa Sone who`s mission is to travel around the world to find ancient treasures before the famous evil robbery called Lord Zero and his men get his greedy hands on them. A story filled with adventure, comedy and action.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="43">6.09</permanent>
<temporary count="44">7.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5193.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3313</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2218</identifier>
<identifier>dkasod</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/archives/montana_index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Montana_Jones</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>モンタナ・ジョーンズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1400</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4259" parentid="2857" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>animal world</name>
<description>All characters of the show are walking-talking animals. Their behaviour and clothing can resemble that of humans. They also may try to mirror human society.
There are no humans present in this world.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3968 [animal protagonist].</description>
<picurl>10254.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4424" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>American derived</name>
<description>A work which was created as a continuation/remake of an American based franchise or cartoon series. These works are completely Japan original, but which lack roots within Japanese media.
See also: http://anidb.net/t3714 [cartoon remake]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="48732" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">翼よあれがマヤの灯だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The secret of the gold medal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geheimnis des Goldmedallions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le médaillon d`or des mayas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48734" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底2万センチ カリブの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The giant squid</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Riesenkraken-U-Boot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aventures aux Caraïbes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48735" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イスタンブールより愛をこめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasure hunting in Istanbul</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf Schatzsuche in Istanbul</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de la cathédrale Sainte-Sophie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48736" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰がためにプラハの鐘はなる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The discovery of the jewel bible</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Fund der Edelsteinbibel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le manuscrit de Prague</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48737" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タージマハルの秘かな愉しみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The silk-carpet of the Taj Mahal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Seidenteppich vom Taj Mahal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aventures en Inde</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48738" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪男はチベットがお好き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The horrible snowman</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Land des Schneemenschen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor du dalaï-lama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48739" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピラミッドの鍵貸します</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The tomb from the Pharao</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Pharaonengrab</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tombeau du pharaon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48741" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">突然アーサー王のごとく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King Arthur`s sword</title>
<title xml:lang="de">König Arthur`s Schwert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée du roi Arthur</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48742" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンドルは舞いおりた・インカの秘宝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The secret code of the Inkas</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der geheime Code der Inkas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le code secret des incas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48743" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チャイナタウンに手を出すな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Criminals in Chinatown</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verbrecherjagd in Chinatown</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trafic à Chinatown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48744" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイキングはわかってくれない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adventuring with the Vikings</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abenteuer bei den Wikingern</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aventures chez les vikings</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48745" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えよバビロン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The treasure in the desert</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Schatz unterm Wüstensand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de Babylone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルハンブラのある夜の出来事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The secrets of the dried fountain</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der geheimnisvolle Brunnen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voyage en Espagne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48753" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンコールワットは危険な香り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A secret entrance in the castle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Geheimgang im Königsschloß</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La disparition d`Alfred</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48754" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラスト騎士(ナイト)・イン・パリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The subterranean waterfalls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die unterirdische Wasserfalle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les grains de riz en or d`Angkor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48755" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アポロン神殿・デルフィで昼食を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kidnapped to castle Mauleon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Entführung nach Schloß Mauleon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les templiers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48756" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">白鳥城からの脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A muddy fight for the future</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schlammschlacht um die Zukunft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère du trésor d`Apollon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48757" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">香港で激突! 皇帝の指令を探せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The golden dragon from Hong Kong</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der gelbe Drache von Hong Kong</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aventures à Hong-Kong</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48758" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミラノ大捜査線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The hidden flymachine</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die versteckte Flugmaschine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La machine volante de Léonard de Vinci</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48759" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">寒い国から来た招待</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The clock from Iwan the Terrible</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Glocke von Iwan dem Schrecklichen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La visite à Moscou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48760" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">王様と私・ジンバブエの黄金</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chased in the goldmine</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verfolgungsjagd in der Goldmine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor du roi Matope</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48761" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い砂漠の大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The rescueing boomerang</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der rettende Bumerang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voyage au pays des kangourous</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48762" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンテカルロに進路をとれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack of the sharks</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Angriff der Haie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La statue de Monté-Carlo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48763" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シルクロード大攻防戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The flood`s coming!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Sintflut-Falle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor des Nabateens</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48764" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊急指令! イースター島異常あり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emergency! Landing on Easter Island</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Notlandung auf der Osterinsel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère des statues de l`île de Pâques</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48765" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">王様は二つの鐘を鳴らす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The sunken goldbell.</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die versunkene Goldglocke</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cloche en or</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48766" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンゴル高原・荒野の三人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The attack of the bandits in Mongolia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Banditenangriff in der Mongolei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voyage en Mongolie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48767" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古城の恋のメロディ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The haunted house in Scotland</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geisterschloß in Schottland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La couronne royale</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48768" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレタ島・迷宮にご用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Searching through the labyrint of King Minos</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Labyrinth von König Minos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor du roi Minos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48769" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エルドラドの冒険者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Colombian jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Urwald von Kolumbien</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bateau en or</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48770" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイル強奪事件・神殿の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saved by the crocodiles</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rettung vor den Nilkrokodilen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La statue en or de Karnak</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48771" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アラビアンナイト・カリフの熱い夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The treasure of the caliph</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Schatz des Kalifen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor du calife</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48772" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海賊に明日はない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The secret pirateship</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das geheimnisvolle Piratenschiff</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cap sur Lisbonne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48773" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1994-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラキュラ城のトリコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emergency! Landing on treasure island</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Notlandung auf der Schatzinsel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voyage en Transylvanie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48774" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SOSケティ号・忘れられた孤島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adventure in China</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abenteuer in China</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bateau du roi Ptolémée IV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48775" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下より永遠(とわ)に・始皇帝の遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Straight through Austria</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kreuz und quer durch Österreich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aventures en Chine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48776" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モーツァルトにラブソングを</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The crown of the tsar</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Krone des Zaren</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de l`empire Ottoman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイカルは燃えているか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marie Antoinette`s Collier</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Marie Antoinettes Collier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor du lac Baïkal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48778" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風車とダイヤモンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lemuria: The hidden land</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Land Lemuria</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le collier de la reine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48779" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">失われたレムリアを求めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The secret of the Mont St. Michel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geheimnus des Mont St.Michel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cap sur l`île de Java</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48780" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お宝は天使の匂い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The dragon of stone</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der steinerne Drache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mystère au Mont Saint-Michel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48781" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな目撃者・ラインの黄金</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Artemis Temple</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tempel der Artemis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Promenade sur le Rhin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48783" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女神の金庫は危険がいっぱい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get to the Chaco-Canyon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Chaco-Canyon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le temple d`Artémis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48784" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリフパレスの禁じられた遊び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Travel through Transsylvania</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Reise nach Transsylvanien</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sur les traces des ancêtres des indiens</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48785" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エトルリアの黒い罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trapped in Toscana</title>
<title xml:lang="de">In der Toscana</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aventures en Étrurie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48786" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルフレッド怒りの脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ormeca</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ormeca</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Truquoises du Dieu Jaguar</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48787" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルコ・ポーロ, ベニスに消ゆ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marco Polo`s heir</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Marco Polos Erbe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lettre de l`empereur de Chine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48788" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サハラの熱い日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deseperatly lost in the desert</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verirrt in der Wüste</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trésor de la cité antique</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48789" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイスの危険なめぐりあい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The baker and the knight room</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Bäcker und die Ritterburg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret du trésor de Charles II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48790" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">日本へ! 嘆きの戦士・義経の財宝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keanu, daughter of the chief</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Keanu, die Tochter des Häuptlings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un drôle de tunnel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48791" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミシシッピの大いなる遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The monk and the samurai</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Mönche und der Samurai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`armure d`or du samouraï</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48792" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばサバンナの陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost in Africa</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verschollen in Afrika</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voyage en Afrique</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128275" update="2011-02-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
