<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="359" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-04-20</startdate>
<enddate>1996-04-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tenchi Muyou! in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Tenchi Muyo! The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tenchi the Movie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">天地無用! in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tenchi the Movie: Tenchi Muyo in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Tenchi the Movie - Tenchi Muyo in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Tenchi enamorado</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Tenchi Muyo! In Love</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="376" type="Sequel">Tenchi Muyou! in Love 2 - Haruka Naru Omoi</anime>
<anime id="409" type="Prequel">Tenchi Muyou!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="508260">Even if you haven`t seen Tenchi Muyo, this movie is a great stand-alone introduction to the series.  Some of the best animation from the 90s and just the right combination of scifi and fantasy.  Often compared to Back to the Future in story, it stands apart with some pretty unique ideas and a powerful ending.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/index.html?years=1996&amp;?type=movie</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="3849" type="Character Design">Horiuchi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="3849" type="Chief Animation Direction">Horiuchi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4305" type="Direction">Negishi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="34256" type="Music">Christopher Franke</name>
<name id="1956" type="Work">Miura Tooru</name>
</creators>
<description>The notorious criminal http://anidb.net/ch48057 [Kain] has escaped from the Galaxy Police (GP) headquarters. He had been captured before through the joint efforts of the Jurai Royal Family and the GP.
Around the same time, http://anidb.net/ch9722 [Tenchi]`s house on Earth suddenly disappears... even Tenchi himself is fading fast! It seems that Kain has gone back in time to alter things to his favour. Tenchi and the gang must now go back to the year 1970, and save Tenchi`s parents from certain doom at the hands of Kain.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1148">6.13</permanent>
<temporary count="1152">7.27</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>6435.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>230</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1006</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>410</identifier>
<identifier>uhacow</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tenchi_the_Movie:_Tenchi_Muyo_in_Love</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89739</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3738" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-05">
<name>aliens living on earth</name>
<description>There`s an alien or a hive of aliens blending into society near you!</description>
<picurl>70750.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8916" type="main character in" update="2015-12-16">
<rating votes="179">5.21</rating>
<name>Masaki Aeka Jurai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aeka is typically shown as the beautiful first princess of the planet Jurai who has fallen in love with the title character, Masaki Tenchi. Aeka is portrayed as being modest, well mannered, traditional, and aristocratic, but can also be snobbish (her proper accent is evidence of her aristocratic upbringing). She can also be very fierce when she feels that anyone or anything she cares for is in danger, such as Tenchi or her younger sister Sasami, of whom she is very protective.
Aeka is a rival of Ryouko for Tenchi`s affections. Often the conflict between the two comes out of their decidedly different personalities and backgrounds, with Ryouko being more blunt, open and sexual in her attempts to gain Tenchi`s love. The level of the rivalry can vary between being equatable to a pair of bickering siblings to an all-out feud. Ryoko`s teasing and efforts often bring out some of Aeka`s worse aspects. However, there are times when Aeka puts aside her rivalry whenever Tenchi is in danger, such as the battle with Kagato.</description>
<picture>28319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="557" picture="228659.jpg">Takada Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8917" type="main character in" update="2015-12-16">
<rating votes="779">7.15</rating>
<name>Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While details of her character differ between the various series, Ryouko is typically shown as an attractive, semi-reformed powerful space pirate who is madly in love with the series main character, Masaki Tenchi. In the various series, Ryouko is portrayed as being impulsive, hedonistic (with a penchant for sake), poor-mannered, often immodest, recklessly violent, and hot-tempered although she sometimes reveals her more emotional and vulnerable side.
In the anime, Ryouko universally holds an intense rivalry with the character Aeka, who also fights for Tenchi`s affections. Often the conflict between the two comes out of their decidedly different personalities, with Ryouko being the tomboyish troublemaker and Aeka being the well-mannered, but often snooty aristocrat. The level of the rivalry can vary between being equitable to a pair of bickering siblings to an all-out feud.</description>
<picture>28321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8918" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-16">
<rating votes="177">8.24</rating>
<name>Masaki Sasami Jurai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The younger sister of Aeka and so is also a princess of Jurai. Within the family group Sasami usually takes on the dual role of younger sister/mother. She may be the most responsible of the group and takes care of all the cooking duties. She has a rarely-seen mischievous streak within her however, and takes great delight in fooling the older girls. She has teal-coloured hair tied in long pigtails with melon pink eyes.</description>
<picture>28323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9722" type="main character in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="227">4.86</rating>
<name>Masaki Tenchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenchi is the crown prince of Jurai and the grandson of a Juraian prince named Yosho and an Airaian priestess named Airi. He gains possession of a "Master Key" called `Tenchi`, also known as the Tenchi Sword (Tenchi-ken), that can form a lightsaber-like blade. He later receives a special ring from Tsunami that can create a Juraian battlesuit for him and acts as a "Guardian System", protecting him. Tenchi also has the innate ability to create kou-ou-yoku ("Light Hawk Wings"), and the ill-defined ability of Material-Energy Conversion.
Tenchi initially lives in the city with his father to attend school and visits his grandfather`s shrine every summer, where he trains to become a Shinto priest and learns his family`s special style of swordsmanship.
Tenchi suffers a great deal of stress as he tries his hardest to be a gentlemen while most of the women within the household will take the opportunity to display their attraction for him.</description>
<picture>29487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9725" type="appears in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="164">7.57</rating>
<name>Ryou-Ouki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryou-Ouki`s appearance is similar to a cross between a cat and a rabbit, and for this reason Ryou-Ouki is commonly referred to as a cabbit.
Ryou-Ouki is usually a shapechanger, but the shapes, aside from the "cabbit" form, vary according to the series. Ryou-Ouki `s background and other traits vary considerably from one series to another.</description>
<picture>2349.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9732" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="272">7.79</rating>
<name>Hakubi Washuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakubi Washuu is a self-proclaimed greatest scientific genius in the universe. Her character differs depending on the continuity, though she sometimes displays a number of innate powers which she rarely uses, preferring to solve problems with reason or technology. In all incarnations, Washuu has also shown to be somewhat prudent and is generally trickier to fool than Tenchi or the other girls, which makes it harder for her to fall into an enemy trap. In all three Tenchi series Washu had also created an inter-dimensional laboratory in the closet of the Masaki house, although her laboratory is a lot bigger in the OVA series than in both of the TV series.</description>
<picture>29497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1901" picture="186579.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10332" type="appears in" update="2009-07-12">
<rating votes="89">7.01</rating>
<name>Masaki Katsuhito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly known as Masaki Youshou Jurai, he fled Jurai over 700 years ago to "retire" on Earth. He was once the greatest swordsman on Jurai. Currently Katsuhito is a Shinto priest who is not only training Tenchi to be a Shinto priest but also training him in Jurai swordsmanship. Youshou had a marriage arranged with half-sister Aeka, but left. At the time, not all Juraians liked the idea of mixed blood heritages (he is part human, on his mother`s side) and he used Ryouko`s attack as an excuse to slip away to Earth. In the OVA, he expected that Aeka was trying to track him down and arranged for Tenchi to fight Ryouko so that his grandson would go in his place to Jurai. Although he had dropped contact with his parents, he was still in touch with Seto (through whom he was able to send Tennyo and Kiriko, among others, into space via the Galaxy Police) although her collusion in his plans is not known. While he appears to be of advanced age, his grey hair and lined face are merely an illusion hiding his true form, which he shows to only a select few (such as his mother).
He is in a common law marriage with Airi and has two children from that union called Minaho and Kiyone. He has married at least one other woman in the past (named Kasumi, and possibly Funaho`s niece), and his descendants along that line include Nobuyuki, Rea, and Kiriko.</description>
<picture>30912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10340" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-12">
<rating votes="253">5.04</rating>
<name>Kuramitsu Mihoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mihoshi is known as one of the finest officers in the Galaxy Police, but her career soon hit a major roadblock after an incident hinted at in the 4th episode of the 1st OVA, and the 4th episode of the 3rd one. Now she suffers from frequent difficulties to focus on a single thought track and, due to her clumsiness, she causes a lot of collateral damage during her assignments, which eventually causes Mihoshi to be demoted. The desk of the Section 7 commander is covered with misconduct reports and bills from all the damages she causes. As a result, she is assigned to a special area of the galaxy, the Sol system, which is Juraian territory, in the vain hope that she wouldn`t cause any more trouble.</description>
<picture>30928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47476" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="53">6.87</rating>
<name>Makibi Kiyone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiyone is one of Mihoshi`s colleagues at the Galaxy Police, and also her total opposite in character.
Very skilled, committed and intelligent she could probably aim for a picture book career if only she had not been assigned partners with Mihoshi Kuramitsu.</description>
<picture>91801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48055" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-23">
<rating votes="3">4.23</rating>
<name>Nobuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48056" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-23">
<rating votes="7">7.17</rating>
<name>Achika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48057" type="appears in" update="2012-08-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4305" update="2018-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>1996-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>The space criminal Kain escaped from prison, destroyed the GXP HQ, and singled out Earth as his next target! Meanwhile, Tenchi has problems of his own! His house has suddenly vanished, his body is disappearing, and his only hope is a trip back in time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4539" update="2008-02-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1996-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14993" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1996-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
