<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3611" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-12-13</startdate>
<enddate>1996-12-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Angel Densetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Angel Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">エンジェル伝説</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1099" approval="11" total="16">Sakigake!! Cromartie Koukou</anime>
<anime id="7934" approval="6" total="12">Beelzebub</anime>
<anime id="9173" approval="3" total="3">Shibaitaroka</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="246008">I watched raws. It seems to be pretty faithful to the manga, and that`s a good thing because the manga is epic. Too bad only two episodes were made, because it stops just when the story gets interesting. I`ll say recommended for fans of the manga.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="396751">A premise that lands itself well to comedy. I laughed a couple of times but this was too short to get a feel of the characters. It is enjoyable and I recommend it if you have 50 minutes to kill.

The Good: The premise lands itself well to humour. The backgrounds are nice and the animation is decent.

The Bad: Only two episodes really isn`t enough to immerse yourself and get attached to any of the characters. Their background and personnality are left blank for the most part.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="23642" type="Music">Tsuyoshi</name>
<name id="7420" type="Original Work">Yagi Norihiro</name>
<name id="6476" type="Character Design">Itou Naoyuki</name>
<name id="4449" type="Direction">Kaizawa Yukio</name>
<name id="4619" type="Music">Katsumata Ryuuichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr7420 [Yagi Norihiro]`s manga from Shounen Jump.
New kid in town http://anidb.net/ch23399 [Kitano Seiichirou] is a noble, sensitive boy with "the face of a devil and the kindness of an angel." Pushed into a world of drugs and crime simply because of the way he looks, he tries to make the world a better place without fighting.
Source: The Anime Encyclopedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="744">7.23</permanent>
<temporary count="745">7.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>7938.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5251</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Angel_Densetsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エンジェル伝説</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235633</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="931" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>weird eyes</name>
<description>Eyes suggesting something supernatural.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3107" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-12">
<name>unfoundedly feared character</name>
<description>Due to some strange misunderstanding, or some other unfounded reason the character in the anime is feared by his contemporaries.
Example: A male student with an "evil eye" is mistaken for a delinquent, and thus feared by the students in his class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="23399" type="main character in" update="2010-10-28">
<rating votes="6">9.42</rating>
<name>Kitano Seiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seiichirou Kitano is a kind and naive boy with the heart of an angel, but the sinister looks of a devil. This causes many misunderstandings, leading people to assume that he is a villain or heroin addict, and results in a career as the head thug, or "school guardian" at his new school.
(source: ANN)</description>
<picture>58138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23548" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<name>Kuroda Seikichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The former "guardian" of Hekikuu high. He`s been a slave to the previous guardian for most of his high school life, and he thought he could enjoy being the guardian in his last year of school, but he is forced to resign soon after meeting Kitano. He`s the most delinquent-like of the group, skipping lessons to smoke and provoking fights. Although he usually gets beaten up by others (Koiso Ryoko, Takehisa, other delinquents), he isn`t physically weak - he is big and has a strong punch. The fact he is constantly defeated lies in his mind - he is easily scared and has tendency to panic. He is also simple-minded enough to be manipulated.
Kuroda desperately tries to reserve a leftovers of his dignity by acting like a guardian before Ogisu and his sempais. Also he has one-sided crush on Ryoko.
Ooshita and Tokiyama are his two lackeys/friends. Both of them have rarely been referred to by their actual names. Koide, the class president`s assistant calls it a "miracle" that he was able to obtain their full names. As the story progresses, they realize Kuroda`s weakness (and strengths, rarely good, though), but they kept on being loyal to him.
Another piece of trivia from the author himself, Kuroda serves as a pivotal character at the very start of the series, when the author experienced a writer`s block.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>58131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23549" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">7.31</rating>
<name>Takehisa Yuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The strongest delinquent of Hekikuu high, previously suspended for beating up one of the teachers: after being defeated by Kitano, he proclaims himself his "little brother". He sports spiked bleached hair and has no eyebrows.
After claiming loyalty to Kitano, he becomes less delinquent-like. He doesn`t get into a lot of fight anymore (although he doesn`t lose any of his fighting skill), nor does he skip classes, staying calm most of the time. His old, hot-blooded self, comes to the surface when someone tries to harm Kitano or himself.
At the end of the series, when confronted with the fact of Kitano being `normal` - Takehisa`s old comrades had come and asked him to join up in order to beat up Kitano - he proclaimed that whether or not Kitano is a delinquent, he is still Takehisa`s best friend. He then proceeded to beat up his old comrades with a smile on his face.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>58132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3704" picture="76764.jpg">Tsukui Kyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23550" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-28">
<rating votes="1">5.86</rating>
<name>Kojima Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakkun high school`s banchou</description>
<picture>58133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="53680" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最「恐」顔[フェイス]登場!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Devil Face Appears!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sai "Osore" Face Toujou!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111986" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の幕あけ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beginning of the Legend!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Maku Ake!!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
