<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3622" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1985-12-16</startdate>
<enddate>1985-12-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Love Position, Legend of the Halley</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ハレー伝説 ラブ・ポジション</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ラブポジション LEGEND OF HALLEY</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ラブ・ポジション ハレー伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Love Position - The Legend of Halley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Love Position Halley Densetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラブ・ポジション THE LEGEND OF HALLEY</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1467" approval="0" total="4">Kindan no Mokushiroku Crystal Triangle</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="3518" type="Character Design">Koujina Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Plan">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="4348" type="Music">Wakakusa Kei</name>
<name id="8402" type="Character Design">Chikanaga Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="5864" type="Character Design">Matsushita Hiromi</name>
<name id="5155" type="Direction">Iuchi Shuuji</name>
<name id="35042" type="Character Design">Uesugi Emiko</name>
<name id="39022" type="Character Design">Indori Koya</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="887" type="Animation Work">Sunshine Corporation</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr1195 [Tezuka Osamu].
An agent who was sent riding on Halley`s comet to the earth. She was actually given an order to destroy the earth. Captivated by planet`s beauty, however, she is no longer able to destroy the planet. Seventy-six years later, another agent from Halley`s comet is sent to earth, taking over the body of an escaped murderer in the Nevada deserts and heads out to liquidate the traitor who took the form of a Girl in Vietnam called Lamina.
Note: This is the very first original animated video produced by http://anidb.net/cr723 [Tezuka Productions].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="80">4.46</permanent>
<temporary count="81">5.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>42927.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4832</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5878</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3251</identifier>
<identifier>ryttak</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ラブ・ポジション_ハレー伝説</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88837</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2682" parentid="2812" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Nevada</name>
<description>Nevada is a state in the western, mountain west, and southwestern regions of the United States. Nevada is the 7th most extensive, the 35th most populous, and the 9th least densely populated of the 50 United States. Over two-thirds of Nevada`s people live in one single county, Clark County, which contains the Las Vegas–Paradise metropolitan area, where the state`s three largest incorporated cities are located. Nevada`s capital is Carson City.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214274.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3222" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Vietnam</name>
<description>Vietnam, officially the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, is the easternmost country on the Indochina Peninsula in Southeast Asia. Vietnam is bordered by China to the north, Laos to the northwest, Cambodia to the southwest, Thailand across the Gulf of Thailand to the southwest, and the Philippines, Malaysia and Indonesia across the South China Sea to the east and southeast. Its capital city has been Hanoi since the reunification of North and South Vietnam in 1976, with Ho Chi Minh City as the most populous city.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214337.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="47477" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>1985-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
