<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="364" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>1997-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Slayers Try</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Slayers: Magiczni wojownicy III</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">秀逗魔导士3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スレイヤーズ TRY</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Slayers Try</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Slayers Try</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Slayers Try</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Рубаки Try</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">슬레이어즈 트라이</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Magiczni wojownicy 3</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Slayers: A kis boszorkány új kalandjai</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Убийствен опит</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5818" type="Sequel">Slayers Revolution</anime>
<anime id="95" type="Prequel">Slayers Next</anime>
<anime id="123" type="Prequel">Slayers Premium</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://www.slayers-tv.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1089" type="Animation Work">E&amp;G Films</name>
<name id="1338" type="Original Work">Kanzaka Hajime</name>
<name id="2745" type="Character Design">Miyata Naomi</name>
<name id="7271" type="Series Composition">Takayama Jirou</name>
<name id="1338" type="Series Composition">Kanzaka Hajime</name>
<name id="3848" type="Original Work">Araizumi Rui</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="4395" type="Music">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="6752" type="Music">Vink</name>
</creators>
<description>A magical barrier has just been broken down... now our heroes can visit places that they have never seen before. After being commissioned by princess http://anidb.net/ch7898 [Filia], a Golden Dragon, the group is at work to stop a terrible prophecy from coming true. As http://anidb.net/ch1000 [Lina], http://anidb.net/ch7616 [Gourry], http://anidb.net/ch7618 [Zel], and http://anidb.net/ch7619 [Amelia] travel through new towns and kingdoms, it becomes apparent that magic is not as common as in their home towns. This does not mean that the people are not strange, however. The town of fish people will bring back fond memories of Noonsa...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2505">7.23</permanent>
<temporary count="2523">7.83</temporary>
<review count="3">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>152835.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1172</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>375</identifier>
<identifier>ecuqku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.slayers-tv.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スレイヤーズ_(アニメ)#.E3.82.B9.E3.83.AC.E3.82.A4.E3.83.A4.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BATRY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>699</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6713" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-08">
<name>dragon person</name>
<description>Dragon people, often known by other names such as dragon-kin and dragonewts, are reptilian demi-humans, often said to be descended from or related to dragons. Dragon people are generally partially covered by scales that tend to be very strong and often able to withstand edged weapons or even deflect projectiles, and may also have a tail and a pair of wings.</description>
<picurl>189103.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1000" type="main character in" update="2014-09-22">
<rating votes="1994">9.10</rating>
<name>Lina Inverse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lina Inverse is the primary protagonist and the only character appearing in the whole Slayers-franchise. She is an adolescent but very powerful sorceress, with a great love for money, treasure and food. In the anime and manga (but not in the light novel) Lina uses overly destructive magic recklessly, often with little provocation. She is reputed to be an evil, powerful, destructive, diminutive sorceress (the evil part is arguably not true, though one may consider her greed and general lack of concern for others unless they are in danger of being killed can be considered "evil").
Lina has gained many different nicknames, including "Bandit Killer" and "Dragon Spooker", neither of which she`s very fond of, though to her, her most embarrassing nickname is "Lina the Pink" which is her official title amongst the sorcerer`s guild.</description>
<picture>161200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7489" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-23">
<rating votes="247">8.76</rating>
<name>Xellos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Xellos is a mazoku and the priest of Greater Beast Zelas Metallium.
Xellos was created by Zelas during the Kouma War. The mazoku put a barrier over the peninsula and managed keep the enemy`s reinforcements out of the battle. Because of this, however, four of the five lords were unable to participate in the war anymore, so priests and generals were created in order to represent them. Because he is her only immediate servant, and he was created from a great deal of her power, Xellos is more powerful than all the other priests and generals of Ruby Eye Shabranigdu`s subordinates.
In the Kouma War, Xellos single-handedly killed thousands of golden dragons; he is feared and hated by them ever since. They refer to him as the Dragon Slayer, although he does not like this name, probably because it does not fit the "image" he wants others to view him as. After the war, before serving Hellmaster, Xelloss`s duty for a thousand years was to find stray copies of the Claire Bible and destroy them so that humans could not find an easy way to defeat mazoku (with Zanaffar), or utilise the power of the Lord of Nightmares.
Xelloss` true astral form is that of a simple black cone. He is able to divide his power into dozens of tiny cones that can inflict damage over a long period of time.</description>
<picture>26124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7616" type="main character in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="257">7.19</rating>
<name>Gourry Gabriev</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Lina Inverse destroyed the Dragon no Kiba (Dragon`s Fang) gang, and was later encountered by a small array of vengeful bandits, Gourry Gabriev jumped in to save her. Though Lina appreciated the offer, she initially opted against accepting Gourry as a bodyguard, but Gourry`s big-brotherly nature prevented him from acting otherwise. Gourry, dense as a brick, saw Lina as a younger girl in need of protection, and thus, he offered it.
Gourry is the owner of the most powerful sword known to man, the mysterious Sword of Light. The Sword of Light channels its users intentions into energy, usually taking the form of a gleaming blade of light. Gourry has learned how to utilize the sword`s energy in different forms, though, most notably the power of swinging it quickly downwards to form energy beam projectiles.
Gourry is the swordsman of the group, and acts the role very well. He`s single-minded in his protection of Lina, and even after helping Lina defeat Ruby-Eye Shabranigdu, he has resolved to follow Lina around wherever she goes. Supposedly, he has nothing better to do, and perhaps still sees himself as her guardian.</description>
<picture>26399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7617" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="149">8.82</rating>
<name>The Slayers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Major characters of the series, which form (mostly) stable group.</description>
<picture>26408.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7618" type="main character in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="293">7.70</rating>
<name>Zelgadis Greywords</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Lina Inverse overthrew the Dragon`s Fang bandit gang, one of Zelgadiss` men, Zolf, happened to be stuck inside. And, well, he got incinerated. Needless to say, Zelgadiss was mad. More importantly, though, Lina had gotten a very valuable Orihalcon statue, which was the reason Zolf was there to begin with. Zelgadiss wanted the statue in hopes that it could cure his chimaeric curse.
Only, it didn`t quite work out that way. Zelgadiss didn`t quite cure himself, even after the whole incident with Rezo, the Red Priest and Ruby-Eye Shabranigdu. So, he`s still searching for a cure, hoping to find one of the fabled Clair-Bibles in hopes to cure himself. The curse makes him 1/3 golem, 1/3 demon, and 1/3 human, which makes him impervious to most physical weapon such as swords and buckshot, but not to the physical impact of, say, a cannonball.
Zelgadiss is quite self-conscious about his appearance, almost ashamed of it. In fact, he`s a very quiet character all around, only speaking when necessary, and only interested in the shortest path to his cure. He also tends to get embarassed easily wherever the topic of romance is brought up.
Zelgadiss is a superb swordsman, having trained many long years. He often enhances his blade with the Astral Vine spell, one of many Shamanist spells at his disposal. He has more or less mastered the Spirit category of Shamanism, having learned its most powerful spell, the Ra-Tilt, among numerous other spells in other categories.</description>
<picture>26411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7619" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="293">6.53</rating>
<name>Amelia Wil Tesla Seyruun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amelia is the daughter of Philionel el de Seyruun, Crown Prince of the kingdom of Seyruun. Like her father, Amelia is a self-proclaimed Champion of Justice(tm) and is singleminded in her quest for truth, honor, and dignity. Also like her father, she`s a complete klutz and has no clue of what IS and ISN`T a true cause for justice.
Amelia has trained since birth for her cause; once convinced, she isn`t easily dissuaded from inflicting her particular flavor of justice on whoever she perceives to be an "enemy of the people". She thinks of Lina as a hero - a destructive hero, but nevertheless a hero - and wants to be just like her and every other good hero that comes along.
Amelia gets bored being royalty sometimes - she often follows her father Phil on journeys around the countryside. She often looks for trouble, simply so that she can right it. Whenever scouting out an area, she always includes a quick look for the highest place to stand.
...
Why does she always look for the highest place to stand, you ask? In case the enemy strikes, she wants to be able to strike back with a dynamic, triumphant pose of her own, terrifying the enemy with fear of justice. A lot of times, she ends up falling, too, she`s only a young girl after all. In fact, Amelia has the reputation of being one of the clumsiest characters in all of Slayers, topped only by Martina.
Amelia is also a budding sorcerer in her own right. Her specialty is white magic, however she also has reached the highest level of training in Shamanist Spirit magic, a testament to her quick learning time and eagerness to learn. She has even developed a spell or two of her own, most notably the Visfarank spell, which seems to be the glowing manifestation of justice as a pair of boxing gloves.</description>
<picture>169335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7711" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="49">6.24</rating>
<name>Philionel El Di Seyruun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phil is the Crown Prince of Seyruun, and presumably the only one trusted to take the throne after numerous assassination attempts. Phil, like his daughter, is dominated by his thirst for justice, so much that he has dedicated his life to being a pacifist. Or at least that`s what he says, he acts more like a pro wrestler sometimes.
Unlike most of the Seyruun royal family, Phil has no magical powers, but he does have a lot of brute strength. He uses this mostly in the form of oxymoronic, justice-themed physical attacks, such as "Pacifist Crush", "Kindness to All Creatures Kick", "Benevolent Giant Swing", and "Goodwill Towards Man Smash". His sheer brute strength is even enough to destroy lesser demons.</description>
<picture>26578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1821" picture="20697.jpg">Anzai Masahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7722" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="11">3.98</rating>
<name>Aka Me no Maou Shabranigdu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Many, many years ago, so long ago that no one knows just how long ago it was (presumably at the world`s genesis), Ruby Eye and the shinzoku of his world, Flare Dragon Ceifeed, began a massive battle for control of the world. As a mazoku, Ruby Eye`s goal was to completely destroy the world, while Flare Dragon wanted to protect it from destruction. The length of this battle is unknown, but the conclusion was reached approximately around 4000 BK. Before his destruction at the hands of Ruby Eye, Flare Dragon created four alter-egos of himself, then broke Ruby Eye into seven parts and scattered them throughout the world, sealed in humans. Flare Dragon`s reasoning for sealing Ruby Eye in humans was that since humans have such short lives compared to those of other races, Ruby Eye would eventually be purged through reincarnation before re-awakening. Unfortunately for Flare Dragon, this hypothesis was more or less incorrect. If a human carrying a piece of Ruby Eye develops a great hatred of the world, the piece could awaken and combine with the human to become a special kind of a half-demon; this already happened a couple of times and the pieces are still far from being purified.</description>
<picture>159071.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7875" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-07-23">
<rating votes="5">4.58</rating>
<name>Greater Beast Zelas Metallium</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Greater Beast Zelas Metallium was created during the Shinma War, and is over 5000 years old. Though the Shinma War has ended, the overall conflict between shinzoku and mazoku has not. Shabranigdu at some point created five subordinates of his own: Hellmaster Fibrizo, Chaos Dragon Garv, Greater Beast Zelas Metallium, Dynast Grausherra, and Deep Sea Dolphin.
The most we have seen of the Greater Beast in the animated series so far are flashes of her legs and arms, and a momentary glimpse of her true form behind her servant, Xelloss in the openings of several seasons, but that does not mean nothing is known of her.
Zelas resides on Wolf Pack Island, the southern base of the former mazoku barrier, and is probably best known for her servant, Xelloss. Her wise investment rendered him the most powerful mazoku outside of Ruby Eye Shabranigdu`s five servants.
Her true form is an armored wolf with wings. In the anime, we are given the impression that Zelas is an elegantly-dressed woman with long, silver hair who smokes.</description>
<picture>26917.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7890" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="13">3.26</rating>
<name>Valgarv</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valgarv is a half-mazoku, half-ancient dragon, a trusted servant of Chaos Dragon Garv.
Valgarv is approximately 1000 years old, as he was apparently alive during or after the Kouma War, although only as a young boy.
Before becoming a servant of Garv, he was an ancient dragon known as Val. With no future as a dragon, Garv turned him into a mazoku and thus, he became Valgarv. Possibly due to the mazoku barrier, he was unable to assist Garv with his objectives and could not prevent his death at the hands of Hellmaster Fibrizo, who was destroyed by the Lord of Nightmares, thus his chance for vengence against the Hellmaster was unknowingly ruined. However, when news of his master`s death reached him, Valgarv incorrectly believed that Lina Inverse was the one responsible for Garv`s death, and he wanted her to die at his hands.</description>
<picture>26929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7898" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-16">
<rating votes="15">5.73</rating>
<name>Filia Ul Copt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Filia Ul Copt is a golden dragon, formerly serving as a priestess under Flarelord Vrabazard.
Being a dragon, Filia has two bodies- her original golden dragon form, and the form we see most often, the young human woman. She can transform between these at will, but she does not enjoy transforming to dragon in front of other people, as it requires her to shed all her clothing in the process. Her dragon form is extremely large, and when she is in human form, she maintains her original weight, physical strength and her tail, which pops out when she becomes angry or startled. She says this is because she has yet to perfect her transformations. Even in human form, Filia retains her dragon magic and skills, such as holy spells and the ability to teleport herself and others over fairly long distances. She also carries a large mace on a garter belt attached to her leg.</description>
<picture>26934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51596" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-01-14">
<rating votes="13">8.25</rating>
<name>Lord of Nightmares</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Theirs is an existence too large to comprehend. The mother of all darkness. The true lors of the Monster race. One who longs to regain their original form. A darkness beyond blackest pitch. Deeper than the deepest night. One who shines like gold upon Sea of Chaos. A void witchin everything. The source of all chaos. One who has dominion over all terrible dreams. In short, the Lord of Nightmares.</description>
<picture>148569.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="63120" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-01-14">
<rating votes="12">3.79</rating>
<name>Flare Dragon Ceiphied</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Many, many years ago, so long ago that no one knows just how long ago it was (presumably at the world`s genesis), Ruby Eye and the shinzoku of his world, Flare Dragon Ceifeed, began a massive battle for control of the world. As a mazoku, Ruby Eye`s goal was to completely destroy the world, while Flare Dragon wanted to protect it from destruction. The length of this battle is unknown, but the conclusion was reached approximately around 4000 BK. Ceiphied was successful in weakening his demonic counterpart Ruby-Eye Shabranigdo by cutting the Ruby-Eyed Lord into seven pieces. Ceiphied died in so doing, but left behind four beings to continue his struggle: Aqualord Ragradia, Flarelord Valbazard, Earthlord Rangort and Airlord Valwyn.</description>
<picture>148571.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68711" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-18">
<rating votes="3">2.14</rating>
<name>Dark Star Dugradigdu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dark Star revived and began fighting with Vorfeed again. This was a huge battle, involving the servants of both Dark Star and Vorfeed and the remaining humans in the world. However, both Dark Star and Vorfeed became tired and realized that their war was destined to go on forever. Wanting to stop the fear and hate that was engulfing the universe, Vorfeed, against the wishes of her subordinates, allowed Dark Star to absorb her so that they could destroy their world together, in order to recreate it into a form where the shinzoku-mazoku conflict would not exist.</description>
<picture>158253.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68712" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-18">
<rating votes="4">2.63</rating>
<name>Armace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Armace is a shinzoku and one of the three subordinates of Night Dragon Vorfeed</description>
<picture>158254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68713" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-18">
<rating votes="4">1.49</rating>
<name>Erulogos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Erulogos is a shinzoku and one of Night Dragon Vorfeed`s subordinates.</description>
<picture>158255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4686" picture="171399.jpg">Hori Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68714" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-18">
<rating votes="4">2.73</rating>
<name>Sirius</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sirius is a shinzoku and one of Night Dragon Vorfeed`s subordinates.</description>
<picture>158256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68715" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-18">
<rating votes="6">2.89</rating>
<name>Jillas Jillos Jilles</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jillas Jillos Jilles is a red fox beastman and a servant of Valgarv.</description>
<picture>158257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68716" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-18">
<rating votes="3">1.44</rating>
<name>Gravos Maunttop</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gravos Maunttop is a beastman, a servant of Valgarv.</description>
<picture>158258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4345" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">連続発射! 戦いの荒磯!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Continuous Fire! The Wind-Swept Shore of Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die magischen Gefäße</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tirs continus ! La côte de la bataille !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Постоянный обстрел! Ветреное побережье битвы!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Renzoku Hassha! Tatakai no Araiso!</title>
<summary>Lina`s gang ends up in the middle of a war between two rival nations. Aiding one side in the long-standing conflict could be Inverse`s only path to freedom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4346" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">用意周到! 計画は動き出した!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Be Careful! The Plan Has Begun!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Valgarvs Geschichte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prudence ! Le plan se met en marche !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Берегитесь! План начал исполняться!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youishuutou! Keikaku wa Ugokidashita!</title>
<summary>Almayce reveals his intentions for the Sword of Light. When Valgaav moves to attack, Filia unseals Lina`s magic and a battle erupts!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4347" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無我夢中! 迷宮の追跡行!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Selfless and Senseless! Pursuit Through the Labyrinth!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Jagd nach dem Lichtschwert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Colère noire ! Poursuite dans le labyrinthe !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Без страха и без чувств! Погоня в лабиринте!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugamuchuu! Meikyuu no Tsuisekikou!</title>
<summary>With Jillas on the run, Lina`s party must go their separate ways in a twisting labyrinth. They encounter Almayce, Xellos, and Filia, and learn shocking insight into Valgaav`s intentions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4348" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和平会談? これがドラゴンの神殿か?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Peace Conference? This Is the Dragon Shrine?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Heiligtum der Drachen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un entretien paisible ? C`est ça, le temple des dragons ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мирные переговоры? Это Храм драконов?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wahei Kaidan? Kore ga Dragon no Shinden ka?</title>
<summary>After Lina rebuilds the castle, the Golden Dragons confess their doubts in her ability to complete the important mission. She better not let it bother her - Almayce is about to attack!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4349" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">難関突破? 男ジラスの底力!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hurdle`s Cleared? Jillas`s True Power!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf der Kippe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Triomphe des difficultés ? La force cachée de Jiras !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Препятствия пройдены? Тайная сила Джилласа!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nankan Toppa? Otoko Jiras no Sokojikara!</title>
<summary>Within a dark castle, a shady guide causes Gourry to become separated from the gang. Possession of the Sword of Light is in the balance - will Jillas finally obtain the power he has sought?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4350" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流浪流転? 暴走神殿の旅を!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wandering Around? The Runaway Shrine Takes a Trip!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Horrorfahrt zum Tempel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les mésaventures de l`errance ? Voyage incontrôlable vers le temple !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Заплутали? Беглый храм отправляется в путь!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rurou Ruten? Bousou Shinden no Tabi o!</title>
<summary>As the gang nears the Fire Dragon temple, they find they can`t use their magic! To get their powers back, Inverse unleashes the Dragon Slave - and as usual, does more harm than good.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4351" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追放覚悟! 二人の愛は永遠よね?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ready for Exile! Isn`t Two People`s Love Eternal?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sera und Marco</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Résolus à l`exil ! Leur amour est éternel, hein ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Готовьтесь к изгнанию! Разве любовь двоих не вечна?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuihou Kakugo! Futari no Ai wa Eien yo ne?</title>
<summary>Gravos uses his powerful sword against Lina and the gang, and Inverse must rely on the Dragon Slave. Suddenly, after the island is destroyed, a bridge appears between the two kingdoms!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4352" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流言飛語? 炎を吐かなきゃ煙は立たぬ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Wild Rumor? You Can`t Have Smoke Without Fire?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kein Rauch ohne Feuer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fausse rumeur ? Il n`y a pas de fumée sans cracher du feu ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Нелепые слухи? Нет дыма без огня?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuugen Higo? Honoo o Hakanakya Kemuri wa Tatanu?</title>
<summary>Filia encounters trouble in a town where her kind is not allowed. When Lina`s gang rushes to help her, Xellos`s insults unleash Filia`s anger, and the whole town pays the price!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4353" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東奔西走! ヤツの狙いはカタキ討ち?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On the Move! He`s Out for Revenge?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Valgarv sieht rot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Panique ! Il veut se venger ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">В путь! Он жаждет мести?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhonseisou! Yatsu no Nerai wa Katakiuchi?</title>
<summary>Valgaav is out for revenge, as well as Gourry`s Sword of Light! When the villain retreats, Xellos warns that Inverse`s magic might not be enough to stop him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4354" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傍若無人なアイツはどこへ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where`d That Arrogant Guy Go?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein neuer Gegner</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Où est cette personne insolente ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">И где же этот нахал?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boujakubujin na Aitsu wa Doko e?</title>
<summary>In a land where the citizens are mystified by their amazing magic, Lina`s gang encounters Xellos - and a powerful new enemy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4355" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">半信半疑? 故郷[くに]からの手紙に!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Doubtful? A Letter from Home!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lina in der Klemme</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Incrédulité ? Une lettre venue de chez moi !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сомнения? Письмо из дома!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanshinhangi? Kuni kara no Tegami ni!</title>
<summary>When Lina`s crew lands in search of food, Filia gives Inverse a letter from her sister and reveals that the gang has been chosen for an important mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4356" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">威風堂々? 旅立ちの帆をあげろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Majestic? Hoist Sails for the Journey!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Setzt die Segel!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Majestueux ? Levons les voiles du voyage !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Гип-гип ура? Ветер надувает паруса!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ifuu Doudou? Tabidachi no Ho o Agero!</title>
<summary>After a Golden Dragon attack pushes them into the sea, Lina and the crew inadvertently destroy the harbor. With no way to return to land, the gang begins a journey!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4357" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一触即発! 鍵を握る者!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Explosive Situation! The One Who Holds the Key!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Weltuntergang naht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Situation explosive ! Celui qui détient les clés !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Напряжённое положение! Тот, у кого ключ!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isshoku Sokuhatsu! Kagi o Nigiru Mono!</title>
<summary>Deep inside his lair, Valgaav confronts Lina, Gourry, Almayce and the others. When the villain gains control of the Sword of Light, he uses his power to transport Inverse`s gang far away!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4462" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三者三様! 光の示す先!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three People, Three Ways! Where the Light Leads!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschungen aus der Lichtsäule</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trois personnes différentes ! En direction de la lumière !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Трое на распутье! Куда укажет свет!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanshasan`you! Hikari no Shimesu Saki!</title>
<summary>Almayce unleashes a horde of monsters to locate the last weapon, and only Lina and the gang can stop their rampage! When they encounter Jillas, he holds a weapon as powerful as Lina`s mightiest spell!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4463" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">適材適所! 正義の里のアメリア!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Right Person in the Right Place! Amelia in the Village of Justice!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kämpfer für Gerechtigkeit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mesure adaptée ! Amélia au village de la justice !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Нужный человек в нужном месте! Амелия в Деревне справедливости!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tekizaitekisho! Seigi no Sato no Amelia!</title>
<summary>Gourry and Amelia visit a land with a demon problem, and are tasked with confronting the creatures. Before the battle ends, they find that the demons are actually old familiar friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4464" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">効果覿面? 恋の行方は紙一重!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Immediate Results? Love Is in the Tiny Differences</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebesintermezzo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Effet immédiat ? L`amour est à un pas !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Мгновенный эффект? Любовь таится в деталях!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukatekimen? Koi no Yukue wa Kamihitoe!</title>
<summary>Amid sea monsters and cross-dressing, Amelia and Gourry get caught up in the romantic drama of fishy Layla and her human boyfriend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4465" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">喧々囂々! 呪われた壷の恐怖!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pandemonium! Terror of the Cursed Jar!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geisterschiff</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Grosse frayeur ! L`horreur de la jarre maudite !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ад кромешный! Кошмар проклятого кувшина!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenkengougou! Norowareta Tsubo no Kyoufu!</title>
<summary>Lina, Zelgadis, and Filia take to the sea to locate Gourry. They soon find themselves battling hordes of ghosts in exchange for the chance to claim a rare and powerful jar.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4466" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">厄難奇難? ここは不思議の島!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disaster and Danger? This Place Is a Wonder Island!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lina im Wunderland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Malheur et péril ? Nous sommes sur une étrange île !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Несчастье и опасность? Это Остров чудес!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakunan Kinan? Koko wa Fushigi no Shima!</title>
<summary>Lina wanders an unfamiliar land with a pig as her guide. She finds Zelgadis acting strangely and uses her magic to break free from the odd realm - only to discover that Filia might not want to leave!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4467" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">横行闊歩! 終わりなき慟哭!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Striding and Swaggering! Lamentation Without End!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schleuse öffnet sich!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avancée à grand pas ! Lamentations éternelles !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сплошное хвастовство! Бесконечные терзания!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oukoukappo! Owarinaki Doukoku!</title>
<summary>Valgaav is summoning Dark Star, forcing Lina to use her most powerful spells. As the gate between worlds closes, the scene is rocked by a giant explosion!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4468" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者降臨? 少女の祈りは誰のため?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hero`s Advent? For Whom Does the Young Girl Pray?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Annas großer Held</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arrivée du héros ? Pour qui est la prière de la fillette ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Пришествие героя? За кого молится девушка?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Kourin? Shoujo no Inori wa Dare no Tame?</title>
<summary>In a crumbling village, one of Almayce`s underlings takes on Lina`s crew - and somehow ends up becoming a hero to the townsfolk!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4541" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未開未踏! 封じられた歴史!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Savage and Unexplored! History Sealed Away!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tempel im Eis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terre sauvage ! Les annales scellées !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Дикость и неизвестность! Сокрытая история!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikai Mitou! Fuujirareta Rekishi!</title>
<summary>The history of the warring Dragons is revealed! Meanwhile, after Almayce attempts to keep Xellos from forming an alliance that could lead to Dark Star`s emergence, the Golden Dragons appear!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4542" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永逝永訣! 倒れし者への叫び!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Death, Final Farewells! A Cry to the Fallen!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schlacht im Tempel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Repos éternel ! Le cri vers les vaincus !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Вечная смерть, последнее прощание! Оплакивание павших!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eisei Eiketsu! Taoreshi Mono e no Sakebi!</title>
<summary>Xellos takes Filia hostage! Lina tries to help, and attacks Almayce with the coveted ultimate weapon - but the powerful bow soon falls in the wrong hands!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4737" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TRYagain! 白く還りし刻!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Try Again! When All Returns to White!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rückkehr zu den Wurzeln</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">TRY again! Le moment où l`aube arrive !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Попробуй снова! Возвращение в белизну!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Try Again! Shiroku Kaerishi Toki!</title>
<summary>Just as it seems Valgaav cannot be defeated, Xellos and Filia give Lina the amazing magic power she needs to save the world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4738" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の星より出ずる者!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He Who Emerges from the Dark Star!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Valgarvs schreckliche Pläne</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celui sorti de l`étoile des ténèbres !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Рождённый Тёмной звездой!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Hoshi yori Izuru Mono!</title>
<summary>Valgaav is unleashed! Filia and Jillas try to stop him, along with Lina`s crew. As the powers of darkness reach unbelievable levels, Lina finds the Dragon Slave is worthless!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4739" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">推測不能! 開かれし禁断の門!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Way to Guess! The Forbidden Gateway Is Opened!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Zweckbündnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Présomptions impossibles ! La porte défendue s`ouvre !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Никаких сомнений! Запретный проход открыт!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suisoku Funou! Hirakareshi Kindan no Mon!</title>
<summary>Dark Star emerges before the gate can be closed, and Lina and the crew attack with all they`ve got! Just as the powerful entity seems to be defeated, he escapes - and Valgaav appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4740" update="2018-09-26">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">問答無用! 決戦の地を目指せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Time for Arguing! Head for the Showdown!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ist die Welt noch zu retten?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas de discussion ! Vers le lieu du combat décisif !</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Спорить некогда! Близится время развязки!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mondou Muyou! Kessen no Chi o Mezase!</title>
<summary>Lina vows to stop the chaos that is thinning the ranks of the Golden Dragons, and the crew heads for Valgaav`s lair. They better hurry - Xellos has plans for the Dark Star!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120794" update="2019-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176465" update="2019-08-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
