<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3654" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-01-13</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ayakashi: Japanese Classic Horror</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Аякаси - Классика японских ужасов</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">怪</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">怪~ayakashi~ JAPANESE CLASSIC HORROR</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ayakashi - Samurai Horror Tales</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ayakashi - Japanese Classic Horror</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ayakashi</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5113" type="Same Setting">Mononoke</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7056" approval="25" total="33">Aoi Bungaku Series</anime>
<anime id="1543" approval="1" total="8">Samurai Champloo</anime>
<anime id="5292" approval="1" total="5">Kyuubi no Kitsune to Tobimaru (Sesshouseki)</anime>
<anime id="362" approval="1" total="4">The Hakkenden</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="255559">hidden treasure for last arc
definitely a must see for mononoke fans</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="160474">Pretty OK. Just skip the first 4 eps IMHO.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/ayakashi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3306" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="4282" type="Direction">Imazawa Tetsuo</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="4804" type="Character Design">Hashimoto Takashi</name>
<name id="9263" type="Character Design">Itou Hideki</name>
<name id="4804" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hashimoto Takashi</name>
<name id="10056" type="Original Work">Izumi Kyouka</name>
<name id="6087" type="Direction">Nakamura Kenji</name>
<name id="9263" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Hideki</name>
<name id="19523" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kadota Hidehiko</name>
<name id="20517" type="Original Work">Tsuruya Nanboku</name>
<name id="47221" type="Direction">Nagayama Kouzou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Third installment in Fuji Television`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [Noitamina] late-night anime time slot. A collection of three classic Japanese horror stories. The first is a retelling of Yotsuya Kaidan, one of the most famous ghost stories in Japan, written by the 18th century kabuki playwright http://anidb.net/cr20517 [Tsuruya Nanboku]. The second is based on Tenshu Monogatari, a play by http://anidb.net/cr10056 [Izumi Kyouka]. The third, Bakeneko, is an original story.
Yotsuya Kaidan:
Tamiya Iemon is a samurai married to Oiwa, a beautiful woman, but he cannot bear the poverty they live in. One day, he is offered the opportunity to marry a rich woman and starts planning to kill Oiwa.
Tenshu Monogatari:
Himekawa Zushonosuke is a falconer sent by his master Harima to retrieve a falcon at the reputedly haunted Sirasagi castle. On his way, Zushonosuke meets a woman of an evanescent beauty bathing in a lake.
Bakeneko:
During the Edo period, the daughter of a family of samurai dies under mysterious circumstances, just before getting married. A wandering medicine seller senses that she was killed by a Bakeneko, a cat ghost. To fight it, he needs to know the form, the truth, and the reason why the Bakeneko has appeared, and the dark secrets of this uncommon family begin to unfold.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1814">6.49</permanent>
<temporary count="1834">7.39</temporary>
<review count="4">7.28</review>
</ratings>
<picture>44085.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3044</identifier>
<identifier>gakkyl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/ayakashi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ayakashi:_Samurai_Horror_Tales</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>怪_〜ayakashi〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324534</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7925</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1679" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-07">
<name>onmyoudou</name>
<description>Onmyoudou (also in`youdou, lit. "The Way of Yin and Yang") is a traditional Japanese esoteric cosmology that mixes natural science and occultism. A practitioner of onmyoudou is called an onmyouji.
Onmyoudou is based on the Chinese philosophies of Wu Xing (five elements) and yin and yang, introduced into Japan at the beginning of the 6th century and accepted as a practical system of divination. These practices were further influenced by Taoism, Buddhism and Shintoism, evolving into the system of onmyoudou around the late 7th century.
Onmyoudou was under the control of the imperial government, and later of the Tsuchimikado family of courtiers, until the middle of the 19th century, at which point it became prohibited as superstition.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2690" parentid="2641" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Tokugawa period</name>
<description>The anime takes place during a period of Japanese history running from 1603 to 1868.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4575" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-20">
<name>ukiyo-e</name>
<description>A genre of Japanese woodblock printing and painting, featuring motifs of landscapes, tales from history, the theatre, and pleasure quarters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6418" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Yotsuya Kaidan</name>
<description>Yotsuya Kaidan, the story of Oiwa and Tamiya Iemon, is a tale of betrayal, murder and ghostly revenge. Arguably the most famous Japanese ghost story of all time, it has been adapted for film over 30 times, and continues to be an influence on Japanese horror today.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7447" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-07">
<rating votes="184">9.31</rating>
<name>Kusuriuri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mysterious medicine seller (kusuriuri, 薬売り) whose name, age and identity are all unknown; simply refers to himself as a "mere medicine seller".
He has shoulder-length grey-brown hair, blue-grey eyes and long pointed ears; he wears what appears to be face paint around his eyes and nose, and is heavily accessorized.
Despite not showing any particular interest in women, the latter can often be found admiring his beauty worthy of a handsome young man.
His personality is characterized by an apathetic demeanour and pretentious manner of speech; yet when dealing with danger, his behaviour and tone of voice are intimidating and powerful.
He does not seem to have a determined goal, simply wandering from place to place exorcising Mononoke. But it is vaguely implied that should Mononoke cease to exist, he would disappear also, due to having lost his purpose.
In order to do banish these entities, he carries a mysterious talking sword referred to as the Sword of Exorcism (Taima no Ken, 退魔の剣 voiced by Takemoto Eiji, 竹本英史) which can`t be unsheathed unless the Form (Katachi), Truth (Makoto) and Reason (Kotowari) of the Mononoke he is facing are known.</description>
<picture>139557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15021" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-08">
<rating votes="8">5.17</rating>
<name>Kayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4028.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19634" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-21">
<rating votes="3">7.64</rating>
<name>Tomi-hme</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomi-hme holds the title of princess of the forgotten gods who reside in the "Tenshu Monogatari" 「天主物語」 arc</description>
<picture>51285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19635" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-15">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Himekawa Zushonosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19636" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-07">
<rating votes="2">4.68</rating>
<name>Tamiya Iemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19637" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-07">
<rating votes="4">6.78</rating>
<name>Tamiya Oiwa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19638" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-15">
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<name>Kikimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kikimaru is a friendly slim demon. Who is always along side with Kaikaimaru. He helps Zushonosuke surviving. This pair of demons only think about finding treasures in Tomi Hime`s castle.</description>
<picture>51290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19639" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-15">
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<name>Kaikaimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaikaimaru is a fat demon who is always besides his demon friend Kikimaru. Kaikaimaru is a friendly demon who helps Zushonusuke surviving. This pair of demons only think about finding treasures in Tomi Hime`s castle.</description>
<picture>51291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65439" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Tsuruya Nanboku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65440" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Yotsuya Osode</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65441" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Naosuke Gonbee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65442" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Itou Oume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65443" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Satou Yomoshichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65444" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Takuetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65445" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Koboto Kohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65446" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Akiyama Choubee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7007" picture="31995.jpg">Morozumi Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65447" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Okuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65448" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Shitanagauba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2820" picture="22867.jpg">Mayama Ako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65449" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Oshizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65450" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Kojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151195.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65451" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Hagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23026" picture="60818.jpg">Sakamoto Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65452" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Ominaeshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2291" picture="23193.jpg">Kano Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65453" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Susuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65454" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Kikyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23024" picture="79055.jpg">Kamada Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65455" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Kuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23291" picture="61849.jpg">Yoshikura Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65456" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="595" picture="17993.jpg">Kimoto Orie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65457" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Kagerou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23291" picture="61849.jpg">Yoshikura Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65458" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Odajima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65459" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sakai Yoshiyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65460" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sakai Yoshikuni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65461" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sakai Yoshiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3441" picture="149777.jpg">Sasaki Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65462" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sakai Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23024" picture="79055.jpg">Kamada Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65463" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23024" picture="79055.jpg">Kamada Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65464" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Hoozuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23026" picture="60818.jpg">Sakamoto Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65465" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sakai Mizue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2049" picture="228615.jpg">Soumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65466" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sasaoka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65467" type="appears in" update="2014-03-07">
<name>Sato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2879" picture="170992.jpg">Hino Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="46077" update="2019-12-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="23">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四谷怪談 序の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yotsuya Ghost Story - Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Histoire de fantômes de Yotsuya - Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotsuya Kaidan: Jo no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46177" update="2019-12-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="23">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四谷怪談 二の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yotsuya Ghost Story - Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Histoire de fantômes de Yotsuya - Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotsuya Kaidan: Ni no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46206" update="2019-12-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四谷怪談 三の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yotsuya Ghost Story - Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Histoire de fantômes de Yotsuya - Partie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotsuya Kaidan: San no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46207" update="2017-04-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四谷怪談 大詰め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yotsuya Ghost Story - Part 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Histoire de fantômes de Yotsuya - Partie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotsuya Kaidan: Oozume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46208" update="2014-08-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天守物語 序の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of Tenshu - Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le donjon des âmes perdues - Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshu Monogatari: Jo no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46209" update="2014-08-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天守物語 二の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of Tenshu - Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le donjon des âmes perdues - Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshu Monogatari: Ni no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46210" update="2017-04-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天守物語 三の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of Tenshu - Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le donjon des âmes perdues - Partie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshu Monogatari: San no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46211" update="2017-04-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天守物語 大詰め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of Tenshu - Part 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le donjon des âmes perdues - Partie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshu Monogatari: Oozume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46212" update="2019-12-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="24">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化猫 序の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bakeneko - Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakeneko: Jo no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46213" update="2019-12-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="23">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化猫 二の幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bakeneko - Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakeneko: Ni no Maku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46214" update="2019-12-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="24">9.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">化猫 大詰め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bakeneko - Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakeneko: Oozume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81149" update="2014-08-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">2.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81150" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81151" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81152" update="2007-08-09">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81153" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">4.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81154" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81155" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81156" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81157" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81158" update="2014-08-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81159" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81160" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81161" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81162" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
