<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3664" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1983-11-08</startdate>
<enddate>1985-01-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kojika Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Story of a Fawn</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Yearling</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Il cucciolo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">子鹿物語 THE YEARLING</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Alle Meine Freunde</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Jody en het Hertejong</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Elukevad</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="3653" type="Character Design">Seki Shuuichi</name>
<name id="3668" type="Series Composition">Yukimuro Shun`ichi</name>
<name id="7089" type="Direction">Oosumi Masaaki</name>
<name id="5311" type="Music">Sugiyama Kouichi</name>
<name id="9341" type="Original Work">Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings</name>
<name id="51795" type="Music">Kamiyama Jun`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on The Yearling (1938) by http://anidb.net/cr9341 [Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings].
Set in Hokkaido, Japan`s outback, a young boy discovers a fawn whose mother has been hit by a car and attempts to raise it himself.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="27">3.75</permanent>
<temporary count="27">5.16</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221522.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1701</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2568</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Yearling</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>子鹿物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235388</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="40664" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スルーフットとの対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown with Slewfoot</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Meister Petz</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40665" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨を呼ぶポスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letter which calls down the rain</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die große Dürre</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40666" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくたちの先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die junge Lehrerin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40667" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻のスペイン人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A rare Spaniard</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vorahnungen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40668" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きな木の小さな家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little house in a big tree</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Baumschule</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40669" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりオオカミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lone wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verlorener Stolz</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40670" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラッグと灰色の子ギツネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flag and the gray foxcub</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tierliebe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40671" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オオカミになった父さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dad becomes a wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Wölfe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40672" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">母さんの演奏会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother`s concert</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mutters Geheimnisse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40673" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹の中のフラッグor虹のなかのフラッグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flag in a rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Es muss sein</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40674" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鳥になった親友</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend turned into a bird</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bruchlandung</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40675" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バックにいさんのネックレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother Buck`s necklace</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die bittere Wahrheit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40676" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">町から森へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From the town to the forest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schule fängt an</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40677" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まぼろしの隣の家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The elusive house next door</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der seltsame Gast</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40678" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢のなかの噴水</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Water fountain in a dream</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Heimweh</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40679" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エラリーに春の風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring breeze for Ellary</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bartneid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40680" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたとうもろこしor消えたとうもろこし畑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The disappeared corn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Neue Zäune - alte Träume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40681" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな冒険旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A little trip of adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nach dem Regen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40682" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">空かけるフォダウィング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fodawing flies the sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschied von einem Freund</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40683" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界一小さな教室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The world`s smallest classroom</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der kluge Tausch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40684" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あらしの中の三人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three in a storm</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Unwetter</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40685" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">十二匹の子熊or十二匹の小熊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twelve bearcubs</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der kleine Bär</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40686" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人になりたくない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I don`t want to become an adult</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wachsen tut weh</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40687" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならの汽笛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whistle of farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lebt wohl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40688" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消された贈りもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The erased gift</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Weihnachtseinkauf</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40689" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくたちは名付け親</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re godparents</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Stolze Paten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40690" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">家出犬ダッシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dash the runaway dog</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unter Wölfen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40691" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボストンだってアメリカだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boston`s part of America too</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine lange Reise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40692" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さなふたりの大学生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two little college students</title>
<title xml:lang="de">In der großen Stadt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40693" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二歳からの親友</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Best friends from the age of two</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alte Zeiten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40694" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">子鹿に会った日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The day I met a fawn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Kitz kommt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40695" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いたずらフラッグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischevious Flag</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Lauf der Dinge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40696" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出席をとられたフラッグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flag loses a seat</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Überraschender Besuch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40697" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボストン発フラッグゆきorボストン発フラッグ行き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Boston to Flag</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Heimreise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40698" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョディが荒馬に乗った日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The day Jodie rode a wild horse</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gezähmt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40699" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トゥインク先生馬にのる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mr Twink rides a horse</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Reitschule</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40700" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エラリーのベットorエラリーのペット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ellary`s bet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefährliche Spiele</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40701" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生き返りパーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome back to life party</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Ausreißer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40702" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくがあにきでおとうとで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m both big and little brother</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fleck hat Glück</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40703" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜空の太陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Midnight sun</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Große Pläne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40704" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">町からきた少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boy who came from town</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das große Abenteuer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40705" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の残されぼうず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two boys left behind</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Traurige Ferien</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40706" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハシカをありがとう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thanks for the measles</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freunde in Not</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40707" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">森の花嫁さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bride of the forest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Hochzeit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40708" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">瞳の中の水車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Water mill in the eye</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Familienzuwachs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40709" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よろこび二倍かなしみ半分</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twice the happiness, half the sadness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Worte, an die man denkt</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40710" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくのおとうと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My little brother</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wie ein kleiner Bruder</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40711" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イノシシ坊や</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boar boy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freunde für einen Tag</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40712" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1983-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨の日が日曜日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sundays are rainy days</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Regentage und Sonnentage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40713" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">十一才の老犬or十一歳の老犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eleven-year-old dog</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jody und Julia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40714" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フォダウィングの贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fodawing`s gift</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Entweder - Oder</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40715" update="2006-02-16">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボストンからの宿題</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homework from Boston</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Einladung</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
