<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3667" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>20</episodecount>
<startdate>1985-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>1985-10-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Honoo no Alpenrose: Jeudi &amp; Lundi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Flaming Alpen Rose: Jeudi &amp; Lundi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Honoo no Alpen Rose: Judy &amp; Randy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hono no Alpenrose Judy &amp; Landy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hono no Alpenrose Jeudi &amp; Lundi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">炎のアルペンローゼ ジュディ&amp;ランディ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Alpenrose of Fire Judy and Randy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Julie et Stéphane</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Alpenrose</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">زهرة الجبل</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8559" type="Summary">Dramatic Memory Honoo no Alpenrose</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/alpine_rose.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="830" type="Work">Tatsunoko Production</name>
<name id="3008" type="Character Design">Takada Akemi</name>
<name id="2119" type="Series Composition">Tomita Sukehiro</name>
<name id="4289" type="Chief Direction">Ueda Hidehito</name>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
<name id="11221" type="Original Work">Akaishi Michiyo</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the same-titled shojo manga by http://anidb.net/cr11221 [Akaishi Michiyo]. Manga published by Shogakukan Flower Comics in 8 volumes.
While Randy was walking through the Swiss countryside he finds a small girl, who seemed to be the only survived person from an airplane crash. The little girl didn`t remember anything, and Randy decided to take care of her and he called her Judy. The both go their childhood together. A few years later, Judy, now 16 years old, wants to find her past. With the help of Randy, she leaves to research her origins. Her single clue is a song that she keeps hearing in her head, the song is called Alpine Rose. At a time of world war, these two young people will have to overcome many obstacles to arrive at their goal in this time of war, with having only each other to comfort and support. the depth of their love.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="49">5.67</permanent>
<temporary count="49">6.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204618.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1960</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35628</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3807</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>35627</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2064</identifier>
<identifier>cbjjmm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/alpine_rose.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Alpen_Rose</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アルペンローゼ_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89268</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1217</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2691" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-21">
<name>World War II</name>
<description>World War II, or the Second World War (often abbreviated WWII or WW2), was a global military conflict which involved most of the world`s nations, including all great powers, organised into two opposing military alliances: the Allies and the Axis. The war involved the mobilisation of over 100 million military personnel, making it the most widespread war in history. In a state of "total war," the major participants placed their entire economic, industrial, and scientific capabilities at the service of the war effort, erasing the distinction between civilian and military resources. Over seventy million people, the majority civilians, were killed, making it the deadliest conflict in human history.
The start of the war is generally held to be September 1, 1939, with the invasion of Poland by Nazi Germany and subsequent declarations of war on Germany by most of the countries in the British Empire and Commonwealth, and by France. Many countries were already at war before this date, such as Ethiopia and Italy in the Second Italo-Abyssinian War and China and Japan in the Second Sino-Japanese War. Many who were not initially involved joined the war later, as a result of events such as the German invasion of the Soviet Union, the attacks on Pearl Harbor and British colonies, and subsequent declarations of war on Japan by the United States, the Netherlands, and British Commonwealth.
In 1945, the war ended in a victory for the Allies. The Soviet Union and the United States subsequently emerged as the world`s superpowers, setting the stage for the Cold War which continued for the next 46 years. The United Nations was formed in the hope of preventing another world conflict. The acceptance of the principle of self-determination accelerated decolonization movements in Asia and Africa, while Western Europe itself began moving toward integration.
------
About the picture
Top left: Battle of Wuhan
Top right: Second Battle of El Alamein
Middle left: Battle of Stalingrad
Middle right: German dive bombers over Eastern Front winter 1943-1944
Bottom left: Wilhelm Keitel signing German Instrument of Surrender
Bottom right: Invasion of Lingayen Gulf</description>
<picurl>40430.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4691" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-08">
<name>Switzerland</name>
<description>Switzerland, officially the Swiss Confederation is a federal republic in Europe. While still named the "Swiss Confederation" for historical reasons, modern Switzerland is a federal directorial republic consisting of 26 cantons, with Bern as the seat of the federal authorities, called "federal city". The country is situated in Western-Central Europe, and is bordered by Italy to the south, France to the west, Germany to the north, and Austria and Liechtenstein to the east. Switzerland is a landlocked country geographically divided between the Alps, the Swiss Plateau and the Jura, spanning an area of 41,285 km². While the Alps occupy the greater part of the territory, the Swiss population of approximately eight million people is concentrated mostly on the plateau, where the largest cities are to be found: among them are the two global and economic centres Zürich and Geneva.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192470.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31110" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Katarina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31111" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Gourmont</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31112" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<rating votes="2">8.36</rating>
<name>Jeudi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jeudi (which means Thursday in French) is a girl who was separated from her family after an accident with no memory of her past except for her pet Pompom and a song.With Lundi, she seeks to find her family.</description>
<picture>69650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31113" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Francoise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5058" picture="43359.jpg">Yoshida Rihoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31114" type="main character in" update="2019-07-15">
<rating votes="2">8.36</rating>
<name>Lundi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lundi (which means Monday in French) is a boy who met Julie as a young child and is madly in love with her; he will do anything to protect her.</description>
<picture>69651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31115" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Duvau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3246" picture="215972.jpg">Ueda Toshiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109005" type="appears in" update="2020-04-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Martha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68732.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109006" type="appears in" update="2020-04-02">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Klara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68733.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="9582" picture="219362.jpg">Yokozawa Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109007" type="appears in" update="2020-04-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Hans</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68734.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109008" type="appears in" update="2020-04-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Henri Guisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68735.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="47" picture="16638.jpg">Oohira Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109009" type="appears in" update="2020-04-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Liesel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68736.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6819" picture="173758.jpg">Sasaki Run</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109145" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Robert Lewis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68756.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109146" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<name>Johann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68757.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109506" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-17">
<name>Leonhardt Aschenbach</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68848.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109507" type="appears in" update="2020-04-17">
<name>Heinrich Graf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68849.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109508" type="appears in" update="2020-04-17">
<name>Schleicher</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68850.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4478" picture="26750.jpg">Matsuoka Fumio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109509" type="appears in" update="2020-04-17">
<name>Bormann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68851.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109521" type="appears in" update="2020-04-18">
<name>Marie Muller</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68853.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="8092" picture="32723.jpg">Takahashi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109522" type="appears in" update="2020-04-18">
<name>Muller</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68854.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109523" type="appears in" update="2020-04-18">
<name>Jid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68855.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="8058" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109524" type="appears in" update="2020-04-18">
<name>Zug</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68856.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109541" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Friedrich Brendel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68861.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3371" picture="24398.jpg">Nakamura Shuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109543" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68864.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5073" picture="33047.jpg">Sasaki Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109546" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Christine Dunant</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68865.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="109547" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Jacques Dunant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68866.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109549" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Helene Brendel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68867.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23935" picture="67085.jpg">Munakata Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109550" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Michel Toulonchamp</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68868.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109551" type="appears in" update="2020-04-19">
<name>Matilda Toulonchamp</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68869.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2055" picture="21393.jpg">Shimazu Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109717" type="appears in" update="2020-04-25">
<name>Edita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68887.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109723" type="appears in" update="2020-04-25">
<name>Hans</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68888.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12580" picture="222815.jpg">Chijimatsu Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="72511" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛・激流への序章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand départ</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72512" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢のつばさを広げて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les aîles du rêve</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72513" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自由に向けられた銃口</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La liberté</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72514" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の歌が霧の中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un chant d`amour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72515" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パリの殺人鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un crime monstrueux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72516" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃がし屋ハンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une aide précieuse</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72517" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりぽっちのピアノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le piano brisé</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72518" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">安らぎにさようなら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les adieux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72519" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聞かせてよ愛の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La forteresse inébranlable</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72520" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人のアリシア!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une autre Alicia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72521" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えつきた野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ambition</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72522" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶は別れの朝に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les souvenirs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72523" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">剣の騎士ランディ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chevalier au sabre</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72524" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華麗なる逃亡者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fuite éperdue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72525" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">響け! 祖国の空へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chant du courage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72526" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤いバラの旋律</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rose rouge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72527" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去を秘めた花園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jardin qui connaît le passé</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72528" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秒きざみのワナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le piège imminent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72529" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汽笛は死を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un torrent de larmes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72530" update="2010-01-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光の中の天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cadeau merveilleux</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88279" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95648" update="2008-12-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120278" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126467" update="2010-12-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video: The Symphony of Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126468" update="2010-12-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video: The Sweet Memory</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
