<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3672" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-09-30</startdate>
<enddate>1993-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Oyayubi Hime Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">おやゆび姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Thumb Princess Story</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Story of Princess Thumbelina</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Nowe Przygody Calineczki</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="synonym">H Τοσοδούλα</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Oyayubi Hime</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">おやゆび姫物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Thumbelina</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Däumelinchens Reise</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Calineczka</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مايا رحلة الأحلام</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">O Livro de Thumbelina</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Peukaloliisa ihmemaassa</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Hüvelyk Panna nyomában</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2227" type="Other">Sekai Meisaku Douwa: Oyayubi Hime</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="21301" type="Character Design">Morino Usagi</name>
<name id="4249" type="Series Composition">Sakai Akiyoshi</name>
<name id="6754" type="Work">Enoki Films</name>
<name id="6648" type="Work">Enoki Yoshinori</name>
<name id="5511" type="Direction">Morita Hiromitsu</name>
<name id="6294" type="Original Work">Hans Christian Andersen</name>
<name id="49270" type="Work">Meruhensha</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on Thumbelina by http://anidb.net/cr6294 [Hans Christian Andersen].
A bratty girl named Mia is given a book, Thumbelina, which upon reading she is shrunk and transported into the world of the book. She embarks on a journey to return home, and to normal size making friends and learning lessons on the way, but that`s only the beginning of her adventures.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="24">3.40</permanent>
<temporary count="24">5.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5404.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1754</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2783</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2198</identifier>
<identifier>ulfsto</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Thumbelina:_A_Magical_Story</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>おやゆび姫物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89077</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="78397" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ママ, 目を覚まして!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Reise ins Land der Träume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78398" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さようならハッピーツリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Glücksbaum</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78399" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傘の下の不思議な町</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Stadt unter dem Regenschirm</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78400" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれ, 弱虫ビリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Käferbande</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78401" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カエルの花嫁さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Froschbraut</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78402" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法城のママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Zauberschloß</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78403" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーヤ, 空飛ぶ船にのる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jan, der Schneeforscher</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78404" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノゾミテタウンへようこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Land der Wünsche</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78405" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の魔術師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der geheimnisvolle Zauberer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78406" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蜃気楼の燈台</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Annes Leuchtturm</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78407" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーヤと魔法の時計</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die magische Uhr</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78408" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">南の国の水晶王子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Maya und der Schattenprinz</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78409" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">花と光のドラゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der kleine Lichtdrache</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78410" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女神になったマーヤ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Waldkönigin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78411" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">懐かしい再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zwei dicke Freunde</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78412" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モグラトンネルの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Maulwurfslabyrinth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78413" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">だまされたプロポーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Erpressung</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78414" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーヤの結婚式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Maulwurfsbraut</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78415" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三人の旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bei den Eulen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78416" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホタルの岬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Pikari, der Leuchtkäfer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78417" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡の入江とハンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Spiegelmeer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78418" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水晶城の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Prinz im Glaspalast</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78419" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目が覚めたの, ママ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Maya zwischen zwei Welten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78420" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">この河は渡らせない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Flußgeist</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78421" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘルーラ最後の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fast am Ziel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78422" update="2007-06-30">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1993-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただいま, ママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Glückliche Reise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134091" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Compilation Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
