<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3684" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rakugo Tennyo Oyui</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magical Travelers</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">落语天女</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">落語天女おゆい</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.rakugo-tennyo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="794" type="Animation Work">TNK</name>
<name id="3779" type="Character Design">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="1536" type="Direction">Takamoto Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="22949" type="Original Work">Katsura Utawaka</name>
<name id="6741" type="Series Composition">Yoritsune Kouji</name>
<name id="3779" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="6673" type="Music">Ichikawa Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>Six girls including http://anidb.net/ch43235 [Tsukishima Yui] were summoned into the end of Edo period by the power of mystic stones. They became celestial nymphs to protect cities from evils. Each girl obtained her own power. The power Yui obtained was word. She would fight against evils by her words that gave people hope.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="106">3.98</permanent>
<temporary count="107">6.16</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>10084.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2244</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3482</identifier>
<identifier>virxom</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rakugo-tennyo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rakugo_Tennyo_Oyui</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>落語天女おゆい</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324475</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7917</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2060" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-20">
<name>rakugoka</name>
<description>Rakugo (literally "fallen words") is a Japanese verbal entertainment. The lone storyteller (rakugoka) sits on the stage, called the Kouza. Using only a paper fan and a small cloth as props, and without standing up from the seiza sitting position, the rakugo artist depicts a long and complicated comical story. The story always involves the dialogue of two or more characters, the difference between the characters depicted only through change in pitch, tone, and a slight turn of the head.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2690" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Tokugawa period</name>
<description>The anime takes place during a period of Japanese history running from 1603 to 1868.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="43235" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Tsukishima Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43236" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Kotodama Tennyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43237" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Asukayama Miyabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43242" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Kotodama Tennyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43243" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Yanaka Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43245" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Kagura Tennyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43246" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Koishikawa Suzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43247" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Keiryaku Tennyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43248" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Sengoku Ryou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43249" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Kenkaku Tennyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43250" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Naitou Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43251" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Karakuri Tennyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43252" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Sanyuutei Enchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3142.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43253" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Hiraga Gennai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3147.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43254" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Kotsukahara Sakyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3148.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43255" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Kotsukahara Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3157.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43256" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Katsura Utamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34091" picture="94714.jpg">Katsura Utamaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43257" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Katsura Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="58346" picture="236941.jpg">Kanda Kurenai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43258" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Ponta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3793" picture="44861.jpg">Kojima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43259" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Ponta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85309.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43260" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Ogin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3160.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43262" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Ohisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3184.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="43263" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Ohana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3186.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="43264" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Osetsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3189.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="43265" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Osaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3191.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="43266" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Onatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3194.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="43269" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Eigo Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4628" picture="224317.jpg">Kobayashi Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43271" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Shitsuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3965" picture="25836.jpg">Souya Shigenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43272" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Sanyuutei Koyuuza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52344" picture="208898.jpg">Sanyuutei Koyuuza</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="45735" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華のお江戸に天女舞う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Celestal Dance at the Edo of Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana no Edo ni Tennyo Mau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45890" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園祭で唯, 反省!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui at the School Festival, Reflection!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuensai de Yui, Hansei!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46573" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ! 唯 妖魔を倒せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run! Yui, Defeat the Ghost!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire! Yui, Youma o Taose!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46574" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">落語天女おゆい登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story-telling Celestial Maiden Oyui On Stage!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakugo Tennyo Oyui Toujou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46575" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おーっほほほ! 落語天女みやび登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oooohohoho! Story-telling Celestial Maiden Miyabi On Stage!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oooohohoho! Rakugo Tennyo Miyabi Toujou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46712" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の行方 それぞれの覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Yukue, Sorezore no Kakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47508" update="2006-05-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼, 覚醒! 決闘! 高田馬場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryou, Kakusei! Kettou! Takadanobaba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47509" update="2006-05-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の行方ふたたび 江戸湾大決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Missing Love Once Again! Edo Bay`s Final Showdown!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Yukue Futatabi! Edo Wan Dai Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47510" update="2006-05-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒衣の花嫁 明かされる秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokui no Hanayome, Akasareru Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47511" update="2006-05-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖魔軍侵攻! 火事と天女は江戸の華!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion of the Ghost Army! Fire and Celestial Maidens are The Flowers of Edo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youmagun Shinkou! Kaji to Tennyo wa Edo no Hana!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47741" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の戦い 失われる命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Battle, Lost Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Tatakai, Ushinawareru Inochi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48325" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じる言葉 ふれあう心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Believing Words, Touching Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjiru Kotoba, Fureau Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91135" update="2008-05-31">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91136" update="2008-05-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
