<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3705" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-12-17</startdate>
<enddate>2007-02-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saint Seiya: Meiou Hades Meikai Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Los Caballeros del Zodiaco - Saga de Hades - Infierno</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">圣斗士星矢 冥界篇</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">圣斗士星矢 冥王哈迪斯冥界篇</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖闘士星矢 冥王ハーデス冥界編</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Saint Seiya: The Hades - Chapter Inferno</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Saint Seiya: The Hades Chapter - Inferno</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Os Cavaleiros do Zodíaco - Hades: A Saga do Inferno</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5670" type="Sequel">Saint Seiya: Meiou Hades Elysion Hen</anime>
<anime id="343" type="Prequel">Saint Seiya: Meiou Hades Juuni Kyuu Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="177141">This is certainly a must see to all the Saint Seiya fans, not the best arc of the manga series, but it was worth waiting for the anime convertion of the greatly expected 2nd part (of 3) of the Finale.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/sp/seiya_zenshou/index2.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="1833" type="Direction">Katsumata Tomoharu</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="867" type="Original Work">Kurumada Masami</name>
<name id="4116" type="Character Design">Araki Shingo</name>
<name id="4248" type="Character Design">Himeno Michi</name>
<name id="4116" type="Chief Animation Direction">Araki Shingo</name>
<name id="4248" type="Chief Animation Direction">Himeno Michi</name>
<name id="4295" type="Music">Yokoyama Seiji</name>
</creators>
<description>Seiya and the rest of the Bronze and Gold Saints who have survived the Sanctuary battle have entered the world of the Dead. They are fighting to get to Athena and give her Athena`s Cloth for the upcomming battle with Hades!
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="752">5.88</permanent>
<temporary count="770">7.29</temporary>
<review count="1">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10148.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35326</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3494</identifier>
<identifier>ipxnso</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/sp/seiya_koushou/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/sp/seiya_zenshou/index2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖闘士星矢_冥王ハーデス編</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2448</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323754</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7693</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="29" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-18">
<name>Western zodiac</name>
<picurl>161118.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10499" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="20">8.53</rating>
<name>Libra no Douko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Libra Douko is the Libra Gold Saint in Lost Canvas. He shows signs of slight rashness and immaturity, and has big respect for his partners, turning pretty furious if they are in danger. However, in these occasions, he does not quite concern about consequences. He is a good friend of Aries Shion and Taurus Aldebaran to whom he often talks to and sometimes say his way of thinking is thanks to them.</description>
<picture>31481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10544" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="29">7.93</rating>
<name>Aries no Muu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Under the tutelage of Shion, the Pope of the Sanctuary, Muu was able to become the Gold Saint of Aries at a young age. While all gold saints have a base of psychic powers to some degree, Muu has been stated to possess the strongest raw psychic talent among all living gold saints. This allows him to manipulate his gift to various degrees: psychokinesis, telepathy, teleportation, and various other powers are at his command.
Muu is very soft spoken, with a scholarly-like personality; his demeanor is very tranquil and logical, almost as if he is a professor of the Sanctuary. He is good friends with Taurus Aldebaran, and is very respectful to the 243 year old master Libra Douko.</description>
<picture>31552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10553" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<name>Taurus no Aldebaran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aldebaran is one of the 12 Guardians of Sanctuary, with the Taurus as his destined constellation. He was the physically strongest of the Gold Saints of modern era. He is Brazilian in origin.
Unlike most of the characters, Aldebaran is often depicted as a friendly guy, laughing and being less serious in times of peace. He was a good friend of Aries Mu, and with Pegasus Seiya (as this last is said in the anime adaptation of the Hades Saga, when Aldebaran sacrificed himself with the other eleven Gold Saints to destroy the Wailing Wall).</description>
<picture>31560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17684" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="11">5.91</rating>
<name>Virgo no Shaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although Gemini Saga and Leo Aiolia were the first Gold Saints introduced by Masami Kurumada in his manga, Virgo Shaka was the first one he showed fully revealing his status as Gold Saint and wearing his Gold Cloth, in the chapter 18, contained in vol. 5.
Shaka is one of the Twelve Gold Saints. As the guardian of the Temple of Virgo along the path of Sanctuary, Shaka has played a pivotal role chiefly in the battle between Athena and the Pope in the Sanctuary arc, and also in the Hades arc. He is referred to many times on the story as the "the man who is almost a god" due to his immense power and is also considered the only Gold Saint that has full control over the Araya Shiki (8th sense). He is supposed to be Buddha`s reincarnation.
Shaka alone of all saints occupies the rarefied spot between God and man, but living between two worlds has its blessings as well as curses. As a Bodhisattva, and endowed with the most powerful cosmos of all the saints, Shaka well deserves his reputation as the man closest to God. Even as a child in India, Shaka was precocious and communed with God himself—a scene recounted in the flashbacks moments before Shaka`s death in the Twin Sala`s Garden. For someone whose life has just begun, he had been unusually sensitive to sufferings and mortality of human life. Seeing pain and death as reflected in the Ganges gives the boy Shaka enough despair, if not a crisis of faith. With esoteric learning and training, Shaka eventually became powerful enough to don the Gold Cloth of Virgo, which he wore even as a boy in the manga, and wise enough to rise above human passions and attachments. For most of his life, he would look on human feelings with a mix of pity and compassion without being bound to them, with charity but not always with love. Detachment seems to be Shaka`s answer to the poignant questions raised by human life, and he is seeing humanity from the point of God rather than living the experience. He would be disabused of this attitude in his encounter with Ikki. In the end, Shaka would have to remember that he is a man, as well, and return to whence he came.</description>
<picture>48026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17687" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="7">5.72</rating>
<name>Gemini no Kanon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanon is a character with a substantial importance in the universe of Kurumada`s manga, and therefore in its anime adaptation. He is directly responsible for triggering two main events : the conflict of the 12 temples by inciting Gemini Saga to succumb to his evil desires, and the resurrection of Poseidon, Emperor of the Seas. Also, Kanon is notable for redeeming himself after all his sins in the past and wreaking havoc as the Gemini Gold Saint in the army of Hades` 108 [[Specters.
Kanon is the younger twin brother of Gold Saint Gemini Saga, and later took up his position as a Gold Saint after Saga`s death. Before finally embracing his destiny as the Gemini Saint, Kanon masqueraded as the Sea Dragon General of the North Atlantic, one of Poseidon`s seven Sea Generals. At first, Kanon was depicted as a treacherous man, always tempting his twin brother to use his status and power to advance his status of influence beyond that of a Gold Saint. He concluded that their amazing and powerful abilities were gifts from the Gods for them to take advantage of. Much to his dismay, his brother opposed this and caused his incarceration at Cape Sounion. After his redemption, however, Kanon becomes a much centered person, much like his brother.
Kanon was the one person responsible for Poseidon`s awakening, although he kept Poseidon just half awakened so that he could pose as the true leader of the Marines as a Marine General and use Poseidon`s army to achieve his desires. In order to do so, Kanon stole the scales of Sea Dragon and pretended to be the Sea Dragon General under Poseidon`s order. Even after joining forces with the Athena, Kanon retains his ruthless personality and harsh characteristics, scolding Pegasus Seiya and Andromeda Shun that they should never hesitate to finish their enemies, because their hesitation was a weakness that their enemies would take advantage of. Even so, he quickly absorbs the honor of a Gold Saint.</description>
<picture>48027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30885" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="73">6.82</rating>
<name>Pegasus no Seiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33220" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="93">7.06</rating>
<name>Andromeda Seiza no Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12421" picture="78914.jpg">Kasuya Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33221" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="54">6.26</rating>
<name>Cygnus no Hyouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="552" picture="23199.jpg">Miura Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33222" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="82">8.28</rating>
<name>Dragon no Shiryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33223" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="74">8.27</rating>
<name>Phoenix no Ikki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33224" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="93">7.58</rating>
<name>Kido Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33232" type="appears in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="10">4.38</rating>
<name>Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miho is Seiya`s best friend, she works at an orphanage, which is the same one where Seiya and his sister Seika lived before Seiya was taken away. Apparently she`s in love with Seiya to some degree, and in a sense represents the point of view of the normal people who are mere witnesses to the struggle between the Gods.</description>
<picture>73104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33496" picture="91130.jpg">Ookoshi Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33473" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="9">6.27</rating>
<name>Eagle no Marin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1624.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36508" picture="171390.jpg">Inoue Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33474" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="11">9.73</rating>
<name>Gold Saints</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The most powerful Saints in Athena`s Army and personal guard to her, invincible among them since the ages of myth. They wear the 12 Gold Cloths that correspond to the zodiac constellations, the most powerful among the 88 Cloths. The Gold Saints have mastered the seventh sense, the essence of Cosmo, which grants them miraculous abilities, among them, the capacity of attaining the speed of light.</description>
<picture>73617.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33475" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="23">8.46</rating>
<name>Bronze Saints</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>73618.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33481" type="appears in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Hydra no Ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hydra Ichi was like the other Bronze Saints that participated in the Galaxian Wars a fellow orphan. His and the other Bronze Saint`s father Mitsumasa Kido was the founder of the Graud foundation. After being taken from the orphanage by Mitsumasa he was sent out to train in Finland to become a Saint of Athena. He came back years later to participate in the Galaxian Wars that were now held by Mitsumasa`s adopted granddaughter Saori Kido. In his first match Ichi had to battle Cygnus Hyouga. The Hydra Saint underestimated his opponent who froze him to near death. Ashamed by his defeat, he asked Saori for permission to undergo further training in Finland with his master. She agreed and thus Ichi didn`t reappear until Saori was put in danger in Sanctuary after being struck by a golden arrow. From then on, he served her as Athena and came to reside in Sanctuary. Later he protected Sanctuary from the revived Saints, and protected Pegasus Seiya`s sister from the death god Thanatos.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>73625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33483" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="4">8.05</rating>
<name>Unicorn no Jabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second Bronze Saint to appear in the story was Jabu the Unicorn Saint. As a fellow orphan he had been sent out with 99 more of his brothers by their father Mitsumasa Kido. He achieved the Unicorn Cloth in Algeria and returned to Japan to participate in the Galaxian Wars tournament to receive the Gold Cloth of Sagittarius. He easily defeated Lionet Ban in his first match but was outmatched against Andromeda Shun whose chains proved impenetrable. He returned to his master in Algeria to further his training, and during this time his Cloth came to upgrade itself as well. When Saori Kido had been shot by a golden arrow, he came to her rescue and protected her from the then antagonistic forces of the Sanctuary. After that he came to reside in the Sanctuary and protected it against the Saints Hades had revived, and protected Pegasus Seiya`s sister Seika from the attacks of the god of death.</description>
<picture>73627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33484" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<name>Wolf no Nachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nachi is one of the 100 orphans that were brought into the Graud Foundation to fulfill a project: to be trained to become future Saints for the goddess Athena. Only 10 of the children survived the entire process, and they grew up to become Bronze Saints. In the Galaxy Wars arc, Nachi loses the tournament and decides to return to Liberia to continue his training, later returning with the other four Bronze Saints to rescue Tatsumi and the comatose Athena. They stay with them until Gold Saint Gemini Saga, the false Pope of Sanctuary, is defeated. In the Hades arc, Nachi and Ichi are appointed commanders over the Sanctuary guards. As the dead Silver Saints start appearing and they realize their attacks are useless, they are saved by the timely appearance of Jabu. Later Nachi risks his life to protect Seika from Thanatos.</description>
<picture>73628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10401" picture="38335.jpg">Kojima Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43807" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">6.50</rating>
<name>Ophiuchus no Shaina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A temperamental but courageous female Silver Saint, Athena`s prohibition of women becoming Saints demanded of Shaina to abandon her femininity when starting her training as a Saint and forever hide her face from men. Shaina was mentor to Pegasus Seiya`s rival Cassios, whose defeat seemingly caused Shaina to bear a grudge against Seiya. At first, Shaina served the false Pope of Sanctuary, as she was determined to take Seiya`s life for the humiliation she caused her, but later, suspicion towards him grew in her, which led her to side with the Bronze Saints in their rebellion against Sanctuary. Shaina saved Seiya`s life from Leo Aiolia, sent by the Pope to kill him; being gravely wounded herself, she revealed that her grudge derived not from the fact that Seiya defeated Cassios, but because Seiya was the first man to ever see Shaina`s face, the worst offence against a female Saint. Rigid tradition forced female Saints to either of two choices: either kill the offender or fall in love with him, Shaina unwillingly choosing the latter. Convalescing during the conflict of the twelve temples, Shaina is shocked to learn about her pupil Cassios` death to save Seiya`s life, to spare her from grieving. Shaina then saves Eagle Marin`s life, who moments before had saved Seiya`s in the funeral roses stairway. After the false Pope is defeated, Shaina pledges her loyalty to Athena. Despite her love towards Seiya being unrequited, during the battle against Poseidon, Shaina is instrumental in the victory of Athena`s army, being sent by Libra Roushi to bring the Bronze Saints the imprescindible Libra Gold Cloth and going as far as to challenge Poseidon herself, but suffering defeat. Mere weeks later, Shaina leads the Bronze Saints and the rankless soldiers of Sanctuary in the protection of the surroundings, after the invasion of Hades` army. In the climax of the battle against Underworld, Shaina valiantly risks her life to protect Seiya`s sister Seika from the assault of the merciless Thanatos.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>86506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2801" picture="23195.jpg">Komatsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43864" type="appears in" update="2012-04-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Kiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Apprentice under Aries Mu. Also known as Appendix Kiki. Like his master and grandmaster, Kiki also bears the ornaments on his forehead and is the youngest of the people of the continent of Mu. He never fights, but can use powerful telekinesis against normal humans. In the Poseidon arc, he was given the duty of bringing the Libra Cloth to all the Bronze Saints, fulfilling it valiantly even at the risk of his life.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>86602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2987" picture="23718.jpg">Shouji Umeka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48982" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-18">
<rating votes="4">4.49</rating>
<name>Pandora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48983" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-18">
<rating votes="6">4.41</rating>
<name>Tenmousei Wyvern Rhadamanthys</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49009" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<rating votes="3">9.84</rating>
<name>Specters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>94364.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="87991" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-02">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Lyra no Orphee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64818.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87992" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-02">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Sphinx no Pharaoh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64819.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87993" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-02">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Balron no Lune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64820.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87994" type="appears in" update="2017-03-02">
<name>Acheron no Charon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64821.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87995" type="appears in" update="2017-03-02">
<name>Skeleton no Markino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87996" type="appears in" update="2017-03-02">
<name>Eurydice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64822.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88003" type="appears in" update="2017-03-03">
<name>Golem no Rock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2401" picture="23194.jpg">Kawazu Yasuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88004" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-03">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Ten`yuusei Garuda no Aiacos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88005" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-03">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Tenkisei Griffon no Minos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88021" type="appears in" update="2017-03-03">
<name>Lycaon no Phlegyas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88022" type="appears in" update="2017-03-03">
<name>Deadly Beetle no Stand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88052" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Harpy no Valentine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107858" type="appears in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Tenrousei Minotauros no Gordon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242826.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107864" type="appears in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Tenmasei Alraune no Queen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107867" type="appears in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Tenshousei Basilisk no Sylphid</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="42941" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渡れ! アケローンの河</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross Over! Acheron River</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Atravesadlo! El río Aqueronte</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Atravessem! O Rio Aqueronte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watare! Acheron no Kawa</title>
<summary>Shiryū, Shun, and Hyōga meet Dohko at the entrance to the pit where Seiya and Radamanthys fell. Saint of Libra tells them they must awaken their Eighth Sense in order to enter the world of the dead without getting killed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42942" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静かなる法廷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Courtroom Becomes Silent</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El tribunal silencioso</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Tribunal Silencioso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizukanaru Houtei</title>
<summary>Seiya and Shun come to the courthouse and accidentally upset a soldier.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42943" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の聖闘士オルフェ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary Saint Orpheus</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Orfeo! El caballero legendario</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Santo lendário, Orfeu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Saint Orpheus</title>
<summary>Seiya and Shun leave the Valley of Air and run in the rain as they encounter an Egyptian building. Suddenly, the smell of death reaches them and they discover a three-headed monster that eats the dead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42946" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルフェ 悲しき鎮魂歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orpheus, The Sad Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Orfeo, el réquiem trágico</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Orfeu, o Triste Réquiem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orpheus Kanashiki Chinkonka</title>
<summary>Orpheus plays the strings of his lyre. Pharaoh loses control of his hand and drops the armor of Athena, which Seiya collects.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42947" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハーデス! 驚愕の憑依</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hades! A Surprising Possession</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Hades! La posesión sorprendente</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Hades! Uma Possessão Surpreendente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hades! Kyougaku no Hyoui</title>
<summary>Pandora tells Radamanthys to be silent, that they shouldn`t tell Hades everything that happens in the world of the dead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="42948" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! ジュデッカへの道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fierce Fighting! Road to Giudecca</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Combate encarnizado! Camino de Judeca</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Combate Intenso! O Caminho para Giudecca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Giudecca e no Michi</title>
<summary>Hyōga and Shiryū wake after crossing the Fourth Prison, but they don`t see Kanon, deducing that they must continue with the mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65852" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神罰! グレイテスト エクリップス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Divine Punishment! Greatest Eclipse</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Castigo divino! El último eclipse</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Punição Divina! O Grande Eclipse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinbatsu! Greatest Eclipse</title>
<summary>Garuda hits Ikki, deciding to use his most powerful technique: Galactic Illusion.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="65994" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一輝! 慟哭の拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikki! The Blow of the Moan</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Ikki! El puño de la lamentación</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ikki! O Punho da Lamentação</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikki! Doukoku no Ken</title>
<summary>Shun tells his brother to kill Hades no matter what.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="66974" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女神! その命をかけて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goddess! Gamble with Life</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Atenea! Arriesga su propia vida</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Atena! Arriscando sua Vida</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Athena! Sono Inochi o Kakete</title>
<summary>In Cociytos, Seiya is hit by Valentine but doesn`t let go of Athena’s armor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="66992" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望! 嘆きの壁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperation! The Wailing Wall</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Desesperación! El muro de las lamentaciones</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Desespero! O Muro das Lamentações</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou! Nageki no Kabe</title>
<summary>Seiya is unconscious in Cocytos, but is animated by Marin from his unconsciousness and is encouraged to proceed to Athena.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67684" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結! 黄金聖衣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assemble! The Gold Clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Reunión! Las armaduras de oro</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Reunidas! As Vestes de Ouro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu! Gold Cloth</title>
<summary>The five Golden Knights ignite their cosmos, throwing everything against the Wailing Wall but the wall returns everything back to them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67685" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば! 黄金の聖闘士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell! Gold Saints</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Adiós! Caballeros de oro</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Adeus! Santos Dourados</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba! Ougon no Saint</title>
<summary>The Golden Knights: Death Mask of Cancer, Saga of Gemini, Shura of Capricorn, Aiolos of Sagittarius, Aldebaran of Taurus, Aphrodite of Piscesm, and Camus of Aquarius appear before their peers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129025" update="2011-03-26">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129026" update="2011-03-26">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129027" update="2011-03-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131945" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (12)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131946" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (11)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131947" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (10)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131948" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (9)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131949" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (8)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131950" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (7)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131951" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (6)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131952" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (5)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131953" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (4)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131954" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (3)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131955" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131956" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (1)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131957" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening (7-12)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131958" update="2011-07-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening (1-6)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
