<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3706" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-12-09</startdate>
<enddate>2006-06-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">I``s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アイズピュア</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">I``s OVA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">I``s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">I``s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">I``s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">I``s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">I``S</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">I``s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">I"s Pure</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">I"s Pure</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="404" type="Side Story">From I``s: Mou Hitotsu no Natsu no Monogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9751" approval="1" total="5">Kimi no Iru Machi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://www.a-rms.co.jp/works/ispure.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="724" type="Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="866" type="Original Work">Katsura Masakazu</name>
<name id="3063" type="Character Design">Rin Sin</name>
<name id="1405" type="Direction">Kanbe Mamoru</name>
<name id="771" type="Animation Work">Arms</name>
<name id="8195" type="Music">Konishi Kayou</name>
<name id="8198" type="Music">Kondou Yukio</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch2963 [Seto Ichitaka] has a crush on http://anidb.net/ch2964 [Yoshizuki Iori], a girl in his class who has become so popular she now has her own fan club at school. But only a miracle could make him be with her, since the day he first saw Iori-chan, Ichitaka has been too shy to even talk to her. This miracle happened and now he and Iori are working together on the Freshmen Welcoming Party. It seems that things start to look bright for Ichitaka, but then a special childhood friend visits...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1941">5.94</permanent>
<temporary count="1970">7.47</temporary>
<review count="1">9.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10733.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5896</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1235</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>811</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3489</identifier>
<identifier>gvnnwt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a-rms.co.jp/works/ispure.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>I"s#I.22s_Pure_OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>I"s#I.22s_Pure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323438</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7939</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7222" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-30">
<name>groping</name>
<description>Groping is the act of subjecting another person to unwanted sexual touching.</description>
<picurl>68310.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7238" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>attempted rape</name>
<description>Attempted rape is an unsuccessful attempt at http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape]. For AniDB purposes, generally an "unsuccessful" attempt is where both fellatio and penetration did not occur. Discretion should be applied on a case-by-case basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2963" type="main character in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="20">2.51</rating>
<name>Seto Ichitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seto Ichitaka has a generally shy and reserved nature, and, due to misfortunes with girls when he was younger, he has acquired a reflexively defensive posture when dealing with women. Thus, he`s prone to rude comments when it seems some people are just trying to help, and can place an emotional wall in front of himself when people ask about his feelings. Many complications get in the way of Ichitaka`s goal of being with Iori, such as amorous pursuits made towards him by other girls (notably Izumi, who can be seen as being the most assertive in showing her feelings). Regardless, he constantly thinks about Iori and it would seem he`d want nothing more than for her to be his girlfriend. Throughout the series he finds himself lost in daydreaming or imagination, and several times, he even drifts off right in front of Iori.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>87449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2027" picture="21353.jpg">Nomura Katsuhito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2964" type="main character in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="29">6.84</rating>
<name>Yoshizuki Iori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshizuki Iori was born March 21, 1981 (she is 16 years old as the series begins). Iori is prim, proper, and friendly, not to mention gorgeous. She`s a young lady who`s easy to like and get along with. This generally positive outlook is put to the test from the beginning of the series, which opens on a magazine article featuring Iori in a swimsuit spread. Suddenly, Iori`s the center of attention, and she finds it difficult to differentiate whether people (particularly men) like her for herself or her beauty.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>18600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2965" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="18">6.05</rating>
<name>Akiba Itsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akiba Itsuki is loud, reckless, and shameless, and seems to be a complete opposite of Iori, including her affinity towards wearing boyish clothing and having a short haircut. Itsuki and Ichitaka had been friends since grade school, with Itsuki (although a year younger) often being an emotional coach to Ichitaka, particularly with women. The two seemed to become closer than friends in their young life, a relationship that was suddenly interrupted when Itsuki moved away to America years before the series begins. Itsuki just as abruptly returns to Ichitaka`s life soon after the series starts, now a fully grown young lady, but still with real feelings for Ichitaka. But later in the series, she goes back to America to work with a world-renowned sculptor, and is further unseen. She occasionally appears in Ichitaka`s mind to scold him during his bouts of self-pity, though these manifestations are really Ichitaka`s subconscious trying to tell him something important.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>18602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="163" picture="25711.jpg">Nakase Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2966" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="5">6.48</rating>
<name>Isozaki Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>
Izumi Isozaki is two years younger than the other characters and is very much like Itsuki Akiba. However, she isn`t as shy in expressing her emotions, especially her love for Ichitaka Seto. In fact, she announces her love to pretty much everyone she knows. Also, she`s more daring and is quite superstitious when it comes to love. She constantly tails Seto, and on more than one occasion, had tried to seduce Seto to go to bed with her in order to prove her love. Izumi persists in attempting to obtain Seto`s love and says that she will try whatever it takes to get him to be with her. She is introduced half-way through the manga, where she meets Seto on the beach on their summer vacation, and after that, she discovers that they go to the same school. She falls for Seto after he defends her from her overly-aggressive boyfriend, and tricks him into going on dates throughout the series. She is determined that he is her soulmate, and she wants him to be her boyfriend.
Taken from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>18605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31333" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-17">
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<name>Teratani Yasuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichitaka`s best friend, helps him out quite a few times throughout the series.</description>
<picture>70094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42817" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37864" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="5">5.42</rating>
<name>ZET</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79735.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44460" type="appears in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>Seto Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichitaka`s mother.</description>
<picture>87444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44461" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="7">5.71</rating>
<name>Morisaki Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morisaki Yuuka is a classmate of Ichitaka/Iori`s, and along with Nami, is one of Iori`s closest friends. Though she doesn`t stand out too much among the rest of the group, she seems to be the only one that Iori can talk deeply to about her issues in life.</description>
<picture>87474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44462" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="3">1.05</rating>
<name>Samejima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Samejima is a former senior in Ichitaka`s high school, he is the main recurring villain. A sexual deviant who tries to take advantage of Iori.</description>
<picture>87446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2252" picture="223545.jpg">Naruse Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44463" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="6">5.55</rating>
<name>Tachiba Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nami is a classmate of Ichitaka, Iori, Teratani, and others, and is generally the mood-maker of the group whenever they are all together on a trip, school project, etc.</description>
<picture>87471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2249" picture="61951.jpg">Suzuki Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44464" type="appears in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Matsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsuo is a boy who tried to convince Iori to attend the beaty contest in a nearby high school in episode three.</description>
<picture>87448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4986" picture="188518.jpg">Yamanaka Masahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44485" type="appears in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="4">1.24</rating>
<name>Furukawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iori`s manager.</description>
<picture>87469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44486" type="appears in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Isai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isai is a owner of Isai Production for that Iori workes.</description>
<picture>87470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7007" picture="31995.jpg">Morozumi Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44487" type="appears in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Teratani no Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teratani`s brother.</description>
<picture>87473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12597" picture="223672.jpg">Miura Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44488" type="appears in" update="2012-05-08">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichitaka`s father.</description>
<picture>87472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3156" picture="76983.jpg">Sakaguchi Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="42981" update="2005-11-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I``s Pure Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45292" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au commencement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45313" update="2006-03-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="8">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichitaka`s Delusion Diary 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal des rêves humides d`Ichitaka 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46369" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">回想</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reminiscence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaisou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46696" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46881" update="2006-02-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="6">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichitaka`s Delusion Diary 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal des rêves humides d`Ichitaka 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47422" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目まい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vertigo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vertige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Memai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49162" update="2006-11-01">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichitaka`s Delusion Diary 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal des rêves humides d`Ichitaka 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50079" update="2006-11-01">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichitaka`s Delusion Diary 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal des rêves humides d`Ichitaka 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50305" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration d` amour</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Déclaration d`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50306" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一緒に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ensemble</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ensemble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issho ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52295" update="2006-11-01">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichitaka`s Delusion Diary 5</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le journal des rêves humides d`Ichitaka 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90840" update="2008-05-18">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Staff Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139476" update="2012-05-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162582" update="2014-09-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2005-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
