<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="372" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>1998-11-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Brain Powerd</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Brain Powered</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="short">BP</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブレンパワード</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Brain Powerd</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Brain Powerd</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2826" approval="7" total="9">Koukyoushihen: Eureka Seven</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="121683">One of the best mecha`s I`ve watched. And I don`t like mecha`s. It has a great story.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.brainpowered.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="147" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="7477" type="Character Design">Shigeta Atsushi</name>
<name id="6578" type="Main Design">Nagano Mamoru</name>
<name id="2743" type="Main Design">Inomata Mutsumi</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
</creators>
<description>In the not so distant future much of the earth has been submerged under the sea or destroyed by earthquakes. At the center of the turmoil is the mysterious Orphan. Orphan may or may not be the original cause of the cataclysms. Orphan`s goal is to raise a ship hidden deep beneath the sea to the surface, but doing so would result in the destruction of all humans except for the small number which are loyal to Orphan.
Orphan`s agents pilot mysterious mecha known as Grand Cheres, and search the world for mysterious, giant disks which occasionally appear, flying at high speeds and wrecking much of the countryside, or cities, when they hit the ground. After a dying disc almost kills Hime, a Brain Powerd is born from the disc. Brain Powerds are another type of Mecha, similar to but not the same as Grand Cheres.
Hime becomes the Brain Powerd`s pilot, forming a symbiotic relationship with the living mecha and joins an International Organization dedicated to stopping Orphan, or at the very least saving humanity should Orphan succeed.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="461">3.67</permanent>
<temporary count="465">6.13</temporary>
<review count="3">5.11</review>
</ratings>
<picture>152811.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>122</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1542</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>85</identifier>
<identifier>zgpvtb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.brainpowered.jp</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=132</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Brain_Powerd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブレンパワード</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90338</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1656</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4004" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>organic mecha</name>
<description>An organic mecha is a mecha that has organic tissue in its composition. The most prominent historical example is http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion].</description>
<picurl>224892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12375" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="3">9.63</rating>
<name>Utsumiya Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Utsumiya Hime is a young, teenage girl and the female lead character of the story. She comes into contact with an organic plate which later witnessed its revival into an Antibody, a Brain Powerd, and became its pilot. Supposedly she was chosen to become Orphan`s force of hope in giving understanding to its intention to move freely, which in the end she gave Orphan the meaning of life, like a seed growing to a garden of beauty.</description>
<picture>67710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3087" picture="23993.jpg">Murata Akino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12376" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Isami Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young, teenage boy and the male lead character of the story. A former Reclaimer, after a fateful encounter with Hime Utsumiya, Yuu decides to leave Orphan, escaping with a Brain Powerd. Despite the frictions between his family`s ambitions to discover more of Orphan`s nature and his own freedom, Yuu understands the value of keeping life precious and the memories that would cherish in his life. He has lone wolf tendencies, often going off on his own for unofficial missions or just sitting on deck staring at the sky without the company of others.</description>
<picture>67699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12377" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Jonathan Glenn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Reclaimer at Orphan. Disgruntled at the way Yuu was favored from his parents, he became very bitter towards him and wants to compete who is the strongest Antibody pilot. And even his resentment towards his real mother, Capt. Anoa McCormick since he was abandoned since childhood, but was replaced by his undying loyalty to Baron Maximillian. He is agressive and powerful. Commonly competing with Quincy Issa for control of the Reclaimers. He is always eager to fight and desires to beat both Yuu and Quincy. He is afraid of living and fighting independently.</description>
<picture>67864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3090" picture="23995.jpg">Aoba Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12378" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Quincy Issa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young, teenage girl and Yuu`s elder sister. She is the pilot of red Quincy Grand. A brash leader of the Reclaimers she disregards any human emotion and resents Yuu for being favored by the Antibodies of Orphan. But it was to the point that she became confused about Yuu`s conviction to let Orphan be released from any guilt that her Gran Cher rebelled against her confused state and even Orphan favored her to become the "Girl of Orphan", the chosen embodiment of Orphan`s will. But in the end she was rescued by Yuu and gave her the understanding of what Orphan wanted to do in the end.</description>
<picture>67867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12379" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Kanan Gimms</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young and talented former Grand Cher pilot. She was Yuu`s best friend and had been raised on Orphan. She later leaves Orphan and joins Novis Noah. She is the pilot of Kanan Brain, the other twin Brain Powerd created from the single Antibody B-Plate. Although she has deep feelings for Yuu, she maintains her spirited energy but she has this reluctance in leaving her home in Orphan and discover new things in Novis-Noa.</description>
<picture>67701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12380" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Anoa McCormick</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the captain of state-of-the-art warship Novis Noah. Her strong exterior hides the dark secret inside her because of her longing to be close with her own son Jonathan Glenn. But to her own frustrations she was always being ostracized by her own son, harboring all hate against his own mother. But in the end she almost got lost in a Chakra wave, which she reappears as a dark character named Baron Maximillian.</description>
<picture>67705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10113" picture="224830.jpg">Isobe Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12381" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Lasse Lundberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brain powerd pilot aboard the novis noah. he is one of the first brain powerd pilots on novis noah along with Nanga and Hime. He is a slim blond haired man with an intrest in Kanan Gimms. He has Lukimia and has lived so long without treatment due to his interaction with the Brain Powers.</description>
<picture>67700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12382" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Nanga Silverly</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another Brain Powerd pilot who is with Lasse and Hime in their quest to search for other B-Plates. He is the offical squad leader of the Brain Powerd and one of the most muscular men onboard.</description>
<picture>61171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12383" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Higgins Saz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the pilot of a yellow Brain Child, Higgins Brain the other twin Brain Powered created from a single Antibody B-Plate. Higgins has a rose tattoo that reacts warmly every time Orphan reacts to a positive emotion. Higgins is almost always in a yellow jump suit. It is noted that she and Captain Laite are romanticly involved.</description>
<picture>67703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12384" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-21">
<name>Kant Kestner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A genius kid who became a scientist at age 12. he soon befriends one of nakki`s brain powerds and becomes its pilot later in the series. Kant is a gifted artest with a love of plants and is able to base most of his papers and theories on photosythesis. Due to his young age and intellect, he had a hard childhood without friends. Even though he is curious about organic energy, he has no desire to go to Orphan to learn.</description>
<picture>61170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6819" picture="173758.jpg">Sasaki Run</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12385" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Irene Carrier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Irene Carrier is the medical doctor, acupuncturist and, in later series, new captain of Novis Noah after Capt. McCormick`s disappearance. While she is a doctor, she was also a top officer in the military. She is looked up to by Hime since she has motherly tendencies in keeping everyone in Novis-Noa safe.</description>
<picture>5096.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10115" picture="37418.jpg">Nagoshi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12386" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Nakki Guys</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the pilot of surprisingly four Antibodies, three Brain Powerds and one Grand Cher. Brash and Impulsive, Nakki has the tendency to outlook other Brain pilots and has affections for Hime. But because of his impulsiveness he always get into trouble during battle.</description>
<picture>67865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12387" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Comodo Mahama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A recoinasance fighter pilot who wishes to have her own Brain Powerd since she was jealous at her fellow coleagues in the Novis Noa. A devotee to her god Ogoun, she always pray for strength in her battles and ask for a sign if she will be with Nanga.</description>
<picture>67702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10114">Sakura Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12388" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Winston Geybridge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The current UN secretary general who is also the supreme leader of the Reclaimer faction. He was romantically linked with Naoko Isami in the past until now, but his intentions in keeping Orphan is to maintain the balance of Earth`s environment. He was ousted by Baron Maximillian and arrested with Naoko until the release of Quincy from her state as the girl of Orphan.</description>
<picture>67704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4681" picture="27277.jpg">Sako Masato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12389" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Isami Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the matriarch of the Isami household, she is Yuu`s caring and loving grandmother. Even though she resents her son and daughter-in-law`s research on using their children as initial "vessels" for the Antibodies, she was able to give her own wisdom to Yuu. She is the long lost lover of Winston Geybridge and until now she still is close to him.</description>
<picture>67863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10117" picture="37420.jpg">Sugimoto Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12390" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-21">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Shiela Glass</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another Reclaimer Grand Cher pilot, quite amazonic and has zealousness in following the ideals of the Reclaimers. The reason is that she has a sibling who died during the Grand Cher wars, but in the end she realized that she was following the wrong idealism after her encounter with Higgins Saz. Shiela is very physically strong, being able to lift Higgins clear off the ground with only one hand. She is in support of Johnathan Glenn over the Isami family that rules Orphan.</description>
<picture>61169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12391" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Baron Maximillian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the pilot of a powerful and evolved Antibody, the Barons Grand Cher. At first he was just a mentor for Jonathan that temporarily he gave his Baron Grand Cher to him, which in the end he/she was actually Anoa McCormick, the missing captain of Novis Noa. Baron Maximillian takes control of Orphan all in the name of Jonathan.</description>
<picture>67860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10113" picture="224830.jpg">Isobe Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12392" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Nelly Kim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A lone Brain Powerd pilot whom Yu met when he and his Brain was damaged by the Baron Grand Cher. She gave Yu pieces of wisdom on how to listen and understand carefully of how his Brain feels. But in the end on the second attack made by the Baron Grand Cher she fell and disappeared in a storm gust as the two damaged Brains fused in a Chakra wave and became a hybrid Brain Powerd named Nelly Brain.</description>
<picture>67866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10116">Takahagi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12393" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-18">
<name>K.D. Dean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is an Orphan`s undercover spy working at Novis Noah. K.D. is also a Grand Cher pilot but gets shot down while fleeing the ship. He like, most others touched by orphen, is ambitious and willing to kill anyone in his way. He survives and stays on Novis Noa.</description>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12394" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Yukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6763">Asakawa Miya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12395" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Kumazoo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the three children living in the Novis Noah. Although he was involved in some unfortunate events, he was able to listen and understand how the Brains are affected on the changes of Orphan.</description>
<picture>153051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12396" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the three children on board the Novis Noah.</description>
<picture>153050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10114">Sakura Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12397" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Reito Kanchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of Novis Noah`s Private submarine and Higgens` lover. He is a tall bald man who has little role in series other then recon.</description>
<picture>153049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12398" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<name>Isami Kensaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuu and Quincy`s father who is a researcher in the Antibody project and later as the head scientist inside Orphan. He was more interested in his research than the welfare of his own children, being used as guinea pigs in researching on the Antibodies in response to human emotions.</description>
<picture>67861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4484" picture="26762.jpg">Horibe Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12399" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Isami Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kensaku`s wife and assistant. She has little love for her husband. She merely marries him to progress research into organic energy and to gain a solid power base to become the leader of Orphan. She is a cold and calculating woman who is more then willing to use her own children as mere tools for her goals.</description>
<picture>67862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10111">Kanoki Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6301" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動く山脈</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moving Mountain Range</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La montagne en mouvement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugoku Sanmyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6302" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の淵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Depths of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les profondeurs de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Fuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6303" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カーテンの向こうで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond the Curtain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Derrière le rideau</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Curtain no Mukou de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6304" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">招かれざる客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Uninvited Guest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des invités indésirables</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maekarezaru Kyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6305" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一点突破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perfect Breakthrough</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Percée gagnante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichiten Toppa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6306" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂は孤独</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are Souls Solitary</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les âmes sont-elles solitaires ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii wa Kodoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6307" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョナサンの刃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jonathan`s Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La blessure de Jonathan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jonathan no Jin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6308" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堂々たる浮上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stately Surfacing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`émergence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doudoutaru Fujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6309" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寄港地で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Port of Call</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au port de l`appel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikouchi de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6310" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">単独行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Independent Course of Action</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les choses s`accélèrent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tandokkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6311" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">拒否反応</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rejection</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rejet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyohi Hannou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6312" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉と弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sister and Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Frères et sœurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ane to Otouto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6313" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダブル・リバイバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Revival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Double renaissance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Double Revival</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6314" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレートの誘惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Temptation of the Plates</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`appel de la plaque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Plate no Yuuwaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6315" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛翔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`envol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6316" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵か味方か</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend or Foe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ami ou ennemi ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki ka Mikata ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6317" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルファンのためらい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orphan`s Hesitation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`hésitation d`Orphen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orphan no Tamerai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6318" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">故郷の炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hometown Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La maison d`enfance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furusato no Honoo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6319" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶のいたずら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tricking Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mémoire nous joue des tours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku no Itazura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6320" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuu`s Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat de Yuu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuu no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6321" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイート・メモリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sweet Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les jours heureux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sweet Memories</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6322" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fated Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retrouvailles programmées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6323" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乾坤一擲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All or Nothing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tout pour le tout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenkonitteki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6324" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">深海を発して</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departing from the Ocean Depths</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Renaissance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkai o Hasshite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6325" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻視錯綜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Problem of Hallucination</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hallucinations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genshi Sakusou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6326" update="2006-08-11">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガバナーの野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Governor`s Ambitions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ambition du gouverneur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Governor no Yabou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97260" update="2009-03-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97261" update="2019-08-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219810" update="2019-08-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219811" update="2019-08-29">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
