<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="38" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-18</startdate>
<enddate>2001-06-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">kurumi zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kurumi0</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">鋼鉄天使くるみ零</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Steel Angel Kurumi Zero</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="88" type="Alternative Setting">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi</anime>
<anime id="89" type="Alternative Setting">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi 2-shiki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20110808221312/http://www.ponycanyon.co.jp/pc-moe/zero/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="2256" type="Character Design">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="3840" type="Direction">Takahashi Naohito</name>
<name id="2256" type="Chief Animation Direction">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="6517" type="Original Work">Kaishaku</name>
</creators>
<description>Sometime in the distant future, http://anidb.net/ch4792 [Kurumi], http://anidb.net/ch4793 [Saki] and http://anidb.net/ch4794 [Karinka] share an apartment with another girl named Excelia. One day, after school, Kurumi tells everyone that she is in love with a man she met named Michihito Kagura, but she does not know when she will see him again.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="499">2.77</permanent>
<temporary count="504">5.82</temporary>
<review count="1">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221932.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1853</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>556</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768</identifier>
<identifier>atgwzh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20110808221312/http://www.ponycanyon.co.jp/pc-moe/zero/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Steel_Angel_Kurumi#Steel_Angel_Kurumi_Zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>鋼鉄天使くるみ#鋼鉄天使くるみ零</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>313</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>233920</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3647" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-05">
<name>drastic change in sequel</name>
<description>This anime differs greatly in genre and/or overall mood from its prequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4791" type="main character in" update="2009-03-11">
<rating votes="6">1.00</rating>
<name>Kagura Nakahito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The primary male protagonist for the show, Nakahito unwittingly becomes the master of Steel Angel Kurumi when he accidentally awakens her with a kiss. Hesitant and unsure of himself, he teaches Kurumi as much as he can while slowly falling in love with the hyperactive girl.</description>
<picture>20940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4792" type="main character in" update="2009-03-11">
<rating votes="24">6.10</rating>
<name>Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Steel Angel built by Dr. Ayanokouji and equipped with a Mark II Heart, she is awakened by Nakahito`s kiss in the first episode and immediately becomes possessive of him while simultaneously pledging her love and service to him. The main female lead and an incredibly wild individual, she is overwhelmingly manic when it comes to Nakahito (whom she calls "Master"). Whenever her antics become too much, one word from her master will make her stop (usually). Very protective of her master and her sisters, she will stop at nothing to ensure their safety. She is impossibly strong and rather handily defeats all her opponents due to her Mark II Heart.</description>
<picture>20938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4793" type="main character in" update="2009-03-11">
<rating votes="18">6.65</rating>
<name>Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another Steel Angel built by Dr. Ayanokouji, Saki was activated by Dr. Amagi with Dr. Brandow`s help, and given orders to destroy Kurumi and seize her Mark II Heart. Amagi and the General decide to use the largest of the seized Angel Hearts to give Saki as much power as possible.</description>
<picture>20939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4794" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="8">4.16</rating>
<name>Karinka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third Steel Angel built on the design by Dr Ayanakouji, she was activated by the Academy to destroy Kurumi. She is very strong due to being installed with two Angel Hearts instead of one (however this also means she is exempted from following the orders of Dr. Walski, her creator). She is very temperamental, devious, and has occasionally shown traits of sadism (shown explicitly during the time she held Saki hostage). She later joins Nakahito and the group, originally to figure out Kurumi`s power, but she eventually develops a crush on Nakahito.</description>
<picture>21016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66367" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="8">5.94</rating>
<name>Amagi Hakase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="229" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2001-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンゼル フォース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Force</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Force</title>
</episode>
<episode id="230" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2001-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンゼル スマイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Smile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2001-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンゼル ハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Heart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120868" update="2010-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
