<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="385" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-07-24</startdate>
<enddate>1998-02-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Blue Seed 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Blue Seed OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Blue Seed 2: Operation Mitama</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブルーシード 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blue Seed Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Blue Seed Beyond</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="644" type="Prequel">Blue Seed</anime>
<anime id="3127" type="Prequel">Blue Seed 1.5</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/contents/works_sp/0320_/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="872" type="Original Work">Takada Yuuzou</name>
<name id="5440" type="Direction">Murayama Yasushi</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="3573" type="Character Design">Ishii Akiharu</name>
<name id="4605" type="Direction">Kamiya Jun</name>
</creators>
<description>The Aragami return once again to ravage the city, and it is up to the Terrestrial Administration Centre to stop them. http://anidb.net/ch35064 [Fujimiya Momiji] and http://anidb.net/ch35065 [Kusanagi Mamoru]`s relationship is on ice; the rest of the TAC is scrambling to get things together so they can effectively wipe out the Aragami. A mysterious girl, claiming to be a half-Aragami like Mamoru, is causing chaos for the TAC and Momiji as well. Will they be able to pull together in time?
Source: Anime Colony (scifi.com) (edited)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="399">4.12</permanent>
<temporary count="401">6.45</temporary>
<review count="1">9.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>4868.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1815</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1119</identifier>
<identifier>ghqmmz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/contents/works_sp/0320_/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BLUE_SEED</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88218</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2116</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>blue-seed</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2079" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-05">
<name>magatama</name>
<description>Magatama are curved beads which first appeared in Japan during the Joumon period. They are often found inhumed in mounded tumulus graves as offerings to deities. They continued to be popular with the ruling elites throughout the Kofun Period of Japan, and are often romanticised as indicative of the Yamato Dynasty of Japan. They are mainly made of jade, agate, quartz, talc, and jasper. Some consider them to be an Imperial symbol, although in fact ownership was widespread throughout all the chieftainships of Kofun Period Japan. It is believed that magatama were popularly worn as jewels for decoration, in addition to their religious meanings. In this latter regard they were later largely replaced by Buddhist prayer beads in the Nara period. In modern Japan, the magatama`s shape of a sphere with a flowing tail is a common visual representation of the human spirit.
The most important magatama is the Yasakani no Magatama, which is part of the Imperial Regalia of Japan, added some time around the Heian period. The Yasakani no Magatama stands for benevolence, and is one of the three items used in the ceremony of imperial ascension. In Japanese mythology, the jewels, along with the mirror, were hung on the tree outside of Amaterasu`s cave to lure her out. It is believed to be a necklace composed of jade magatama stones instead of a solitary gem as depicted in popular culture. It is believed to be enshrined in Kokyo, the Japanese Imperial Palace.
The consensus among Japanese archaeologists is that magatama originated in Joumon Japan before spreading to the Asian continent through the Korean peninsula. It is claimed that the earliest Korean prehistoric magatama date to the Early Mumun (post-850 BC) and are generally found in the southern part of peninsula in proximity to Japan. Charles Keally, an archaeologist who has conducted research on magatama, states: The magatama`s origins are more controversial. These curved jewels of jadeite are common in Kofun Period burials, and they are common also in Korean sites of the same age. But magatama are found in Yayoi sites, too, and unquestionable true magatama are reported also in Jomon sites in Tohoku as early as about 1000 B.C., long before true magatama appeared in Korea. The magatama is found also on early Korean royal gold crowns and has long been considered a sign of royalty in Korea as well as being a connection with Shamanistic elements.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>62069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5307" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-01-24">
<name>aggressive plants</name>
<description>Plants that can actually attack humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35064" type="main character in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="10">6.56</rating>
<name>Fujimiya Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35065" type="main character in" update="2011-07-31">
<rating votes="4">7.64</rating>
<name>Kusanagi Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35066" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Kunikida Daitetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35067" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="5">6.02</rating>
<name>Matsudaira Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35068" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="5">6.02</rating>
<name>Takeuchi Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35069" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="5">6.02</rating>
<name>Sawaguchi Koume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35070" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-03">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Yaegashi Yoshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35071" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-17">
<rating votes="6">7.15</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36993" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<name>Moccha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36994" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Valencia Tachibana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4484" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇稲田封滅作戦 Operation Mitama Phase-1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission: Eradicate Kushinada, Operation Mitama, Phase I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kushinada Fuumetsu Sakusen: Operation Mitama Phase-1</title>
<summary>Aragami are appearing again when that should be impossible, beginning with a direct attack on Kunikida and the TAC.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784065</identifier>
<identifier>blue-seed</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8773" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1996-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇稲田封滅作戦 Operation Mitama Phase-2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission: Eradicate Kushinada, Operation Mitama, Phase II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kushinada Fuumetsu Sakusen: Operation Mitama Phase-2</title>
<summary>The battle is taken to America to stop the new generation of Aragami.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784066</identifier>
<identifier>blue-seed</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8774" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美人OL6人旅 秘湯大爆破</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Six Babes Bathing in a Killer Hot Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bijin OL Rokunin Tabi Hiyu Daibakuha</title>
<summary>A trip to a hot springs should be relaxing for all involved, until a phone call that the springs have been wired with explosives by a terrorist who wants to play a game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784067</identifier>
<identifier>blue-seed</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121945" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179713" update="2016-08-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Dancing Little Love</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
