<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3947" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-07-20</startdate>
<enddate>1991-07-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gamba to Kawauso no Bouken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Adventures of Gamba and Sea Otter</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The adventure of Gamba and the otter</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Adventure of Gamba and Otter</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガンバとカワウソの冒険</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5411" type="Prequel">Gamba no Bouken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/movie/data/m_gamba2.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="917" type="Financial Production">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="5578" type="Direction">Ooga Shunji</name>
<name id="5607" type="Music">Kondou Hiroaki</name>
<name id="8825" type="Original Work">Saitou Atsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>The final chapter of the Gamba saga, released in theatres 15 years after the original TV series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9">3.97</permanent>
<temporary count="9">5.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238682.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20175</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1426</identifier>
<identifier>gadjbd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.com/library/old/movie/data/m_gamba2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/english/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=234</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ガンバとカワウソの冒険</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>151442</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2141</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=1F-oHwDXrJg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35411" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-09">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Ikasama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1484" picture="19079.jpg">Hori Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35412" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-09">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Gakusha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3252" picture="24231.jpg">Tomiyama Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35413" type="main character in" update="2011-08-09">
<rating votes="3">9.63</rating>
<name>Gamba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35414" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-09">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Shijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3309">Shimada Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35416" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-09">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Bobo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29844">Mizuki Ranko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35417" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-09">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Yoisho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41123" update="2005-09-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>1991-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
