<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3972" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-11-06</startdate>
<enddate>1994-11-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Captain Tsubasa: Saikyou no Teki! Holanda Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Captain Tsubasa: European Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Captain Tsubasa Holland Youth Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Captain Tsubasa - Holland Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キャプテン翼 最強の敵! オランダユース</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="507" type="Parent Story">Captain Tsubasa J</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/1994/07_TSUBASAnew/TSUBASAnew.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="4232" type="Chief Animation Direction">Okaseko Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="3674" type="Music">Miratsu Takeo</name>
<name id="4232" type="Character Design">Okaseko Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="733" type="Work">Yomiko Advertising</name>
<name id="720" type="Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="5117" type="Original Work">Takahashi Youichi</name>
<name id="5416" type="Direction">Kogawa Yoriyasu</name>
</creators>
<description>We jump right into the exhibition game series between Japan and Holland youth teams. Things are not looking too good for Japan with http://anidb.net/ch8344 [Hyuuga] having an injured leg and http://anidb.net/ch30220 [Misaki`s] lack of confidence as the captain. In order to boost team morale and confidence, the management contacts http://anidb.net/ch2084 [Wakabayashi] (living in Germany) and http://anidb.net/ch2083 [Tsubasa] (living in Brazil) to come back to Japan for the final game against Holland.
Note: Screened during the Jump Super Anime Tour `94/`95 (ジャンプ・スーパー・アニメツアー`94`/95) starting from November 1994 until May 1995. The VHS version went on sale on 16.12.1995.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="124">4.99</permanent>
<temporary count="125">6.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>225301.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4612</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2122</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/1994/07_TSUBASAnew/TSUBASAnew.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キャプテン翼_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3110</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2083" type="main character in" update="2011-03-19">
<rating votes="52">7.61</rating>
<name>Oozora Tsubasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A prodigious soccer player, Tsubasa dreams of one day winning the FIFA World Cup for Japan. His position is midfielder, usually wearing jersey #10.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>68134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3147" picture="49928.jpg">Ogai Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2084" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-19">
<rating votes="38">6.90</rating>
<name>Wakabayashi Genzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wakabayashi Genzou is an extroardinary goalkeeper who can catch almost anything thrown at him. Not many shots can come past Genzou. A charismatic guy, Genzou is also loyal to his friends and he is firm with his decisions. Genzou always keeps his feelings to himself and people close to him as seen in Shin Captain Tsubasa, when he`s willingly criticize his teammates` performance in order to make them realize that football in Europe is different than what they play in Japan. His actions caused a lot of Japanese players to dislike him and Genzou only told Tsubasa his true intentions. From early childhood, he has aimed to be the best goalkeeper in the world. He tended to be selfish, and brag about his skills before he met and played a couple of games against Tsubasa. After his match against Tsubasa, he has learned to enjoy the game with his other teammates.</description>
<picture>68135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8344" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="60">8.46</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Kojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>To help his family, Hyuuga Kojirou wants to be a professional player, an ace striker. His devotion to football and his persistence to shoot the goal is outstanding. He was both Tsubasa`s and Genzou`s top rival. A great guy, Hyuuga is not only strong, he is also tough but at the same time caring. Can be a bit impulsive at times, though. He was once famous because of his roughness and many players were scared of him. But, Hyuuga is actually a kind boy who cares about his family and friends. In the World Youth series, Hyuuga was one of the 7 players to be excluded from the Japanese National team after they lost 3 group matches with Real Japan 7 (R.J.7). Determined to get back into the team, Hyuuga developed a new shot, the Raijuu shot, a shot which is a bit similar to Tsubasa`s Drive Shoot, except that Hyuuga`s Raijuu Shot is a ground shot that will curve upward, unlike Tsubasa`s Drive Shooter which will go up then curve downward.</description>
<picture>68133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30152" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-13">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Nitta Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30217" type="main character in" update="2018-06-16">
<rating votes="33">7.50</rating>
<name>Ishizaki Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3838" picture="25826.jpg">Satou Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30218" type="main character in" update="2018-06-16">
<rating votes="14">3.40</rating>
<name>Nakazawa Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30220" type="main character in" update="2014-03-16">
<rating votes="31">7.03</rating>
<name>Misaki Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1901" picture="186579.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30221" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="32">6.96</rating>
<name>Misugi Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30222" type="main character in" update="2014-08-12">
<rating votes="26">8.43</rating>
<name>Wakashimazu Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "Karate Keeper", Wakashimazu Ken is a goalkeeper on par with http://anidb.net/ch2084 [Wakabayashi Genzou], but more offense-oriented. As his nickname implies, he is an expert karateka since his father is the master of a dojo. His father originally disapproved his efforts to become a footballer and his opposition to become the heir of the dojo.
Wakashimazu became interested in football when http://anidb.net/ch8344 [Hyuuga Kojirou] invited him to join the Meiwa team after being impressed by his abilities in a one-on-one duel that Wakashimazu lost. Since then, they are close friends.
Despite being an excellent goalkeeper, he originally was a forward and only became goalkeeper because Meiwa didn`t have competent goalkeepers.
A reliable partner of Hyuga while in the Meiwa and Toho teams, he and Wakabayashi regularly alternate in the goalkeeper position with the Japanese team.</description>
<picture>68148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42576" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-18">
<name>Souda Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makoto Soda is a fearsome defender who knows how to injure people with tackles without the referee`s knowledge. He is quite fast and he tends to put effects on his balls when he passes or shoots.</description>
<picture>84092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80205" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="2">5.70</rating>
<name>Sawada Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80208" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="10">6.83</rating>
<name>Matsuyama Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80215" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="3">5.10</rating>
<name>Tachibana Masao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3028" picture="228622.jpg">Kamei Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80216" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<rating votes="3">5.10</rating>
<name>Tachibana Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80221" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-14">
<name>Jitou Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86424" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-08">
<name>Katagiri Munemasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95984" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-09">
<rating votes="6">5.90</rating>
<name>Mikami Tatsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98501" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-07">
<name>Sugimoto Kumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A manager of the Nankatsu middle school football team, during the middle school arc of the Captain Tsubasa series, Kumi true interest is not in football but in http://anidb.net/ch2083 [Oozora Tsubasa] for whom she has a crush on. While a true rival of http://anidb.net/ch30218 [Nakazawa Sanae], Tsubasa already has someone he likes.</description>
<picture>225167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10864" picture="25797.jpg">Motoi Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98539" type="appears in" update="2018-10-18">
<name>Announcer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ubiquitous voice that narrates most matches during the Captain Tsubasa series.</description>
<picture>225738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98560" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-09">
<name>Nishimoto Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A close friend of http://anidb.net/ch30218 [Nakazawa Sanae], Yukari is also a manager of the Nankatsu football team during the middle school arc of the Captain Tsubasa series. She and http://anidb.net/ch30217 [Ishizaki Ryou] eventually become a couple.</description>
<picture>225304.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41324" update="2014-10-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1994-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
