<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3977" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>1995-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tottemo! Luckyman</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Luckyman</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">行运超人</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とっても!ラッキーマン</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1990/tv_028.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1944" type="Character Design">Kanada Yoshinori</name>
<name id="17915" type="Original Work">Gamou Hiroshi</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="4243" type="Series Composition">Urasawa Yoshio</name>
<name id="1966" type="Direction">Nabeshima Osamu</name>
<name id="4326" type="Music">Honma Yuusuke</name>
</creators>
<description>This gag comedy series focused on the adventures of a bizarre superhero powered by special cooking and fights against various aliens and other enemies threatening the planet Earth.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="14">4.49</permanent>
<temporary count="14">5.60</temporary>
<review count="1">8.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>93718.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4625</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3672</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2223</identifier>
<identifier>zhndkl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1990/tv_028.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tottemo!_Luckyman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とっても!ラッキーマン#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89016</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>921</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="61413" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かまきり星人でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61414" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おやじマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61415" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バードマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61416" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強男爵でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61417" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛獣使いマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61418" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オタッキーマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61419" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブサイクゴンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61420" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">努力マンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61421" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">千顔マンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61422" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">またまた最強男爵でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61423" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">めだち変身でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61424" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">芸術星人でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61425" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">芸術星人でラッキーのつづき!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61426" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">こりずに最強男爵でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61427" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーティー荒らしマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61428" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">半魚人でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61429" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おっかけマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61430" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">借金トリマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61431" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目立の秘密でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61432" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆弾マンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61433" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">納豆づけでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61434" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">納豆づけでラッキーのつづき!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61435" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">G-5[ジーゴ]でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61436" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンデレラでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61437" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">極悪教師マンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61438" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運動会マンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61439" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">江戸時代でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61440" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍者マンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61441" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スポーツマンでラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61442" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">合体星人でラッキー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61443" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会!勝利・友情・努力三兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61444" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">非常事態!全宇宙の危機!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61445" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">努力マンの過去!兄たちの裏切り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61446" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙われたヒーロー協会会長!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61447" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">来襲!恐怖の殺し屋ヒットマン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61448" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖!お手手戦隊指レンジャー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61449" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今, 始まる!宇宙最大の戦い!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61450" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃!小指グリーンの正体!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61451" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">完全体!スピードマンターボ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61452" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二の敵!薬指イエロー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 40</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61453" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第三の敵!鋼鉄・パワー二人組</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 41</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61454" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活!美しき兄弟愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 42</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61455" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">苦節50年!豆腐ゲタの威力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 43</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61456" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆発!怒りの努力マン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 44</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61457" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">血の嵐!努力マンのフルパワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61458" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒーロー伝説!天才マンの悲劇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 46</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61459" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決!ラッキーマン対天才マン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 47</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61460" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">残忍!最高に苦しい殺し方!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 48</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61461" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵!無敵の世直しマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 49</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61462" update="2006-08-18">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の決戦!最強の合体パワー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 50</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
