<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="3983" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-07-18</startdate>
<enddate>2003-07-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bokutachi Pichu Brothers: Party wa Oosawagi! no Maki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pichu Bros. Wild Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Boku-tachi Pichu Brothers: Party wa Oosawagi! no Maki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぼくたちピチューブラザーズ ~パーティはおおさわぎ! のまき~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pichu Bros. In Party Panic!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1041" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters Advanced Generation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<description>This is an animated cartoon that was released inside the game Pokémon Channel.
A half-hour long anime show, broken into five short segments, featuring the Pichu Brothers. Meowth throws a party that the Pichu brothers and their friends are not invited to. After a series of events, they find out they were invited, but their invitations were simply delivered late. They go to Meowth`s Party and hear him sing. The series has a total of five episodes, each on its own channel.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="143">3.58</permanent>
<temporary count="146">5.57</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>35061.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15664</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ポケットモンスター_(OVA)#.E3.81.BC.E3.81.8F.E3.81.9F.E3.81.A1.E3.83.94.E3.83.81.E3.83.A5.E3.83.BC.E3.83.96.E3.83.A9.E3.82.B6.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA.E3.83.BB.E3.83.91.E3.83.BC.E3.83.86.E3.82.A3.E3.81.AF.E3.81.8A.E3.81.8A.E3.81.95.E3.82.8F.E3.81.8E.21.E3.81.AE.E3.81.BE.E3.81.8D</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="541" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Ordile</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Feraligatr is the final form of the Totodile evolutionary line. Feraligatrs are massive, Godzilla-like crocodiles with long, blue bodies and four legs, although they may also stand upright on land. Their appendages have sharp claws at the ends, and its jaw is lined with teeth. On its head, back, and tail there are red, jagged scales. As stated in the Pokédex in Pokémon Ruby and Sapphire, "Feraligatr intimidates its foes by opening its huge mouth. In battle, it will kick the ground hard with its thick and powerful hind legs to charge at the foe with incredible speed."
Feraligatrs are ferocious and have a tendency to lash out at those that come too close. They eat Magikarp and other fish-like Pokémon, as well as larger prey (such as Stantler and Tauros) when they come close enough to the water.</description>
<picture>243046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="568" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Marilli</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azumarill is the evolved form of Marill. Azumarill resembles a blue, bipedal rabbit with a large, ellipsoid body, long blue ears with red insides, and a blue ball on the end of its thin, elastic black tail. The white bubble-like pattern on its lower stomach helps it to camouflage itself from potential predators when it is in the water.
Azumarill`s long ears act as sensors to identify sounds even in fast running rivers. Otherwise, when alone, Azumarill plays in water as a natural pastime, though it must roll up its elongated ears to prevent the sensitive sensory materials inside them from getting wet. The ball at the end of its tail can act as a sensor and guide it while under water. It can make thick, liquid balloons out of thin air with the saliva-water stored in its body. If it spots a drowning Pokémon in any body of water, it fashions such air balloons and jumps in to give the troubled Pokémon air balloons to help it breathe.
In the Pokémon anime, Paul owned an Azumarill which he used in a gym battle against Roark. Although it knew powerful Water attacks like Hydro Pump, it lost to Roark`s Geodude, which prompted Paul to give it to a Pokémon trainer passing by, being disappointed by its strength.</description>
<picture>243068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="601" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Upah</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wooper are similar to Axolotl. They are light teal-colored Pokémon with round feet, no arms, and a long tail. Their simplistic face consists of mainly of a large mouth, primarily while open. They have purplish barbed antennae on the sides of their head. Three purple, though sometimes shaded blue or pink, gills are on its stomach. Wooper will usually live in cold water: however, they occasionally come out onto land in search of food. When doing so, they coat their bodies with slimy, poisonous film. Touching the slime with bare hands will cause a shooting pain. Male Wooper have two barbs on their antennae, while female Wooper have one barb. Males also have larger gills.</description>
<picture>243078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="485" picture="223410.jpg">Shintani Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="605" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Yamikarasu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Murkrow is a small black crow with red eyes. The top of its head is styled as a witch`s hat and its tail bristles out like a broomstick. Murkrow is rather unpopular in the Pokémon world. Its dismal appearance and nocturnal nature have long caused it to be considered an omen of ill fortune to all who see it. If a Murkrow finds itself wounded, it fights back by leading its pursuer to dark mountain trails in an attempt to get him hopelessly lost in the darkness.
Murkrow is also attracted to bright, shiny objects, which it collects to stash in its nest. This, of course, leads to many arguments between Murkrow and Meowth, who both share a common love of stashing things - and taking from each other! It does not hesitate to steal such objects if necessary and has even been known to attempt to snatch rings off their owner`s fingers (and complete strangers too, for that matter). With the addition of Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, it is revealed that some Murkrow are servants to its evolved form, Honchkrow, who spends all of its time preening and ordering the Murkrow around. Also with Diamond and Pearl`s release, Murkrow, like many other Pokémon, have gender differences. In this case, Males have a taller "hat" - technically, the crest that resembles a three-pointed witch hat - than females would. Murkrow can only be found wild in the Pokémon Diamond Version in Eterna Forest, while Misdreavus can only be found in Pokémon Pearl at the same location.</description>
<picture>243082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="633" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Himeguma</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teddiursa is a bear cub, resembling a teddy bear more than a real bear. Teddiursa have a crescent mark on their forehead, which grows (both in thickness and in circumference) as the Pokémon ages. Once the crescent fully closes into a circle, the Teddiursa is ready to evolve into an Ursaring. Teddiursa, although an omnivore, has a diet that almost exclusively consists of honey. It makes its own honey out of fruit and pollen from Beedrill. It lets the honey soak in its paws, making it often lick its paws.</description>
<picture>243096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="828" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Delvil</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Houndour is a small, black dog with a red underbelly, resembling the Doberman and Rottweiler breeds in shape and coloration. Houndour is a nocturnal carnivorous Pokémon that organizes itself in packs. A Houndour pack works with perfect teamwork to pursue prey. Individual members of the pack approach the intended target from different spots and begin the hunt. They then communicate their location to each other using special howls, ensuring that the victim is eventually surrounded and unable to escape.</description>
<picture>243107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="838" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Muchul</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smoochum is a the pre-evolution of Jynx that was introduced a generation after. It is a female-only species that uses its lips, the most sensitive part of its body, to examine new and unfamiliar objects, and remember its likes and dislikes. This sensitivity quickly develops as it grows. It actively runs about, but often falls. When idle, it rocks its head back and forth, as if it were kissing someone. It constantly searches for ways to see its reflection, so it can see if its face is dirty.</description>
<picture>243116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="840" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Buby</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magby is the baby form of Magmar. Its body temperature and the fire that it breathes are constantly over 1100 F. Its health is determined by the state of its flame; healthy Magbys have pure yellow flames, while black smoke is mixed in with unhealthy ones. As it breathes, embers constantly dribble out of its nostrils and its mouth. It lives in volcanic craters, and an eruption is imminent when many Magby gather in one place.</description>
<picture>243118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27470" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<name>Pichu (Otouto)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Pichu Brothers live in Big Town.</description>
<picture>81322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40510" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<name>Pichu (Ani)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Pichu Brothers live in Big Town.</description>
<picture>81319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="41688" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2003-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Show</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
