<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4023" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>2006-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lemon Angel Project</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">レモン エンジェル プロジェクト</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">レモンエンジェルプロジェクト</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Lemon Project</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">柠檬天使计划</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">LAP</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">LEMON ANGEL PROJECT</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4210" type="Alternative Setting">Cream Lemon: Lemon Angel</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20060207135228/http://www.lemon-angel-project.com/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="8360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamakawa Kouji</name>
<name id="7798" type="Music">Sasaki Akira</name>
<name id="8032" type="Direction">Chiba Daisuke</name>
<name id="8398" type="Original Work">AMG Entertainment</name>
<name id="28264" type="Series Composition">Takimoto Masashi</name>
<name id="19299" type="Character Design">Watanabe Yukari</name>
<name id="19299" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Yukari</name>
<name id="5206" type="Animation Work">Radix Ace Entertainment</name>
</creators>
<description>In the summer of 2017, the Lemon Angel, an idol group of girls, suddenly discontinued its activity without any notice when they were at the height of popularity.
10 months have passed since then. Minaguchi Tomo enters a high school to fulfill her promise with her senior student, Kono Yui, whom she respected. Tomo is asked to audition for the rebirth project of Lemon Angel. Then she learns that Yui organized the Lemon Angel, and Tomo resolved her mind to audition for Yui. However, being chosen as the members of the Lemon Angel, they must be selected girls whose singing and dancing abilities are supreme.
There are various jealous and harasses seething in the audition places. During the continuous lessees of sing and dancing, Tomo meets rivals girls who complete each other. At the same time, they are friends to understand each other.
Soon, 6 beautiful girls are chosen. What is waiting for them?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="347">3.75</permanent>
<temporary count="358">6.34</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>83976.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6095</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>671</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3576</identifier>
<identifier>nsaejv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.imagicatv.jp/content/LAP/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Lemon_Angel_Project</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>LEMON_ANGEL_PROJECT</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324688</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7928</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10590" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="3">3.39</rating>
<name>Minaguchi Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomo is the protagonist of the series and lead singer of the Lemon Angels. She has light blue hair with an ahoge and two long pigtails. Very squeaky-voiced, clumsy, and loves to eat. She had no talents whatsoever coming into the Project, but gained both singing and dancing skills as the series progressed. She is best friends with Saya and Erika.</description>
<picture>31619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6862" picture="31625.jpg">Shihono Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10591" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="3">8.29</rating>
<name>Erika Campbell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Erika is Tomo`s other best friend and a Lemon Angel. She has dark skin and white hair. Always sticks up for Tomo and Saya, and wants everyone to stop fighting with each other and just be friends. She came to live in Japan from Brazil with her adopted brother Takumi, who is a famous rock star from the band Third Sence. She was constantly picked on by her peers (except for her friends, of course) for being a foreigner and not knowing anything about Japanese culture, and was used in episode 5 by Haruka and the other unnamed characters to meet Takumi when it turned out he was unavailable to meet them. She is also a good cook.</description>
<picture>31621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10608" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<name>Sakakibara Fuyumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuyumi is one of the Lemon Angels. Has short brown hair and is a meganekko. She grew up as a successful childhood actress and acted with Haruka, but as she got older, she went more into singing and volunteering. She is very shy and has a heavy conscience. She is also a good cook.</description>
<picture>31662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6863" picture="31622.jpg">Hirama Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10610" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="2">5.79</rating>
<name>Nagisa Miru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miru is one of the new Lemon Angels. She has long, flowing black hair, and seems to dress in the Gothic Lolita style. Very soft spoken and does not talk or sing unless she really needs to. She lost her parents in a fire at a young age and became a hikkikomori until she listened to the Lemon Angels. From that day forward, she wanted to become just like Anne, the lead singer for the last group, and also wanted to be the lead singer of the newly formed Lemon Angels, but withdrew from her desires once she discovered that Tomo was just like Anne and deserved to be lead singer instead.</description>
<picture>31664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10611" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<name>Yuuki Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saya is Tomo`s best friend and a Lemon Angel. She has red hair done in pigtails. She was once a magazine model and a cosplay model at the same time, but left both jobs to pursue a life of singing. She states that she wants to sing to make others happy. Although she is assertive and stuck up, she has inner feelings for Tomo and Erika. She is a horrible cook, as shown in episode eight when she made the other Lemon Angels sick from her cooking.</description>
<picture>31765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10612" type="main character in" update="2016-10-31">
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<name>Suwa Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miki is the leader of the group and a Lemon Angel, although she did not try out for the role. She helped create the Project with Yui and was good friends with her (just like Tomo). She is very strict on the outside but deep down inside she is very caring for the other Angels.</description>
<picture>31669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3175" picture="181014.jpg">Maruyama Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85895" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-31">
<name>Kouno Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85896" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-31">
<name>Himuro Shin`ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85897" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-31">
<name>Kogure Ryouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3295" picture="38451.jpg">Ogihara Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85898" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-31">
<name>Kudou Masami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="45849" update="2006-01-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢から覚めた天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The angel which awakens from a dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume kara Sameta Tenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="45850" update="2006-01-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Evolution</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First time`s rival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Evolution</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46266" update="2006-05-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">I will</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I will</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46549" update="2006-02-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Smile means love</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smile means love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46550" update="2006-06-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達でいいから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Better Off As Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi de Ii kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46551" update="2006-02-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Promise you</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise you</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46934" update="2006-02-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたを知りたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Know You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata o Shiritai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46935" update="2006-02-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">避暑地の森の天使たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angels Of The Summer Resort`s Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hishochi no Mori no Tenshi-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46936" update="2006-02-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀愁のシンフォニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Symphony Of Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aishuu no Symphony</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47102" update="2006-02-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青いスタスィオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Station</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Station</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49163" update="2006-04-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">背徳のシナリオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenario of immorality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haitoku no Scenario</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49164" update="2006-04-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミカヅキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crescent Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikazuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49165" update="2016-10-31">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Never give up</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never give up</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
