<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4031" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-09-05</startdate>
<enddate>1990-03-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hi-Speed Jecy</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">High Speed Jessie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハイスピード・ジェシー</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="171" approval="3" total="3">Seihou Bukyou Outlaw Star</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="59024" type="Original Work">Saitou Eiichirou</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="512" type="Character Design">Mikimoto Haruhiko</name>
<name id="2119" type="Series Composition">Tomita Sukehiro</name>
<name id="1949" type="Direction">Kageyama Shigenori</name>
<name id="14453" type="Character Design">Takahashi Akinobu</name>
</creators>
<description>Jecy is a young man on a quest for revenge; he lost his parents to the hands of the organized crime syndicate called the Bismark House - a group on a hunt to acquire a product called "lyzorium" at any cost. With incredible abilities such as increased speed and agility, Jecy travels through space with a girl named Tiana; Fork Green, a priest of the Heartland religion who kills criminals slowly to send them to heaven; and a living ship called Paolon. However, Jecy`s revenge won`t come easily - a woman named Jera, her bloodthirsty little brother Cross and a number of other adversaries stand in their way!
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="50">3.98</permanent>
<temporary count="50">5.38</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>5642.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2697</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2669</identifier>
<identifier>yaeovt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hi-SPEED_JECY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88664</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2357</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="226" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-21">
<name>priest</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4459" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>undefeatable spaceship</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30515" type="main character in" update="2011-03-29">
<name>Jecy Moore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88086" type="appears in" update="2017-03-06">
<name>Mayor Sabatini</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="42203" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PROLOGUE 起爆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Prologue Kibaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42204" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MOBIUS 記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mobius</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mobius Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42205" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FIGHT 追撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fight Tsuigeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42206" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ZONE 魔空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42207" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HIJACK 陥穽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hijack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijack Kansei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42208" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">STAMPEDE 巨塊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stampede</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stampede</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42209" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FIRE 愛憎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fire Aizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42210" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">AMBIVALENT 思慕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ambivalent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ambivalent Shibo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42211" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TIANA 誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tiana</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiana Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42212" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">DUMMY 暗殺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dummy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dummy Ansatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42213" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">KHAOS 戦場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chaos Senjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42214" update="2005-10-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠に...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Eternity...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien ni...</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
