<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4033" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1981-12-19</startdate>
<enddate>1981-12-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchuu Senshi Baldios (1981)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Revenge of the Space Warriors</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Space Warriors: Battle for Earth Station S-1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Uchuu Senshi Baldios Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宇宙戦士バルディオス (1981)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Space Warrior Baldios the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Baldios - Os Guerreiros do Espaço</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3123" type="Prequel">Uchuu Senshi Baldios</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/theatrical/w001.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4249" type="Original Work">Sakai Akiyoshi</name>
<name id="4122" type="Chief Direction">Toriumi Hisayuki</name>
<name id="3469" type="Music">Haneda Kentarou</name>
</creators>
<description>Plot Summary: From a poluded and destroyed planet called S-1 arrives an invasion on earth, Marin one of the people of S-1 helps the earthlings fighting the invaders with his super ship Baldios.
Comment: Created from footage originally made for the closing episodes of the TV series and some new footage. Two versions of the film were made, a 117 minute version, and a shorter 99 minute version. The US version is the 99 minute version.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="64">5.51</permanent>
<temporary count="64">5.99</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>154279.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2557</identifier>
<identifier>hugefe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pro-reed.com/works/theatrical/w001.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Space_Warrior_Baldios</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宇宙戦士バルディオス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>147918</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1747</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宇宙戰士</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>space-warrior-baldios</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="42219" update="2019-05-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>1981-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Instead of cleaning up their own nuclear waste, Planet S-1 brings their dirty work to Earth. Their military rulers want to knock us all off so their dying world can relocate here. Flying against fate, an S-1 rebel tries to defect to our side. But can a desperate and divided World Federation welcome him with open arms? Is this young Marine Leigan an ally or a spy? Can his robot ship Baldios and our Blue Strike Force unite to defeat The Red Fighters? And will it even matter if the impending doom arrives ahead of schedule? It’s space war fought on the environmental front. The ultimate battle for survival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784076</identifier>
<identifier>space-warrior-baldios</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
