<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4046" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-04-29</startdate>
<enddate>2006-11-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tsubasa Chronicle Dai 2 Series</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Tsubasa Chronicle 2nd Series</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Хроника крыльев (сезон второй)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tsubasa Chronicle Dai Ni Series</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">trc2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">翼 年代记 第2季</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Tsubasa S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">tsubasa2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ツバサ・クロニクル 第2シリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tsubasa: RESERVoir CHRoNiCLE (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Tsubasa Chronicle (2. Staffel)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Tsubasa Chronicle - Saison 2</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Tsubasa, Las Crónicas de Sakura 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Tsubasa Chronicle - Sezon 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Tsubasa: As Crónicas de Sakura 2</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">สึบาสะ สงครามเทพข้ามมิติ ปี 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5301" type="Sequel">Tsubasa Tokyo Revelations</anime>
<anime id="2733" type="Prequel">Tsubasa Chronicle</anime>
<anime id="4032" type="Same Setting">xxxHOLiC</anime>
<anime id="170" type="Alternative Setting">Kidou Tenshi Angelic Layer</anime>
<anime id="841" type="Alternative Setting">Clamp Gakuen Tanteidan</anime>
<anime id="12" type="Alternative Setting">Chobits</anime>
<anime id="30" type="Alternative Setting">X (2001)</anime>
<anime id="127" type="Alternative Setting">Magic Knight Rayearth</anime>
<anime id="429" type="Alternative Setting">X</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313575">Just like first season, very nice and entertaining.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="760053">watch library arc after Watch tokyo relevation ova!

after episode 16 all filler episode!!!

after that go see tsubasa chronicle manga for complete ending</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/tsubasa/</url>
<creators>
<name id="749" type="Animation Work">Bee Train</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="691" type="Direction">Mashimo Kouichi</name>
<name id="8131" type="Direction">Morioka Hiroshi</name>
<name id="3580" type="Series Composition">Kawase Toshifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Syaoran, a boy who wants to become an archaeologist, and Sakura, a princess from the Clow Kingdom, are childhood friends with a close relationship. On a fateful night, Sakura lost all her memories as a result of a conspiracy to obtain her powers. In order to regain her memory, Syaoran seeks help from the witch, Yuuko. Yuuko tells Syaoran that he has to travel from one alternate reality to another to collect fragments of Sakura`s memory. However, even if Sakura regains her memory, she will have no recollection of Syaoran. Traveling together with them is Kurogane, a warrior who was exiled from his country, and Fay, a magician who wants to escape from his King. With the help of a magical creature, Mokona, they set off on an exciting journey through time and space.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3463">6.27</permanent>
<temporary count="3516">7.66</temporary>
<review count="1">7.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>150172.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4591</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3677</identifier>
<identifier>dxxmqv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/tsubasa/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tsubasa:_Reservoir_Chronicle</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>884</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>324902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7197</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4236" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-16">
<name>crossover episode</name>
<description>Usually refers to the fact that one or more characters on this title come from other separate titles — often from series by the same creator/studio. Something like a "guest star", but in a more important role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4477" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>communication with the dead</name>
<description>This character is able of some manner of communication with the dead, or at least with one dead person. This includes talking to the dead, seeing the dead, outright mediumship, or any form of unidirectional or bidirectional form of communication that ordinary characters are not generally able to achieve.
This does not apply in environments where characters are expected to be dead, or where nobody is alive to begin with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="859" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="1667">8.91</rating>
<name>Ichihara Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Being one extremely experienced in her industry, Yuuko is not foolish enough to give away her real name like Watanuki. That aside, Yuuko has served as a major catalyst for Watanuki`s transformation, acting somewhat as his mentor. She loves to drink and eat Watanuki`s wonderful cooking and dragging Watanuki on crazy outings at the drop of a hat.</description>
<picture>130737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="868" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="216">7.90</rating>
<name>Larg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While the white Mokona left to travel the worlds with the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group, the black Mokona stayed behind to act as a liaison between the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group and Yuuko. Mokona likes to be around Yuuko, drink with her and eat the meals that Watanuki has made, and mostly chirps in with Maru and Moro. Yuuko has mentioned that the Mokonas were created a very long time ago by herself and Clow Reed, in preparation for a future event - the arrival and subsequent journey of the Tsubasa: Reservoir Chronicle group - as well as to stop Fei Wong Reed`s plans and save "two futures".</description>
<picture>15187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="426" picture="44708.jpg">Kikuchi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2165" type="appears in" update="2010-11-18">
<rating votes="360">8.49</rating>
<name>Chii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chii is a Chobit, a type of persocom that is far more technologically advanced than regular persocoms, and who are said to possess true machine intelligence rather than relying on the execution of pre-loaded software programs like other persocoms.</description>
<picture>43625.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4555" type="appears in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="139">6.53</rating>
<name>Sumomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A miniature "mobile persocom"—the equivalent of a laptop computer. Wearing an outfit that makes her resemble a genie, she is programmed to be cute and tends to be quite hyperactive, for example leading Hideki in wakeup exercises each morning and dancing when she is in standby mode.</description>
<picture>20635.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4565" type="appears in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="101">6.17</rating>
<name>Kotoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another laptop persocom like Sumomo, but she was custom-built by Yoshiyuki and has much higher specifications than Sumomo.</description>
<picture>20645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7021" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-21">
<rating votes="147">7.53</rating>
<name>Soel</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="426" picture="44708.jpg">Kikuchi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7156" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="145">8.18</rating>
<name>Shaoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kept asleep in a liquid chamber at Fei Wong Reed`s palace, with his left eye covered by an eyepatch, his hands and arms by binding spells and wearing clothes marking Fei Wong Reed`s bat symbol. In fact, this Shaoran is the original while the Shaoran at Sakura`s side is only a clone that Fei Wong Reed created. This Shaoran is of Clow Reed`s bloodline, the son of Sakura and Shaoran from another dimension (from CCS), and can thus use magic.
He gave his eye and with it half of his heart to his clone to stop Fei Wong`s plan temporarily, hoping that this action could create a true heart in the clone. Because he had given his eye Shaoran was able to witness all the events the clone did. He was depicted as a villain (it was believed that he was controlling the clone`s actions, while it was only the clone`s true nature showing) until it was discovered that the protagonist Shaoran is his clone. Now the real Shaoran is the story`s protagonist. This Shaoran is able to summon a sword, the same one used by his father and he also uses the same spells.</description>
<picture>60839.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7157" type="main character in" update="2009-11-10">
<rating votes="164">7.08</rating>
<name>Shaoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An excellent martial artist and an aspiring archaeologist with extensive knowledge of various languages, histories, and artefacts. His right eye is blind; sometimes, in mysterious dreams, he can see out of the eye and look at a person he recognises as himself in endless mirrors. Shaoran was found in his childhood wandering the streets without a memory, before he was discovered and adopted by Fujitaka (Sakura`s father in Cardcaptor Sakura), who recently passed away, leaving his foster son to continue his great work. He obtained his sword Hien during his stay at Ooto, which he learned to use from Kurogane, and learned his fighting abilities from now-enemy Seishirou, who can also travel between worlds and says he is looking for vampires.
As a clone, he has no mind or consciousness and exists only to collect all of Sakura`s feathers and to return them to her. Of all the clones created by Fei Wong Reed, he is the closest to what Fei Wong Reed intended. Although he has no magic of his own, he does, however, possess the ability to store and use magic. After the real Shaoran was released and arrived in Tokyo to face him the clone gouged out one of Fay`s eyes in order to absorb his magical power.</description>
<picture>25462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7158" type="main character in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="195">6.72</rating>
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Princess of Clow Country. Sakura is a cheerful, selfless, and stronghearted being. She states if there was ever something that she could do, she would try her absolute best. She possesses a mysterious power, namely her "wings" that can actually change the world, though no-one understands what that means. Her wings are the manifestation of her soul, namely her heart and memories. She is targeted by Fei Wong for that very power. After losing her memories, Shaoran gave up their relationship in order to save her. Meaning, even if she regains all of her memories, the one that she would never retrieve would be the knowledge of Shaoran`s existence. She is unusually excellent at games of chance, whether it`s her mysterious power or, as Chun Hyang mentioned in the Country of Koryo, extremely lucky from being "a favourite of the gods," meaning she gets such good fortune from being one of the gods` favourite daughters. Her main goal is to find the clone of Shaoran, who has now separated from the group.</description>
<picture>60838.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7159" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-23">
<rating votes="204">8.35</rating>
<name>Kurogane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rough-mannered ninja from the world of Nihon, a world based on ancient (Japan), exiled for his recklessness. He originally possessed the replica of Ginryuu, a sword, before giving it to Yuuko as price for his deal with her. He obtained a new sword in Ooto called the Souhi, and taught Shaoran the skills of sword fighting and sensing attacks from the left. In the grand scheme of the series, he is considered `Yuuko`s pawn`. Fei Wong Reed murdered Kurogane`s mother in an attempt to make a deal with him, his servitude for the return of his mother. However, this plan was thwarted by Yuuko and Tomoyo when Yuuko warns Tomoyo of this event. This warning leads to Tomoyo ending Kurogane`s mad rampage and Kurogane becoming one of her ninjas. He also acquired the Ginryuu replica from Tomoyo as the original was to be buried with his mother in place of his father`s corpse.</description>
<picture>25465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7160" type="main character in" update="2013-07-03">
<rating votes="262">7.99</rating>
<name>Fay D. Flourite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A laid-back mage from the Country of Selece. He is on the run from King Ashura (a crossover character from RG Veda), whom he put into a near-eternal slumber. Although he seems happy-go-lucky and pretends to know less than he does, there is more to him than meets the eye. His assistant in Selece, currently guarding against the awakening of Ashura, is a very organic-looking Chii (a crossover character from the series Chobits) It is also revealed that Fay created Chii according to his mother`s looks.</description>
<picture>60741.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7161" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="64">8.77</rating>
<name>Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The princess of a feudal country called Nihon who sends the ninja Kurogane on the quest that causes him to join the dimension travelers. Tomoyo is the Tsukuyomi, a powerful miko sorceress responsible for maintaining the wards of Nihon that protect the country from demons. She is also a dreamseer with the ability to see into other people`s, to enter another`s dreams, can send trans-dimensional messages through dreams and is able to see the future in her dreams. However, she gave up her dreamseer power to Yuuko as the price for bringing Kurogane, Fay, Shaoran and Mokona to Nihon. Another incarnation of her appears In Piffle World, where she retains much of her nature from Daidouji Tomoyo in Cardcaptor Sakura.</description>
<picture>60819.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7239" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="92">7.27</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cerberus is the guardian of the mystical yet dangerous book of Clow cards. He is the guardian of the sun, one of the two duty bound to protect the powerful cards, and opposite of the lunar guardian, Yue. For several decades he was locked away in the book of the Clow, which held the cards upon the death of their previous master, Clow Reed, until a new master appeared to take hold of the cards and their guardians. Cerberus` character first appears at the beginning of the series when this new master, Sakura Kinomoto, releases him from the book. Once Cerberus is awakened (he was napping on the front cover) and released from the book he discovers the Clow cards have vanished, and appoints Sakura the title of Cardcaptor, and sends her off to retrieve the cards.</description>
<picture>82458.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10936" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="28">3.10</rating>
<name>Fei Wong Reed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60820.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="242" picture="238968.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11877" type="appears in" update="2013-11-14">
<rating votes="10">6.50</rating>
<name>Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Touya is the older brother of Princess Sakura and the young king of the Kingdom of Clow.
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>60827.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11878" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="6">7.15</rating>
<name>Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The kind and respectful High Priest of Clow Country and a close friend of Touya.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>60824.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11880" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="14">4.56</rating>
<name>Chun Hyang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fiery young girl who dares to oppose the corrupt Ryanban, a government official, and his son. Chun Hyang`s mother was a powerful sorceress, but was unfortunately defeated by the Kiishim, a sorceress under the control of the Ryanban.
- wikipedia</description>
<picture>60841.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12014" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="16">4.81</rating>
<name>Xing Huo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fei Wong`s assistant. Not much about her is known besides the fact she is Fei Wong`s assistant and was somewhat also a "failed creation".</description>
<picture>60833.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36911" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="4">9.16</rating>
<name>Sakura no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura`s father.</description>
<picture>60828.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3272" picture="172136.jpg">Mizushima Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="49325" update="2006-05-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険なレース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Race</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das gefährliche Rennen</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Gara pericolosa</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การแข่งเสี่ยงตาย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken na Race</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49326" update="2006-05-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つのバッジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Badges</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die drei Abzeichen</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I tre gettoni</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เครื่องหมายทั้งสาม</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mittsu no Badge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49327" update="2006-05-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">栄光のゴール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goal of Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das glorreiche Ziel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Finale glorioso</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เส้นชัยอันทรงเกียรติ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikou no Goal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49328" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しいキセキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorrowful Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das traurige Wunder</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il triste miracolo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปาฏิหาริย์อันแสนเศร้า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashii Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49438" update="2006-05-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2006-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49477" update="2006-06-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年のケツイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Young Man`s Resolve</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Entschluss des Jungen</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La determinazione dei ragazzi</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การตัดสินใจของเด็กหนุ่ม</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen no Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49734" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔術師とデート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Date with the Wizard</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Date mit einem Magier</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un appuntamento con la maga</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ออกเดทกับพ่อมด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majutsushi to Date</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49872" update="2006-07-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">阿修羅のイワレ2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Origins of Ashura</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ashuras Geschichte</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La storia di Ashura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตำนานแห่งอาชูร่า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashura no Iware</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50253" update="2006-07-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなきイクサ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless War</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Schlacht ohne Ende</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La battaglia infinita</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สงครามที่ไร้จุดสิ้นสุด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owarinaki Ikusa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50352" update="2006-07-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたつのキオク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die zwei Erinnerungen</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I due ricordi</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความทรงจำทั้งสองส่วน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50845" update="2006-07-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時をこえるオモイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love That Transcends Time</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefühle, die Zeit überwinden</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I sentimenti che attraversano il tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความคิดคำนึงที่ข้ามกาลเวลา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Koeru Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50873" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おえかきモコナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mokona the Artist</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mokona, der Maler</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Mokona il disegnatore</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โมโคน่ายอดจิตรกร</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oekaki Mokona</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51155" update="2006-07-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険なロード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Road</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die gefährliche Straße</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La strada pericolosa</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เส้นทางอันตราย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken na Road</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51551" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まりのワカレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Parting of Beginnings</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Abschied vom Anfang</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คำอำลาเพื่อการเริ่มต้น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51723" update="2006-08-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒き鋼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Steel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der schwarze Stahl</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เงาอดีตของคุโรงาเนะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroki Hagane</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51916" update="2006-08-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">図書館のヒミツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret of the Library</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geheimnis der Bibliothek</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความลับของหอสมุด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshokan no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52112" update="2010-09-06">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody of Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52395" update="2006-07-24">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">望郷のカナタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faraway Homesickness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die andere Seite des Heimwehs</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อดีตที่โหยหา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boukyou no Kanata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="54374" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五つ目のチカイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fifth Oath</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der fünfte Schwur</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คำสาบานข้อที่ห้า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsutsume no Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="58272" update="2006-08-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケロちゃんとモコナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kero and Mokona</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kero-chan und Mokona</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เคโระจังกับโมโคน่า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kero-chan to Mokona</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61824" update="2006-11-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二度目のクナン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Hardship</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das zweite Leid</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ภัยพิบัติระลอกสอง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nidome no Kunan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62015" update="2006-08-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘術のゴクイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Hijutsu</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das wahre Wesen der geheimen Künste</title>
<title xml:lang="th">แก่นแท้ของวิชามนตรา</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hijutsu no Gokui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62129" update="2006-09-02">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はたらくサクラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura Works</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die arbeitende Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระคนขยัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hataraku Sakura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62427" update="2007-01-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羽王カオス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feather-King Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Federkönig Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คาออส ราชาขนนก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haou Chaos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63194" update="2006-09-16">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歪んだネガイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Warped Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der verzehrte Wunsch</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความปรารถนาที่บิดเบือน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuganda Negai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63631" update="2007-01-23">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意のナカマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Determined Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Gefährten der Entscheidung</title>
<title xml:lang="th">พรรคพวกผู้เด็ดเดี่ยว</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui no Nakama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63820" update="2006-10-22">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凍てつくミタマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Frozen Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die gefrorene Seele</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดวงวิญญาณเยือกแข็ง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itetsuku Mitama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63952" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2006-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日へのツバサ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wings Toward Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Flügel zum Morgen</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปีกโบยบินสู่วันพรุ่งนี้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita e no Tsubasa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125454" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125455" update="2010-11-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
