<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="406" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>1999-10-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kachou Ouji: Hard Rock Save the Space</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Столоначальник Оззи: Тяжелый рок спасет мир!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Столоначальник Одзи: Легенда о Черных Небесах</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Зіркова Сага Блек Хевену</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Black Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="short">Легенда о "Черных Небесах"</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">課長王子: Hard Rock Save the Space</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Legend of Black Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kacho-Ohji - Hard Rock save the Space</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Офісний Планктон Оззі</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2320" approval="4" total="8">Beck: Mongolian Chop Squad</anime>
<anime id="5587" approval="4" total="4">Detroit Metal City</anime>
<anime id="8" approval="2" total="6">Aquarian Age: Sign for Evolution</anime>
<anime id="12088" approval="2" total="6">Fukumenkei Noise</anime>
<anime id="1094" approval="2" total="4">BPS: Battle Programmer Shirase</anime>
<anime id="442" approval="2" total="4">Macross 7</anime>
<anime id="8870" approval="1" total="4">Sakamichi no Apollon: Kids on the Slope</anime>
<anime id="10" approval="1" total="4">Bastard!! Ankoku no Hakai Shin</anime>
<anime id="850" approval="1" total="3">Salaryman Kintarou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="295404">Its a cool  idea good animation the only problem is that its story development is somewhat slow maybe not for everyone but i totally recommend generally if its not for u you will know form the beginning if its for u then its a must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="396751">Despites low production values this title is entertaining. The characters are likable and there is a good variety of themes, although it doesn`t delve very deep into any of them.

I think adults will connect a little more with the protagonist, him being a middle aged man in a sort of mid-life crisis phase, but it can still be enjoyed by all ages.

Considering it`s only 12 episodes I would say it is worth your time.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/kacho-ohji/home.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="811" type="Work">A.P.P.P.</name>
<name id="3725" type="Character Design">Nakazawa Kazuto</name>
<name id="3760" type="Series Composition">Arakawa Naruhisa</name>
<name id="1903" type="Original Plan">Hayashi Hiroki</name>
<name id="1424" type="Direction">Kikuchi Yasuhito</name>
<name id="7254" type="Music">Korenaga Kouichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Once he was Gabriel Tanaka, lead guitarist for Black Heaven, the hottest band around. His life was filled with passion and excitement, but no longer. Now he`s just Ouji Tanaka, saddled with a mundane job, little pay, a shrewish wife, and a young son. The only thing he has left are the memories of his youth until an odd and beautiful woman asks him to pick up his guitar once more, and help save the galaxy with his song.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="934">5.96</permanent>
<temporary count="944">7.14</temporary>
<review count="5">7.46</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233835.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>401</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1025</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>491</identifier>
<identifier>tmdnjr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/kacho-ohji/home.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>課長王子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2841</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4298" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-07">
<name>rotoscoping</name>
<description>Rotoscoping is an animation technique in which animators trace over footage, frame by frame, for use in live-action and animated films.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4785" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>rock music</name>
<description>Rock music is a genre of popular music that originated as "rock and roll" in the United States in the 1950s, and developed into a range of different styles in the 1960s and later, particularly in the United Kingdom and the United States. Musically, rock has centered on the electric guitar, usually as part of a rock group with electric bass guitar and drums. Typically, rock is song-based music usually with a 4/4 time signature using a verse-chorus form, but the genre has become extremely diverse. Like pop music, lyrics often stress romantic love but also address a wide variety of other themes that are frequently social or political in emphasis. The dominance of rock by white, male musicians has been seen as one of the key factors shaping the themes explored in rock music. Rock places a higher degree of emphasis on musicianship, live performance, and an ideology of authenticity than pop music.</description>
<picurl>10250.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9644" type="main character in" update="2009-10-22">
<rating votes="5">8.37</rating>
<name>Layla Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tasked with tracking down Oji and getting him on their side to play music in order to activate the ultimate weapon. After finding him, she basically plays the role of an agent, acting as the go between the band and Fomalhaut, the space army commander.</description>
<picture>2698.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16473" type="main character in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="3">7.84</rating>
<name>Tanaka Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly Gabriel, the lead guitarist of Black Heaven, Tanaka takes an office job following the break-up of the band to support his growing family. Years later, he`s facing mid-life, wondering what went wrong, when Layla Yuki approaches him, asking him to play for her.</description>
<picture>3176.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16474" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="4">4.75</rating>
<name>Tanaka Yoshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A groupie of Black Heaven, she marries Oji when he finds out she is pregnant. She plays the role of the housewife and mother, watching in dismay as Oji reverts to his rocker persona and suspicious that he may be having an affair with Layla.</description>
<picture>3177.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16475" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>Tanaka Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of Oji and Yoshiko.</description>
<picture>3178.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16476" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="4">6.42</rating>
<name>Eriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Layla`s subordinates, who work in the same building as Oji and Layla and help with her assignments. They are identified with their respective hair colors of blue, purple, and green.</description>
<picture>3179.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="8790" picture="33155.jpg">Yanagihara Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16477" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="3">7.27</rating>
<name>Kotoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Layla`s subordinates, who work in the same building as Oji and Layla and help with her assignments. They are identified with their respective hair colors of blue, purple, and green.</description>
<picture>3180.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16478" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="2">7.84</rating>
<name>Rinko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Layla`s subordinates, who work in the same building as Oji and Layla and help with her assignments. They are identified with their respective hair colors of blue, purple, and green.</description>
<picture>3181.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16479" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="1">2.88</rating>
<name>Fomalhaut</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3182.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16480" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="4">7.80</rating>
<name>Hamil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3183.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16487" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>Satou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly Michael of Black Heaven, he plays guitar and is the lead vocalist.</description>
<picture>45859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16488" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly Raphael of Black Heaven, he plays bass. After the break-up of the band, he opened up a grocery store.</description>
<picture>45860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2219" picture="23794.jpg">Ishino Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16489" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-07">
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly Luke of Black Heaven, he plays drums. After the break-up of the band, he went into the real-estate business.</description>
<picture>45861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4773" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天国への階段</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stairway to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tengoku e no Kaidan</title>
<summary>Oji Tanaka starts the day by losing his beloved "Flying V" guitar twice because his wife wants to get rid of it. At work his boss harries him. Later, after work, he believes he is being seduced by his new coworker (an alien in disguise).
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784918</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5008" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オール・ナイト・ロング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Night Long</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">All Night Long</title>
<summary>The next morning, Tanaka`s son Gen accidentally destroys his prized autographed LP record by his idol Michael Schenker, and his wife is shown to be entirely unmoved by his loss. At work, Tanaka believes that his "stairway to heaven" experience from the night before was not a dream.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784920</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5009" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホット・ハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hot House</title>
<summary>Spurred by busybody rumormongering neighbors, Yoshiko`s suspicion that Oji is cheating on her grows, though she tries to suppress it. It did not help matters that she spots Oji with Layla.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784922</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5088" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の10年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ten Years Ago</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no 10 Nen</title>
<summary>Black Heaven, and by extension the ultimate weapon, is not at full power because it is missing its keyboardist Watanabe/Joseph.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784936</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5089" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝ける日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">These are the Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayakeru Hibi</title>
<summary>Oji feels re-energized and dresses in his old rock outfits (blond wig, leather jacket, and leather pants, which he can`t button anymore because he`s gained weight) in an attempt to revive his rocker identity as "Gabriel."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784926</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5090" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペース・チャイルド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Child</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Space Child</title>
<summary>Oji reluctantly babysits his son Gen because Yoshiko is going to her high school reunion, but feels compelled to play his guitar at the model house, leaving Gen behind in his haste.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784924</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5091" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりぼっちの世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Off of my Cloud</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no Sekai</title>
<summary>Oji attempts to recruit members for his new band, the New Black Heaven, and has his son Gen draw the "space attitude" recruitment poster.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784934</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5092" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジ・エンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The End</title>
<summary>1999 The final battle begins, and Black Heaven plays a marathon session in their struggle against the Watanabe clone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784941</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5093" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オールライト・ナウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Right Now</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">All Right Now</title>
<summary>Oji invites his surviving former bandmates from Black Heaven, Sato/Michael, Yamada/Luke, and Suzuki/Raphael for drinks. They reminisce about the old times and Oji tells him about the alien war and his music weapon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784932</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5094" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イントゥー・ジ・アリーナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Into the Arena</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Into the Arena</title>
<summary>The rival aliens test their ultimate weapon "Biomechanical Android Watanabe", which has 6 arms and can play 3 keyboards simultaneously, and almost destroy the aliens, canceling out Black Heaven.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784940</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5095" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イン・ニード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Need</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">In Need</title>
<summary>The aliens are under increasing attacks from their enemies. Hamill tries to persuade Oji to play music, and he seems receptive by playing twice. However, the ultimate weapon mysteriously does not fire properly.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784930</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5096" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やりたい気持ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sweet Emotion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaritai Kimochi</title>
<summary>The rival aliens are perfecting their own final weapon using a clone of Watanabe`s corpse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784938</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5097" update="2019-05-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォーク・アウェイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walk Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Walk Away</title>
<summary>Oji is in a funk because he`s decided to quit music. Alien Chief Scientist Hamill vows to do anything she can to have Oji play again. Meanwhile, Kotoko, Eriko, and Rinko try various futile methods to "inspire" Oji,
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>784928</identifier>
<identifier>the-legend-of-black-heaven</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="42288" update="2005-10-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42289" update="2005-10-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
